<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>dotnet/maui</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/maui</link>
      <description>.NET MAUI is the .NET Multi-platform App UI, a framework for building native device applications spanning mobile, tablet, and desktop. - dotnet/maui</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/maui</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 07:07:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-04-21</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/04/app-developer-links-2021-04-21/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/04/app-developer-links-2021-04-21/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 07:07:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converting a 13 year old .NET WPF app called BabySmash to a self-contained .NET 5 app with the .NET Upgrade Assistant</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/converting-a-13-year-old-net-wpf-app-called-babysmash-to-a-selfcontained-net-5-app-with-the-net-upgrade-assistant</link>
      <description>13 years ago I wrote a .NET 3.5 WPF application for my then 2 year old ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/converting-a-13-year-old-net-wpf-app-called-babysmash-to-a-selfcontained-net-5-app-with-the-net-upgrade-assistant</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 06:07:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denormalization in Production: Common Problem and Solution - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/blogs/denormalization-in-production-common-problem-and-solution/</link>
      <description>After a young developer (or database developer) learns about normalization, the quality of his databases increases a lot, there is no doubt about that.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/dennes.torres)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/blogs/denormalization-in-production-common-problem-and-solution/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 06:07:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Pulumi 3.0</title>
      <link>https://www.pulumi.com/blog/pulumi-3-0/</link>
      <description>Announcing Pulumi 3.0, the next major version of the Pulumi open source project.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pulumi.com/blog/pulumi-3-0/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 06:07:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next comment tool for your website</title>
      <link>https://cusdis.com/</link>
      <description>Open source, lightweight (4.7kb gzip), privacy-friendly alternative to Disqus.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cusdis.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 02:07:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code Python Tooling Gets &amp;#39;Most Requested&amp;#39; Feature: Poetry Support -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/04/20/vscode-python-421.aspx</link>
      <description>The wildly popular Python extension for Visual Studio Code is previewing support for Poetry, which eases Python packaging and dependency management.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel04/20/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/04/20/vscode-python-421.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 01:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>r/dotnet - Minimal hosting making its way to ASP.NET Core with .NET 6.</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/dotnet/comments/mup6bm/minimal_hosting_making_its_way_to_aspnet_core/</link>
      <description>116 votes and 93 comments so far on Reddit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/dotnet/comments/mup6bm/minimal_hosting_making_its_way_to_aspnet_core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 01:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Day Exploits in SonicWall Email Security Lead to Enterprise Compromise</title>
      <link>https://www.fireeye.com/blog/threat-research/2021/04/zero-day-exploits-in-sonicwall-email-security-lead-to-compromise.html</link>
      <description>Mandiant Managed Defense identified three zero-day vulnerabilities in SonicWall’s Email Security (ES) product that were being exploited in the wild.
</description>
      <author> (by Josh Fleischer, Chris DiGiamo, Alex Pennino)</author>
      <guid>https://www.fireeye.com/blog/threat-research/2021/04/zero-day-exploits-in-sonicwall-email-security-lead-to-compromise.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bash + ElasticSearch MultiSearch – Pedro Sim&amp;#245;es</title>
      <link>https://seomis.cc/blog/kibana-surrounding-bash</link>
      <description>Trying to automate common searches on ElasticSearch using Bash.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://seomis.cc/blog/kibana-surrounding-bash</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:08:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why we still use Oracle DB</title>
      <link>https://idiallo.com/blog/why-use-oracle-db-today</link>
      <description>In 2017, I worked for a large conglomerate. When a company grows a certain size, change is never welcomed. &amp;amp;ldquo;If it ain&amp;#39;t broke, don&amp;#39;t fix it&amp;amp;rdquo; is the motto and software is the first victim. </description>
      <author> (Ibrahim Diallo)</author>
      <guid>https://idiallo.com/blog/why-use-oracle-db-today</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:08:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial growth for people in engineering roles | DEEP/TEST</title>
      <link>https://moolya.com/deeptest/2021/01/21/financial-growth-for-people-in-engineering-roles/</link>
      <description>I took money lightly. I paid a huge price. I don&amp;#39;t want you to. I fixed the money part and I want to help you to be better engineer than me, a better</description>
      <author> (Pradeep Soundararajan)</author>
      <guid>https://moolya.com/deeptest/2021/01/21/financial-growth-for-people-in-engineering-roles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:08:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why you should never quit too early ... - DONN FELKER</title>
      <link>https://www.donnfelker.com/why-you-should-never-quit-too-early/</link>
      <description>About 8 years ago this month I quit too early. If I had stayed with the business and rode through the storm, I’d be very well off right now. I wouldn’t be writing this newsletter to you about this story. I can’t say that I regret giving in at the time, but as always … …</description>
      <author> (http://www.facebook.com/donnfelker)</author>
      <guid>https://www.donnfelker.com/why-you-should-never-quit-too-early/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:07:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to detect breaking changes and lint Protobuf automatically using Gitlab CI and Buf</title>
      <link>https://mionskowski.pl/ci-pipeline-for-protobuf</link>
      <description>Protocol Buffers or Protobufs are language-agnostic mechanisms for serializing data. 
Protobuf schemas are specified using Protocol Buffer language, which is among the most popular and widely adopted IDLs in the industry.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mionskowski.pl/ci-pipeline-for-protobuf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:07:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve BlankA Path to the Minimum Viable Product</title>
      <link>https://steveblank.com/2021/04/20/the-secret-to-the-minimum-viable-product/</link>
      <description>I first met Shawn Carolan and his wife Jennifer at the turn of the century at 11,000 feet. I was hiking with my kids between the Yosemite High Sierra camps. Having just retired from a career as an …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steveblank.com/2021/04/20/the-secret-to-the-minimum-viable-product/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:07:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coveralls in a monorepo</title>
      <link>https://chay.dev/posts/coverage/</link>
      <description>A short rant</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chay.dev/posts/coverage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:07:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts And Projects For The Future</title>
      <link>https://danielwasserlauf.com/2021/04/14/thoughts-and-projects-for-the-future/</link>
      <description>Preface Below I wanted to reflect on the past year and solidify some ideas I’ve been having on mental/physical health. I also wanted to start discussing a project I’m interested in sharing in a development blog sort of fashion. Reflection My last real article was at the beginning of the novel corona virus outbreak. Between then and now the world and I have changed. In reflection on working from home and living during quarantine I’ve come to realize some truths about myself: Intense daily repetition and social isolation causes intrusive thoughts and eventually self destructive behavior To be truly independent we need to ask for help. During the past fall and early winter I’ve gone through periods of intense isolation and repetition. Specifically I went months without really leaving my home except for food, and each day was spent doing the same routine of rolling out of bed getting on a computer, working, eating, and then sleeping. With some breaks to watch TV/slack-off, or as my parents would call it when I was growing up, “Vegetate.” This cycle quickly caused me to have depressive behaviors. With nothing to break up the day, all of my daily actions would give me anxiety and I began to stress out over the smallest topics/details. Getting up and doing the same action each day became harder. What finally broke my depressive cycle was varied social interaction, which oddly enough I wanted to avoid at all costs. Specifically I began speaking about my problems to those who I loved. Just talking about my issues and feeling truly vulnerable enabled me to brake me out of my rut. I know talking about personal issues and problems isn’t rocket surgery. However, for me it’s been a new skill to learn. While growing up, I had an idea about what it really meant to be an “adult.” I needed to be strong, independent, tenacious, and intelligent. While great traits to have they really miss the point. Being an adult is best when sharing life with others, and insurmountable difficulties are inevitable. I now understand becoming more mature is more like finding my childhood. Empathy, humility, kindness, and thoughtfulness are some of the first lessons I had during pre-school. I think I somehow lost them along the way, and in relearning I found out how to get back up. Future Projects Some background first, I’m a software engineer by passion and trade. I really enjoy authoring programs, and solving technical problems. I want to try and let others into this world regardless of skill level to see what the process is actually like. I’ve recently started a new job at a fantastic company, Marklogic. Without getting into too much detail my current team has been using the Python programming language. In my past work I hadn’t really had to interact with Python in any professional capacity. I’ve done some small projects and I have a passing understanding of it, however I never really had to work with it deeply. In a few coming articles I will explore an example project of creating a webcrawler from scratch.</description>
      <author> (Dwasserlauf)</author>
      <guid>https://danielwasserlauf.com/2021/04/14/thoughts-and-projects-for-the-future/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:07:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Slack, no one can hear your scream! | 8th Light</title>
      <link>https://8thlight.com/blog/ian-carroll/2021/04/20/in-slack-no-one-can-hear-you-scream.html</link>
      <description>Hey, my name’s Ian. I’m a Senior Consulting Software Engineer at 8th Light’s Pod Services division. And I have struggled with remote collaboration for a long time. Before the pandemic, I struggled with in-person communication,...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://8thlight.com/blog/ian-carroll/2021/04/20/in-slack-no-one-can-hear-you-scream.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:07:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js 16 available now</title>
      <link>https://nodejs.medium.com/node-js-16-available-now-7f5099a97e70</link>
      <description>We are excited to announce the release of Node.js 16 today! Highlights include the update of the V8 JavaScript engine to 9.0, prebuilt…</description>
      <author> (https://nodejs.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://nodejs.medium.com/node-js-16-available-now-7f5099a97e70</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 22:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust and cryptographic code | Bulletproof TLS Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://www.feistyduck.com/bulletproof-tls-newsletter/issue_74_rust_and_cryptographic_code</link>
      <description>Bulletproof TLS Newsletter is a free periodic newsletter bringing you commentary and news
surrounding SSL/TLS and Internet PKI, designed to keep you informed about the latest
developments in this space. Maintained by Hanno B&amp;#246;ck.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.feistyduck.com/bulletproof-tls-newsletter/issue_74_rust_and_cryptographic_code</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 22:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple unveils new iPad Pro with M1 chip and stunning Liquid Retina XDR display</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2021/04/apple-unveils-new-ipad-pro-with-m1-chip-and-stunning-liquid-retina-xdr-display/</link>
      <description>The most powerful and advanced iPad Pro ever pushes the limits of what’s possible on iPad with the addition of the Apple-designed M1 chip.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2021/04/apple-unveils-new-ipad-pro-with-m1-chip-and-stunning-liquid-retina-xdr-display/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 21:06:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube CEO receives freedom of expression award sponsored by the video platform itself - Market Research Telecast</title>
      <link>https://marketresearchtelecast.com/youtube-ceo-receives-freedom-of-expression-award-sponsored-by-the-video-platform-itself/34449/</link>
      <description>YouTube CEO Susan Wojcicki has received an award for freedom of expression that has Google’s own video platform as one of its sponsors and that is awarded by the American…</description>
      <author> (MRT Staff)</author>
      <guid>https://marketresearchtelecast.com/youtube-ceo-receives-freedom-of-expression-award-sponsored-by-the-video-platform-itself/34449/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 21:06:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iMac features all-new design in vibrant colors, M1 chip, and 4.5K Retina display</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2021/04/imac-features-all-new-design-in-vibrant-colors-m1-chip-and-45k-retina-display/</link>
      <description>Apple today introduced an all-new iMac featuring an extraordinary design enabled by the M1 chip, and the best camera, mics, and speakers ever in a Mac.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2021/04/imac-features-all-new-design-in-vibrant-colors-m1-chip-and-45k-retina-display/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 21:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV 4K</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/apple-tv-4k/</link>
      <description>Watch Apple TV+, movies, and shows in 4K High Frame Rate HDR. Stream live sports and news. Play Apple Arcade, work out with Apple Fitness+, and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/apple-tv-4k/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 21:06:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ministers encourages citizens concerned over Facebook leak to visit Have I Been Pwned? website</title>
      <link>https://www.publictechnology.net/articles/news/ministers-encourages-citizens-concerned-over-facebook-leak-visit-have-i-been-pwned</link>
      <description>Credit: Sarah Marshall/CC BY 2.0 A government minister has encouraged citizens concerned about the recent leak of personal data gained in a major breach of Facebook to visit the Have I Been Pwned? website to check whether they have been affected. Data from a reported 533 million users was gained from the social network up to 2019 via data scraping – an automated process through which information is extracted from websites and typically imported into local files, such as spreadsheets. This data, understood to largely comprise phone numbers, was recently published online. About 11 million UK Facebook account holders are understood to have been affected. Minister for media and data John Whittingdale indicated that the government’s advice for those who are concerned that their information may have been leaked is to visit HIBP – a website set up to allow people to check if and when their personal data has been compromised in a data breach. Visitors to the site can enter their email address and phone number and see all the breaches in which these details have been posed. Related content Dowden: ‘The idea that free speech can be switched off by a button in California is unsettling’ Digital secretary meets with Australian counterpart over Facebook face-off Online harms law could see social networks fined billions of pounds Whittingdale said: “The National Cyber Security Centre recommends that members of the public who are concerned that their email and/or phone number may have been leaked in the 2019 breach and any other data breaches should check the website https://haveibeenpwned.com. This website has been supported by the National Cyber Security Centre in the past.” The Facebook breach is now the subject of an inquiry by Ireland’s Data Protection Commission, which last week announced the launch of an official probe. “The DPC, having considered the information provided by Facebook Ireland regarding this matter to date, is of the opinion that one or more provisions of the GDPR and/or the Data Protection Act 2018 may have been, and/or are being, infringed in relation to Facebook Users’ personal data,” it said. The data minister, who was speaking in answer to a written parliamentary question from shadow digital minister Chi Onwurah, said that UK regulators will assist with the probe. “The Information Commissioner’s Office continues to work with and support its Irish counterpart to ensure that the data of UK citizens is protected,” he said. “The government has made it clear that all organisations, especially large global tech firms who process vast amounts of personal data, must comply with the UK’s data protection legislation, which poses strict obligations on organisations to ensure that UK citizens’ data is processed safely, securely and transparently. Organisations which fail to comply with the legislation may be investigated by the Information Commissioner’s Office and subject to increased fines.”</description>
      <author> (Sam Trendall)</author>
      <guid>https://www.publictechnology.net/articles/news/ministers-encourages-citizens-concerned-over-facebook-leak-visit-have-i-been-pwned</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 21:06:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Developers Sound Off on Visual Studio 2022 -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/04/20/vs-2020-feedback.aspx</link>
      <description>Hot topics were: 64-bit; support (or perceived lack thereof) of Azure DevOps; Linux; the legacy .NET Framework; and even refreshed icons.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel04/20/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/04/20/vs-2020-feedback.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 21:06:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power consumption of Game Boy flash cartridges</title>
      <link>https://gekkio.fi/blog/2021/power-consumption-of-game-boy-flash-cartridges/</link>
      <description>Flash cartridges (= &amp;quot;carts&amp;quot;) are commonly used to run Game Boy ROMs, such as homebrew games or dumped officially released games, on real hardware. Different kinds of flash carts with various features and performance characteristics have been available for a long time, but flash carts have in general the reputation of consuming a lot of power, greatly reducing the battery life of a Game Boy system, and possibly causing other additional problems. System stability might suffer, especially on Game Boy Pocket, and flash carts can also increase audible noise. Many of these problems have become more obvious in the recent years, since Game Boy modding is nowadays very popular and many modern mods, such as IPS screens, consume a lot of extra power. Some people claim that certain mods are simply incompatible with flash carts, and sometimes people say an extra regluator mod is needed in order to safely use flash carts. There is some truth to these claims, but unfortunately the fine details tend to matter and these kind of blanket statements can be misleading!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gekkio.fi/blog/2021/power-consumption-of-game-boy-flash-cartridges/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 20:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grafana, Loki, and Tempo will be relicensed to AGPLv3</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2021/04/20/grafana-loki-tempo-relicensing-to-agplv3/</link>
      <description>We believe that this change allows our community and users to have the same core freedoms of free and open source software that they have enjoyed since the inception of Grafana Labs and encourages third parties to also contribute back.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://grafana.com/blog/2021/04/20/grafana-loki-tempo-relicensing-to-agplv3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 20:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RQfgeW0cOFk</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io/</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
    

    
      
    .NET Foundation
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RQfgeW0cOFk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 19:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Sagas to Process Orders - DZone Microservices</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-sagas-to-process-orders</link>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ll see how it&amp;#39;s possible to use a Saga to orchestrate a very simple Order Processing workflow with OpenSleigh.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-sagas-to-process-orders</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 19:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blaze It: More Than 90% of Americans Support Legal Weed in New Poll</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/blaze-it-more-than-90-of-americans-support-legal-weed-1846716103</link>
      <description>A recent poll suggests that more than 90% of Americans support cannabis legalization in one shape or another.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gizmodo.com/blaze-it-more-than-90-of-americans-support-legal-weed-1846716103</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 19:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Spotify is Killing the Open Podcast Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://singhkays.com/blog/how-spotify-is-killing-the-open-podcast-ecosystem/</link>
      <description>Earlier this year, when Spotify announced that “The Joe Rogan Experience” would stream exclusively on Spotify, it sent shockwaves throughout the podcast ecosystem. This deal – reportedly worth over $100 million – is one of the most lucrative podcast deals. The presence of this deal, let alone the magnitude, is rare for the podcast ecosystem, which is built on open principles i.e. all podcasts are available everywhere. Therefore, the concept of exclusivity does not exist in the vocabulary of podcast listeners nor podcast creators.</description>
      <author> (Kay Singh)</author>
      <guid>https://singhkays.com/blog/how-spotify-is-killing-the-open-podcast-ecosystem/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 19:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple introduces AirTag</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2021/04/apple-introduces-airtag/</link>
      <description>Apple today introduced AirTag, an accessory that works with iPhone and other Apple devices to track and find important belongings.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2021/04/apple-introduces-airtag/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 19:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover The Best Books To Read &amp;#128218;</title>
      <link>https://shepherd.com/</link>
      <description>Shepherd feels like you are browsing the best bookstore in the world.
  Curated lists recommending the best books on every topic imaginable.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shepherd.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 19:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 9 init accessors and records - Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2021/04/20/c-9-init-accessors-and-records/</link>
      <description>Learn how to combine C# 9&amp;#39;s new init accessors and records to build immutable data models, which support change via the with expression.</description>
      <author> (By Tom Deseyn April 20, 2021April 19, 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2021/04/20/c-9-init-accessors-and-records/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 18:06:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to .NET - Learn</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/dotnet-introduction/?WT.mc_id=onedevquestion-c9-dotnet5</link>
      <description>Start learning about .NET. Understand what .NET is and how it works. Quickly build a small app in a web-based .NET environment.</description>
      <author> (bobtabor-msft)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/dotnet-introduction/?WT.mc_id=onedevquestion-c9-dotnet5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 17:06:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - ASP.NET Core updates in .NET 6</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mot8qAWEnj8</link>
      <description>There are a lot of exciting new features for ASP.NET Core developers in .NET 6! Come hear all about it from Daniel Roth, and ask your questions live in the c...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mot8qAWEnj8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 17:06:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Cloudflare Images beta to simplify your image pipeline</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/announcing-cloudflare-images-beta/</link>
      <description>Today, we are announcing the beta of Cloudflare Images: a simple service to store, resize, optimize, and deliver images at scale.</description>
      <author> (Zaid Farooqui)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/announcing-cloudflare-images-beta/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 17:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 Status (@auth0status)</title>
      <link>https://nitter.snopyta.org/auth0status</link>
      <description>The latest tweets from Auth0 Status</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nitter.snopyta.org/auth0status</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 17:06:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>devRant - !dev

My neighbours have so many fucking IoT devices that they basically fuck over the entire 2.4GHz spectrum over here just by themselves...
Thanks for that you cuntbags.</title>
      <link>https://devrant.com/rants/4186069/dev-my-neighbours-have-so-many-fucking-iot-devices-that-they-basically-fuck-over</link>
      <description>Connect with fellow developers over fun rants about tech</description>
      <author> (devRant)</author>
      <guid>https://devrant.com/rants/4186069/dev-my-neighbours-have-so-many-fucking-iot-devices-that-they-basically-fuck-over</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 17:06:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increased errors in Auth0</title>
      <link>https://status.auth0.com/incidents/zvjzyc7912g5</link>
      <description>Auth0&amp;#39;s Status Page - Increased errors in Auth0.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://status.auth0.com/incidents/zvjzyc7912g5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 17:06:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>learn.tv&amp;#160;-&amp;#160;This website is for sale!&amp;#160;-&amp;#160;learn Resources and Information.</title>
      <link>http://learn.tv/</link>
      <description>This website is for sale! learn.tv is your first and best source for all of the information you’re looking for. From general topics to more of what you would expect to find here, learn.tv has it all. We hope you find what you are searching for!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://learn.tv/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 17:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 Status</title>
      <link>https://status.auth0.com/</link>
      <description>Welcome to Auth0&amp;#39;s home for real-time and historical data on system performance.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://status.auth0.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 17:06:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>danfragoso/thdwb</title>
      <link>https://github.com/danfragoso/thdwb</link>
      <description>&amp;#127789; The hotdog web browser and browser engine &amp;#127789;. Contribute to danfragoso/thdwb development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (danfragoso)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/danfragoso/thdwb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 16:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Documentation &amp;amp; C# 9</title>
      <link>http://jesseliberty.com/2021/04/20/net-documentation-c-9/</link>
      <description>Bill Wagner of the C# 9 Documentation team at Microsoft talks about changes and improvements to the Microsoft documentation as well as key features in C# 9</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>http://jesseliberty.com/2021/04/20/net-documentation-c-9/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 15:06:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C++ coroutines: Getting rid of our atomic variant discriminator | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210420-28/?p=105128</link>
      <description>We continue the refinement of our coroutine implementation by removing the atomic variable used as the discriminant of our result holder variant. The discriminant needed to be atomic because we used it in await_ready to peek at whether the coroutine had completed.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210420-28/?p=105128</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 15:06:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thunder Client - Visual Studio Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=rangav.vscode-thunder-client</link>
      <description>Extension for Visual Studio Code - Rest API Client for VS Code, GUI based Http Client</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=rangav.vscode-thunder-client</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 14:27:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did the IETF specifically choose 192.168/16 to be a private IP address class?</title>
      <link>https://superuser.com/questions/784978/why-did-the-ietf-specifically-choose-192-168-16-to-be-a-private-ip-address-class</link>
      <description>Why did the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF) choose 192.168/16 to be a private IP address classand not something else?

Why specifically 192.168/16 and 10/8 and 172.16/12 and not 145.243/16 for </description>
      <author> (CornbeetleCornbeetle
        
            1,23022 gold badges88 silver badges99 bronze badges)</author>
      <guid>https://superuser.com/questions/784978/why-did-the-ietf-specifically-choose-192-168-16-to-be-a-private-ip-address-class</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 14:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open source goes to Mars &amp;#128640; - The GitHub Blog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/2021-04-19-open-source-goes-to-mars/</link>
      <description>Celebrating the nearly 12,000 developers who aided Ingenuity&amp;#39;s first Martian flight with a profile badge that recognizes their contributions to this historic achievement.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/2021-04-19-open-source-goes-to-mars/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 14:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Don&amp;#39;t Need Postman Anymore!! I Use VS Code Instead...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AbCTlemwZ1k</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve completely replaced the need for Postman with this one extension in VS Code! The Thunder Client extension for VS Code can do everything I need to when t...</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick
  
  
    

    
      
    James Q Quick
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AbCTlemwZ1k</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 14:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS General Rules of Thumb</title>
      <link>https://rehansaeed.com/css-general-rules-of-thumb/</link>
      <description>Getting to grips with CSS is difficult. This post describes some general rules of thumb that can guide you down the right path to success.</description>
      <author> (Muhammad Rehan Saeed)</author>
      <guid>https://rehansaeed.com/css-general-rules-of-thumb/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 13:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start building your own private network on Cloudflare today</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/build-your-own-private-network-on-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>Starting today, your team can build a private network on Cloudflare’s network.</description>
      <author> (Sam Rhea)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/build-your-own-private-network-on-cloudflare/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 13:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A System for Grouping &amp;amp; Sorting CSS Properties</title>
      <link>https://rehansaeed.com/system-for-grouping-and-sorting-css-properties/</link>
      <description>Grouping and Sorting CSS properties can make your CSS easier to read and helps with consistency in a team environment. There is no correct answer but something is better than nothing.</description>
      <author> (Muhammad Rehan Saeed)</author>
      <guid>https://rehansaeed.com/system-for-grouping-and-sorting-css-properties/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 13:05:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixing build warning NETSSDK1138 when building projects with end-of-life .NET frameworks</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/fixing-build-warning-netsdk1138-when-building-end-of-life-projects-with-dotnet-5/</link>
      <description>In this post I describe how to hide the warning generated by the dotnet CLI when working with end-of-life frameworks like .NET Core 3.0 (netcoreapp3.0)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/fixing-build-warning-netsdk1138-when-building-end-of-life-projects-with-dotnet-5/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 13:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Classroom now offers a pre-made GitHub starter course (Public Beta) - GitHub Changelog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-04-20-github-classroom-now-offers-a-pre-made-github-starter-course-public-beta/</link>
      <description>GitHub Classroom now offers a pre-made GitHub starter course (Public Beta)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-04-20-github-classroom-now-offers-a-pre-made-github-starter-course-public-beta/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 11:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gʀᴀᴘʜɪᴄs Cᴏᴅᴇx</title>
      <link>https://graphicscodex.courses.nvidia.com/app.html</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://graphicscodex.courses.nvidia.com/app.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 11:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software infrastructure 2.0: a wishlist</title>
      <link>https://erikbern.com/2021/04/19/software-infrastructure-2.0-a-wishlist.html</link>
      <description>Erik Bernhardsson</description>
      <author> (Erik Bernhardsson)</author>
      <guid>https://erikbern.com/2021/04/19/software-infrastructure-2.0-a-wishlist.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 11:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geico Data Breach Let Fraudsters Steal Driver&amp;#39;s License Numbers</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/a-geico-data-breach-let-cyber-fraudsters-steal-customer-1846717328</link>
      <description>The thieves could use your information to apply for unemployment benefits.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gizmodo.com/a-geico-data-breach-let-cyber-fraudsters-steal-customer-1846717328</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 09:05:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vitling: The Endless Acid Banger</title>
      <link>https://www.vitling.xyz/toys/acid-banger/</link>
      <description>Algorithmic music experiement by Vitling</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.vitling.xyz/toys/acid-banger/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 08:06:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>