<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>This is Best Way To Create CLI Apps in .NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=4KHFrbJHCHc</link>
      <description>Use code CLEAN20 and get 20% off the brand new &amp;quot;Deep Dive in Clean Architecture&amp;quot; course on Dometrain: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-clean-architectu...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=4KHFrbJHCHc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 15:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Projects Need This Type of Tests: Architecture Tests</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_kbKF8VHHmE</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (React Conferences by GitNation
  
  
  
    React Conferences by GitNation
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_kbKF8VHHmE</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 15:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Times sues Open AI, Microsoft over copyright infringement</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2023/12/ny-times-sues-open-ai-microsoft-over-copyright-infringement/</link>
      <description>Shows evidence that GPT-based systems will reproduce Times articles if asked.</description>
      <author> (John Timmer
    -    12/27/2023, 11:05 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2023/12/ny-times-sues-open-ai-microsoft-over-copyright-infringement/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 14:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I made JSX for Lua (because I hate static sites)</title>
      <link>https://bvisness.me/luax/</link>
      <description>This site now runs on a custom dialect of Lua.</description>
      <author> (Ben Visness)</author>
      <guid>https://bvisness.me/luax/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 14:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENERATION JUNK </title>
      <link>https://walterkirn.substack.com/p/generation-junk</link>
      <description>Nothing I Buy Works</description>
      <author> (Walter Kirn)</author>
      <guid>https://walterkirn.substack.com/p/generation-junk</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers experience burnout, but 70% of them code on weekends</title>
      <link>https://shiftmag.dev/developer-lifestye-jetbrains-survey-2189/</link>
      <description>Three-quarters of developers have experienced burnout, quit learning program or course and almost three-quarters of them code for fun during weekends.</description>
      <author> (Antonija Bilic Arar)</author>
      <guid>https://shiftmag.dev/developer-lifestye-jetbrains-survey-2189/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - jasonjmcghee/rem: An open source approach to locally record and enable searching everything you view on your Apple Silicon.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/jasonjmcghee/rem</link>
      <description>An open source approach to locally record and enable searching everything you view on your Apple Silicon. - GitHub - jasonjmcghee/rem: An open source approach to locally record and enable searching...</description>
      <author> (jasonjmcghee)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/jasonjmcghee/rem</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 13:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An opinionated list of tips for building .NET 8 app templates</title>
      <link>https://www.mytechramblings.com/posts/an-opinionated-list-of-tips-for-building-a-dotnet-8-template/</link>
      <description>I have been developing .NET templates for quite some time, and as a result, I thought it might be helpful to compile a list of tips to consider when creating a .NET template for your own or your company&amp;#39;s apps.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mytechramblings.com/posts/an-opinionated-list-of-tips-for-building-a-dotnet-8-template/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 13:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking &amp;quot;DRM&amp;quot; in Polish trains</title>
      <link>https://media.ccc.de/v/37c3-12142-breaking_drm_in_polish_trains</link>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ve all been there: the trains you&amp;#39;re servicing for a customer suddenly brick themselves and the manufacturer claims that&amp;#39;s because you...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://media.ccc.de/v/37c3-12142-breaking_drm_in_polish_trains</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 11:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No new iPhone? No secure iOS: Looking at an unfixed iOS vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://joshua.hu/apple-ios-patched-unpatched-vulnerabilities</link>
      <description>What’s the deal with iOS security updates, anyway?</description>
      <author> (Joshua Rogers)</author>
      <guid>https://joshua.hu/apple-ios-patched-unpatched-vulnerabilities</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 11:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valetudo</title>
      <link>https://valetudo.cloud/</link>
      <description>Cloud replacement for vacuum robots enabling local-only operation</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://valetudo.cloud/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 10:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implement Custom Authorization Policy Provider in ASP.NET Core - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/aspnetcore-implement-custom-authorization-policy-provider-in-asp-net-core/</link>
      <description>In this article, we explored how to implement and use Custom Authorization Policy Provider in ASP.NET Core</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/aspnetcore-implement-custom-authorization-policy-provider-in-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - KristofferStrube/Blazor.WebAuthentication: A Blazor wrapper for the Web Authentication browser API.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/KristofferStrube/Blazor.WebAuthentication</link>
      <description>A Blazor wrapper for the Web Authentication browser API. - GitHub - KristofferStrube/Blazor.WebAuthentication: A Blazor wrapper for the Web Authentication browser API.</description>
      <author> (KristofferStrube)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/KristofferStrube/Blazor.WebAuthentication</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 billion if statements</title>
      <link>https://andreasjhkarlsson.github.io//jekyll/update/2023/12/27/4-billion-if-statements.html</link>
      <description>I recently stumbled upon this screenshot while researching social media on the train. Of course, it was followed by a cascade of spiteful comments, criticizing this fresh programmer’s attempt to solve a classical problem in computer science. The modulus operation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andreasjhkarlsson.github.io//jekyll/update/2023/12/27/4-billion-if-statements.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Extension Method Will Make Your Life Easier</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=7XeEVU_JbFE</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=7XeEVU_JbFE</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 08:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks! Space in 2023 Geek Out</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/details/1878</link>
      <description>Time for the annual Space Geek Out! Richard summarizes many of the important space stories of the past year, including SpaceX&amp;#39;s record number of Falcon 9 flights and the first two flights of Starship. The conversation also explores the state of the International Space Station, Dream Chaser, Artemis, and other moon missions, including India&amp;#39;s successful landing! Richard then digs into the Crisis in Cosmology - how the James Webb Space Telescope has changed our understanding of the universe, and how it is disrupting the current models of the universe. But new science is good - the more you know!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/details/1878</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 07:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing ChatGPT&amp;#39;s Structured Data Support To Its Limits</title>
      <link>https://minimaxir.com/2023/12/chatgpt-structured-data/</link>
      <description>“Function calling” with ChatGPT is ChatGPT’s best feature since ChatGPT.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://minimaxir.com/2023/12/chatgpt-structured-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 04:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shinjuku Station Indoor</title>
      <link>https://satoshi7190.github.io/Shinjuku-indoor-threejs-demo/</link>
      <description>「新宿駅周辺屋内地図データ」（国土交通省）（https://www.geospatial.jp/ckan/dataset/mlit-indoor-shinjuku-r2）を加工して作成</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://satoshi7190.github.io/Shinjuku-indoor-threejs-demo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 01:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4-year campaign backdoored iPhones using possibly the most advanced exploit ever</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2023/12/exploit-used-in-mass-iphone-infection-campaign-targeted-secret-hardware-feature/</link>
      <description>&amp;quot;Triangulation&amp;quot; infected dozens of iPhones belonging to employees of Moscow-based Kaspersky.</description>
      <author> (Dan Goodin
    -    12/27/2023, 9:03 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/security/2023/12/exploit-used-in-mass-iphone-infection-campaign-targeted-secret-hardware-feature/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be kind to attendees eyes - Kevin Chant</title>
      <link>https://www.kevinrchant.com/2023/12/27/be-kind-to-attendees-eyes/</link>
      <description>In this post I want to cover how you can be kind to attendees eyes when presenting. Because I think it is an important thing to be aware of.</description>
      <author> (Kevin Chant)</author>
      <guid>https://www.kevinrchant.com/2023/12/27/be-kind-to-attendees-eyes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with OCaml and Functional Programming | Sandro Maglione</title>
      <link>https://www.sandromaglione.com/articles/getting-started-with-ocaml-and-functional-programming</link>
      <description>Get started writing functional programming code using the OCaml programming language: install OCaml, create a new project using dune, learn how to write functional programming code.</description>
      <author> (Sandro Maglione)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sandromaglione.com/articles/getting-started-with-ocaml-and-functional-programming</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing the Marketing Hierarchy: Why Topical Authority Is the New Currency</title>
      <link>https://aimd.app/blog/2023-12-26-revolutionizing-the-marketing-hierarchy-why-topical-authority-is-the-new-currency</link>
      <description>Delving deep into the importance of topical authority in SEO and content marketing, highlighting its role as the new standard for online credibility and expertise. Uncover key insights into Google algorithm updates, including BERT, May 2020 Core Update, and recent Reviews Updates, and their influence on SEO practices. Learn about the pivotal role of keyword research, content excellence, and strategic link building in establishing topical authority. Additionally, discover the significance of social media in enhancing brand visibility and credibility, along with essential tactics for building a lasting legacy of topical authority.</description>
      <author> (Understanding Topical Authority)</author>
      <guid>https://aimd.app/blog/2023-12-26-revolutionizing-the-marketing-hierarchy-why-topical-authority-is-the-new-currency</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Folding Consumption | TL;DR</title>
      <link>https://mazzzystar.github.io/2023/12/27/folding-consumption/</link>
      <description>Behind every search trick for a substitute product lies a form of folding in life.

It all started when I saw a post about how to use alternative sea</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mazzzystar.github.io/2023/12/27/folding-consumption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is How Your Parents Used to Build Websites – Nikola Brežnjak blog</title>
      <link>https://nikola-breznjak.com/blog/javascript/this-is-how-your-parents-used-to-build-websites/</link>
      <description>Hey future web wizards! Are you ready to embark on your journey into the vast world of web development? This post is your beginner-friendly guide to HTML. We’ll break down the essentials, infuse some humor, and provide plenty of examples for you to experiment with. By the end of this, you&amp;#39;ll be well on your way to crafting your first web page. Let’s dive into the world of tags and elements and make them your new best friends!</description>
      <author> (Written by Nikola Brežnjak)</author>
      <guid>https://nikola-breznjak.com/blog/javascript/this-is-how-your-parents-used-to-build-websites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sticking To What Works - Nick Conn</title>
      <link>https://nicksbasecamp.com/sticking-to-what-works/</link>
      <description>Tech changes every day, but that doesn’t mean we should change our tools I was building a new side project. It was going to be focused on weather data, specifically tornadoes. I already know Django on the back-end, but I didn’t know Tailwind CSS on the front. A new front-end framework! My front-end experience consisted ... Read more</description>
      <author> (Nick Conn)</author>
      <guid>https://nicksbasecamp.com/sticking-to-what-works/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing rep &amp;amp; ren: A New Approach to Command-Line Find &amp;amp; Replace, and Renaming</title>
      <link>https://blog.robenkleene.com/2023/12/26/introducing-rep-ren/</link>
      <description>How to Use Rep</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.robenkleene.com/2023/12/26/introducing-rep-ren/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tool - Personal Goal Report Card</title>
      <link>https://blog.robertsimoes.org/posts/tool--personal-goal-report-card/</link>
      <description>Personal goal setting is a common habit for each new year. For the past several years, I’ve set goals for the coming new year while also reflecting and reviewing on how I did during the year. More often than not, I fall short of my ambition in so far as I had a cross-off-worthy outcome; how dreadful, to deny that sweet satisfaction. At the same time, however, I often have made some progress towards a goal but, for whatever reason: uncontrollable factors, escalating priorities, laziness, life events, et cetera, the progress stalled or stopped.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.robertsimoes.org/posts/tool--personal-goal-report-card/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poor Man&amp;#39;s Web</title>
      <link>https://zserge.com/posts/small-web/</link>
      <description>The Small Web Renaissance, Finger, Gopher and Gemini. How they work and what makes them different from the modern Big Web.</description>
      <author> (Serge Zaitsev)</author>
      <guid>https://zserge.com/posts/small-web/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where on the doll did software eng. evangelism hurt you?</title>
      <link>https://trolololo.xyz/software-evangelism-mess</link>
      <description>Where on the doll did software eng. evangelism hurt you?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://trolololo.xyz/software-evangelism-mess</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM security - Introduction</title>
      <link>https://rnikhil.com/2023/12/18/ai-llm-security-part1.html</link>
      <description>Since I quit my job couple months back, I’ve been tinkering around with various emerging technologies. I have been pretty obsessed with the current AI evolution of large language models (LLMs) and their surprising text generation capabilities. Whether you are surprised or not, people have started integrating them into just about every software we interact with and after spending countless hours asking it to generate song lyrics, I eventually wanted to understand what was happening behind the scenes. I am no AI engineer and I barely remember the Machine learning/ Neural network courses I took in college, but given my computer security background, what better way to learn how these LLM’s work than by trying to break them? In this post, we look at the basics of AI security, current “known” attacks, common defenses and some CTF challenges. I’ve been meaning to write this post for a while but this field was moving so fast that keeping up latest publications is a full time job. Now that NeurIPS is over and things have calmed down, I finally got time to work on this.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rnikhil.com/2023/12/18/ai-llm-security-part1.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being Stuck in Someone Else’s Theory</title>
      <link>https://jimmyhmiller.github.io/stuck</link>
      <description>Software development can be an incredibly frustrating venture. Not primarily because programming is hard and we often make mistakes. Nor because there are countless tedious things like dependency management that we have to deal with. Nor because we are confronted by an overwhelming number of choices on what library or framework to use. Instead, I think the primary reason stems from something much more deeply unsettling, being forced to live in someone else’s theory.</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Miller)</author>
      <guid>https://jimmyhmiller.github.io/stuck</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PostgreSQL Internals: 3 Things to Know About UPDATE Statements</title>
      <link>https://patrick.engineering/posts/postgres-internals/</link>
      <description>I recently finished reading PostgreSQL 14 Internals by Egor Rogov. It is one of the great books that teach applied computer science without watering down the difficult parts.
One particularly interesting topic is PostgreSQL’s execution of UPDATE statements. Updates in relational databases are inherently complex. They can be affected by conflicts, anomalies, and deadlocks. However, some behavior is specific to PostgreSQL. This can lead to surprises.
1. Write Amplification PostgreSQL generally does not update rows in-place.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://patrick.engineering/posts/postgres-internals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linera Developer School Autumn 2023: Kick-Off</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dA7Vw-HfCy4%3Flist%3DPLdGxlJxLrfgLjfUJJ2iwDBnHa8XBI91x2</link>
      <description>Join us in kicking-off the Linera Autumn Developer School! In this event, Linera Founder Mathieu Baudet will do a deep dive on Linera, showcasing the vision ...</description>
      <author> (freeCodeCamp.org
  
  
  
    freeCodeCamp.org
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dA7Vw-HfCy4%3Flist%3DPLdGxlJxLrfgLjfUJJ2iwDBnHa8XBI91x2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 22:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonah Goodman &amp;#183; A National Evil</title>
      <link>https://www.lrb.co.uk/the-paper/v45/n23/jonah-goodman/a-national-evil</link>
      <description>At the turn of the 20th century, the Swiss were plagued by strange, interlinked medical conditions, which existed...</description>
      <author> (Jonah Goodman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.lrb.co.uk/the-paper/v45/n23/jonah-goodman/a-national-evil</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 21:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 billion if statements</title>
      <link>https://andreasjhkarlsson.github.io/jekyll/update/2023/12/27/4-billion-if-statements.html</link>
      <description>I recently stumbled upon this screenshot while researching social media on the train. Of course, it was followed by a cascade of spiteful comments, criticizing this fresh programmer’s attempt to solve a classical problem in computer science. The modulus operation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andreasjhkarlsson.github.io/jekyll/update/2023/12/27/4-billion-if-statements.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 20:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supersymmetry</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2873/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2873/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 20:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new lock type in .NET 9</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/d7f923b3-13ff-4ecc-8b8f-d847ae581f68</link>
      <description>There is a new sheriff in town when it comes to the lock keyword, And that is the new System.Threading.Lock type that is introduced in .NET 9. And yes, I know - we still need time to digest the big .NET 8 release.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/d7f923b3-13ff-4ecc-8b8f-d847ae581f68</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 19:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING: 2 Killer C# Iterator Bugs (And How To Prevent Them)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=noLWaVzFJJk</link>
      <description>C# iterators are a powerful feature that leverage IEnumerable in C# as well as the yield return syntax. Iterators are lazily evaluated which can be really us...</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader
  
  
  
    Dev Leader
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=noLWaVzFJJk</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 18:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does it mean when the compiler says that it can&amp;#39;t convert something to itself? - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231227-00/?p=109195</link>
      <description>Why is it even thinking about a conversion?</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231227-00/?p=109195</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 17:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve your ASP.NET core web app performance using Azure Cache for Redis | .NET Conf 2023</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=hVdgRw68GHM</link>
      <description>Learn how to use Redis Cache to improve performance and resiliency with your ASP.NET core web application. We will look into scenarios such as session store,...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=hVdgRw68GHM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:03:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>