<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Dennis Ritchie’s Lost Dissertation - CHM</title>
      <link>https://computerhistory.org/blog/discovering-dennis-ritchies-lost-dissertation/</link>
      <description>Until recently, across a half-century perhaps fewer than a dozen people had ever had the opportunity to read Dennis Ritchie’s dissertation—the intellectual and biographical fork-in-the-road separating an academic career in computer science from the one at Bell Labs leading to C and Unix. Why?</description>
      <author> (David C. Brock)</author>
      <guid>https://computerhistory.org/blog/discovering-dennis-ritchies-lost-dissertation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 20:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 2</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mCrhSBCju4E</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mCrhSBCju4E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 18:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual:  Steve Collins - .NET Core Dependency Injection – The Booster Jab</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Milton-Keynes-NET-Meetup-Group/events/271371131/</link>
      <description>Tue, Jul 14, 2020, 7:00 PM: Hello MK.NET folks,We're proud to present another virtual MK .NET meetup for July;As before, we'll be hosting on Zoom.We're excited to be joined by Steve Collins who will b</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/Milton-Keynes-NET-Meetup-Group/events/271371131/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 1</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ysmejeF5umg</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ysmejeF5umg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bug #1463112 “Cat sitting on keyboard crashes lightdm” : Bugs : Unity</title>
      <link>https://bugs.launchpad.net/unity/+bug/1463112</link>
      <description>14.04, locked screen to go to lunch, upon return from lunch cat was sitting on keyboard, login screen was frozen &amp; unresponsive.

To replicate:  In unity hit ctrl-alt-l, place keyboard on chair.  Sit on keyboard.  

Resolution: Switched to virtual terminal, restarted lightdm, lost all open windows in X session.

What should have happened: lightdm not becoming unresponsive.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bugs.launchpad.net/unity/+bug/1463112</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 15:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair Programming - Dan Clarke</title>
      <link>https://www.danclarke.com/2020-pair-programming</link>
      <description>20 June 2020</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.danclarke.com/2020-pair-programming</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 14:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 1</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2-4Dvc9WO9E</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2-4Dvc9WO9E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 06:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud to be |_____|</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@martin_29969/proud-to-be-e19375a0bd89</link>
      <description>If someone you knew exclaimed “I’m proud to be French!”, what would be your first thought? The Louvre? French cuisine? The Eiffel Tower…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@martin_29969)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@martin_29969/proud-to-be-e19375a0bd89</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 05:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The live coders conference</title>
      <link>https://atndesign.github.io/Live-coders-conference/</link>
      <description>An online-only conference put on by The Live Coders team on Twitch! You may be wondering who we are! We are The Live Coders, an outgoing and enthusiastic group of friendly channels that write code, teach about technology, and promote the technical community.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://atndesign.github.io/Live-coders-conference/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 05:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 2</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OLWlY3j-u0M</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OLWlY3j-u0M</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 05:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Queer Living: A history of DIY culture in the Black LBGT+ community</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UV3uPtzDoyA</link>
      <description>What is DIY culture? How does DIY culture intertwine with the Black LGBT+ culture? Get these questions answered, and learn a few easy beginner DIY tutorials to do on t-shirts! No previous experience required!
---
Harold studied computer science at the University of Texas at Austin. He's started Black Queer Living, a youtube channel dedicated to teaching life skills 101, centering queer and trans* people of color: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCx3ihWKRcPrTDdhk87M2yeg</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UV3uPtzDoyA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What they don't teach you about fundraising as a Black Founder</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=leetllfwNTI</link>
      <description>useneu.com has made 3 attempts at raising capital for our business. Each attempt brought with it some valuable, and often unintuitive, lessons about the fundraising process. Join me as I recount our fundraising experiences and the main lessons learned after each one. Should you ever need to fundraise, you'll know the key DOs and DONTs.
---
Claudius Mbemba was born in Cameroon, Africa to hard-working blue-collar parents who taught him the value of hard work, being a self-starter, and always learning. Immigrating to the US at the age of 7, Claudius saw how technology vastly improved the lives of Americans. It was then his love for technology was born. Following high school, Claudius pursued his Bachelors Degree in Computer Science while on the Varsity Football team at The Ohio State University. Upon completing his degree he accepted employment at Microsoft in Seattle, WA where he worked as a Software Engineer, largely focusing his time on Voice, Mobile, Cloud, Bots, DevOps, ML/AI, &amp; Blockchain. Claudius is currently CTO of Neu Inc, a startup building a marketplace that provides automated hotel-grade turnovers for Airbnb/vacation rentals.

Learn more about Claudius on his website: www.claudiusmbemba.com</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=leetllfwNTI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowerment to the People! What You Need to Know about Black People, Disability, and Accessibility</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2W7QCYzOn_U</link>
      <description>About one fifth (20%) of the global population lives with disabilities.​ According to the 2017 American Community Survey, 13.6 percent of Black and African Americans have a disability. Further, the unemployment rate for people with disabilities is almost double of other people, and the people with disabilities who are employed have lower earnings, in general.

This means we have an opportunity and a duty to empower Black people with technology. One of the most powerful ways we can do this is to make our messaging accessible—no matter the platform or media.

While many of us have heard that accessibility is important, we seldom hear about how to implement it in our everyday work. Angela will discuss how people in every discipline—including PMs, content writers, designers, engineers, and more—can do so and further amplify the voices of Black people.
---
Angela Hooker is a Senior Accessibility Program Manager at Microsoft, where she's built a center of expertise for accessibility, user experience, and universal design. She's brought her web management, development, design, accessibility, and editorial and content management expertise to the government and private sector for over 20 years.

Angela also advocates for role-based accessibility and believes that teaching people how to incorporate principles of accessibility in their everyday work creates a sustainable program and produces the most accessible user experiences. Angela speaks on and writes about accessibility, disability, user experience, and plain language.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2W7QCYzOn_U</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combatting Bias in ML</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NIxUAlmnqz0</link>
      <description>In this talk I cover how to see the bias in your data and machine learning models. By giving examples from recent research on biased facial recognition systems as well as cutting edge explainability algorithms, attendees can expect clarification on what bias means in machine learning.
---
Ayodele Odubela is a Data Scientist working on driver risk mitigation at SambaSafety in Denver, CO. Previously she earned her Master's degree in Data Science after transitioning to tech from social media marketing. She's created algorithms that predict consumer segment movement, goals in hockey, and the location of firearms using radio frequency sensors.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NIxUAlmnqz0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Combat To Code  How Vets Who Code Trained Over 250 veterans how to Code and Get Jobs For Free</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CESi0jv4B_E</link>
      <description>A detailed origin story of how I became known as the Web's Captain America and how Vets Who Code trains veterans for free. We will go over how we came to be, how we train our troops, our teams and how you can help us continue our mission.

Jerome Hardaway is a Google Developer Expert (Web) UI/UX engineer, Dev Advocate and Geek At Arms (Founder and Executive Director) of Vets Who Code, a 501(c)3 veteran-led charitable non-profit dedicated to filling the nation’s technical skills gap with early-stage transitioning veterans and military spouses through remote software development training.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CESi0jv4B_E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving Back to Tech without Burnout</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dOmzzo0vTUI</link>
      <description>You did it! You’re a Software Engineer! After many hours of studying and learning difficult concepts, you made it through. Now you want to volunteer and give back your tech skills to a needed cause. Exciting, right? Wait…here’s a few tips to avoid giver burnout before you start.

In this talk, Mo will discuss ways tech givers can continue to volunteer without spreading themselves too thin. Tips will include: how do you give your talent without depleting your energy, choosing volunteer opportunities or open source projects with great impact, and how to say no.
---
Mo Hampton is a Software Engineer at GDIT. Her passion for web application development led her to the Open Source community to learn full-stack JavaScript. When not thriving off of coffee, meditation or travel, she builds cost-effective, user-friendly business applications.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dOmzzo0vTUI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journaling as a Dev</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UYiAlmTr_dA</link>
      <description>Are you working with impact and purpose? Are you solidly attuned on what you're doing month-to-month with your role? How difficult is it for you to track your accomplishments at work? If any of these questions lead to uncertain answers, then you should learn what it means to journal professionally as a dev. This talk will cover my exploration into journaling and its application to tracking my goals and progress as a software engineer. I will discuss how to set up your journal for any goals and how to score on your performance review!
-----
Brittney is a software engineer who loves a good cup of tea. In her spare time, she draws illustrations for teaNotes.dev on Instagram. Brittney strives to connect with folks who geek out over code with hopes to contribute to a friendly and inviting tech community.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UYiAlmTr_dA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keynote: The Journey To Inclusive Innovation Incubator (In3DC)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8cgPjeVhlEI</link>
      <description>How we ended up building an innovation space for black and underrepresented communities. Our focus on tech enabled startups and small business is driven by our roots in the development firm Clearly Innovative Inc, mobile partners for NMAAHC.
---
Aaron Saunders CEO Inclusive Innovation Incubator, Clearly Innovative, 30 years in technology /entrepreneurship space as developer, manager, founder and CEO</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8cgPjeVhlEI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ideal Community Model:  Lessons Learned</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d0QRQWhej-s</link>
      <description>There are many ways to push your career to a point it takes a great turn, but I found out in 2017 that community participation is a must. Community involvement can be anything from Open Source Contributions, Writing articles, answering questions on social media/StackOverflow to speaking at conferences. Participation in your community will expand your network.

By attending small meetups or having conversations in slack channels will lead you to meet new people in your industry. Sharing will increase your visibility in the ecosystem by Founders, people of related skill sets, recruiters, and more.

There isn’t just one way to share your expertise with your community. Open Source Contributions isn't just code, you can write articles/documentation about the product you would like to contribute to about your experiences or speak at conferences. Collaboration helps you to be seen as a leader in your community. You can collaborate with others in your network by mentoring, organizing an event, or working together on a personal project/ideas

I learned most of the things I know today about the community the hard way because I never saw it as anything important, and all I cared about was just write the code and today I am a Senior Developer Advocate at Fleek, and also the lead organizer of some major communities in Africa which included, unStack, Developers Circles Lagos from Facebook, Open Source Community Africa, NaijaHacks, and AfricaHacks.

Key Takeaways:

1) Attendees will learn how to build a community on their own
2) Attendees will learn how open-source works in a community
3) Attendees will learn how to contribute to ideas to a community

----------------

Shodipo Ayomide is a Developer Advocate, Engineer, and Occasional Designer, who also contributes to a lot of open-source projects over on GitHub, he also runs some major communities like unStack, Developers Circles Lagos from Facebook, Open Source Community Africa and NaijaHacks driving Nigeria &amp; Africa forward in Technology, he is an international speaker who has spoken at a lot of conferences over time in various locations, in his free time he loves to, Read, See a Movie and Occasionally play video games, Loves Travelling and Family.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d0QRQWhej-s</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking into Tech  From the Trenches</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2N5fI5j-IIs</link>
      <description>Bottom Line: Grit is required from historically underrepresented groups to change the demographic of Software Engineers and Developers. This talk will share my personal obstacles from a non-traditional career path (Veteran, women of color, mother and coding bootcamp graduate) to a Software Engineer.

The intent is to encourage passionate developers who are members of historically underrepresented groups, but not limited to new developers from non-tech industries, developers starting second careers, re-entering the workforce, and those who have attended coding bootcamps, to build and support a community in Open Source.
---
Mo Hampton is a Software Engineer at GDIT. Her passion for web application development led her to the Open Source community to learn full-stack JavaScript. When not thriving off of coffee, meditation or travel, she builds cost-effective, user-friendly business applications.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2N5fI5j-IIs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your next open source contribution</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UzI2Wdl3arE</link>
      <description>Today Open Source is ubiquitous and comprises nearly 80% – 90% of the code in a “typical” application. There is a need to use Open Source to stay competitive, but what about the need to use open source to advance your career?

In this talk, I will talk through actionable ways to make open-source contributions to grow your career.
---
Brian Douglas is a Developer Advocate at GitHub where he works on increasing use of the GitHub API by iterating on the onboarding process and helping users with evergreen technical content.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UzI2Wdl3arE</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowered By Imposter Syndrome</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qheqnbhldI8</link>
      <description>Imposter syndrome is something that the industry continues to represent as a negative. My take on this as a black woman in tech is we need to turn all of our disadvantages into growth opportunities. Adding structure to our learning path is the best way of removing the negative image of feeling like an imposter and allows us to flourish.
---
Valerie Phoenix is a Founder &amp; CEO at Tech By Choice and a Senior Software Engineer at Mastery Logistics. She holds a BS in Psychology &amp; Art. Valerie is passionate about creating secure human-centered digital experiences. As a successful self-taught developer, Valerie started Tech By Choice to give back to the community that helped her succeed.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qheqnbhldI8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth History</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/hh6i_SjfCYI</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/hh6i_SjfCYI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:41:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth History</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hh6i_SjfCYI</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hh6i_SjfCYI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:41:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Juneteenth – GenX Jamerican</title>
      <link>https://www.genxjamerican.com/2020/06/19/my-first-juneteenth/</link>
      <description>Today marks the date in 1865 when General Gordon Granger read General Order 3 to the people of Galveston Bay, Texas, informing the enslaved there and in all of Texas of freedom that had been rightfully theirs two years earlier.  That was essentially the full extent of my understanding of Juneteenth until recently, so I’ve taken the additional time off my employer gave us today to dig a bit deeper.  Juneteenth.com, the Wikipedia entry about Juneteenth, and this explainer by Dr. Henry Louis Gates, Jr. have been my starting points.  I shared these links with my direct reports as well as my co-workers before our 2PM close today, and was heartened by how generously they were received.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.genxjamerican.com/2020/06/19/my-first-juneteenth/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workshop: Docker and Kubernetes - 1/2 - NDC Melbourne 2020</title>
      <link>https://ndcmelbourne.com/talk/workshop-docker-and-kubernetes-1-4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;Module 1/4&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
Containers such as Docker and container orchestration such as Kubernetes are hot topics right now, if you’re working on microservice architectures it very likely you’ll be looking at these technologies as they are a natural fit for microservices. Containers are also a great way of dealing with legacy applications and allowing you to use modern deployment techniques for these older applications.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ndcmelbourne.com/talk/workshop-docker-and-kubernetes-1-4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home : Hypothesis</title>
      <link>https://web.hypothes.is/</link>
      <description>Homedwhly2020-06-19T15:25:55-07:00</description>
      <author> (dwhly)</author>
      <guid>https://web.hypothes.is/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emancipation Statue - Barbados Pocket Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.barbadospocketguide.com/our-island-barbados/monuments/emancipation-statue.html</link>
      <description>Welcome to the Barbados Pocket Guide, a comprehensive source of information about our island, it's people, culture and life in general.</description>
      <author> (Gloria)</author>
      <guid>https://www.barbadospocketguide.com/our-island-barbados/monuments/emancipation-statue.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 01:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTTPS is NOT Secure Enough for API</title>
      <link>https://vec.io/posts/https-is-not-secure-enough-for-api</link>
      <description>Mixin me 25566</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vec.io/posts/https-is-not-secure-enough-for-api</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:52:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Figma Wins - kwokchain</title>
      <link>https://kwokchain.com/2020/06/19/why-figma-wins/</link>
      <description>Companies are a sequencing of loops. While it’s possible to stumble into an initial core loop that works, the companies that are successful in the long term are the ones that can repeatedly find the next loop. However, this evolution is poorly understood relative to its existential impact on a company’s trajectory. Figma is a … Continue reading Why Figma Wins →</description>
      <author> (Kevin)</author>
      <guid>https://kwokchain.com/2020/06/19/why-figma-wins/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:52:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Got My 7 Person Startup Featured In Entrepreneur Magazine - David Kemmerer</title>
      <link>https://davidkemmerer.co/entrepreneur-magazine/</link>
      <description>If you have the word “Co-Founder” or “Chief ______ Officer” in your LinkedIn title, there’s a good chance your inbox gets flooded with pitches from all sorts of sales people. It doesn’t even matter if the title is legit or not.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidkemmerer.co/entrepreneur-magazine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:52:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ugly truth</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.com/posts/2019/06/the-ugly-truth/</link>
      <description>I am so excited to meet my old friend Vinay after a long time. It has been almost one and half year we spoke to each other. We worked together in one of my previous organizations and he is a close friend and kind of mentor to me too. We both got busy in our lives and we are not in touch lately. I am so happy to meet him after a long time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.com/posts/2019/06/the-ugly-truth/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:52:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing a brainfuck CPU in Ghidra - part 1: Setup and disassembly</title>
      <link>https://spinsel.dev/2020/06/17/ghidra-brainfuck-processor-1.html</link>
      <description>This blog post is part of the series Implementing a brainfuck CPU in Ghidra: Setup and disassembly Decompilation of pointer and arithmetic instructions Decompilation of I/O and control flow instructionsRenaming the analyzer and adding a manual (future post)Recognizing common patterns (future post)More posts may be added to this series in the future.</description>
      <author> (Matthijs Poppe)</author>
      <guid>https://spinsel.dev/2020/06/17/ghidra-brainfuck-processor-1.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:52:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting from the Problem not the Solution</title>
      <link>https://odone.io/posts/2020-06-19-starting-from-the-problem-not-the-solution.html</link>
      <description>I spent most of the day in solution space. The wrong solution space. In fact, I was solving a problem that didn't exist.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://odone.io/posts/2020-06-19-starting-from-the-problem-not-the-solution.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:52:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wolf</title>
      <link>https://randsinrepose.com/archives/the-wolf/</link>
      <description>You’ve heard of the 10x engineer, but I am here to tell you about the Wolf. They are an engineer and they consistently exhibit the following characteristics:  They appear to exist outside of the well-defined process that we’ve defined to get things done, but they appear to suffer no consequences fo</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://randsinrepose.com/archives/the-wolf/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:51:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switching from Fedora &amp; Gnome to Arch &amp; Sway | Josh Mcguigan</title>
      <link>https://www.joshmcguigan.com/blog/hot-take-fedora-gnome-arch-sway/</link>
      <description>I’ve been a Linux user for ~1 year, switching from macOS which I had been using for a long time. I installed Fedora on a 4th generation X1 Carbon and everything just worked.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.joshmcguigan.com/blog/hot-take-fedora-gnome-arch-sway/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:51:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good and Bad Parts of Ansible after 2 Years of Usage</title>
      <link>https://mtyurt.net/post/2020/good-bad-parts-of-ansible-after-two-years.html</link>
      <description>Personal experiences from Ansible usage after two years.</description>
      <author> (M. Tarık Yurt)</author>
      <guid>https://mtyurt.net/post/2020/good-bad-parts-of-ansible-after-two-years.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:51:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>johang/btfs</title>
      <link>https://github.com/johang/btfs</link>
      <description>A bittorrent filesystem based on FUSE. Contribute to johang/btfs development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/johang/btfs</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police-Data-Accessibility-Project/Police-Data-Accessibility-Project</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Police-Data-Accessibility-Project/Police-Data-Accessibility-Project</link>
      <description>A repository for all code related to the Police Data Accessibility Project - Police-Data-Accessibility-Project/Police-Data-Accessibility-Project</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Police-Data-Accessibility-Project/Police-Data-Accessibility-Project</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Download the App and it Doesn't Work</title>
      <link>https://youdownloadtheappanditdoesntwork.com/</link>
      <description>Examples of capriciousness in App Store policymaking.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youdownloadtheappanditdoesntwork.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Written communication is remote work super power</title>
      <link>https://snir.dev/blog/remote-async-communication/</link>
      <description>Update: An interesting discussion around this started in hacker news</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://snir.dev/blog/remote-async-communication/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 22:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCCXLIII - Muscle Sword</title>
      <link>https://swordscomic.com/comic/CCCXLIII/</link>
      <description>**Puny Hero:** Muscle Sword! Give me your power!

&gt; The Puny Hero becomes a Muscly Hero with a CHONK! sound

&gt; Muscle Hero leaps at a dragon

**Muscle Hero:** HYAAAAH!

&gt; Dragon is stabbed with the Muscle Sword and every part of its body becomes covered in muscles

**Muscle Hero:** Haha! Whoops!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://swordscomic.com/comic/CCCXLIII/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 21:38:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 196</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-196/</link>
      <description>All my things are breaking 😭 Mic broke, PC broke, boat shed handle broke, fridges (both of them) broke, fireplace broke, roof broke... and that's just the stuff I could remember in the live stream. But in happier news, listening back to that video now I'm really happy with the audio</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt's Picture)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-196/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 21:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join us live! - JuneteenthConf - June 19th and 20th 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/index.html</link>
      <description>Juneteenth Conference is a free virtual tech conference made for and featuring Black people in technology. The conference celebrates Black Excellence and promotes community for Black people who are severely underrepresented in the tech industry. We welcome anyone and everyone aligned with this goal to come and listen to the conversation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 21:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>