<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>5.1.4 Overhead Speaker Setup</title>
      <link>https://www.dolby.com/us/en/guide/speaker-setup-guides/5.1.4-overhead-speaker-setup-guide.html</link>
      <description>5.1.4 Overhead Speaker Setup</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dolby.com/us/en/guide/speaker-setup-guides/5.1.4-overhead-speaker-setup-guide.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 20:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is BGP safe yet? · Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://isbgpsafeyet.com/</link>
      <description>On the Internet, network devices exchange routes via a protocol called BGP (Border Gateway Protocol). Unfortunately, issues with BGP have led to malicious actors being able to hijack and misconfigure devices leading to security problems which have the potential to cause widespread problems. BGP security can be greatly improved by using technologies such as RPKI to sign Internet routes. This page attempts to track the progress of major Internet players (ISPs, transit operators, and content providers) in their progress to adopt RPKI and other technologies.</description>
      <author> (Cloudflare)</author>
      <guid>https://isbgpsafeyet.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 20:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I made a basketball hoop that always goes in</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vtN4tkvcBMA</link>
      <description>I've wondered if it is possible to make a basketball hoop where the ball always goes in. Imagine throwing a ball and if it hits the backboard it somehow gets directed into the hoop. Thanks to physics it isn't quite possible to make ALL possible shots go in though you can make a hoop where the ball goes in a lot more often. In this video I show how I wrote a program to calculate the optical backboard then machined and fabricated it. It worked out better than I was expected so I'm really happy with it!

*Sorry for the re-upload to anyone who saw the first one. I made a major rookie mistake and uploaded the wrong file. yikes! Lesson learned.*

"duh-dun" sound from orangefreesounds.com licensed under the CC-NC4.0 license https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/</description>
      <author> (Stuff Made Here)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vtN4tkvcBMA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 19:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2019 for Mac - Preview Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/visualstudio/releasenotes/vs2019-mac-preview-relnotes#preview2</link>
      <description>Release notes for new/upcoming features in Visual Studio for Mac, available for pre-release testing by downloading the Preview version.</description>
      <author> (gregm)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/visualstudio/releasenotes/vs2019-mac-preview-relnotes#preview2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 18:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[wsl2] filesystem performance is much slower than wsl1 in /mnt · Issue #4197 · microsoft/WSL</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/WSL/issues/4197</link>
      <description>I decided to open this as a separate issue because although it&amp;#39;s related to the generic issue of filesystem performance it&amp;#39;s directly related to WSL 2 while the other issues are for WSL 1 a...</description>
      <author> (therealkenc)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/WSL/issues/4197</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 17:21:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Light is beautiful | Thoughts of a graphics programmer and spare time photographer</title>
      <link>http://lousodrome.net/blog/light/</link>
      <description>Over the last few months I have been trying to push my understanding of Physically Based Shading, by actively exploring every corner and turning over every stone, to uncover any area where I lack knowledge. Although this is still an ongoing process and I still have a lot to do, I thought I could already share some of what I have learned in the process.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://lousodrome.net/blog/light/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 17:21:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trains․NET - Episode 25 - Fighting with Blazor to JavaScript interop to try to extract some speed</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zaEhO8dVAjc</link>
      <description>Originally streamed at https://twitch.tv/davidwengier

In this episode we finish off drawing on a HTML canvas and hook up some mouse events, only to be hit by the brick wall of terrible performance with interop between .NET running on WASM and trying to call JavaScript in the browser. Technically it works, just not very well 😀</description>
      <author> (David Wengier)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zaEhO8dVAjc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 17:20:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squaring The Circle (feat. James Grime) - Objectivity #171</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B4gzt8v401Q</link>
      <description>Dr James Grime joins us at The Royal Society to look at all manner of things from secret codes to fancy objects... More links below ↓↓↓

Featuring Dr James Grime speaking with Brady and Keith Moore.

Accompanying documents: http://www.bradyharanblog.com/blog/squaring-the-circle-the-documents

Squaring the circle: https://youtu.be/CMP9a2J4Bqw

White Gloves of Destiny: http://bit.ly/White_Gloves

Check out Numberphile: https://www.youtube.com/user/numberphile

Objectivity on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/objectivity

Subscribe to Objectivity: http://bit.ly/Objectivity_Sub
Films by James Hennessy and Brady Haran

Royal Society website: http://bit.ly/Royal_Society

The Royal Society's own YouTube channel: https://www.youtube.com/user/RoyalSociety

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/ObjectivityVideos
Twitter: https://twitter.com/objectivity_vid

Patron thank you page: http://www.bradyharanblog.com/objectivity-patrons

Objectivity T-Shirts: https://teespring.com/en-GB/stores/objectivity</description>
      <author> (Objectivity)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B4gzt8v401Q</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 16:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internode</title>
      <link>https://www.internode.on.net/</link>
      <description>Australia’s #1 Broadband Provider with plans available across NBN, ADSL2+, Naked DSL, VoIP, Home Phone and 4G Mobile as well as Corporate &amp; Business Internet solutions. Join Internode today!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.internode.on.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 16:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONLINE] Entity Framework Past and Future</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Louisville-DotNet/events/270049199/</link>
      <description>Thu, May 21, 2020, 7:00 PM: ** VIRTUAL/ONLINE Event **For the next couple of months, Louisville .NET Meetup will be an online event. This way we can still get together, learn about awesome things abou</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/Louisville-DotNet/events/270049199/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 16:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Segal Dev - Nand to Tetris is a great course</title>
      <link>https://mattsegal.dev/nand-to-tetris.html</link>
      <description>Matt's blog on backend web development.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mattsegal.dev/nand-to-tetris.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 14:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET JIT compiler is not type safe – TooSlowException</title>
      <link>https://tooslowexception.com/net-jit-compiler-is-not-type-safe/</link>
      <description>Everyone knows that C# is a strongly typed language and incorrect type usage is simply not possible there. So, the following program will just not compile:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tooslowexception.com/net-jit-compiler-is-not-type-safe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 13:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Userscripts Are Fun And Are Still Very Much Relevant</title>
      <link>https://dutzi.party/userscripts-are-fun/</link>
      <description>Sharing my thoughts on userscripts, a phenomenon the swept the internet back in the 00s.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dutzi.party/userscripts-are-fun/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 13:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roundup #69: ASP.NET Core Urls &amp; Ports, Tye, Orleans, and Diagnostics - CodeOpinion</title>
      <link>https://codeopinion.com/roundup-69/</link>
      <description>After a bit of a break, the .NET Roundups are back! This week, it’s almost as if Andrew Lock was working on the exact same I was as he had two posts back to back that solved two issues I was having. Incredible timing and as always great content from Andrew. 5 ways to set …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://codeopinion.com/roundup-69/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 12:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICANN delays .org sell off after California's attorney general intervenes at last minute, tears non-profit a new one over sale</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.co.uk/2020/04/17/icann_california_org_sale_delay/</link>
      <description>DNS overseer accused of ignoring the very people it is supposed to represent</description>
      <author> (17 Apr 2020 at 00:40)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.co.uk/2020/04/17/icann_california_org_sale_delay/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Released: Microsoft.Data.SqlClient 1.1.2</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server/released-microsoft-data-sqlclient-1-1-2/ba-p/1311082</link>
      <description>We recently released an update to Microsoft.Data.SqlClient, version 1.1.2. The update addresses a few issues that are important to our customers.   Updates in Microsoft.Data.SqlClient 1.1.2 are:   Added  Allowed passing username with Active Directory Interactive Authentication #493 #516 Fixed  Fixed...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/343280)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server/released-microsoft-data-sqlclient-1-1-2/ba-p/1311082</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Code Tired | Pretty Method Display in xUnit.net</title>
      <link>https://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Pretty-Method-Display-in-xUnitnet</link>
      <description>Don't Code Tired - Jason Roberts on Software Development and .NET -</description>
      <author> (Jason)</author>
      <guid>https://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Pretty-Method-Display-in-xUnitnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure on the Cheap - Azure Storage Static Website and Azure Front Door</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-developer-community-blog/azure-on-the-cheap-azure-storage-static-website-and-azure-front/ba-p/1297084</link>
      <description>Azure on the Cheap posts focus on the architecture, techniques and technology in Azure that add considerable value without breaking the bank. This value is being measured in both the amount of effort taken to develop, provision, and maintain the resources, as well as the monthly charge for the resou...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/141713)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-developer-community-blog/azure-on-the-cheap-azure-storage-static-website-and-azure-front/ba-p/1297084</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple changes default MacBook charging behavior to improve battery health</title>
      <link>https://sixcolors.com/post/2020/04/apple-battery-health-management/</link>
      <description>


The way MacBook batteries charge is about to change. Apple has released a new developer preview of macOS Catalina 10.15.5, and as these releases often do, it contains a new feature: Battery Health Management.

The new feature, which will only be availa...</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/jsnell)</author>
      <guid>https://sixcolors.com/post/2020/04/apple-battery-health-management/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Diagnostics Client Library for .NET Core</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Introducing-the-Diagnostics-Client-Library-for-NET-Core</link>
      <description>In this episode, we're joined by Software Engineer Sung Yoon Whang from the .NET Runtime team. He's here to talk to us about the diagnostics client .NET Core. Using the library, you can communicate wi</description>
      <author> (by Cecil Phillip, Rich Lander)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Introducing-the-Diagnostics-Client-Library-for-NET-Core</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating CommonJS-based npm packages via TypeScript</title>
      <link>https://2ality.com/2020/04/npm-cjs-typescript.html</link>
      <description>This blog post describes how to use TypeScript to create npm packages with CommonJS modules. All the artifacts that are shown can be downloaded via the GitHub repository ts-demo-npm-cjs (I deliberately have not published it to npm).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2ality.com/2020/04/npm-cjs-typescript.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Rant On Reusability</title>
      <link>https://makingloops.com/reusability-rant/</link>
      <description>The author rants about why reusability should not be taken lightly.</description>
      <author> (Joe Petrakovich)</author>
      <guid>https://makingloops.com/reusability-rant/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rider 2020.1 Is Released! - .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/04/16/rider-2020-1-released/</link>
      <description>Hello everyone, We’ve published Rider 2020.1 today! Let’s talk about the most important updates we have for you in this release. The backend runs on .NET Core runtime Finally, the backend runs on .NET Core runtime by default on macOS … Continue reading →</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/04/16/rider-2020-1-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See What's New in Visual Studio 2019 v16.6 Preview 3! | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/new-in-visual-studio-2019-v16-6-preview-3/</link>
      <description>Visual Studio 2019 v16.6 Preview 3 releases today with new features in Git user experiences, Terminal, Mobile Developer, and Microsoft Fakes for .NET Core.</description>
      <author> (Jacqueline WiddisProgram Manager, Release TeamFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/new-in-visual-studio-2019-v16-6-preview-3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Uno Platform support for Visual Studio Code - Uno Platform</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/announcing-uno-platform-support-for-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <description>We are happy to announce the preview of Uno Platform support for Visual Studio Code, following the progress made by the .NET team on the Visual Studio Code WebAssembly debugger integration. This blog will walk you through the set-up process for building and debugging WebAssembly apps with Uno wherever Visual Studio Code runs – Windows, Linux or macOS. Also, it is important to note that by using Visual Studio Code, you will be able to create or edit only your Web (WebAssembly) Uno Platform projects. About Uno Platform For those new to Uno Platform – it enables for creation of single-source C# and XAML apps which run natively on iOS and Android, and Web via WebAssembly. Uno Platform is Open Source (Apache 2.0) and available on GitHub. To learn more about Uno Platform, see how it works, or create a small sample app.   Create a new Uno Platform project for WebAssembly 1. Launch Code, then in the terminal type the following to install the Uno Platform templates: dotnet new -i Uno.ProjectTemplates.Dotnet::2.2.0-dev.494 Note that this command was updated since the original publication of this article. If the command below did not work, try re-running it to update to the latest …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/announcing-uno-platform-support-for-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper Ultimate 2020.1: Improved Support for C# 8.0 and C++20, Dataflow Analysis of Integer Values, and Much More - .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/04/16/resharper-ultimate-2020-1/</link>
      <description>Try out the first major update this year! Read about the most exciting updates we have for you in the 2020.1 release.</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/04/16/resharper-ultimate-2020-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity Framework Core Part 2</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Entity-Framework-Core-Part-2</link>
      <description>In this episode, Robert is joined by Phil Japikse for part 2 of a 5 part series on Entity Framework Core. Aimed at folks new to EF Core, Phil shows how to start with an existing SQL Server database, c</description>
      <author> (by Robert Green)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Entity-Framework-Core-Part-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 187</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-187/</link>
      <description>Spiders! Ok, not your normal start to a weekly update but yeah, we had a bit of an infestation this week which did take the mind of other current events for a while. Much of what's happened beyond that this week has resulted in various tweet storms; the Zoom credential</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-187/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing policy, Y Combinator cuts its pro rata stake and makes investments case-by-case – TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2020/04/16/changing-policy-y-combinator-cuts-its-pro-rata-stake-and-makes-investments-case-by-case/</link>
      <description>In a message posted to its internal communications channel earlier this week, the massive startup accelerator Y Combinator said it will change the terms of its own PPP (the YC pro rata investment program) and investing in companies raising seed and Series A rounds on a case-by-case basis. The compa…</description>
      <author> (Jonathan Shieber@jshieber / 1:25 pm PDT • April 16, 2020comment Comment)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2020/04/16/changing-policy-y-combinator-cuts-its-pro-rata-stake-and-makes-investments-case-by-case/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 04:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Vue Apr 16 2020</title>
      <link>https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1LHp-8hEtXEMSE1fd6YLAhYmtndQelQKbWlGggZKe4y8/edit?usp=sharing</link>
      <description>State of Vue ThisDot Online Meetup Apr 16th, 2020</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1LHp-8hEtXEMSE1fd6YLAhYmtndQelQKbWlGggZKe4y8/edit?usp=sharing</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 03:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Excel with s0lly: 5. Simulating the Game of Life</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IiyVHIxdrYo</link>
      <description>This video is a simple implementation of the Game of Life in Excel - where you can follow along with my approach to creating the spreadsheet from A-to-Z.

You can find the file here: https://github.com/s0lly/GameOfLifeInExcel

Hope you find this useful, and that it gives you good ideas for building your own simulations!

As always, please let me know if there is any particular content you'd like to see!


Other Social Media stuffs:

https://www.twitch.tv/s0llygaming
https://twitter.com/s0lly
https://www.instagram.com/s0lly.gaming/
https://github.com/s0lly
https://www.patreon.com/s0lly</description>
      <author> (s0lly)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IiyVHIxdrYo</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 01:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herding Code 241: The Freaky Friday macOS / Windows Switch</title>
      <link>https://herdingcode.com/herding-code-241-the-freaky-friday-macos-windows-switch/</link>
      <description>Recently Jon switched to developing on macOS, and Rob's been developing on Windows. It's time for the Freaky Friday edition! The guys compare notes, what they like, what's confusing, and what they've learned.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://herdingcode.com/herding-code-241-the-freaky-friday-macos-windows-switch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 01:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatsby and Sanity.io - Part 3 (Live Stream)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LFnGv6y91K4</link>
      <description>Gatsby and Sanity.io are a great pair for creating JAMstack projects like blogs. In these videos, I am working to migrate my Gatsby blog from using markdown files to using the Headless CMS called Sanity.io. After starting this migration, I am loving Gatsby and Sanity.io

https://www.jamesqquick.com
https://www.jamesqquick.com/uses/ (hardware, software, etc.)
https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
https://www.learnbuildteach.com/

Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code!!
https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/

Build a Quiz App with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/

Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/jamesqquick</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LFnGv6y91K4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 23:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Workers Now Support COBOL</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-workers-now-support-cobol/</link>
      <description>COBOL is often a source of amusement for programmers because it is seen as old, verbose, clunky, and difficult to maintain. COBOL can now be used to write code for Cloudflare’s serverless platform Workers.</description>
      <author> (John Graham-Cumming)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-workers-now-support-cobol/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 23:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using .NET Core to provide Power Query for Excel on Mac | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/using-net-core-to-provide-power-query-for-excel-on-mac/</link>
      <description>Power Query is a data connection technology that enables you to discover, connect, combine, and refine data sources to meet your analysis needs. Features in Power Query are available in Excel and Power BI Desktop. Power Query was developed for windows and is written in C# targeting .NET Framework.</description>
      <author> (Oded HansonPrincipal Software Engineer, ExcelFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/using-net-core-to-provide-power-query-for-excel-on-mac/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workstream Home</title>
      <link>https://workstream.paperspace.com/</link>
      <description>Workstream is a super-fast, virtual computer you can use for anything. Get a new computer in less than 5 minutes, zero-configuration required.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://workstream.paperspace.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 22:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's like JSON. but fast and small.</title>
      <link>https://msgpack.org/index.html</link>
      <description>MessagePack is an efficient binary serialization format. It lets you exchange data among multiple languages like JSON. But it's faster and smaller. Small integers are encoded into a single byte, and typical short strings require only one extra byte in addition to the strings themselves.</description>
      <author> (Salvatore Sanfilippo, creator of Redis)</author>
      <guid>https://msgpack.org/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 21:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>