<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>From Skeuomorphic to Liquid Glass: Apple's Strategic Bet on the Post-Touch Future</title>
      <link>https://omc345.substack.com/p/from-skeuomorphic-to-liquid-glass</link>
      <description>Why Apple Just Killed the iPhone Interface (And What Comes Next)</description>
      <guid>https://omc345.substack.com/p/from-skeuomorphic-to-liquid-glass</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 11:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run C# Scripts With dotnet run app.cs (No Project Files Needed)</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/run-csharp-scripts-with-dotnet-run-app-no-project-files-needed</link>
      <description>With .NET 10, you can now run C# files directly. No project files, no Main method, just code. In this issue, I'll show you how to use the new `dotnet run app.cs` feature in practice: from quick one-liners to a real-world SQL seeding script.</description>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/run-csharp-scripts-with-dotnet-run-app-no-project-files-needed</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OxCaml | About</title>
      <link>https://oxcaml.org/</link>
      <description>It is both Jane Street’s production compiler, as well as a laboratory for experiments focused towards making
            OCaml better for performance-oriented programming. Our hope is that these extensions can over time be
            contributed to upstream OCaml.</description>
      <guid>https://oxcaml.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 01:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern ESLint Configurator for Next.js</title>
      <link>https://blog.azula9713.dev/why-i-built-a-modern-eslint-configurator-for-nextjs</link>
      <description>Discover Yae Lint Config: A modern ESLint configurator for Next.js, simplifying setup, staying current, and boosting productivity for developers</description>
      <author> (https://hashnode.com/@azula9713)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.azula9713.dev/why-i-built-a-modern-eslint-configurator-for-nextjs</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Narrative Fallacy — Ludicity</title>
      <link>https://ludic.mataroa.blog/blog/the-narrative-fallacy/</link>
      <description>Note: This is an edited re-post of something I wrote in 2019 on a now-defunct blog, apparently a month before I started my first job in tech. I need to reference it in a future post. As a result, it is a little bit different stylistically from my current writing. I hope you enjoy it anyway!</description>
      <guid>https://ludic.mataroa.blog/blog/the-narrative-fallacy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some thoughts on Kagi search after two months - @olly</title>
      <link>https://olly.pagecord.com/some-thoughts-on-kagi-search-after-two-months</link>
      <description>I’m old enough to remember when you had to search the internet using a portal such as Yahoo!, Excite or Alta Vista. I stopped using these when Google first...</description>
      <guid>https://olly.pagecord.com/some-thoughts-on-kagi-search-after-two-months</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Essentials for getting the most from Coding Agents </title>
      <link>https://dylanwatt.com/posts/2025-06-12-5-things/</link>
      <description>5 Essentials for getting the most from Coding Agents Spend the time to teach them your Project There are a lot of AI coding agents out there, but they all stall out if you don’t tool your codebase for them. There’s a ceiling of how effective they can be if they’re running in a boilerplate environment, with no customized context or guidance.</description>
      <guid>https://dylanwatt.com/posts/2025-06-12-5-things/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Sulka, the Hardened Yocto Distro - ejaaskel</title>
      <link>https://ejaaskel.dev/introducing-sulka-the-hardened-yocto-distro/</link>
      <description>For years I have been telling myself that it's a bit too much for a single person to try and manage a distro, but now I think it's time to give it a go.</description>
      <guid>https://ejaaskel.dev/introducing-sulka-the-hardened-yocto-distro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Computation</title>
      <link>https://aartaka.me/lost-compute.html</link>
      <description>We keep losing context and computation when running programs. But we don't have to. Let’s see how this lost compute can be avoided.</description>
      <guid>https://aartaka.me/lost-compute.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Nearly Accessed Millions Of Maruti Suzuki Customer Records</title>
      <link>https://rtvkiz.github.io/2025/06/13/How-I-Nearly-Accessed-Millions-Of-Maruti-Suzuki-Customer-Records.html</link>
      <description>Opinions expressed are solely my own and do not express the views or opinions of my employer</description>
      <guid>https://rtvkiz.github.io/2025/06/13/How-I-Nearly-Accessed-Millions-Of-Maruti-Suzuki-Customer-Records.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treat Your Humans Better Than Your Agents</title>
      <link>https://etodd.io/2025/06/13/treat-your-humans-better-than-your-agents/</link>
      <description>Folks are starting to figure out what kind of environment AI agents need to be productive. The gist is:
Agents need clear guidelines in a markdown file at the root of the repository explaining how to contribute to the project. Agents need a clean, isolated, reproducible environment in which they can run tests and go wild without breaking stuff and getting stuck. If the environments are sufficiently isolated, you can run them in parallel and allow multiple agents to work concurrently. Agents need fast tools so they can get feedback quickly. Tests should run fast. Speed of the iteration loop is everything. Documentation and code comments help agents figure out what’s going on. Agents work best with small contained tasks which can be reviewed and deployed continuously, rather than in huge risky chunks. What’s maddening is, if you replace the word “agents” with “humans”, all these sentences are equally true, if not more so.</description>
      <guid>https://etodd.io/2025/06/13/treat-your-humans-better-than-your-agents/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>» Audio stream across network to remote Raspberry Pi from Pipewire to Pulseaudio</title>
      <link>http://serendipity.ruwenzori.net/index.php/2025/06/13/audio-stream-across-network-to-remote-raspberry-pi-from-pipewire-to-pulseaudio</link>
      <description>Ten years ago, I set up Pulseaudio to sending audio streams across the LAN to a remote Raspberry Pi – from my home office’s desk to the livingroom… Still working ten years later: a solid solution.</description>
      <guid>http://serendipity.ruwenzori.net/index.php/2025/06/13/audio-stream-across-network-to-remote-raspberry-pi-from-pipewire-to-pulseaudio</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel Memory Safety: Mission Accomplished</title>
      <link>https://asterinas.github.io/2025/06/04/kernel-memory-safety-mission-accomplished.html</link>
      <description>(Forword: This post distills our research paper Asterinas: A Linux ABI-Compatible, Rust-Based Framekernel OS with a Small and Sound TCB, which is to be published at USENIX ATC 2025. The preprint can be found on arXiv.)</description>
      <guid>https://asterinas.github.io/2025/06/04/kernel-memory-safety-mission-accomplished.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pitfalls of premature closure with LLM assisted coding</title>
      <link>https://www.shayon.dev/post/2025/164/pitfalls-of-premature-closure-with-llm-assisted-coding/</link>
      <description>When LLM models generates clean, professional-looking code, it's tempting to stop exploring alternatives. But therein lies the risks that comes with premature closure. So what is premature closure?</description>
      <guid>https://www.shayon.dev/post/2025/164/pitfalls-of-premature-closure-with-llm-assisted-coding/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This can't be real, can it?</title>
      <link>https://www.tomoliver.net/posts/tms</link>
      <description>Fixing the chronic pain in my hands without medicine or surgery. This is my story of recovering from RSI and experiencing the mind-body connection.</description>
      <guid>https://www.tomoliver.net/posts/tms</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I vibe coded for two weeks</title>
      <link>https://joaomagfreitas.link/i-vibe-coded-for-two-weeks/</link>
      <description>I've been solo working on a new project at my current company, which involves migrating a desktop browser extension to mobile (fairly simple software that involves scanning and downloading images).</description>
      <guid>https://joaomagfreitas.link/i-vibe-coded-for-two-weeks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zed — Agentic Engineering</title>
      <link>https://zed.dev/agentic-engineering</link>
      <description>Combining human craftsmanship with AI tools to build better software.</description>
      <guid>https://zed.dev/agentic-engineering</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say "but yes", not "yes but"</title>
      <link>https://www.seangoedecke.com/but-yes-not-yes-but/</link>
      <description>When you’re agreeing with someone but you have a caveat, don’t say “yes, but”. Instead, say “but yes”. For instance, if you’re happy with a suggested approach…</description>
      <guid>https://www.seangoedecke.com/but-yes-not-yes-but/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Convinced HP's Board to Buy Palm for $1.2B. Then I Watched Them Kill It in 49 Days</title>
      <link>https://philmckinney.substack.com/p/i-convinced-hps-board-to-buy-palm</link>
      <description>The systematic thinking errors that kill breakthrough technology and the decision framework that prevents these disasters</description>
      <guid>https://philmckinney.substack.com/p/i-convinced-hps-board-to-buy-palm</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 21:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rendering Crispy Text On The GPU</title>
      <link>https://osor.io/text</link>
      <description>Rubén Osorio’s blog</description>
      <guid>https://osor.io/text</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading a Big Number</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3102/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3102/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>