<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>latest, x86 64-bit, x86-64 ABI</title>
      <link>https://syscalls.mebeim.net/?table=x86%2F64%2Fx64%2Flatest</link>
      <description>High-quality browsable Linux kernel syscall tables for multiple architectures</description>
      <author> (Marco Bonelli)</author>
      <guid>https://syscalls.mebeim.net/?table=x86%2F64%2Fx64%2Flatest</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 06:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike broke Debian and Rocky Linux months ago, but no one noticed</title>
      <link>https://www.neowin.net/news/crowdstrike-broke-debian-and-rocky-linux-months-ago-but-no-one-noticed/</link>
      <description>CrowdStrike recently caused a widespread Blue Screen of Death (BSOD) issue on Windows PCs, disrupting various sectors. However, this was not an isolated incident, CrowdStrike affected Linux PCs also.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/pradeepviswav)</author>
      <guid>https://www.neowin.net/news/crowdstrike-broke-debian-and-rocky-linux-months-ago-but-no-one-noticed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 02:10:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modchipping a fridge</title>
      <link>https://kennedn.com/blog/posts/fridgepwn/</link>
      <description>I own a fridge that has a really cool ‘feature’. It beeps if the door is open for more than 60 seconds. 95% of the time this is more annoying than it is helpful. In my opinion it should just shut up and trust that I know best.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kennedn.com/blog/posts/fridgepwn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ansible at scale — working with multiple  environments is easy</title>
      <link>https://localnest.xyz/ansible-at-scale-working-with-multiple-environments-is-easy-b512d3afc71b</link>
      <description>How to introduce the concept of “environments” to effortlessly manage multiple different types of Ansible deployments at scale.</description>
      <author> (https://localnest.xyz)</author>
      <guid>https://localnest.xyz/ansible-at-scale-working-with-multiple-environments-is-easy-b512d3afc71b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How We Achieved Over 30,000 Installs on Our VSCode Extension</title>
      <link>https://blog.trysixth.com/2024/07/how-we-achieved-over-30000-installs-on.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Precious Balogun

Posted Saturday, July 20, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.trysixth.com/2024/07/how-we-achieved-over-30000-installs-on.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scan HTML even faster with SIMD instructions (C++ and C#) – Daniel Lemire&amp;#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://lemire.me/blog/2024/07/20/scan-html-even-faster-with-simd-instructions-c-and-c/</link>
      <description>Earlier this year, both major Web engines (WebKit/Safari and Chromium/Chrome/Edge/Brave) accelerated HTML parsing using SIMD instructions. These ‘SIMD’ instructions are special instructions that are present in all our processors that can process multiple bytes at once (e.g., 16 bytes).</description>
      <author> (Published by)</author>
      <guid>https://lemire.me/blog/2024/07/20/scan-html-even-faster-with-simd-instructions-c-and-c/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XD1 Log entries. Begin... &amp;#183; Against political realism</title>
      <link>https://xd1.dev/2024/07/against-political-realism</link>
      <description>With the recent developments in US politics, following the attempt on candidate Donald Trump&amp;#39;s life
there is renewed heated and polarised debate, if there wasn&amp;#39;t such heat before. With this, something struck me as odd when talking to other people online, which is, nothing seems to be changing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xd1.dev/2024/07/against-political-realism</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why package by feature first and then by layer?</title>
      <link>https://garrettdbates.com/blog/software-architecture/why-package-by-feature-first-and-then-layer</link>
      <description>3 min read
      
    
    &amp;#183;
      Jul 19, 2024</description>
      <author> (Garrett D Bates)</author>
      <guid>https://garrettdbates.com/blog/software-architecture/why-package-by-feature-first-and-then-layer</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why disallow package within the class name?</title>
      <link>https://garrettdbates.com/blog/software-architecture/why-disallow-package-within-the-class-name</link>
      <description>Motivation After opening a directory it is the developers job to filter out the files that are not relevant to their task at hand. The more words to filter, the more difficult it becomes to quickly orient themselves and start making changes. Disallowing package within the class name promises to reduce this information overload.</description>
      <author> (Garrett D Bates)</author>
      <guid>https://garrettdbates.com/blog/software-architecture/why-disallow-package-within-the-class-name</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy or Rent? RaspberryPi vs VPS</title>
      <link>https://www.andreagrandi.it/posts/buy-or-rent-raspberrypi-vs-vps/</link>
      <description>Recently I was planning to self host a service I&amp;#39;m using and I was immediately stuck on a decision: should I just buy a Raspberry Pi 5 or rent a VPS?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.andreagrandi.it/posts/buy-or-rent-raspberrypi-vs-vps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Entropy?</title>
      <link>https://johncarlosbaez.wordpress.com/2024/07/20/what-is-entropy/</link>
      <description>I wrote a little book about entropy; here’s the current draft: • What is Entropy? If you see mistakes in it, please let me know! An alternative title would be 91 Tweets on Entropy, but p…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://johncarlosbaez.wordpress.com/2024/07/20/what-is-entropy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why prefer unit testing through layer entrypoints?</title>
      <link>https://garrettdbates.com/blog/software-architecture/why-prefer-unit-testing-through-layer-entrypoints</link>
      <description>Status Quo There is significant artistic variance on how to craft tests which provide developers quick and useful feedback. A common point of contention is the number of files which should be included within these quick and useful tests. The most popular strategy is to have a single file under test at a time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://garrettdbates.com/blog/software-architecture/why-prefer-unit-testing-through-layer-entrypoints</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeckString</title>
      <link>https://zarar.dev/deckstring/</link>
      <description>A probably unique string generator based on shuffling a deck of cards.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zarar.dev/deckstring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pin</title>
      <link>https://without.boats/blog/pin/</link>
      <description>The Pin type (and the concept of pinning in general) is a foundational building block on which
the rest of the the Rust async ecosystem stands. Unfortunately, it has also been one of the least
accessible and most misunderstood elements of async Rust. This post is meant to explain what Pin
achieves, how it came to be, and what the current problem with Pin is.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://without.boats/blog/pin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 19:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike: Safe Deployment Practices – Dev Leader Weekly 53</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/07/20/crowdstrike-safe-deployment-practices-dev-leader-weekly-53/</link>
      <description>Welcome to another issue of Dev Leader Weekly! In this issue, I discuss how situations like the CrowdStrike outage can reinforce our safe deployment practices.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/07/20/crowdstrike-safe-deployment-practices-dev-leader-weekly-53/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 14:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI paid for by Ads – the gpt-4o mini inflection point</title>
      <link>https://batchmon.com/blog/ai-cheaper-than-ads/</link>
      <description>AI is cheaper than ever with OpenAI&amp;#39;s latest announcement of gpt4-o mini. AI is so cheap now, that it&amp;#39;s cheaper than the average ad impression.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://batchmon.com/blog/ai-cheaper-than-ads/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 14:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multisatellite Data Depicts a Record-Breaking Methane Leak from a Well Blowout</title>
      <link>https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.4c00399</link>
      <description>Accidental blowouts in oil and gas wells can result in large and prolonged methane emissions, which are often unreported when happening in remote places. The rapid advancement of space-based methods for detecting and quantifying methane plumes provides an essential tool for uncovering these superemission events. We use a number of methane-sensitive satellite missions, including the Sentinel-5P/TROPOMI global mapper and several high-resolution instruments, to document a methane leak from a well blowout happening in Kazakhstan’s Karaturun East oil field in 2023. A dense time series of plume detections from those satellites shows that the leak was active during 205 days and that most of the emissions were in the range 20–50 t/h. Using 48 high-quality emission rate estimates, we calculate that a total of 131 &amp;#177; 34 kt of methane was released to the atmosphere during this leak, which exceeds the total emissions from all previously documented accidents. Our study characterizes the evolution and magnitude of the 2023 Karaturun East methane leak and showcases how different types of satellite instruments can be combined to document and quantify methane leaks active during long time periods.</description>
      <author> (Daniel  Zavala-Araiza)</author>
      <guid>https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.4c00399</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 12:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An open-source distributed object storage service</title>
      <link>https://garagehq.deuxfleurs.fr/</link>
      <description>An open-source distributed storage service you can self-host to fullfill many needs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://garagehq.deuxfleurs.fr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 12:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>