<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create a Comma-Separated String From a List of Strings in C#</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-create-comma-separated-string-from-list-of-strings/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to learn how to create a comma-separated string from a list of strings in C#.</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-create-comma-separated-string-from-list-of-strings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy 20th Anniversary, Npgsql!</title>
      <link>https://fxjr.blogspot.com/2022/05/happy-20th-anniversary-npgsql.html</link>
      <description>&amp;#160; &amp;#160;&amp;#160;&amp;#160; Happy 20th Anniversary, Npgsql! &amp;#160; &amp;#160;&amp;#160; It seems like yesterday when I decided to start Npgsql. And today, Npgsql completes 20 years sinc...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://fxjr.blogspot.com/2022/05/happy-20th-anniversary-npgsql.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duck Chess</title>
      <link>https://duckchess.com/</link>
      <description>This is the home page&amp;#39;s excerpt</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://duckchess.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Very Useful Markup Extensions in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/8-very-useful-markup-extensions-dotnet-maui</link>
      <description>Learn 8 of the most common and useful XAML markup extensions for .NET MAUI.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/8-very-useful-markup-extensions-dotnet-maui</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A SaaS architecture checklist for Kubernetes | Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/05/18/saas-architecture-checklist-kubernetes</link>
      <description>Learn about building SaaS solutions on Kubernetes with this first article in a series on SaaS architecture.</description>
      <author> (Michael Hrivnak)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/05/18/saas-architecture-checklist-kubernetes</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What onion has to do with Clean Code? - Event-Driven.io</title>
      <link>https://event-driven.io/en/onion_clean_code/</link>
      <description>Event-Driven by Oskar Dudycz</description>
      <author> (Oskar Dudycz)</author>
      <guid>https://event-driven.io/en/onion_clean_code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding TypeScript 4.7 and ECMAScript module support - LogRocket Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.logrocket.com/typescript-4-7-ecmascript-module-support/</link>
      <description>The TypeScript 4.7 release comes a major upgrade to ECMAScript module support for Node.js, allowing developers to better support modules.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.logrocket.com/typescript-4-7-ecmascript-module-support/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why a bug fix should &amp;quot;always&amp;quot; include new tests</title>
      <link>https://www.mrlacey.com/2022/05/why-bug-fix-should-always-include-new.html</link>
      <description>Ok, maybe not always, but please don&amp;#39;t start by assuming you&amp;#39;re the exception. (Note that exceptions should come with an adequate, documente...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mrlacey.com/2022/05/why-bug-fix-should-always-include-new.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Modeling - Encapsulation</title>
      <link>https://ardalis.com/domain-modeling-encapsulation/</link>
      <description>Domain models should encapsulate logic operations so that there is only one way to perform a given logical operation. That means avoiding exposing entity state and ensuring operations flow through specific methods. By funneling specific operations through specific code pathways, you can be sure constraints around the operations are enforced.</description>
      <author> (Ardalis)</author>
      <guid>https://ardalis.com/domain-modeling-encapsulation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Big Six Matrix Factorizations</title>
      <link>https://nhigham.com/2022/05/18/the-big-six-matrix-factorizations/</link>
      <description>Six matrix factorizations dominate in numerical linear algebra and matrix analysis: for most purposes one of them is sufficient for the task at hand. We summarize them here. For each factorization …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nhigham.com/2022/05/18/the-big-six-matrix-factorizations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFC 9239: Updates to ECMAScript media types</title>
      <link>https://2ality.com/2022/05/rfc-9239.html</link>
      <description>(This blog post is based on a tweet thread and additional input by Mathias Bynens.)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2ality.com/2022/05/rfc-9239.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mainly Known For</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2621/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2621/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 04:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing Expert Says Programmers Need More Math | Quanta Magazine</title>
      <link>https://www.quantamagazine.org/computing-expert-says-programmers-need-more-math-20220517/</link>
      <description>Leslie Lamport revolutionized how computers talk to each other. Now he’s working on how engineers talk to their machines.</description>
      <author> (By Sheon HanMay 17, 2022)</author>
      <guid>https://www.quantamagazine.org/computing-expert-says-programmers-need-more-math-20220517/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 03:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on OKRs</title>
      <link>https://joeblu.com/blog/2022_05_okrs/</link>
      <description>OKRs are one of those business ideas that are just simple enough to be dangerous. You think you understand it in a day, and you can see where your company is falling short: lacking focus and underdelivering. You see how clear, measurable goals could improve the situation.
Here’s the one sentence version: You set objectives, and for each objective come up with several key results that you can measure to see if you met the objectives.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joeblu.com/blog/2022_05_okrs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 02:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Found Time to Build My Skills</title>
      <link>https://blog.danielvaughan.com/how-i-found-time-to-build-my-skills-ef3b78956c96?gi=aa79d64869e2</link>
      <description>At the beginning of 2014, I felt my development job, although secure and comfortable, was going nowhere. There was so much I knew I didn’t…</description>
      <author> (https://blog.danielvaughan.com)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.danielvaughan.com/how-i-found-time-to-build-my-skills-ef3b78956c96?gi=aa79d64869e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling all Prusa users: It&amp;#39;s time for an upgrade!</title>
      <link>https://e3d-online.com/blogs/news/prusaupgrades</link>
      <description>TL;DR: We explain the process of upgrading your Prusa to Revo and talk about the benefits of making the switch.
&amp;#160;

&amp;#160;Did you know most Prusa 3D printers ship with E3D parts? The Prusa MK2, MK3, MK3S, etc are just some of them, and each uses an E3D V6 as standard!&amp;#160;
&amp;#160;
The need for a new solution
The V6 has been a reliable workhorse in over one hundred thousand Prusa machines across the world, but with the release of our new Revo ecosystem, it’s time for an upgrade. Our ten years in the industry has clearly shown us that swapping nozzles has always been a major pain point for any 3D printer user, whether they’re a hobbyist or an OEM.

If you’re a hobbyist, hot tightening is a necessary step when changing V6 nozzles. It involves heating your HotEnd to nearly 300 degrees and using tools to tighten the nozzle to the heaterblock. Lots can go wrong during this process, including burns and nozzle leaks.
If you’re an OEM, your customers are going to be burdened with the responsibility of hot tightening themselves if they want to change nozzles. In fact, some OEMs we’re partnered with won’t even support hot tightening as they consider the process too dangerous, even when it’s technically possible to do.
Subtractive manufacturing has had the ability to quickly and easily swap tools for decades. Additive is still lagging behind, with users heating things to 300 degrees, hot tightening, and often left hoping for the best.
Lots of users can’t see a reason to change nozzles beyond their trusty 0.40mm, often because the idea of hot tightening is intimidating.

&amp;#160;
Once you’ve experienced Revo, you’ll no longer feel limited by the hassle of nozzle changing. Revo makes it easy – just screw in a nozzle finger-tight, and you’re ready to 3D print. No tools, no hot tightening.
&amp;#160;

&amp;#160;RapidChange Revo is a new product range from E3D that improves on the shortcomings of the V6 ecosystem with a particular focus on ease of use and safety
&amp;#160;
Why should I upgrade to Revo?
An obvious benefit of Revo is you can change nozzles cold in less than 60 seconds. The ease of use and safety improvements this brings has already created some hot anticipation&amp;#160; from the 3D printing community before it’s even released! &amp;#160;
The improvements don’t end there though:

Revo offers a considerable improvement on heat up and cooldown times thanks to its HeaterCore technology.

Revo Nozzles offer a factory sealed assembly which means no more annoying HotEnd leaks.
Revo Nozzles are colour-coded and engraved so you’ll never be left wondering whether your 0.60mm might actually be a 0.40mm.
The Revo ecosystem is just getting started, with lots of exciting options on the way. You’re in for a treat!

&amp;#160;


Changing Revo Nozzles for the first time at formnext 2021
&amp;#160;
How will Revo improve my Prusa?
Revo Six is a great upgrade for any 3D printer that already uses a V6. You’ll be able to take advantage of all the benefits we listed earlier.&amp;#160;They both have the same form factor, and this means you won’t need to print any new parts or adjust your fan shroud/Pinda probe. You don’t need any firmware changes, either.&amp;#160;
Changing Nozzles on the MK3S+ before and after the Revo Six upgrade
&amp;#160;
How easy is this upgrade?
You can find the full Prusa MK3(S/+)&amp;#160;upgrade guide here.&amp;#160;To upgrade your Prusa MK3 to a Revo Six, here’s what you need to do:

Remove your V6
Adjust the length of the PTFE tube
Swap in the Revo Six
Replace the heater and thermistor wires

The upgrade is straightforward, and we’ve already prepared a step-by-step guide to walk you through the process.
Don’t just take our word for it! Check out Andrew Sink’s recent Revo Six review, where he upgrades his Prusa MK3S+ to Revo Six.&amp;#160;

&amp;#160;
&amp;#160;
How will Revo improve my Prusa Mini+?
By using Revo Micro, you’ll be able to take advantage of all the benefits we listed earlier, as well as a toolhead that is 30 grams lighter than the stock Prusa Mini+ HotEnd. You won’t need new firmware (or even a PID tune!) and the nozzle is in the same place, so you won’t lose any build area.
&amp;#160;
How easy is this upgrade?
You can find the parts and guide for the Prusa Mini+ upgrade here.&amp;#160;To upgrade a Prusa Mini+ to a Revo Micro, here’s what you need to do:

Print the new mounting part available here
Disassemble your Mini HotEnd
Attach your Revo Micro
Replace the heater and thermistor wires

Once you’ve got the part printed, the upgrade should only take around an hour.
Again, don’t just take our word for it, check out De3dprintman’s thoughts after finishing the upgrade.&amp;#160;
&amp;#160;













View this post on Instagram























A post shared by De 3D Printman (@de3dprintman)



&amp;#160;
Is Revo Six a drop-in replacement for MK2?
Revo Six is a drop-in replacement for any machine using a stock V6 HotEnd – the height, diameter, and mounting are identical, so it’s easy to fit into your existing print head.
Stock MK2 printers used a V6, so upgrading to Revo Six will be just as easy as the MK3 upgrade. You can even follow the MK3 upgrade guide although some of the disassembly steps will vary due to the difference in design between the two.
&amp;#160;
Can I use Revo Micro on my MK3?
Yes, using Revo Micro is possible, but you would need to print&amp;#160;new extruder parts as the threaded sink is not compatible with your standard Prusa extruder parts. We recommend using Revo Six as we consider it to be a drop-in replacement that keeps the upgrade process simple.


Revo Micro on the MK3 (&amp;#128248;: FilamentFrenzy)

&amp;#160;

Start your Prusa upgrade journey today!

Revo&amp;#160;Micro, Six and Hemera are&amp;#160;already available for pre-order and&amp;#160;are scheduled to ship March 2022. Follow&amp;#160;our Facebook, Twitter, Instagram or Discord for updates.




Discover the Revo&amp;#160;range</description>
      <author> (Written by
                Will Hardy)</author>
      <guid>https://e3d-online.com/blogs/news/prusaupgrades</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a SQLAlchemy Dialect for Airtable</title>
      <link>https://blog.alexrothberg.com/2022/05/18/creating-sqlalchemy-dialect-for-airtable/</link>
      <description>I develop a SQLAlchemy Dialect and associated Python DB-API database driver that allows Apache Superset to query data from Airtable.</description>
      <author> (Alex Rothberg)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.alexrothberg.com/2022/05/18/creating-sqlalchemy-dialect-for-airtable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;X raise sanctions against Y&amp;quot; - Finetune Language model for Sentiment Relation Extraction task [part 1/2] | Attitude Extraction Advances</title>
      <link>https://nicolay-r.github.io/blog/articles/2022-05/extract-sentiment-relations-with-arekit-and-deeppavlov</link>
      <description>Sentiment attitude extraction [6] – is a sentiment analysis subtask, in which attitude corresponds to the text position conveyed by Subject towards other Obj...</description>
      <author> (&amp;quot;X raise sanctions against Y&amp;quot; - Finetune Language model for Sentiment Relation Extraction task [part 1/2] | Attitude Extraction Advances)</author>
      <guid>https://nicolay-r.github.io/blog/articles/2022-05/extract-sentiment-relations-with-arekit-and-deeppavlov</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify issues - Shogan.tech</title>
      <link>https://www.shogan.co.uk/diary/spotify-issues/</link>
      <description>Spotify has been getting progressively worse, as subscription fees have increased. This post lists my top 3 x Spotify issues.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.shogan.co.uk/diary/spotify-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Petabyte Pi Project | Jeff Geerling</title>
      <link>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2022/petabyte-pi-project</link>
      <description>I haven&amp;#39;t had time to write up the details yet, but I wanted to share a project that&amp;#39;s been many months in the making: The Petabyte Pi Project on YouTube.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2022/petabyte-pi-project</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jiminy Click</title>
      <link>https://jiminyclick.com/open-offices-suck</link>
      <description>Whether you&amp;#39;re considering a return to the office or even starting a new one, there are many reasons you might want to choose the open office with no work-from-home option as your approach. Despite what employees may think, it&amp;#39;s not only because you hate them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jiminyclick.com/open-offices-suck</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to feel engaged at work: a software engineer&amp;#39;s guide | Jason Tu</title>
      <link>https://jasont.co/ennui/</link>
      <description>On fighting the feeling of &amp;quot;blah&amp;quot;.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jasont.co/ennui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Reinventing the Wheel Makes Sense</title>
      <link>https://mredigonda.github.io/blog/when-reinventing-the-wheel-makes-sense/</link>
      <description>I have a close friend of mine with whom I share (or shared) many projects and activities.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mredigonda.github.io/blog/when-reinventing-the-wheel-makes-sense/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;m an addict</title>
      <link>https://tarunreddy.bearblog.dev/addict/</link>
      <description>I like watching videos. A lot in fact. Today, I&amp;#39;ve spent over 6 hours watching youtube videos, an hour of reading through comments1 on hacker news, 3 hours of s</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tarunreddy.bearblog.dev/addict/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2022 for Mac Team Fixes Release Candidate Issues -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/05/18/vs-mac-rc-2.aspx</link>
      <description>  Visual Studio 2022 for Mac 17.0 Release Candidate 2 has shipped, cleaning up some issues reported by developers trying out the previous release candidate.
</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel05/18/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/05/18/vs-mac-rc-2.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 23:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s New in Visual Studio Code 1.67 (April 2022 Update) -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/05/18/vs-code-1-67.aspx</link>
      <description>Explorer file nesting is now no longer experimental, along with default bracket pair colorization, new functionality for find all references in markdown and much more.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel05/18/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/05/18/vs-code-1-67.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 23:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposal on release labels by richlander &amp;#183; Pull Request #265 &amp;#183; dotnet/designs</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/designs/pull/265</link>
      <description>The &amp;quot;Current&amp;quot; label is confusing. This proposal aims to change that.</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/designs/pull/265</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Data Community Standup - Testing EF Core Apps (part 2)</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/4JQUJk8muCc</link>
      <description>In this second part of testing EF Core Apps, guest Jon P Smith will focus on the actual code and approaches that you need to test applications using EF Core ...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •
  
  
    
      7K views
    
      Streamed 2 days ago)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/4JQUJk8muCc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spanify some Windows X.509 PAL and improve formatting. by vcsjones &amp;#183; Pull Request #69448 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/69448</link>
      <description>This PR does:

Change DecodeObjectNoThrow to operate off of ReadOnlySpan&amp;lt;byte&amp;gt; instead of byte[]. This lets us save a few allocations since the input is usually from a DATA_BLOB.
Change DecodeObjec...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/69448</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allocate less with X500DistinguishedName by vcsjones &amp;#183; Pull Request #69514 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/69514</link>
      <description>This cleans up some allocations with X500DistinguishedName.

Use ValueStringBuilder since it seems well suited for this task and distinguished names will usually fit in a stack buffer.
ParseOid has...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/69514</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minor cleanup and reduce allocations in Apple X.509 certificate PAL by vcsjones &amp;#183; Pull Request #69497 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/69497</link>
      <description>Some cleanup in the Apple X.509 PAL

Remove allocations when decoding since we have span-accepting X509Extension and X500DistinguishedName.
Set the initial capacity of a List&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; since we know how b...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/69497</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commands &amp;amp; Events: What&amp;#39;s the difference?</title>
      <link>https://codeopinion.com/commands-events-whats-the-difference/</link>
      <description>One of the building blocks of messaging is, you guessed it, messages! But there are different kinds of messages: Commands and Events. So what&amp;#39;s the</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://codeopinion.com/commands-events-whats-the-difference/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 21:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tips for Moving Your Xamarin Library to .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xamarin/tips-for-porting-your-xamarin-library-to-dotnet-maui/</link>
      <description>Luis shares the tips that he learned porting his NuGet Package, Plugin.ValidationRules to support .NET MAUI with minor changes.</description>
      <author> (Luis M)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xamarin/tips-for-porting-your-xamarin-library-to-dotnet-maui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 21:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#128565;‍&amp;#128171; Why billing systems are a nightmare for engineers</title>
      <link>https://www.getlago.com/blog/why-billing-systems-are-a-nightmare-for-engineers</link>
      <description>With billing, the devil is in the details. In this article, Raffi provides a high-level view of the technical challenges we faced while implementing a hybrid pricing (based on both &amp;#39;subscription&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;usage&amp;#39;) at 5x unicorn Qonto.com, and what we learned the hard way in this journey.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.getlago.com/blog/why-billing-systems-are-a-nightmare-for-engineers</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Accelerated PyTorch Training on Mac</title>
      <link>https://pytorch.org/blog/introducing-accelerated-pytorch-training-on-mac/</link>
      <description>In collaboration with the Metal engineering team at Apple, we are excited to announce support for GPU-accelerated PyTorch training on Mac. Until now, PyTorch training on Mac only leveraged the CPU, but with the upcoming  PyTorch v1.12 release, developers and researchers can take advantage of Apple silicon GPUs for significantly faster model training. This unlocks the ability to perform machine learning workflows like prototyping and fine-tuning locally, right on Mac.

</description>
      <author> (by
                      
                        PyTorch)</author>
      <guid>https://pytorch.org/blog/introducing-accelerated-pytorch-training-on-mac/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pegasus Mail Newsflashes</title>
      <link>http://www.pmail.com/newsflash.htm</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.pmail.com/newsflash.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 19:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Spent 2 years Launching Tiny Projects | Tiny Projects</title>
      <link>https://tinyprojects.dev/posts/i_spent_two_years_launching_tiny_projects</link>
      <description>Two years ago, frustrated with a long list of unfulfilled project ideas in my phone notes, I decided to give myself one week to try each idea out in its tiniest form.</description>
      <author> (Benjamin Stokes)</author>
      <guid>https://tinyprojects.dev/posts/i_spent_two_years_launching_tiny_projects</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 18:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please Stop Using Grey Text</title>
      <link>https://tangledweb.xyz/please-stop-using-grey-text-3d3e71acfca8</link>
      <description>For over 1000 years black text on white paper has been the best practice for printed texts worldwide. Since the advent of the web and WCAG…</description>
      <author> (https://andrewsomers.com)</author>
      <guid>https://tangledweb.xyz/please-stop-using-grey-text-3d3e71acfca8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 15:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Google is so unbearable (and how to fix it)</title>
      <link>https://ixns.github.io//lifehacks/computers/internet/2022/05/17/avoid-google-bloatware.html</link>
      <description>Why Google is so unbearable (and how to fix it)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ixns.github.io//lifehacks/computers/internet/2022/05/17/avoid-google-bloatware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 15:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internship Experience: Software Development Intern</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/internship-experience-software-development-intern/</link>
      <description>Back in December 2021, I joined Cloudflare as a Software Development Intern on the Partnerships team to help improve the experience that Partners have when using the platform</description>
      <author> (Ulysses Kee)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/internship-experience-software-development-intern/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 13:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git ignores .gitignore with .gitignore in .gitignore</title>
      <link>https://rubenerd.com/git-ignores-gitignore-with-gitignore-in-gitignore/</link>
      <description>A fun, if predictable and pointless exercise.</description>
      <author> (Ruben Schade)</author>
      <guid>https://rubenerd.com/git-ignores-gitignore-with-gitignore-in-gitignore/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 12:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>