<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Core Guidelines are not Rules - Simplify C++!</title>
      <link>https://arne-mertz.de/2024/03/core-guidelines-are-not-rules/</link>
      <description>There is a difference between guidelines and rules. Boiling down guidelines to one-sentence rules has drawbacks that make your code harder to understand.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://arne-mertz.de/2024/03/core-guidelines-are-not-rules/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detailed Macrophotography of PCBs</title>
      <link>https://niemczuk.tech/2024/02/11/detailed-macrophotography-of-PCBs</link>
      <description>I had to create scans of a small flex PCB to capture more details than a flat scanner could give me. Of course, this task turned out harder than I imagined. I already had a good camera, but I was lacking a good macro lens. Buying one turned out to be hard because the highest magnification ratios on most macro lenses are 1:1. The better ones are, of course, pricier.</description>
      <author> (Jakub Niemczuk)</author>
      <guid>https://niemczuk.tech/2024/02/11/detailed-macrophotography-of-PCBs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConstructorInfo – How To Make Reflection in DotNet Faster for Instantiation</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/17/constructorinfo-how-to-make-reflection-in-dotnet-faster-for-instantiation/</link>
      <description>Using reflection in DotNet to create object instances? See the performance of ConstructorInfo compared to other methods provided by reflection in DotNet!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/17/constructorinfo-how-to-make-reflection-in-dotnet-faster-for-instantiation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using ChatGPT for Podcast Suggestions</title>
      <link>https://ryanbuening.com/posts/chatgpt-for-podcast-suggestions/</link>
      <description>An experiment I tried recently with ChatGPT was to see if it could generate some Podcast suggestions for me based on my current podcast subscriptions. I was able to supply ChatGPT with an OPML file that is commonly used to transfer podcast...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ryanbuening.com/posts/chatgpt-for-podcast-suggestions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Quantum Spin: Qubit Ordering and Operations</title>
      <link>https://hamacher.cloud/my-quantum-spin-qubit-ordering-and-operations</link>
      <description>Overview
Picking up from Learning Quantum Computing, I continue chronicling my learning journey through quantum computing.
This post serves two purposes. First, I had a personal a-ha moment while manually working through the math to find the resultin...</description>
      <author> (https://hashnode.com/@badgerduke)</author>
      <guid>https://hamacher.cloud/my-quantum-spin-qubit-ordering-and-operations</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part one – Ian&amp;#39;s notes</title>
      <link>https://ivdl.co.za/2024/03/02/pretending-to-be-postgresql-part-one-1/</link>
      <description>Established in 2020, this site serves as a memory bank of notes and guides for me to reference again down the line, made public with the knowledge that others are likely to encounter simillar situations, especially in niche environments.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ivdl.co.za/2024/03/02/pretending-to-be-postgresql-part-one-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brilliant Hack: Why does Layer 2/3 Checksum use 1’s Complement, Not 2’s</title>
      <link>https://charlesxu.io/2s-comp/</link>
      <description>A super quick recap, one’s complement represents negative x by reverting every bit of x, while two’s complement negative x as one’s complement of x plus 1. Symbolically,</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://charlesxu.io/2s-comp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the internet works, and how I&amp;#39;ll exploit it – kbrecordzz</title>
      <link>http://kbrecordzz.com/2024/03/how-the-internet-works/</link>
      <description>The internet is cool, a lot of computers around the whole world are connected to each other in all possible directions and angles, and because of that you can do almost anything. There&amp;#39;s no single definitive way for how your computer connects to my web server in Stockholm, but when you visit https://notacarclub.kbrecordzz.com it indeed happens, there are actually many different paths the data can take between your computer and my server, it can change at any time, even in the middle of a connection, and I never understood how it works. The standard explanation for how the internet works, if you&amp;#39;re not looking in thick technical books that require you to already know the answer before you can read it, is that &amp;quot;you enter the domain name &amp;quot;google.com&amp;quot; into your browser, then the browser asks a &amp;quot;DNS server&amp;quot; to convert that domain name to an IP address, which is a type of address that your computer understands&amp;quot; and then everything works. But it still doesn&amp;#39;t explain why the data takes certain paths, and what makes it do it, which is weird because that&amp;#39;s what the internet is: Data taking different paths between computers all around the world. There are billions of computers and they obviously need to keep track of where the other billions of computers are. How is it possible?</description>
      <author> (by kbrecordzz)</author>
      <guid>http://kbrecordzz.com/2024/03/how-the-internet-works/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My (Not-So-Successful) Quest to Conquer the NYT Connections Game with Word2Vec – Quirky Quintet</title>
      <link>https://marshalljiang.com/my-not-so-successful-quest-to-conquer-the-nyt-connections-game-with-word2vec/</link>
      <description>The New York Times’ Connections game: a fairly simple puzzle that has been rising in popularity. The objective? Find four groups for four within a larger sample of sixteen total words such that each subgroup has an overarching theme.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marshalljiang.com/my-not-so-successful-quest-to-conquer-the-nyt-connections-game-with-word2vec/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 Ideas for Life I Repeatedly Share – Daniel Frank</title>
      <link>https://danfrank.ca/daniel-isms-50-ideas-for-life-i-repeatedly-share/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://danfrank.ca/daniel-isms-50-ideas-for-life-i-repeatedly-share/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Default Handler – Edovia Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.edovia.com/2024/03/14/introducing-default-handler/</link>
      <description>Recently, we conducted a poll among our users on both Mastodon and X to gather feedback on whether they would prefer Screens 5 to become the default handler for the “vnc” URL scheme on macOS, or if they would prefer to maintain the current status quo.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.edovia.com/2024/03/14/introducing-default-handler/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS Variable Groups • Lea Verou</title>
      <link>https://lea.verou.me/docs/var-groups/</link>
      <description>CSS Variable Groups is a way to define multiple properties under the same namespace and pass the entire group around,
addressing several pain points around design tokens, design systems, and integrating third-party components.
The proposal has been posted to the CSS WG repo and received significant attention by the community.</description>
      <author> (Lea Verou)</author>
      <guid>https://lea.verou.me/docs/var-groups/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast postgres index creation</title>
      <link>https://stephenn.com/2024/03/fast-postgres-index-creation/</link>
      <description>Fast postgres index creation Postgres is a fantastic database for a multitude of reasons, celebrated for its reliability and flexibility. However, when creating indexes on large tables, it can sometimes feel sluggish. This becomes even more noticeable when your project requires the creation of numerous indexes, potentially slowing down your progress.
Configure CPU and RAM available for index creation There are two settings that control the amount of server resources available for index creation, maintenance_work_mem and max_parallel_maintenance_workers.</description>
      <author> (Stephen Nancekivell)</author>
      <guid>https://stephenn.com/2024/03/fast-postgres-index-creation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IP Geolocation Is Twenty-Five Years Old</title>
      <link>https://www.sanjayparekh.com/ip-geolocation-is-25-years-old/</link>
      <description>Twenty-five years ago I had an idea which changed the way the Internet  worked. Looking back, it was an incredible ride.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sanjayparekh.com/ip-geolocation-is-25-years-old/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG Phriday: Redefining Postgres High Availability</title>
      <link>https://bonesmoses.org/2024/pg-phriday-redefining-postgres-high-availability/</link>
      <description>What is High Availability to Postgres? I’ve staked my career on the answer to that question since I first presented an HA stack to Postgres Open in 2012, and I still don’t feel like there’s an acceptable answer. No matter how the HA techniques have advanced since then, there’s always been a nagging suspicion in my mind that something is missing.
But I’m here to say that a bit of research has uncovered an approach that many different Postgres cloud vendors appear to be converging upon.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bonesmoses.org/2024/pg-phriday-redefining-postgres-high-availability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zen of Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://sjosund.com/zen-of-ml/</link>
      <description>Machine learning can be a frustrating endeavour, and I know several ML engineers who have transitioned to SWE roles – the unpredictability of machine learning being at the heart of their frustrations. You never know if or when your model will be good enough for production or if your new algorithm- or data idea will give any improvements. Usually, they don’t. Additionally, the feedback loop in ML is typically slow. These factors combined can lead to a sense of loss of control.

</description>
      <author> (Lars Sj&amp;#246;sund)</author>
      <guid>https://sjosund.com/zen-of-ml/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patching Software Using Nix (For Laymen)</title>
      <link>https://anthonyoleinik.com/blog_directory/patching-software-using-nix/</link>
      <description>Patching softwarea quick rundown on patching, since it has become apparent that it is not in every dev’s toolbox: code is just text files. There exists a file format that is a diff between real code and desired code; for instance, maybe you want to add a feature or change some functionality. You can make your edits and generate a patch file and then apply it to the source to get a version with your changes. is incredibly powerful. Instead of having to maintain a fork, or figure out how to distribute your version of the patched software, you can keep a .patch file alongside your nix code and apply it at build time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anthonyoleinik.com/blog_directory/patching-software-using-nix/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fifty Things you can do with a Software Defined Radio &amp;#128251;</title>
      <link>https://blinry.org/50-things-with-sdr/</link>
      <description>Last week, I went on an adventure through the electromagnetic spectrum!</description>
      <author> (blinry)</author>
      <guid>https://blinry.org/50-things-with-sdr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - albertan017/LLM4Decompile: Reverse Engineering: Decompiling Binary Code with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://github.com/albertan017/LLM4Decompile</link>
      <description>Reverse Engineering: Decompiling Binary Code with Large Language Models - albertan017/LLM4Decompile</description>
      <author> (albertan017)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/albertan017/LLM4Decompile</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - xai-org/grok-1: Grok open release</title>
      <link>https://github.com/xai-org/grok-1</link>
      <description>Grok open release. Contribute to xai-org/grok-1 development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (xai-org)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/xai-org/grok-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - 0x192/universal-android-debloater: Cross-platform GUI written in Rust using ADB to debloat non-rooted android devices. Improve your privacy, the security and battery life of your device.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/0x192/universal-android-debloater</link>
      <description>Cross-platform GUI written in Rust using ADB to debloat non-rooted android devices. Improve your privacy, the security and battery life of your device. - 0x192/universal-android-debloater</description>
      <author> (0x192)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/0x192/universal-android-debloater</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 17:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 8  .&amp;#128640;&amp;#128293;:  Bye Docker, Hello Podman: Revolutionize Your Web APIs!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sSGVqblVzbA</link>
      <description>In this video we will discuss how to containerise WebApis with PodmanSupport me on Patreon to access the source code:https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawandInt...</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand
  
  
  
    Mohamad Lawand
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sSGVqblVzbA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 12:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Scalable Framework for Folding-based SNARKs</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2024/416</link>
      <description>Trisha Datta, Stanford University</description>
      <author> (Wilson Nguyen, Stanford University)</author>
      <guid>https://eprint.iacr.org/2024/416</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Asynchronous MPC with Linear Communication Overhead</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2024/432</link>
      <description>Gilad Asharov, Bar-Ilan University</description>
      <author> (Ittai Abraham, Intel Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://eprint.iacr.org/2024/432</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I’m excited by Circle STARK and Stwo</title>
      <link>https://elibensasson.blog/2024/03/15/why-im-excited-by-circle-stark-and-stwo/</link>
      <description>Why I’m excited by Circle STARK Math</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://elibensasson.blog/2024/03/15/why-im-excited-by-circle-stark-and-stwo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Return of the Frame Pointers</title>
      <link>https://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2024-03-17/the-return-of-the-frame-pointers.html</link>
      <description>The Return of the Frame Pointers</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2024-03-17/the-return-of-the-frame-pointers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEBRA Proof Explorer</title>
      <link>https://www.nebrascan.io/</link>
      <description>✓</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nebrascan.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zig, Rust, and other languages</title>
      <link>https://notes.eatonphil.com/2024-03-15-zig-rust-and-other-languages.html</link>
      <description>Zig, Rust, and other languages</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.eatonphil.com/2024-03-15-zig-rust-and-other-languages.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Dependents &amp;#183; dotnet/BenchmarkDotNet</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/BenchmarkDotNet/network/dependents</link>
      <description>Powerful .NET library for benchmarking. Contribute to dotnet/BenchmarkDotNet development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/BenchmarkDotNet/network/dependents</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 9 Preview 2 &amp;#183; dotnet/core &amp;#183; Discussion #9217</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/core/discussions/9217d</link>
      <description>We are pleased to announce the release of the second preview of .NET 9, along with release notes that highlight enhancements from the initial preview. You can find detailed release notes about the ...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/core/discussions/9217d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The APL Quest Series | Dyalog Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.dyalog.com/blog/2024/03/the-apl-quest-series/</link>
      <description>It seemed like a normal Friday until mid-afternoon. But on 4 February 2022, I embarked on a journey that, at the time, seemed to stretch impossibly far into the future — a future that wasn’t entirely known yet. In the APL Orchard chat room on Stack Exchange, a dozen APLers, some experts and some newbies, held the very first APL Quest chat event.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dyalog.com/blog/2024/03/the-apl-quest-series/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microservices for the Benefits, Not the Hustle</title>
      <link>https://linkedrecords.com/the-purposes-of-microservices-4e5f373f4ea3?gi=02fe016ae882</link>
      <description>From time to time I hear people saying “It can not be scaled because it is a monolith, we need to rebuild it as microservices”. If you…</description>
      <author> (https://linkedrecords.com)</author>
      <guid>https://linkedrecords.com/the-purposes-of-microservices-4e5f373f4ea3?gi=02fe016ae882</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stuck updating controller on new PS5</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/playstation/comments/1833e84/stuck_updating_controller_on_new_ps5/?share_id=SSjldcotGr0cVcLLcQ_RY</link>
      <description>Just snagged a new slim PS5. Plugged it in, updated the console, and then it wanted to update the controller. Told it to go ahead and now I’m...</description>
      <author> (witheringsyncopation)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/playstation/comments/1833e84/stuck_updating_controller_on_new_ps5/?share_id=SSjldcotGr0cVcLLcQ_RY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing File Formats</title>
      <link>https://fadden.com/tech/file-formats.html</link>
      <description>There are many, many file formats, largely owing to the existence of many,
many different kinds of files.&amp;#160; They range from simple ASCII text documents
to complex databases.&amp;#160; There are a few elements that should be part of any
structured file, but many designers fail to include them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fadden.com/tech/file-formats.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explorations in creating a basic text editor: the foundation — Asko N&amp;#245;mm</title>
      <link>https://nth.ee/explorations-in-creating-a-basic-text-editor</link>
      <description>As part of the development of Sember I&amp;#39;ve long thought I&amp;#39;d like to try create a text editor of my own, completely from scratch, that would then be used as the Paragraph block in the post editor. Currently that role is played by the Markdown block, which is how I&amp;#39;m writing this very blog post, but I personally always liked visual editing a lot more than Markdown, it&amp;#39;s just that Markdown was a quick and dirty way to get to writing blog posts in Sember.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nth.ee/explorations-in-creating-a-basic-text-editor</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercharge Your Visual Studio Code with These Must-Have Extensions</title>
      <link>https://desainova.com/posts/supercharge-visual-studio-code-with-must-have-extensions/</link>
      <description>Indispensable extensions for visual studio code in javascript development.</description>
      <author> (Jose L. Molina Diaz)</author>
      <guid>https://desainova.com/posts/supercharge-visual-studio-code-with-must-have-extensions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Patch A Package Source on NixOS</title>
      <link>https://drakerossman.com/blog/how-to-patch-a-package-source-on-nixos</link>
      <description>This article will introduce you to Alejandra formatter, as well as teach how to leverage the Nix build system to easily patch any source code. This is the continuation of my previous article exploring nix formatters ecosystem.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://drakerossman.com/blog/how-to-patch-a-package-source-on-nixos</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In search of a “Zero Toil” HomeLab: Immutable Linux, ZFS, WatchTower and Keel</title>
      <link>https://blog.gripdev.xyz/2024/03/16/in-search-of-a-zero-toil-homelab-with-immutable-linux/</link>
      <description>I run a HomeLab for hosting a few bits (for example atuin, omnivore and matrix-bridges) Like all software these things need to be kept up-to-date. This saps the fun out of hosting things. I do not …</description>
      <author> (lawrencegripper)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.gripdev.xyz/2024/03/16/in-search-of-a-zero-toil-homelab-with-immutable-linux/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the &amp;quot;worst&amp;quot; spelling bee pangrams?</title>
      <link>https://notes.billmill.org/blog/2024/03/What_are_the__worst__spelling_bee_pangrams_.html</link>
      <description>Mar 16, 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.billmill.org/blog/2024/03/What_are_the__worst__spelling_bee_pangrams_.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomically exchange vfat files in Linux</title>
      <link>https://blog.dowhile0.org/2024/02/10/atomically-exchange-vfat-files-in-linux/</link>
      <description>The Linux kernel implements the POSIX renameat() system call that atomically renames a file, moving it between directories if required. If the newpath already exists, it is atomically replaced by t…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.dowhile0.org/2024/02/10/atomically-exchange-vfat-files-in-linux/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>~MK | Template Strings</title>
      <link>https://matthew.kunjum.men/blog/template-strings/</link>
      <description>Template strings make The Wrong Thing™ easier.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matthew.kunjum.men/blog/template-strings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double Q-Learning Explained</title>
      <link>https://loreley.one/2024-03-double_q/</link>
      <description>My incoherent ramblings</description>
      <author> (Lukas)</author>
      <guid>https://loreley.one/2024-03-double_q/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>beuke.org</title>
      <link>https://beuke.org/terminal-latency/</link>
      <description>A personal blog about functional programming, category theory, chess, physics and linux topics</description>
      <author> (Fabian Beuke)</author>
      <guid>https://beuke.org/terminal-latency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Taste Test</title>
      <link>https://www.robertclaus.com/blog/pizza-taste-test</link>
      <description>We ordered pizza from five different chains and ranked them to figure out what chain is best. This combined a fun party with collecting data and doing analysis!</description>
      <author> (Robert Claus)</author>
      <guid>https://www.robertclaus.com/blog/pizza-taste-test</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How web bloat impacts users with slow devices</title>
      <link>https://danluu.com/slow-device/</link>
      <description>In 2017, we looked at how web bloat affects users with slow connections. Even in the U.S., many users didn&amp;#39;t have broadband speeds, making much of the web difficult to use. It&amp;#39;s still the case that many users don&amp;#39;t have broadband speeds, both inside and outside of the U.S. and that much of the modern web isn&amp;#39;t usable for people with slow internet, but the exponential increase in bandwidth (Neilsen suggests this is 50% per year for high-end connections) has outpaced web bloat for typical sites, making this less of a problem than it was in 2017, although it&amp;#39;s still a serious problem for people with poor connections.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://danluu.com/slow-device/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>