<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Watching sunsets</title>
      <link>https://fabiensanglard.net/sunset/index.html</link>
      <description>Aug 18, 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fabiensanglard.net/sunset/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 22:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just use Postgres</title>
      <link>https://mccue.dev/pages/8-16-24-just-use-postgres</link>
      <description>by:   Ethan McCue</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mccue.dev/pages/8-16-24-just-use-postgres</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 19:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - rfinnie/blockbuster: Blockbuster Video VHS insert template</title>
      <link>https://github.com/rfinnie/blockbuster</link>
      <description>Blockbuster Video VHS insert template. Contribute to rfinnie/blockbuster development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (rfinnie)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/rfinnie/blockbuster</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 12:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design flaw has Microsoft Authenticator overwriting MFA accounts, locking users out</title>
      <link>https://www.csoonline.com/article/3480918/design-flaw-has-microsoft-authenticator-overwriting-mfa-accounts-locking-users-out.html</link>
      <description>Microsoft stands out from the authenticator crowd by annihilating accounts when new accounts are introduced via QR code. Despite user complaints for years, no fix has been issued, leaving IT experts wondering, ‘Why would you pick Microsoft?’</description>
      <author> (by							Evan Schuman
						
		
			Contributor)</author>
      <guid>https://www.csoonline.com/article/3480918/design-flaw-has-microsoft-authenticator-overwriting-mfa-accounts-locking-users-out.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 11:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vital Role of QA: Why Independent Testing is Essential for Software Integrity</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/08/18/the-vital-role-of-qa-why-independent-testing-is-essential-for-software-integrity/</link>
      <description>In the world of real estate, rigorous inspections are essential for a safe and functional home. Similarly, in software development, Quality Assurance (QA) plays a crucial role in testing software f…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/08/18/the-vital-role-of-qa-why-independent-testing-is-essential-for-software-integrity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 10:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software development is hard - Dmitry Kudryavtsev</title>
      <link>https://yieldcode.blog/post/software-development-is-hard/</link>
      <description>For the past few weeks I&amp;#39;ve been thinking about how hard it is to develop software.</description>
      <author> (Dmitry Kudryavtsev)</author>
      <guid>https://yieldcode.blog/post/software-development-is-hard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This week in KDE: System Settings modernization and Wayland color management</title>
      <link>https://pointieststick.com/2024/08/16/this-week-in-kde-system-settings-modernization-and-wayland-color-management/</link>
      <description>Many folks are on vacation right now, but KDE’s tireless contributors still worked hard to bring you a number of improvements anyway, among them some nice System Settings modernization work a…</description>
      <author> (Nate)</author>
      <guid>https://pointieststick.com/2024/08/16/this-week-in-kde-system-settings-modernization-and-wayland-color-management/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Solve Puzzles in Minutes When You Can Code a Solution in Days?</title>
      <link>https://thinhcorner.com/blog/railbound-solver</link>
      <description>A deep dive into solving Railbound puzzles programmatically using a brute-force approach and optimizing it with branch and bound.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thinhcorner.com/blog/railbound-solver</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Numbers Are Bits: Distributed Representations for Sets</title>
      <link>https://cgad.ski/blog/when-numbers-are-bits.html</link>
      <description>According to the superposition hypothesis, vectors of activations inside a neural network are best viewed as superpositions of &amp;quot;feature vectors&amp;quot;—directions in activation space with specific, interpretable meanings. This hypothesis is related to the classic connectionist idea of distributed representation and supported by the surprising fact that a low-dimensional linear projection
y=∑ifixi=Fxy = \sum_i f_i x_i = F x
can encode a much higher-dimensional sparse vector x.x.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cgad.ski/blog/when-numbers-are-bits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should I Close Source my Company? Replying to Supabase | Ben Butterworth</title>
      <link>https://orth.uk/close-source/</link>
      <description>I was reading Supabase&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;Should I Open Source my Company?&amp;#39;, and wanted to add some nuance which might be useful for certain companies and industries.</description>
      <author> (https://orth.uk/about)</author>
      <guid>https://orth.uk/close-source/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sentinel toothpaste: a useful programming technique for everyday life</title>
      <link>https://dunkels.com/adam/sentinel-toothpaste/</link>
      <description>Here’s one programming technique that I found very useful in daily life: the sentinel value. I use it pretty much every day – to manage toothpaste. In programming, a sentinel value is a simple way to keep track of the end of a list of items. Lets say you have a list of items. You make the last item in that list a special one. That way you easily know that you have found the end of the list: when your item is that special one, that’s the end of your list. Here is a visual repressentation using emojis: &amp;#128512; &amp;#129392; &amp;#128526; &amp;#129303; &amp;#128580; &amp;#128540; &amp;#128558;‍&amp;#128168; &amp;#128008; The cat is not a smiley face, so we can use the presence of the cat to know that we have reached the end of the list. One typical usecase for this programming pattern is null-terminated text strings, where the null character \0 is used to mark the end of the characters in the string. To compute the length of the string, we just need to go through the string until we find a null character. That null character is the sentinel value. Here is the string String, with the final \0 character being the sentinal value: S t r i n g \0 Another usecase is a null pointer value in a linked list. If each member of the list is a non-null pointer, we can use the presence of a null pointer to indicate the end of that list. I have found this programming technique extremely useful in daily life, to manage toothpaste tubes. It isn’t fun to run out of toothpaste when you need it the most. You don’t want to find out that you’re out of toothpaste just when you need to brush your teeth before leaving the house. So when I buy toothpaste, I buy a bunch of them, and always make sure to get one tube of toothpaste that is different from the others – the sentinel toothpaste: When I find that the only tube of toothpaste left is that special, sentinel toothpaste, then I know it is time to buy more toothpaste. And then I have ample time to do so. I first learned of the sentinel object technique in a programming lecture by Lennart Andersson, who was one of my first lecturers in computer science and programming and a great computer scientist and teacher. I learned a bunch of extremely useful programming techniques from Lennart, which I have had a lot of use in my professional life, but this is the only one I found useful in life outside of computer science and programming. Here are a few of the useful things I learned from Lennart: How to efficiently write parsers for formal languages, such as mathematical expressions and programming languages. How satisfyingly compact functional programming techniques can be, particularly with map, reduce, and filter operations, even in imperative languages. That (some) printers weren’t just dumb devices that would print bitmaps, but that they were running a fully-fledged language called PostScript. So you could manually write a piece of code that you could send to the printer, which would run it and generate output – on the paper. What a realization! How to avoid comparing floating point values directly with each other – instead, subtract them from each other and check that the difference is small. That is, instead of checking a == b, check abs(a - b) &amp;lt; 0.0001 (or some other small quantity). This is a nifty way to protect against small numerical errors in floating point repressentation. The importance of external vs internal repressentation of data structures: we were given a lab assignment to write a small Excel/VisiCalc clone. We were free to do it in any way we wanted, with one exception – we were not allowed to use a two-dimensional array to repressent the contents of the sheet. The purpose was to teach us that the externally visible repressentation (a two-dimensional sheet of cells) was in no way related to the best way to repressent the same data internally, inside our program. This has stuck with me ever since.</description>
      <author> (adam)</author>
      <guid>https://dunkels.com/adam/sentinel-toothpaste/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hologrammata - Gravity, entropy, and life.</title>
      <link>https://rantonels.github.io/gravity-entropy-and-life/</link>
      <description>Cosmology, or at least basic cosmology, models the world as perfectly homogeneous and isotropic. Everything in the study of the evolution of the Universe actually works out fine if this is at least true at all times on the largest scales, and observations confirm it pretty much is. But at smaller scales, our Universe does not appear like a featureless, homogeneous soup, but as an immense tree of fractal complexity and divisions and subdivisions. Superclusters, clusters, galaxies, stars, planets, mountains and craters. And then there&amp;#39;s life on Earth, an incredible variety of desperate machines grasping for survival. And on the top of the tree (for what we know), human civilizations, our actions and thoughts and the information we produce and consume. All of this complexity is concentrated in minuscule oases of useful information lost in a huge, huge blackness filled only by what is essentially thermal noise.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rantonels.github.io/gravity-entropy-and-life/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subtitle Shenanigans in SwiftUI’s Menu — featherless software design</title>
      <link>https://jeffverkoeyen.com/blog/2024/08/16/SwiftUI-Menu-subtitle-shenanigans/</link>
      <description>Published: Aug 16, 2024</description>
      <author> (Jeff Verkoeyen)</author>
      <guid>https://jeffverkoeyen.com/blog/2024/08/16/SwiftUI-Menu-subtitle-shenanigans/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can&amp;#39;t own a pen | Attainable Felicity</title>
      <link>https://attainablefelicity.mattkirkland.com/20240807/you-cant-own-a-pen.html</link>
      <description>Matt Kirkland is a designer. He probably reads too much.</description>
      <author> (Matt Kirkland)</author>
      <guid>https://attainablefelicity.mattkirkland.com/20240807/you-cant-own-a-pen.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workspace navigation with tmux+fzf</title>
      <link>https://antonsuprun.com/content/post/tmux-fzf-manage-workspaces/</link>
      <description>A brief overview of my workspace management flow</description>
      <author> (Anton Suprun)</author>
      <guid>https://antonsuprun.com/content/post/tmux-fzf-manage-workspaces/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking OpenAI LLMs for JSON Generation</title>
      <link>https://rwilinski.ai/posts/benchmarking-llms-for-structured-json-generation/</link>
      <description>A quick experiment to benchmark OpenAI LLMs for JSON generation and analyze the results focusing on error rates, performance and costs.</description>
      <author> (Rafal Wilinski)</author>
      <guid>https://rwilinski.ai/posts/benchmarking-llms-for-structured-json-generation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>