<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Health Stats</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2581/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2581/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 05:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoLisa</title>
      <link>https://www.monolisa.dev/</link>
      <description>A font family designed for software developers. Font follows function.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.monolisa.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 04:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACM: Developing a new app is an unnecessary and unreasonable condition that Apple imposes on dating-app providers</title>
      <link>https://www.acm.nl/en/publications/acm-developing-new-app-unnecessary-and-unreasonable-condition-apple-imposes-dating-app-providers</link>
      <description>The revised conditions that Apple has imposed on dating-app providers are unreasonable, and create an unnecessary barrier. Apple must therefore pay another 5 million euros.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.acm.nl/en/publications/acm-developing-new-app-unnecessary-and-unreasonable-condition-apple-imposes-dating-app-providers</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 03:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDFs in Django like it’s&amp;#160;2022! — /var/</title>
      <link>https://www.spapas.net/2022/02/14/django-pdfs-2022/</link>
      <description>In a previous article I had written a very comprehensive
guide on how to render PDFs in Django using tools like reportlab and xhtml2pdf. Although these tools
are still valid and work fine I have decided that usually it’s way too much pain to set them up to work&amp;#160;properly.</description>
      <author> (Serafeim Papastefanos)</author>
      <guid>https://www.spapas.net/2022/02/14/django-pdfs-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Vs. Scalability</title>
      <link>https://christianfindlay.com/2022/02/13/performance-vs-scalability/</link>
      <description>
Performance and scalability are two related but separate aspects of a system. However, there is a lot of confusion around the two terms, which often leads to architectural mistakes. This article talks about the difference between the two concepts and how to improve them.



Performance



Performance&amp;#160;is about how fast your system works. It&amp;#39;s the experience users have when waiting for your system to do something, and it&amp;#39;s how fast your underlying code runs. Network latency, bandwidth, and other factors also affect performance.&amp;#160;



When the system does not have a lot of data or users, performance is usually acceptable and easy to manage. When the amount of data and number of concurrent users grow, the servers&amp;#39; resources may reach their maximum, and this will cause performance degradation.



However, there is a key point here. The system&amp;#39;s design and the code quality have a huge impact on how quickly the server&amp;#39;s resources reach their maximum capacity. You can pay for an extremely expensive database server, but data retrieval will consume a lot of resources if you do not put indexes in the right place. Conversely, efficient code can avoid resource depletion even on cheap servers.



If you&amp;#39;ve done elementary computer science and learned the basics of data structures and algorithms, you will be aware of how quickly a poor implementation can chew memory or CPU power. This is what we mean by resources. Poor code will chew these up, your system will reach capacity, and users will experience poor performance.



Basically, bad code and database design will slow your servers down and potentially max out your server&amp;#39;s resources.



Scalability



Scalability&amp;#160;is the ability to handle larger amounts of work when the system is under heavy load by throwing more resources at the problem. This generally means improving performance by buying faster servers or adding more servers. A system is scalable if you can increase the computing power of the existing servers (vertical scaling or scaling up) or increase the number of servers (horizontal scaling or scaling out), and you can also scale back down when there is less system load.



Automatic scaling means that resources become available during busier times but become unavailable when not needed. This is pretty important because you may not be available to add resources during busy times, and you don&amp;#39;t want to pay for extra resources when it&amp;#39;s quiet.&amp;#160;



A system is not horizontally scalable if the code design does not allow multiple servers to respond to requests. For example, if a service depends on the local state of the server, another server may not be able to serve the same requests. If server a) writes local files to the hard drive and needs those to respond, server b) cannot see those files and will give incorrect responses. Horizontal scalability requires special attention to state.



Independent Scalability



Sometimes architects divide systems into smaller parts. They may separate a data store into two physically different parts. This means that one part of the system can scale up or down separately from the other parts of the system. This can be useful when one part of the system receives more traffic than other parts.&amp;#160;



For example, the menu part of the system may receive thousands of requests per second, while the ordering part may only receive a few transactions per second. If the menu part of the system maxes out resources, it may slow down ordering even though ordering is not doing much work. Independent scaling would allow you to throw resources at the menu so that ordering doesn&amp;#39;t suffer performance degradation.



On its face, this seems like a nice-to-have feature of the architecture. However, this may massively increase the system&amp;#39;s complexity, and it may actually increase costs. Database instances are often expensive, and you often pay a flat monthly fee whether you use them heavily or not. Moreover, the busier part of the system should only affect the performance of the less active part if the active part maxes out resources.



The important thing to be clear about here is that you do not need independent scalability to achieve vertical or horizontal scalability in your app. All things being equal, the server will respond to requests across different parts of the app simultaneously. If the server cannot, it probably means that it doesn&amp;#39;t have enough resources or a code issue is causing blocking. 



The System is Slow. What do I do?



The first thing you need is&amp;#160;monitoring and observability. You need to log information about what is happening, and you need to have information about the resource usage of the servers that are serving up the system. You cannot answer any questions without this information. So, when your boss comes to you and says, Please make the system go faster., the first thing you need to look at is whether you can measure how the system is performing.



When you have some data on what is happening, you will be in a position to speculate about whether you need to work on performance, scale-up, or both.&amp;#160;



Let&amp;#39;s say that your GetMenu endpoint takes three seconds, even during quiet times. The server&amp;#39;s CPU is hovering at 10%, and there is plenty of free memory. This is a clear sign that you have a typical performance problem. The system is running slowly, even when there is no extra load on the server. It may be as simple as adding an index to a database table. You should use the existing telemetry (logging) data and&amp;#160;performance profiling&amp;#160;to figure out what is wrong. This scenario is a clear case where you need to optimize code or the software design. Scaling up will not help you in this scenario.



Take a different scenario. During quiet times, the performance is good, but during peak times, all endpoints take 3+ seconds to run, the server is constantly hovering at around 90%+ CPU usage, and there is very little memory left. This suggests that you could alleviate the problem by scaling up or scaling out the servers. But, it does not prove that you don&amp;#39;t have a simple code quality issue. In this scenario, you may want to scale up to improve the experience for users temporarily, but you still need to determine if there is some bad code that is maxing out resources. Again, you will need to use telemetry data and profiling to understand what is happening. There may simply be one code piece that slows the entire system down. Quite often it&amp;#39;s a database query.







Does the System Need Scalability?



It&amp;#39;s important to distinguish between vertical and horizontal scalability. You can usually get vertical scalability for free if you deploy to the cloud. Most cloud providers allow you to upgrade the server with a faster CPU and more memory. However, it may shock many people to read that most systems probably do not need horizontal scalability. Unless you are dealing with a very high-end system with thousands of users, the chances are that you will not need it. Assuming that you will need horizontal scalability is a massive underestimation of modern computing power.&amp;#160;



In 2001 I worked on a warehouse management system for Nike. The team bought a Sun Microsystems server that cost around $100,000 at the time, was about 1 meter cubed and weighed more than one person could carry. The server ran an Oracle database server and served the whole warehouse system. I worked on box scanning, and this took around 10 seconds. I optimized the code and added some indexes to the database, which reduced the time to less than 2 seconds which was satisfactory for performance at the time. This system didn&amp;#39;t need horizontal scalability even though it serviced a large operation. My smartphone is probably more powerful than that server at this point. Computers are fast and getting faster.&amp;#160;



If you build a Saas application and plan to store data from many organizations in one system, you probably need scalability. Let&amp;#39;s say that your application will service businesses that employ 100+ users, and you plan to onboard 100+ businesses to your system. Your app could potentially have 10,000+ concurrent users. In this scenario, you will probably need to spread the load over multiple servers, and this is where horizontal scalability is critical.&amp;#160;



You should design for horizontal scalability because you may need at least two servers running incase one server becomes unavailable. In this sense horizontal scalability relates to availability. But bear in mind that you are far more likely to encounter bad code that slows down your system than hitting a genuine requirement for horizontal scalability. My experience has shown that 9 times out of 10, you can fix performance issues by optimizing the code or database query. I have seen technology or framework upgrades improve response times by 200% to 300%.&amp;#160;



Think about horizontal scalability, but don&amp;#39;t be preoccupied with it. Focus on good code quality and observability. These are core ingredients for systems that perform well. 







Our Code is Old, Messy, and We Don&amp;#39;t Want to Change It.



This leads me to the big mistake. Almost all businesses allow their codebase to degrade over time. The system slows down, refactoring gets harder, and users start complaining. Attempts to improve performance fail and cause bugs instead. This is the point at which many people conclude that you need to rewrite completely and with extreme scalability in mind. Often, people add in the independency scalability clause. The thinking is that the system is performing so badly right now that only going to the extreme opposite will fix the problems.&amp;#160;



This is where the derogatory term monolith comes in. People point to the existing system, note that it only has one database, and then there is no further argumentation necessary to justify massive expenditure on building a new system that supports independent scalability. I&amp;#39;ve seen this mistake over and over. The mistake here is the belief that engineers cannot improve existing code and that upgrading code to newer technologies is too hard. They can, and they need to improve code continuously. If they don&amp;#39;t, you will have the same issue in a few years.



I&amp;#39;ve witnessed companies burning countless months of time and money to rebuild parts of a system only to abandon the project in the end.&amp;#160;



Your company can improve existing code. You can use things like conditional compilation symbols to target two technologies so you can upgrade, and you can add tests to your existing code to make refactoring easier. I can definitely say that this is almost always the cheaper, easier solution. I recently entered a project where the plan was to implement massive scalability. I led a team to upgrade from .NET Framework to .NET Core, and the performance issues disappeared. There was no need for horizontal scaling at all.&amp;#160;



Your business needs to allocate time and resources to improve code over time. You cannot escape this. Not doing this will only ensure that you end up in the same situation again soon.



Wrap-Up



Performance and scalability are things you will have to deal with in your career. It&amp;#39;s important to understand the difference and how they relate to each other. Sometimes you will need to decide which one to focus on, but don&amp;#39;t let the existing slow system with poor code guide your decision-making. Poor performance is the inevitable result of neglecting performance over time. Exhaust the performance optimization approach before you reach for scaling out. Scaling out will cost your business money and won&amp;#39;t address underlying issues. Use monitoring and observability to guide your decisions instead of buzzwords and architecture trends, and don&amp;#39;t get confused between scalability and independent scalability. You don&amp;#39;t necessarily need independent scalability to scale horizontally.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://christianfindlay.com/2022/02/13/performance-vs-scalability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Write Technical Articles</title>
      <link>https://coornail.net/2022/02/why-write-technical-articles/</link>
      <description>I don’t have many people reading my blog, on most days I get about 5 visitors. Why on earth should I keep writing articles? The chance of landing a job is slim and I certainly won’t earn any revenue from the site.</description>
      <author> (Kornel Lugosi)</author>
      <guid>https://coornail.net/2022/02/why-write-technical-articles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Color Is Your Monad</title>
      <link>https://patrickthebold.github.io/posts/what-color-is-your-monad/</link>
      <description>There’s a lovely old blog post What Color is Your Function (WCIYF).
If you haven’t read that, please do so instead of reading this one.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://patrickthebold.github.io/posts/what-color-is-your-monad/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I research any topic</title>
      <link>https://charleswilliamson.com/how-i-research-any-topic/</link>
      <description>Here are some principles that I try to stick to when learning a completely new and unfamiliar topic</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://charleswilliamson.com/how-i-research-any-topic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education is its own privilege</title>
      <link>https://www.zeldman.com/2022/02/12/education-is-its-own-privilege/</link>
      <description>Whether or not it was the most expensive or most competitive college in the land (it wasn’t), it was a place where they’d encounter other smart kids from different backgrounds and discover Truffaut and Bergman and stay up all night enthralled by great ideas or ridiculing them, cracking each other up, sleeping together, experiencing new levels of romance and heartbreak, discovering possibilities.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/jzeldman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.zeldman.com/2022/02/12/education-is-its-own-privilege/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an iPod for 2022</title>
      <link>https://ellie.wtf/ipod/</link>
      <description>I modified an old iPod Video with more storage, a new casing, and more battery life. Also some fancy software :)</description>
      <author> (Ellie)</author>
      <guid>https://ellie.wtf/ipod/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why won’t anyone teach her math?</title>
      <link>https://quomodocumque.wordpress.com/2022/02/12/why-wont-anyone-teach-her-math/</link>
      <description>Lots of discussion in my feeds about this Daily Princetonian piece, “Why won’t anyone teach me math?” by first-year student Abigail Rabieh. She just took Math 202, an intro to lin…</description>
      <author> (By JSE)</author>
      <guid>https://quomodocumque.wordpress.com/2022/02/12/why-wont-anyone-teach-her-math/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As .NET Turns 20, Microsoft Says .NET 7 Preview 1 Coming This Week -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/02/14/net-20.aspx</link>
      <description>  Microsoft, in celebrating the 20th anniversary of .NET, revealed that the first preview of the latest version, .NET 7, will debut this week.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel02/14/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/02/14/net-20.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 01:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FailScout - the crowdsourced database for broken or worn-out products</title>
      <link>https://www.failscout.co/</link>
      <description>We should build a collection about how things break - review broken and worn-out products to teach how to identify cheap products.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.failscout.co/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security of BLS batch verification - Cryptography - Ethereum Research</title>
      <link>https://ethresear.ch/t/security-of-bls-batch-verification/10748</link>
      <description>Security of BLS batch verification By JP Aumasson (Taurus), Quan Thoi Minh Nguyen, and Antonio Sanso (Ethereum Foundation)  Thanks to Vitalik Buterin for his feedback.     In a 2019 post Vitalik Buterin introduced Fast verification of multiple BLS signatures. Quoting his own words this is   a purely client-side optimization that can voluntarily be done by clients verifying blocks that contain multiple signatures   The original post includes some preliminary security analysis, but in this post w...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ethresear.ch/t/security-of-bls-batch-verification/10748</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 23:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineer - Planning &amp;amp; Tracking</title>
      <link>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/3940318</link>
      <description>Remote - US / Canada</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/3940318</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 23:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Last Week in .NET #81] – Happy Birthday, .NET</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2022/02/14/last-week-in-net-81-happy-birthday-net/</link>
      <description>Happy Birthday .NET! You’ve turned 20. &amp;#127874; In honor of your birthday, let’s talk about you for a minute, and all you’ve brought into this world. You’ve had a bit of a shaky li…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2022/02/14/last-week-in-net-81-happy-birthday-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 23:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TripIt Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.tripit.com/uhp/privacyPolicy</link>
      <description>The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that we use the information you provide to us or we gather from you while you use the tripit.com online service.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tripit.com/uhp/privacyPolicy</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 22:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initial revision &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime@480e91e</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/commit/480e91e54517a0fee2e64a9a24dc8319dad03186</link>
      <description>svn path=/trunk/mono/; revision=9


Commit migrated from https://github.com/mono/mono/commit/0fae05ddc83ee034344d50a6d4d618cfb10ee491</description>
      <author> (migueldeicaza)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/commit/480e91e54517a0fee2e64a9a24dc8319dad03186</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 22:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Rule Engine to Rule them all? | Meetup</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/HaintonsDotNetMeetup/events/283608740/</link>
      <description>Thu, Feb 17, 6:00 PM GMT: Join Peter Bull from tombola as he talks about using Rule Engines in C# and how tombola is creating and using a Rule Engine to implement conditional behaviour in their webs</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/HaintonsDotNetMeetup/events/283608740/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zeus &amp;amp; Hera | BMW USA (Official Video)</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/nUC1QA5gRcU</link>
      <description>Electricity in its Ultimate Form: https://www.bmwusa.com/ultimateelectric.htmlExperience the all-electric BMW: https://www.BMWUSA.com/all-electric.htmlSubscr...</description>
      <author> (BMW USA
  
  
  
    BMW USA
  




  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/nUC1QA5gRcU</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 20:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRA Design by Creative Tim</title>
      <link>https://iradesign.io/</link>
      <description>Build your own amazing illustrations.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iradesign.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 20:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Management System (CMS) Platform | Progress Sitefinity</title>
      <link>https://www.progress.com/sitefinity-cms</link>
      <description>Sitefinity&amp;#39;s content management system (CMS) platform is a marketing command center to drive business growth. Easily manage multi-site experiences deployed your way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.progress.com/sitefinity-cms</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 19:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Live!: Training Conferences and Events for Enterprise Microsoft .NET and Azure Developers</title>
      <link>https://vslive.com/Home.aspx</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vslive.com/Home.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 19:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - hamukazu/lets-get-arrested: This project is intended to protest against the police in Japan</title>
      <link>https://github.com/hamukazu/lets-get-arrested</link>
      <description>This project is intended to protest against the police in Japan - GitHub - hamukazu/lets-get-arrested: This project is intended to protest against the police in Japan</description>
      <author> (hamukazu)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/hamukazu/lets-get-arrested</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 19:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualtrics Survey | Qualtrics Experience Management</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_3t2obFGli2fSkjY</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://microsoft.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_3t2obFGli2fSkjY</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 19:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Include diagrams in your Markdown files with Mermaid | The GitHub Blog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/2022-02-14-include-diagrams-markdown-files-mermaid/</link>
      <description>Mermaid is a JavaScript based diagramming and charting tool that takes Markdown-inspired text definitions and creates diagrams dynamically in the browser.</description>
      <author> (By Martin Woodward				

				February 14, 2022)</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/2022-02-14-include-diagrams-markdown-files-mermaid/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 19:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoMapper, Nullable DateTime, and Selecting the Right Constructor</title>
      <link>https://www.paraesthesia.com/archive/2022/02/14/automapper-nullable-datetime-constructors/</link>
      <description>I learned a pretty hard lesson while trying to map nullable DateTimeOffset to nullable DateTime and thought I&amp;#39;d share what I found.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.paraesthesia.com/archive/2022/02/14/automapper-nullable-datetime-constructors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 17:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Framework January 2022 Cumulative Update Preview </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2022/02/NET-framework-cumulative-update/</link>
      <description>Last month, Microsoft released the .NET Framework January 2022 Cumulative Update Preview, part of the company&amp;#39;s promise to support .NET Framework. The update targets .NET Framework versions 3.5 and 4.8 and focuses on the Common Language Runtime and Windows Presentation Foundation.
The preview release aims to increase reliability and quality of the .NET Framework features for Windows OS.</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand
                
            
            
        Technical Architect Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2022/02/NET-framework-cumulative-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 17:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piped</title>
      <link>https://youtube.censors.us/nUC1QA5gRcU</link>
      <description>An alternative privacy-friendly YouTube frontend which is efficient by design.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.censors.us/nUC1QA5gRcU</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 17:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.Net 6 WebApplicationBuilder and Lamar</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2022/02/14/net-6-webapplicationbuilder-and-lamar/</link>
      <description>TL;DR — The latest Lamar V8.0.1 release has some bug fixes and mild breaking changes around the .Net Core DI integration that eliminates user reported problems with the new .Net 6 bootstrappi…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2022/02/14/net-6-webapplicationbuilder-and-lamar/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 17:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Perl Saved the Human Genome Project</title>
      <link>https://www.foo.be/docs/tpj/issues/vol1_2/tpj0102-0001.html</link>
      <description>The human genome project was inaugurated at the beginning of the decade as an ambitious international effort to determine the complete DNA sequence of human beings and several experimental animals. The justification for this undertaking is both scientific and medical. By understanding the genetic makeup of an organism in excruciating detail, it is hoped that we will be better able to understand how organisms develop from single eggs into complex multicellular beings, how food is metabolized and transformed into the constituents of the body, how the nervous system assembles itself into a smoothly functioning ensemble. From the medical point of view, the wealth of knowledge that will come from knowing the complete DNA sequence will greatly accelerate the process of finding the causes of (and potential cures for) human diseases.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.foo.be/docs/tpj/issues/vol1_2/tpj0102-0001.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 17:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What You Should Know About The Stock Market – BetterExplained</title>
      <link>https://betterexplained.com/articles/what-you-should-know-about-the-stock-market/</link>
      <description>Everyone’s heard of the stock market — but few know why it works. Were you aware that each stock has two prices? That you can’t buy and sell for the same amount? That a “stock market” works better and is more open than a “stock store”?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://betterexplained.com/articles/what-you-should-know-about-the-stock-market/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 16:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COM asynchronous interfaces, part 1: The basic pattern - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220214-44/?p=106251</link>
      <description>You can mark your marshaled COM interfaces as supporting asynchronous calls, which unlocks a brand new calling pattern. When you attach the async_uuid attribute to your interface, COM generates a parallel interface with the same name as the synchronous interface, but with the Async prefix.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220214-44/?p=106251</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 16:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debugging a WebView2 component using Playwright in .NET - G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/debugging-a-webview2-using-playwright-in-dotnet.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I explain how to use Playwright to debug a WebView2 component in a .NET application.</description>
      <author> (G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/debugging-a-webview2-using-playwright-in-dotnet.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 15:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Badly implementing encryption: Part II–breaking the code</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/196450-A/badly-implementing-encryption-part-ii-breaking-the-code</link>
      <description>In my previous post, I implemented an &amp;amp;ldquo;encryption system&amp;amp;rdquo; using a stream cipher based on top of Md5. The idea is to start with a given key (128 b...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/196450-A/badly-implementing-encryption-part-ii-breaking-the-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 15:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# Nullable Features thru the times</title>
      <link>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2022/02/14/nullable/</link>
      <description>Exceptions of type NullReferenceException are the most common errors with .NET applications. With C# 8, nullable reference types have been introduced to get rid of these exceptions. The new .NET 6 …</description>
      <author> (Published by
	Christian Nagel)</author>
      <guid>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2022/02/14/nullable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 15:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android 13 virtualization lets Pixel 6 run Windows 11, Linux distributions - CNX Software</title>
      <link>https://www.cnx-software.com/2022/02/14/android-13-virtualization-lets-pixel-6-run-windows-11-linux-distributions/</link>
      <description>The first Android 13 developer preview may have felt a bit underwhelming, but there&amp;#39;s a hidden gem with full virtualization possible on hardware such as</description>
      <author> (Jean-Luc Aufranc (CNXSoft))</author>
      <guid>https://www.cnx-software.com/2022/02/14/android-13-virtualization-lets-pixel-6-run-windows-11-linux-distributions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 14:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The simple system I’m using to stay in touch with hundreds of people</title>
      <link>https://jakobgreenfeld.com/stay-in-touch</link>
      <description>Staying in touch with people is one of these asymmetric habits that require little effort, time and resources but has an unlimited upside.</description>
      <author> (Jakob Greenfeld)</author>
      <guid>https://jakobgreenfeld.com/stay-in-touch</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 13:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wifi Signal Mapping with WiFiman - Using Augmented Reality!</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/ovi5Yub1DHU</link>
      <description>Learn how to map your Wifi signal using the augmented reality feature of the WiFiman app. WifiMan Android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com....</description>
      <author> (Lars Klint
  
  
  
    Lars Klint
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/ovi5Yub1DHU</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 10:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operator Overloading in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-operator-overloading/</link>
      <description>C# operator overloading, is all operator overloadable?, unary, binary operator overloading, real-life code example, benefits, advantages</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-operator-overloading/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 09:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>293: dotnet-trace with dotnet-monitor through dotnet-dsrouter</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/293</link>
      <description>Measure, measure, measure with dotnet-trace a &amp;quot;new&amp;quot; tool that Frank has been exploring to make apps super performant.</description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/293</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 09:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problems with online user authentication when using self sovereign identity</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2022/02/14/problems-with-online-user-authentication-when-using-self-sovereign-identity/</link>
      <description>Using self sovereign identity (SSI), there is no standardized solutions for solving online user authentication when using verifiable credentials and verifying the identity and user. All solutions r…</description>
      <author> (damienbod)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2022/02/14/problems-with-online-user-authentication-when-using-self-sovereign-identity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 09:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data modeling for Power BI - Developer Support</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/data-modeling-for-power-bi/</link>
      <description>Michael Mano shares a few tips for data modeling with Power BI. Data modeling for Power BI Data Modeling is used to connect multiple data sources in Power BI tool using a relationship. A relationship defines how data sources are connected with each other.</description>
      <author> (Developer Support)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/data-modeling-for-power-bi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 09:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sargable predicates and NULLs in SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/codex/sargable-predicates-and-null-values-in-sql-server-c43ec3d8b108</link>
      <description>Convert non-sargable predicates to sargable predicates</description>
      <author> (https://segovoni.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/codex/sargable-predicates-and-null-values-in-sql-server-c43ec3d8b108</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL on Azure: Part 7 - Server-side Authentication</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/graphql-on-azure-part-7-server-side-authentication/ba-p/3152436</link>
      <description>In our journey into GraphQL on Azure we&amp;#39;ve only created endpoints that can be accessed by anyone. In this post we&amp;#39;ll look at how we can add authentication to our GraphQL server. For the post, we&amp;#39;ll use the Apollo Server and Azure Static Web Apps for hosting the API, mainly because SWA provides secur...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/734436)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/graphql-on-azure-part-7-server-side-authentication/ba-p/3152436</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL on Azure: Part 8 - Logging</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/graphql-on-azure-part-8-logging/ba-p/3152454</link>
      <description>As we&amp;#39;ve been looking at how to run GraphQL on Azure we&amp;#39;ve covered several topics of importance with Azure integration, but what we haven&amp;#39;t looked at is how we make sure that we are getting insights into our application so that if something goes wrong, we know about it. So for this post we&amp;#39;re going ...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/734436)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/graphql-on-azure-part-8-logging/ba-p/3152454</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Host Static Web Sites for Free in Azure</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/healthcare-and-life-sciences/host-static-web-sites-for-free-in-azure/ba-p/3152200</link>
      <description>Have a simple site that’s just html, css, javascript and other static content?&amp;#160; You can host it for free in Azure. Not only is it free to host it is much easier to maintain than most off the self content management systems. Scenario Recently a colleague &amp;#160;had a simple question: How do I host my stati...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/1139441)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/healthcare-and-life-sciences/host-static-web-sites-for-free-in-azure/ba-p/3152200</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing FakeAuth for .NET Core</title>
      <link>https://developingux.com/introducing-fakeauth/</link>
      <description>With modern .NET CORE applications, you get 4 types of authentication out of the box. Most people are using the wrong one. You should be using “Microsoft identity platform” for most modern, cloud first applications.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developingux.com/introducing-fakeauth/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six Labors : Announcing ImageSharp 2.0.0</title>
      <link>https://sixlabors.com/posts/announcing-imagesharp-200/</link>
      <description>ImageSharp 2 - Harder, Better, Faster, Stronger!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sixlabors.com/posts/announcing-imagesharp-200/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arduboy</title>
      <link>https://www.arduboy.com/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.arduboy.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside look at modern web browser (part 1) &amp;#160;|&amp;#160; Web &amp;#160;|&amp;#160; Google Developers</title>
      <link>https://developers.google.com/web/updates/2018/09/inside-browser-part1</link>
      <description>Learn how browser turn your code into functional website from high-level architecture to the specifics of the rendering pipeline.</description>
      <author> (By
      
        
          Mariko
          Kosaka)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.google.com/web/updates/2018/09/inside-browser-part1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET and C# Versions - 20th Anniversary ♥</title>
      <link>https://nietras.com/2022/02/13/dotnet-and-csharp-versions/</link>
      <description>

</description>
      <author> (nietras)</author>
      <guid>https://nietras.com/2022/02/13/dotnet-and-csharp-versions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New POSIX Signal Handling Features in .NET 6</title>
      <link>https://carpenoctem.dev/blog/posix-signal-handling-in-dotnet-6/</link>
      <description>Learn about the new .NET 6 feature for handling Linux/Unix signals. Examples in F#.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://carpenoctem.dev/blog/posix-signal-handling-in-dotnet-6/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 20 Years with .NET</title>
      <link>https://rendle.dev/posts/my-20-years-with-dotnet/</link>
      <description>For the 20th birthday of .NET, a look back at my time with it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rendle.dev/posts/my-20-years-with-dotnet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>