<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>What is the “protein folding problem”? A brief explanation</title>
      <link>https://rootsofprogress.org/alphafold-protein-folding-explainer</link>
      <description>AlphaFold from Google DeepMind is said to solve the protein folding problem. What is that, and why is it hard?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rootsofprogress.org/alphafold-protein-folding-explainer</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 13:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core Improvements in .NET 5 </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/12/aspnet-core-improvement-dotnet-5/</link>
      <description>Earlier this month, at the .NET Conf 2020, Microsoft released the .NET 5 platform. This version includes a broad set of new features and improvements, which are also related to the ASP.NET Core framework. This release&amp;#39;s efforts focus primarily on performance improvements, followed by other features regarding Blazor, SignalR, MVC, OpenAPI support, and Azure AD authentication integration.</description>
      <author> (Antonio Liccardi
                
            
        Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/12/aspnet-core-improvement-dotnet-5/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 13:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>monicahq/monica</title>
      <link>https://github.com/monicahq/monica</link>
      <description>Personal CRM. Remember everything about your friends, family and business relationships. - monicahq/monica</description>
      <author> (monicahq)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/monicahq/monica</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 11:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce strikes deal to acquire Slack for $27.7 billion</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2020/12/salesforce-acquires-slack-for-27-7-billion/</link>
      <description>Slack will become &amp;quot;the new interface for Salesforce Customer 360.&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> (Samuel Axon
    -  12/1/2020, 2:37 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2020/12/salesforce-acquires-slack-for-27-7-billion/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 10:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2020-12-02</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/12/app-developer-links-2020-12-02/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/12/app-developer-links-2020-12-02/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 09:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Scope Software Projects When Everything is Something You&amp;#39;ve Never Done Before - 7pace</title>
      <link>https://www.7pace.com/blog/how-to-scope-software-projects</link>
      <description>It’s a common problem for software teams: How do you scope work when you’ve never done this kind of project before? The answer lies in a tool many devs aren’t using to its full potential.</description>
      <author> (By Tyler Hakes)</author>
      <guid>https://www.7pace.com/blog/how-to-scope-software-projects</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 09:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Smell – Primitive Obsession and Refactoring Recipes - NDepend</title>
      <link>https://blog.ndepend.com/code-smell-primitive-obsession-and-refactoring-recipes/</link>
      <description>Understand the Primitive Obsession code smell with examples, when code relies too much on primitives which leads to poor maintainability.</description>
      <author> (Patrick Smacchia)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ndepend.com/code-smell-primitive-obsession-and-refactoring-recipes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 07:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Only Testing that Matters: Testing through User Eyes</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/the-only-testing-that-matters-testing-through-eyes-of-user</link>
      <description>End-to-end testing is the only way to ensure modern, distributed, loosely coupled applications actually work—taking a positive approach to ensuring app quality.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/the-only-testing-that-matters-testing-through-eyes-of-user</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 07:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction - Computer Graphics from scratch</title>
      <link>https://www.gabrielgambetta.com/computer-graphics-from-scratch/introduction.html</link>
      <description>TL;DR: This book will not teach you how to use OpenGL or DirectX; instead, it can teach you how OpenGL and DirectX work. In practice you won’t write a software renderer for production use, but understanding how and why a renderer works will let you use OpenGL and DirectX more effectively.</description>
      <author> (About the author)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gabrielgambetta.com/computer-graphics-from-scratch/introduction.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 07:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New for AWS Lambda – Container Image Support | Amazon Web Services</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-aws-lambda-container-image-support/</link>
      <description>With AWS Lambda, you upload your code and run it without thinking about servers. Many customers enjoy the way this works, but if you’ve invested in container tooling for your development workflows, it’s not easy to use the same approach to build applications using Lambda. To help you with that, you can now package and […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-for-aws-lambda-container-image-support/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 07:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seasons of Serverless Challenge 1: Azure Functions and Azure SQL Database serverless</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/seasons-of-serverless-challenge-1-azure-functions-and-azure-sql-database-serverless/</link>
      <description>Learn how to develop an Azure Function that leverages Azure SQL database serverless with Challenge 1 of the Seasons of Serverless challenge.</description>
      <author> (Drew Skwiers-Koballa Program Manager Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/seasons-of-serverless-challenge-1-azure-functions-and-azure-sql-database-serverless/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 07:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Buy Gifts That People Actually Want - Will Patrick</title>
      <link>https://www.willpatrick.co.uk/articles/how-to-buy-gifts-that-people-actually-want</link>
      <description>Every year, we buy more bad gifts than we realise and nobody tells us about it. Here&amp;#39;s how to avoid the most common pitfalls and to use psychology to drastically improve your gift-giving game.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.willpatrick.co.uk/articles/how-to-buy-gifts-that-people-actually-want</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 07:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Monolith: Domain-Centric Design - Kamil Grzybek</title>
      <link>http://www.kamilgrzybek.com/design/modular-monolith-domain-centric-design/</link>
      <description>Domain-Centric Design for Modular Monolith Architecture</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.kamilgrzybek.com/design/modular-monolith-domain-centric-design/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 07:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s New in Text Analytics: Opinion Mining and Async API</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/AI-Show/Whats-New-in-Text-Analytics-Opinion-Mining-and-Async-API</link>
      <description>In today&amp;#39;s AI show, you will learn about the recently launched Opinion Mining and Async offerings of Text Analytics. In the first half, we will discuss how Opinion Mining (an extension of Sentiment An</description>
      <author> (by Seth Juarez, deeTech)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/AI-Show/Whats-New-in-Text-Analytics-Opinion-Mining-and-Async-API</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 05:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want more PostgreSQL? You just might like Babelfish | Amazon Web Services</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/opensource/want-more-postgresql-you-just-might-like-babelfish/</link>
      <description>“The greatest force in legacy databases is inertia,” a widely regarded industry analyst once told me. Not superior functionality. Not better performance. Not lower cost. None of the above. Just inertia. Developers might say they prefer to run PostgreSQL to proprietary alternatives (and they do), but enterprises have spent years building data models in Microsoft […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/opensource/want-more-postgresql-you-just-might-like-babelfish/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 05:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cryptopals Crypto Challenges</title>
      <link>https://cryptopals.com/</link>
      <description>Work in progress.</description>
      <author> (Thomas Ptacek, Sean Devlin, and Alex Balducci)</author>
      <guid>https://cryptopals.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 05:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radicle - Peer-to-peer code collaboration</title>
      <link>https://radicle.xyz/</link>
      <description>Radicle is a peer-to-peer stack for building software together.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://radicle.xyz/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 05:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is 2020 over?</title>
      <link>https://is2020over.com/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://is2020over.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 04:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon S3 | Strong Consistency | Amazon Web Services</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/s3/consistency/</link>
      <description>Amazon S3 delivers strong read-after-write consistency automatically for all applications for any storage request, without changes to performance or availability, without sacrificing regional isolation for applications, and at no additional cost.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aws.amazon.com/s3/consistency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 03:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our commitment to privacy in Microsoft Productivity Score - Microsoft 365 Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/blog/2020/12/01/our-commitment-to-privacy-in-microsoft-productivity-score/</link>
      <description>At Microsoft, we believe that data-driven insights are crucial to empowering people and organizations to achieve more. We also believe that privacy is a human right, and we’re deeply committed to the privacy of every person who uses our products. As part of that commitment, today we’re making changes to Productivity Score.</description>
      <author> (By Jared Spataro, Corporate Vice President for Microsoft 365)</author>
      <guid>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/blog/2020/12/01/our-commitment-to-privacy-in-microsoft-productivity-score/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 03:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Framework November 2020 Cumulative Update Preview for Windows 10 2004 and Windows Server, version 2004 | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/net-framework-november-2020-cumulative-update-preview-for-windows-10-2004-and-windows-server-version-2004/</link>
      <description>Yesterday, we are releasing the November 2020 Cumulative Update Preview for .NET Framework. Quality and Reliability This release contains the following quality and reliability improvements. CLR1 Improved the clean-up process for X509Certificate2 certificates WPF2 Addressed an issue with a FailFast crash arising in apps with two threads that both load application resources.</description>
      <author> (Tara Overfield Software Engineer II , .NET Servicing)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/net-framework-november-2020-cumulative-update-preview-for-windows-10-2004-and-windows-server-version-2004/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 03:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An iOS zero-click radio proximity exploit odyssey</title>
      <link>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2020/12/an-ios-zero-click-radio-proximity.html</link>
      <description>Posted by Ian Beer, Project Zero NOTE: This specific issue was fixed before the launch of Privacy-Preserving Contact Tracing  in iOS 13.5 in...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2020/12/an-ios-zero-click-radio-proximity.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 02:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity 101: Installation</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/dotnet/unity-101-installation-587a</link>
      <description>Hello, welcome to our Unity 101 video series. This is series will help you to get up and going with U...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/dotnet/unity-101-installation-587a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 01:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slack Technologies - Acquisition Legend</title>
      <link>https://investor.slackhq.com/acquisition-legend/default.aspx?sf133655513=1</link>
      <description>Forward-Looking Statements
        
            This communication relates to a proposed business combination transaction between Salesforce.com, Inc. (“Salesforce”) and Slack Technologies, Inc. (“Slack”). This communication includes forward-looking statements within the meaning of Section 27A of the Securities Act of 1933 and Section 21E of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934. Forward-looking statements relate to future events and anticipated results of operations, business strategies, the anticipated benefits of the proposed transaction, the anticipated impact of the proposed transaction on the combined company’s business and future financial and operating results, the expected amount and timing of synergies from the proposed transaction, the anticipated closing date for the proposed transaction and other aspects of our operations or operating results. These forward-looking statements generally can be identified by phrases such as “will,” “expects,” “anticipates,” “foresees,” “forecasts,” “estimates” or other words or phrases of similar import.&amp;#160; It is uncertain whether any of the events anticipated by the forward-looking statements will transpire or occur, or if any of them do, what impact they will have on the results of operations and financial condition of the combined companies or the price of Salesforce or Slack stock. These forward-looking statements involve certain risks and uncertainties, many of which are beyond the parties’ control, that could cause actual results to differ materially from those indicated in such forward-looking statements, including but not limited to: the impact of public health crises, such as pandemics (including coronavirus (COVID-19)) and epidemics and any related company or government policies and actions to protect the health and safety of individuals or government policies or actions to maintain the functioning of national or global economies and markets; the effect of the announcement of the merger on the ability of Salesforce or Slack to retain and hire key personnel and maintain relationships with customers, suppliers and others with whom Salesforce or Slack do business, or on Salesforce’s or Slack’s operating results and business generally; risks that the merger disrupts current plans and operations and the potential difficulties in employee retention as a result of the merger; the outcome of any legal proceedings related to the merger; the ability of the parties to consummate the proposed transaction on a timely basis or at all; the satisfaction of the conditions precedent to consummation of the proposed transaction, including the ability to secure regulatory approvals on the terms expected, at all or in a timely manner; the ability of Salesforce to successfully integrate Slack’s operations; the ability of Salesforce to implement its plans, forecasts and other expectations with respect to Salesforce’s business after the completion of the transaction and realize expected synergies; and business disruption following the merger. These risks, as well as other risks related to the proposed transaction, will be included in the registration statement on Form S-4 and proxy statement/prospectus that will be filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”) in connection with the proposed transaction.&amp;#160; While the list of factors presented here is, and the list of factors to be presented in the registration statement on Form S-4 are, considered representative, no such list should be considered to be a complete statement of all potential risks and uncertainties. For additional information about other factors that could cause actual results to differ materially from those described in the forward-looking statements, please refer to Salesforce’s and Slack’s respective periodic reports and other filings with the SEC, including the risk factors identified in Salesforce’s and Slack’s most recent Quarterly Reports on Form 10-Q and Annual Reports on Form 10-K. The forward-looking statements included in this communication are made only as of the date hereof. Neither Salesforce nor Slack undertakes any obligation to update any forward-looking statements to reflect subsequent events or circumstances, except as required by law.
No Offer or Solicitation
This communication is not intended to and shall not constitute an offer to buy or sell or the solicitation of an offer to buy or sell any securities, or a solicitation of any vote or approval, nor shall there be any sale of securities in any jurisdiction in which such offer, solicitation or sale would be unlawful prior to registration or qualification under the securities laws of any such jurisdiction.&amp;#160; No offering of securities shall be made, except by means of a prospectus meeting the requirements of Section 10 of the U.S. Securities Act of 1933, as amended.&amp;#160;&amp;#160;
Additional Information about the Merger and Where to Find It
In connection with the proposed transaction, Salesforce intends to file with the SEC a registration statement on Form S-4 that will include a proxy statement of Slack and that also constitutes a prospectus of Salesforce.&amp;#160; Each of Salesforce and Slack may also file other relevant documents with the SEC regarding the proposed transaction. This document is not a substitute for the proxy statement/prospectus or registration statement or any other document that Salesforce or Slack may file with the SEC.&amp;#160; The definitive proxy statement/prospectus (if and when available) will be mailed to stockholders of Salesforce and Slack.&amp;#160; INVESTORS AND SECURITY HOLDERS ARE URGED TO READ THE REGISTRATION STATEMENT, PROXY STATEMENT/PROSPECTUS AND ANY OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS THAT MAY BE FILED WITH THE SEC, AS WELL AS ANY AMENDMENTS OR SUPPLEMENTS TO THESE DOCUMENTS, CAREFULLY AND IN THEIR ENTIRETY IF AND WHEN THEY BECOME AVAILABLE BECAUSE THEY CONTAIN OR WILL CONTAIN IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION.&amp;#160; Investors and security holders will be able to obtain free copies of the registration statement and proxy statement/prospectus (if and when available) and other documents containing important information about Salesforce, Slack and the proposed transaction, once such documents are filed with the SEC through the website maintained by the SEC at http://www.sec.gov.&amp;#160; Copies of the documents filed with the SEC by Salesforce will be available free of charge on Salesforce’s website at www.salesforce.com/investor or by contacting Salesforce’s Investor Relations department at investor@salesforce.com.&amp;#160; Copies of the documents filed with the SEC by Slack will be available free of charge on Slack’s website at investor.slackhq.com or by contacting Slack’s Investor Relations department at ir@slack.com.
Participants in the Solicitation
Salesforce, Slack and certain of their respective directors and executive officers may be deemed to be participants in the solicitation of proxies in respect of the proposed transaction.&amp;#160; Information about the directors and executive officers of Salesforce, including a description of their direct or indirect interests, by security holdings or otherwise, is set forth in Salesforce’s proxy statement for its 2020 Annual Meeting of Stockholders, which was filed with the SEC on May 1, 2020, and Salesforce’s Annual Report on Form 10-K for the fiscal year ended January 31, 2020, which was filed with the SEC on March 5, 2020, as well as in a Form 8-K filed by Salesforce with the SEC on June 1, 2020.&amp;#160; Information about the directors and executive officers of Slack, including a description of their direct or indirect interests, by security holdings or otherwise, is set forth in Slack’s proxy statement for its 2020 Annual Meeting of Stockholders, which was filed with the SEC on May 5, 2020, and Slack’s Annual Report on Form 10-K for the fiscal year ended January 31, 2020, which was filed with the SEC on March 12, 2020.&amp;#160; Other information regarding the participants in the proxy solicitations and a description of their direct and indirect interests, by security holdings or otherwise, will be contained in the proxy statement/prospectus and other relevant materials to be filed with the SEC regarding the proposed transaction when such materials become available.&amp;#160; Investors should read the proxy statement/prospectus carefully when it becomes available before making any voting or investment decisions.&amp;#160; You may obtain free copies of these documents from Salesforce or Slack using the sources indicated above.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://investor.slackhq.com/acquisition-legend/default.aspx?sf133655513=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Wonder Woman 1984’ will be HBO Max&amp;#39;s first 4K movie</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/wonder-woman-1984-hbo-max-4k-222757708.html</link>
      <description>When Wonder Woman 1984 comes out on December 25th, it will be the first title to stream in 4K on HBO Max.</description>
      <author> (https://www.engadget.com/editors/igor-bonifacic)</author>
      <guid>https://www.engadget.com/wonder-woman-1984-hbo-max-4k-222757708.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 23:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce Signs Definitive Agreement to Acquire Slack - Salesforce News</title>
      <link>https://www.salesforce.com/news/press-releases/2020/12/01/salesforce-definitive-agreement-update/</link>
      <description>Combination of #1 CRM platform with the most innovative enterprise communications platform will create the operating system for the new way to work, enabling companies to grow and succeed in the all-digital world SAN FRANCISCO, Dec. 1, 2020 – Salesforce (NYSE: CRM), the global leader in CRM, and Slack Technologies, Inc. (NYSE: WORK), the most […]</description>
      <author> (December 1, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://www.salesforce.com/news/press-releases/2020/12/01/salesforce-definitive-agreement-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 23:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disclosure: Yet another macOS privacy protections bypass</title>
      <link>https://lapcatsoftware.com/articles/disclosure3.html</link>
      <description>Today I&amp;#39;m disclosing a macOS privacy protections bypass. I discovered that an application can use the venerable Unix command-line tool &amp;quot;ls&amp;quot; (list directory contents) to bypass both TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) and the sandbox, enabling unauthorized access to file metadata in directories that are supposed to be protected. This issue remains unaddressed in the latest public versions of Big Sur, Catalina, and Mojave, and is therefore, in one sense, a zero-day. Here is the timeline leading to my disclosure:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lapcatsoftware.com/articles/disclosure3.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 23:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building and deploying web apps with Static Web Apps</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/DevOps-Lab/Building-and-deploying-web-apps-with-Static-Web-Apps</link>
      <description>You are embarking on a new project and have decided to go full Serverless and try out that JAMStack. After all, our application is a web front end and some API&amp;#39;s, so Serverless is the perfect model fo</description>
      <author> (by Damian Brady, Aaron Powell, Channel 9 Studio, deeTech)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/DevOps-Lab/Building-and-deploying-web-apps-with-Static-Web-Apps</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Matthiesen - You can book online!</title>
      <link>https://outlook.office365.com/owa/calendar/MicrosoftVisualStudioforMac@microsoft.onmicrosoft.com/bookings/s/qST2lz5ihkWW4J_hlHCPFg2</link>
      <description>You can now book and manage appointments using our booking page.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://outlook.office365.com/owa/calendar/MicrosoftVisualStudioforMac@microsoft.onmicrosoft.com/bookings/s/qST2lz5ihkWW4J_hlHCPFg2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 23:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KDE Community Edition is now available | PINE64</title>
      <link>https://www.pine64.org/2020/12/01/kde-community-edition-is-now-available/</link>
      <description>We are pleased to announce that the KDE Community Edition (CE) PinePhone is now available for pre-order. This edition of the PinePhone ships with a tailored build of Plasma Mobile built upon Manjaro…</description>
      <author> (admin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pine64.org/2020/12/01/kde-community-edition-is-now-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptologie | Real World Cryptographers Podcast Episode 2</title>
      <link>https://www.cryptologie.net/links/link/2419</link>
      <description>Your name</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cryptologie.net/links/link/2419</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 23:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Can Be Dishonest About Work</title>
      <link>https://amiantos.net/people-can-be-dishonest-about-work/</link>
      <description>Details of my experience with someone trying very hard to commit unemployment fraud.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://amiantos.net/people-can-be-dishonest-about-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If at first you don&amp;#39;t succeed boil it in acid</title>
      <link>http://caps0ff.blogspot.com/2020/12/if-at-first-you-dont-succeed-boil-it-in.html</link>
      <description>In a previous post  we discussed extracting TMS32010 ROMs optically. This information helps the arcade community better understand these cab...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://caps0ff.blogspot.com/2020/12/if-at-first-you-dont-succeed-boil-it-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Eating Meat Be Good For You? And The Planet? by Edlin Choi</title>
      <link>https://www.edlinbetsthefarm.com/blog/can-eating-meat-be-good-for-you-and-the-planet</link>
      <description>30 days, 0 vegetables, 99 pounds of meat, 12 poops, 42.5 hours of deep sleep, $950, and -3.1 pounds of carbon dioxide: An empirical analysis of the carnivore diet, regenerative agriculture, and the potential environmental benefit of meat.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.edlinbetsthefarm.com/blog/can-eating-meat-be-good-for-you-and-the-planet</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Basic JSON APIs with Route-to-code in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/aspnet/core/web-api/route-to-code?view=aspnetcore-5.0</link>
      <description>Learn how to use Route-to-code and JSON extension methods to create lightweight JSON web APIs.</description>
      <author> (JamesNK)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/aspnet/core/web-api/route-to-code?view=aspnetcore-5.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protein folding &amp;amp; The AI ‘Solution’ : A primer for non-scientists</title>
      <link>https://abhirathb.com/2020/11/29/Protein-Folding.html</link>
      <description>TLDR</description>
      <author> (Abhirath Batra)</author>
      <guid>https://abhirathb.com/2020/11/29/Protein-Folding.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn C# with CSharpFritz - Ep11: New Features in C# 9</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=htB7ohlaYKk</link>
      <description>.NET 5 is released and C# 9 is here!  Let&amp;#39;s talk about the new features of C# 9 and tinker with some code to see how it can benefit our applications.

After the C# basics sessions are completed, which user interface framework do you want Fritz to walk through FIRST?  Vote for your favorite with an emote at:  https://github.com/csharpfritz/csharp_with_csharpfritz/issues/13

Questions:
00:05:49 - Why use C# over C++?
00:08:44 - How do you configure .NET3.1 and .NET5 to work side by side on a Linux server? 
00:10:39 - Is C# a good gateway development language into others?
00:12:16 - Does C# 9 produce code that is more efficient just by recompiling applications?
00:13:35 - Is VB at the same level of C# ?
00:15:24 - Is the syntactic sugar C# 9 brings bad for performance?
00:24:26 - Can I still use .NET Standard dlls with .NET 5?
00:34:39 - Does the constructor/assignment syntax work on a normal class as well?
00:37:38 - Could you say a Record type sugarcoats Class types?
00:39:37 - Is C#9 support going to be exclusive to .NET 5
00:40:44 - Are the any breaking changes from C#8 to C#9?
00:42:49 - Is there a way to use C#9 on UWP?
00:55:59 - Are generics supported with record types?
00:57:13 - Are records and anonymous objects related in any ways?
01:02:13 - Can you have init and set defined separately?
01:05:14 - Can you use backing fields with init?
01:12:50 - What if you have two files with top-level statements in a project?
01:13:48 - Do you lose the ability to pass in arguments with top-level statements?
01:16:16 - When would you use top-level statements and not a unit test project?
01:17:57 - How we can execute top-level statements from other files/classes/methods?

Background Music is Harris Heller&amp;#39;s Streambeats - Lo-Fi playlist, available royalty free at https://open.spotify.com/playlist/4kAqBBEZQsBIXMIJl6u8tO?si=94DuMKiaTqaxgh_WlQ-viQ

Source code and interactive content from the stream are available at:  https://github.com/csharpfritz/csharp_with_csharpfritz
Watch live Mondays at 1300 UTC / 9a ET / 6a PT at:  https://twitch.tv/visualstudio</description>
      <author> (dotNET)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=htB7ohlaYKk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airbnb. Thanksgiving. Burglary.</title>
      <link>https://ternaus.blog/incident/2020/12/01/Airbnb-Thanksgiving-Burglary.html</link>
      <description>Bad things happen. And sometimes it is not our fault.</description>
      <author> (Vladimir Iglovikov)</author>
      <guid>https://ternaus.blog/incident/2020/12/01/Airbnb-Thanksgiving-Burglary.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mojo Men Blog</title>
      <link>https://mojomen.blog/why-amateur-porn-is-better</link>
      <description>I’m an actor and a model. I star in gay adult films. I remember after my first shoot, my director said to me you should start an Only Fans and a Twitter as good marketing. (It was mostly for him to sell the films.) I remember being perplexed about posting adult content to Twitter and having absolutely no idea what Only Fans was! I’m also a web developer by day so, being more familiar with Twitter, I went that route. So, I started making amateur homemade porn and posting it to my Twitter account.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mojomen.blog/why-amateur-porn-is-better</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamedev from scratch 0:&amp;#160;Groundwork</title>
      <link>https://eev.ee/blog/2020/11/30/gamedev-from-scratch-0-groundwork/</link>
      <description>You may recall that I once had the ambitious idea to write a book on game development, walking the reader through making simple games from scratch in a variety of different environments, s</description>
      <author> (Eevee)</author>
      <guid>https://eev.ee/blog/2020/11/30/gamedev-from-scratch-0-groundwork/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts and expertise</title>
      <link>https://www.zeptonaut.com/posts/experts-and-expertise/</link>
      <description>A few years ago, I spent about five months trying to improve at chess. In that time, I learned a lot about chess. More importantly, I learned a lot about how to systematically become more effective at something I care about.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.zeptonaut.com/posts/experts-and-expertise/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 22:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Decries WinForms-to-Blazor Performance Degradation -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/12/01/blazor-performance.aspx</link>
      <description>Since shipping .NET 5, Visual Studio 2019 v16.8 and more goodies recently, Microsoft has been touting speed improvements in many components -- including the red-hot Blazor project -- but some real-world developers are finding different results.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel12/01/2020)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/12/01/blazor-performance.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survey Finds That Pandemic Has Exacerbated Sexual Harassment of Tipped Workers</title>
      <link>https://www.eater.com/21755485/survey-of-tipped-workers-finds-increase-in-harassment-throught-covid-19-pandemic</link>
      <description>&amp;quot;He asked me to take my mask off so they could see my face and decide how much to tip me&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> (Jaya Saxena)</author>
      <guid>https://www.eater.com/21755485/survey-of-tipped-workers-finds-increase-in-harassment-throught-covid-19-pandemic</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Arecibo radio telescope&amp;#39;s massive hanging platform has collapsed</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/arecibo-radio-telescope-collapses</link>
      <description>The hanging structure crashed through Arecibo&amp;#39;s radio dish after major cable failures.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/spacecom)</author>
      <guid>https://www.space.com/arecibo-radio-telescope-collapses</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Highlights: 7th edition</title>
      <link>https://www.home-assistant.io/blog/2020/12/01/community-highlights/</link>
      <description>A &amp;#39;Dad status&amp;#39; board, illuminating the steps of your stairs and the most beautiful thermostat you&amp;#39;ve ever seen</description>
      <author> (Franck Nijhof)</author>
      <guid>https://www.home-assistant.io/blog/2020/12/01/community-highlights/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Lambda – Pricing</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/</link>
      <description>With AWS Lambda, you pay only for what you use. You are charged based on the number of requests for your functions and the time your code executes.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 20:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS to FreeBSD migration a.k.a why I left macOS</title>
      <link>https://antranigv.am/weblog_en/posts/macos_to_freebsd/</link>
      <description>macOS to FreeBSD migration a.k.a why I left macOS</description>
      <author> (Antranig Vartanian)</author>
      <guid>https://antranigv.am/weblog_en/posts/macos_to_freebsd/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 20:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Data fetching with GraphQL and Blazor</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iDAYdrFHqGU</link>
      <description>GraphQL supports the ability to subscribe to event streams to enable somewhat real-time scenarios for both clients and servers.

In this episode of the On .NET show, HotChocolate author Michael Staib returns to show us how to enable real-time data fetching with GraphQL using subscriptions .

[T02:02] - What is real-time data fetching?
[T04:30] - What are subscriptions used for?
[T05:48] - Setting up a GraphQL client in Blazor (Demo)
[T10:55] - Updating the GraphQL schema with fragments 
[T16:38] - Updating the Razor components 
[T24:48] - Using GraphQL variables
[T28:18] - Adding subscriptions


HotChocolate in GitHub
https://github.com/ChilliCream/hotchocolate

Subscriptions in GraphQL spec
http://spec.graphql.org/June2018/#sec-Subscription

Introductions to ASP.NET core
https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/aspnet/core/introduction-to-aspnet-core?view=aspnetcore-3.1

#Blazor #AspNETCore #GraphQL #WebAPI</description>
      <author> (dotNET)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iDAYdrFHqGU</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 19:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 5 Runtime Improvements: From Functional to Performant Implementations </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/12/net-5-runtime-improvements/</link>
      <description>During a no-slides presentation at .NET Conf 2020, software architects from the .NET runtime team presented several .NET 5 runtime improvements and how they achieved them, including ARM64 support, HTTP/3, and single-file applications.</description>
      <author> (Eran Stiller
                
            
        Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/12/net-5-runtime-improvements/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 19:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab Hits $6B+ Valuation</title>
      <link>https://www.thetechee.com/2020/12/gitlab-hits-6b-valuation.html</link>
      <description>The Techee - Tech news brought straight to you</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://www.thetechee.com/2020/12/gitlab-hits-6b-valuation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAPI and Versioning for ASP.NET Core Web API</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/openapi-and-versioning-asp-net-core/</link>
      <description>This post is about how to enable and use Open API for ASP.NET Core Web API with versioning enabled. I have created a Web API project in ASP.NET Core 5.0, so Open API is enabled by default. Next I am adding the Microsoft.AspNetCore.Mvc.Versioning package to enable versioning support. And I am enabling version support using the following code in Startup.cs - ConfigureServices method.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/openapi-and-versioning-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 17:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realtime Questions - Stack Exchange</title>
      <link>https://stackexchange.com/questions?tab=realtime</link>
      <description>We make Stack Overflow and 170+ other community-powered Q&amp;amp;A sites.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stackexchange.com/questions?tab=realtime</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 17:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Today, tomorrow and beyond – panel discussion - comitted</title>
      <link>https://commited.tech/events/net-today-tomorrow-and-beyond-panel-discussion/</link>
      <description>.NET Today, tomorrow and beyond – panel discussion - comitted. Committed to tech</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://commited.tech/events/net-today-tomorrow-and-beyond-panel-discussion/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 17:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Your JAM On</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9cwOsW5KBm0</link>
      <description>You are embarking on a new project and have decided to go full Serverless and try out that JAMStack. After all, our application is a Blazor WASM app and some APIs, so Serverless is the perfect fit. But how do we design this solution, tackle local development and most importantly deploy to the cloud? In this session, you&amp;#39;ll see how.</description>
      <author> (dotNET)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9cwOsW5KBm0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 16:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Energy Consumption Index (beta) - Digiconomist</title>
      <link>https://digiconomist.net/ethereum-energy-consumption</link>
      <description>The Ethereum Energy Consumption Index provides the latest estimate of the total energy consumption of the Ethereum network.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://digiconomist.net/ethereum-energy-consumption</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 16:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Energy Consumption Index - Digiconomist</title>
      <link>https://digiconomist.net/bitcoin-energy-consumption</link>
      <description>The Bitcoin Energy Consumption Index provides the latest estimate of the total energy consumption of the Bitcoin network.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://digiconomist.net/bitcoin-energy-consumption</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 16:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABP.IO Platform v4.0 RC Has Been Released based on .NET 5.0!</title>
      <link>https://blog.abp.io/abp/ABP.IO-Platform-v4.0-RC-Has-Been-Released-based-on-.NET-5.0</link>
      <description>Released ABP.IO Platform v4.0 RC. Some new features: Migrated to .NET 5.0, Stable Blazor UI, Identity Server 4 Upgrade, Moved to System.Text.Json, etc. etc. Learn more about what&amp;#39;s new with v4.0 RC release.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.abp.io/abp/ABP.IO-Platform-v4.0-RC-Has-Been-Released-based-on-.NET-5.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 16:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Talk Show: 0250 - Miguel Bernard - Les nouveautes de .NET 5 et C# 9</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiotalkshow.libsyn.com/0250-miguel-bernard-les-nouveautes-de-net-5-et-c-9</link>
      <description>Nous discutons avec Miguel Bernard des nouveaut&amp;#233;s de .NET 5 et de C# 9.&amp;amp;nbsp; Miguel nous explique la strat&amp;#233;gie d&amp;#39;unification des diff&amp;#233;rentes versions du Framework .NET et nous parle de ses coups de coeur avec C# 9. Miguel est passionn&amp;#233; par le partage de ses connaissances, les communaut&amp;#233;s de d&amp;#233;veloppeurs et tout ce qui touche .Net. Ayant plus de 10 ans d&amp;#39;exp&amp;#233;rience avec les technologies Microsoft, il a d&amp;#233;velopp&amp;#233; plusieurs sp&amp;#233;cialisations, incluant C#, F#, Azure et les pratiques DevOps. Il aime partager ses connaissances par son blogue et en pr&amp;#233;sentant &amp;#224; des groupes d&amp;#39;usagers .Net et lors de conf&amp;#233;rences. Il est tr&amp;#232;s impliqu&amp;#233; dans le groupe d&amp;#39;usagers MSDEVMTL &amp;#224; Montr&amp;#233;al, o&amp;#249; il est l&amp;#39;un des coorganisateurs. Liens: Blog:   Twitter: @MiguelBernard88 LinkedIn:   GitHub:   </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiotalkshow.libsyn.com/0250-miguel-bernard-les-nouveautes-de-net-5-et-c-9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 16:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Windows ever find solutions for programs that crashed? | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20201201-00/?p=104498</link>
      <description>When a program crashes, Windows display a message that says, in part, “Windows will close the program and notify you if a solution is available.” Did it ever find solutions? There was a database of problems with known solutions, so if you were lucky,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20201201-00/?p=104498</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 16:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 5 Breaking Changes to the Base Class Library </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/12/net-5-breaking-changes/</link>
      <description>The upcoming release of .NET 5 introduces many breaking changes. While the vast majority of them involve edge cases or previously incorrect behavior, some may take developers by surprise. In the first of this multi-part series, InfoQ looks at the Base Class Library.</description>
      <author> (Jonathan Allen
                
            
        Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/12/net-5-breaking-changes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 15:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export Office 365 calendar events to JetBrains Space using the Microsoft Graph API, the JetBrains Space SDK, and automation</title>
      <link>https://blog.maartenballiauw.be/post/2020/12/01/export-office365-calendar-events-to-space-using-graph-api-and-space-sdk.html</link>
      <description>Chances are you keep a personal calendar, maybe a family calendar, and a work calendar.Working from home, it’s super important to keep these calendars more or less in sync.Colleagues book meetings because your work calendar shows you’re available, while in reality you’ve planned to do some errands or maybe pick up your kids from school.</description>
      <author> (Maarten Balliauw)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.maartenballiauw.be/post/2020/12/01/export-office365-calendar-events-to-space-using-graph-api-and-space-sdk.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 15:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upload Images to a Node.js Server with Uppy, Express.js, and Multer</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JY7OJHKVjEo</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t build an upload widget yourself! Uppy provides an extremely powerful upload widget with just a few lines of code. You can import images from your webcam, a URL, your computer, and tons of other services like Google Drive, Dropbox, and much more!

In this video, we&amp;#39;ll use Uppy to upload images to a Node/Express server. Then, we&amp;#39;ll use the Multer package to create Express.js middleware that will save the image to our local storage.

Get Started with Uppy - https://bit.ly/uppyio
_____________________________________________

Newsletter &amp;#128478;
Interested in exclusive content and discounts? &amp;#129327; Sign up for the newsletter!
https://www.jamesqquick.com
_____________________________________________

Connect with me &amp;#128512;
Live streams on Twitch - https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
Follow me on Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Join the &amp;#128172; Discord Server &amp;#128172; - https://discord.gg/vM2bagU
_____________________________________________

COURSES  &amp;#128187;
Learn how to build Fullstack apps with React and Serverless Functions - https://www.jamesqquick.com/courses/react-and-serverless-fullstack-developmnent
Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code - https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/
Build a Quiz App  - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JY7OJHKVjEo</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 15:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authentication with Graph SDKs | Channel 9</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Authentication-with-Graph-SDKs/player</link>
      <description>To call into Microsoft Graph, your code must acquire an access token from the Microsoft identity platform. To get an access token, your app must be registered and authorized with the Microsoft identit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Authentication-with-Graph-SDKs/player</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 14:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authentication with Graph SDKs </title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Authentication-with-Graph-SDKs?WT.mc_id=dotnet-00000-cephilli</link>
      <description>To call into Microsoft Graph, your code must acquire an access token from the Microsoft identity platform. To get an access token, your app must be registered and authorized with the Microsoft identit</description>
      <author> (by Cecil Phillip)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Authentication-with-Graph-SDKs?WT.mc_id=dotnet-00000-cephilli</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 14:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>