<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>B-trees</title>
      <link>https://shachaf.net/w/b-trees</link>
      <description>Let's invent B(+)-trees.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shachaf.net/w/b-trees</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 09:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluralization with EF Core and EF Core Power Tools</title>
      <link>https://erikej.github.io/efcore/2020/04/26/ef-core-pluralization.html</link>
      <description>EF Core 3 supports pluralization by convention, and allows you to enable and customize it. This blog post will show you how!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://erikej.github.io/efcore/2020/04/26/ef-core-pluralization.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 09:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVIDSafe</title>
      <link>https://www.covidsafe.gov.au/</link>
      <description>COVIDSafe helps you and all of our communities. Assist health officials to quickly understand and tackle the spread of Coronavirus (COVID-19).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.covidsafe.gov.au/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 09:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paxos vs Raft: Have we reached consensus on distributed consensus?</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2004.05074</link>
      <description>Distributed consensus is a fundamental primitive for constructing
fault-tolerant, strongly-consistent distributed systems. Though many
distributed consensus algorithms have been proposed, just two dominate
production systems: Paxos, the traditional, famously subtle, algorithm; and
Raft, a more recent algorithm positioned as a more understandable alternative
to Paxos.
  In this paper, we consider the question of which algorithm, Paxos or Raft, is
the better solution to distributed consensus? We analyse both to determine
exactly how they differ by describing a simplified Paxos algorithm using Raft's
terminology and pragmatic abstractions.
  We find that both Paxos and Raft take a very similar approach to distributed
consensus, differing only in their approach to leader election. Most notably,
Raft only allows servers with up-to-date logs to become leaders, whereas Paxos
allows any server to be leader provided it then updates its log to ensure it is
up-to-date. Raft's approach is surprisingly efficient given its simplicity as,
unlike Paxos, it does not require log entries to be exchanged during leader
election. We surmise that much of the understandability of Raft comes from the
paper's clear presentation rather than being fundamental to the underlying
algorithm being presented.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 10 Apr 2020])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2004.05074</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 08:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AKS Engine Questionnaire</title>
      <link>https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=v4j5cvGGr0GRqy180BHbR_jLfmYe68pDlybMrptnbYhUOFZSUU1aNTJQR0ZGQzFLTFYyVUg5WjNHWC4u</link>
      <description>1.How do you run Kubernetes on Azure?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=v4j5cvGGr0GRqy180BHbR_jLfmYe68pDlybMrptnbYhUOFZSUU1aNTJQR0ZGQzFLTFYyVUg5WjNHWC4u</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 07:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters Weekly 162 -  Replacing Let's Encrypt with Managed Certificates in App Services</title>
      <link>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/04/monsters-weekly/ep162/</link>
      <description>I’ve been using Let’s Encrypt for ages to get SSL on my website but the poor Azure integration is getting me down. In this episode we go into using an Azure managed certificate instead.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/04/monsters-weekly/ep162/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 06:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Flags - Asp.Net Core - The Long Walk</title>
      <link>https://www.pmichaels.net/2020/04/25/feature-flags-asp-net-core/</link>
      <description>Feature flags enable you to create a new piece of functionality in the main code branch, but behind a mask – so the end user doesn’t see the change. This means that you can decide at a later date to turn the feature on, or off. For example, say you wanted to make a change …</description>
      <author> (by pcmichaels)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pmichaels.net/2020/04/25/feature-flags-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 06:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using dotTrace and dotMemory for production analysis on Linux</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/190689-B/using-dottrace-and-dotmemory-for-production-analysis-on-linux</link>
      <description>Recently JetBrains announce that dotTrace and dotMemory supports profiling applications on Linux. We have been testing these out for production usage, analyz...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/190689-B/using-dottrace-and-dotmemory-for-production-analysis-on-linux</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 06:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patterns for Managing Source Code Branches</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/articles/branching-patterns.html#feature-branching</link>
      <description>Mainline, Feature Branching, Continuous Integration, Release Branch and a clutch of other handy patterns.</description>
      <author> (Martin Fowler)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/articles/branching-patterns.html#feature-branching</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 06:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreBoy is a cross platform GameBoy Emulator written in C# that even does ASCII</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/CoreBoyIsACrossPlatformGameBoyEmulatorWrittenInCThatEvenDoesASCII.aspx</link>
      <description>.NET and C# are great languages for programming emulators. Specifically retrogaming and retroarcade emulators. In fact, ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/CoreBoyIsACrossPlatformGameBoyEmulatorWrittenInCThatEvenDoesASCII.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 06:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memories - SizeCoding</title>
      <link>http://www.sizecoding.org/wiki/Memories</link>
      <description>Hello! My name is "HellMood" and this is not a usual wiki style article. It will be written from my point of view, in first person. This article is all about a tiny MS DOS program called "Memories". This program has a size of 256 bytes and won the "PC 256 byte" competition of the demoscene event "Revision" in 2020, as well as the public choice award. You can watch a video of the output of this program here (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Imquk_3oFf4) and a video including live reactions of online audience and moderators here (https://www.twitch.tv/videos/589179638?t=7h02m40s). You can download the release and comment here (https://www.pouet.net/prod.php?which=85227). This wiki article will give you an indepth analysis of the program and point out historical references as well as development steps. In case you did not notice, you are now on the "sizecoding wiki". This will help you not only to understand the interior of "Memories", but also enable you to produce something like this yourself. Feel free to look around! It is recommended that you start with the basics of this wiki first if you're new to sizecoding and/or x86 assembler. While the principles might be easy to grasp, details of the implementation might not.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.sizecoding.org/wiki/Memories</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 05:09:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Statement of the Seven Bay Area Health Officers on Upcoming Extension and Revisions to the Current Shelter-in-Place Orders</title>
      <link>https://sfmayor.org/article/joint-statement-seven-bay-area-health-officers-upcoming-extension-and-revisions-current</link>
      <description>San Francisco, CA – Later this week, the Public Health Officers of the Counties of Alameda, Contra Costa, Marin, San Francisco, San Mateo, and Santa Clara as well as the City of Berkeley will issue revised shelter-in-place orders that largely keep the current restrictions in place and extend them through May. The new order will include limited easing of specific restrictions</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sfmayor.org/article/joint-statement-seven-bay-area-health-officers-upcoming-extension-and-revisions-current</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 04:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18-1150 Georgia v. Public.Resource.Org, Inc. (04/27/2020)</title>
      <link>https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/19pdf/18-1150_7m58.pdf</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/19pdf/18-1150_7m58.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 04:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed: Twitter Kills Off SMS Notifications &amp; Posting In Most Countries And Deletes SMS Followers Without Providing Any Warning - DansDeals.com</title>
      <link>https://www.dansdeals.com/more/site-announcements/twitter-kills-off-sms-notifications-posting-countries-deletes-sms-followers-without-providing-warning/</link>
      <description>Update, 4/27: Twitter has now officially announced that they are killing off SMS in most countries. The Verge covers the story as well. View alternate options for receiving DansDeals alerts here. We are currently looking into other options for SMS alerts. @jack @Twitter You're contradicting yourself. If SMS is insecure, then why use it for …</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/eleff)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dansdeals.com/more/site-announcements/twitter-kills-off-sms-notifications-posting-countries-deletes-sms-followers-without-providing-warning/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 04:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hey, I'm going to the bear pits tomorrow!</title>
      <link>https://bearpits.ytmnd.com/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (pendragon)</author>
      <guid>https://bearpits.ytmnd.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVIDSafe App Teardown &amp; Panel Discussion</title>
      <link>https://www.eventbrite.com.au/e/covidsafe-app-teardown-panel-discussion-tickets-103754889668</link>
      <description>Join us for a detailed look at the Australian COVIDSafe app with some industry experts.
Agenda:
Troy Hunt : Discusison of privacy &amp; identity - Considerations for people on the fence about using COVIDSafe
Matthew Robbins: Initial App Teardown and Walkthrough
Geoffrey Huntley: Further App Teardown and Comments
Panel discussion:
Chair: Alec Tucker
Panel: Troy Hunt, Matthew Robbins, Geoffrey Huntley
Submit a question for the panel
Speakers:
Troy Hunt LinkedIn Twitter
Troy is a long established security expert and consultant, and author of many training courses on the subject. Troy has previously been called to Congress in the U.S. to advise on web security, and is regularly quoted in international news media when an expert opinion is required.
Matthew Robbins LinkedIn Twitter
An IT guru, app developer, and founder of MFractor, Matthew not only writes apps but has also written tools for app developers, and is a regular speaker at IT conferences and events. His analysis of the COVIDSafe app has been referenced by news organisations, including SBS, ABC and The Age.
Geoffrey Huntley LinkedIn Twitter
Geoffrey is a well respected IT consultant with a skillset spanning multiple tech stacks. In addition to performing his own analysis of the COVIDSafe app, Geoffrey has also been documenting the findings of other experts. Geoffrey is an active open source maintainer, and is a fierce and vocal champion of the open source community.
Alec Tucker LinkedIn Twitter
Alec is an established app developer and founder of Obiquitech. He both speaks and and organises tech community events &amp; converences in Sydney and around the world, covering topics including app development and security.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.eventbrite.com.au/e/covidsafe-app-teardown-panel-discussion-tickets-103754889668</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 02:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's coming in Go 1.15</title>
      <link>https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1veyF0y6Ynr6AFzd9gXi4foaURlgbMxM-tmB4StDrdAM/edit</link>
      <description>What's coming in Go 1.15 Go Remote Fest, 2020 - Daniel Martí</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1veyF0y6Ynr6AFzd9gXi4foaURlgbMxM-tmB4StDrdAM/edit</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query Tags in EF Core for ASP .NET Core 3.1 Web Apps</title>
      <link>https://wakeupandcode.com/query-tags-in-ef-core-for-asp-net-core-3-1-web-apps/</link>
      <description>This is the seventeenth of a new series of posts on ASP .NET Core 3.1 for 2020. In this series, we’ll cover 26 topics over a span of 26 weeks from January through June 2020, titl</description>
      <author> (by Shahed C)</author>
      <guid>https://wakeupandcode.com/query-tags-in-ef-core-for-asp-net-core-3-1-web-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Goes to Eleven (Pt. 4/∞)</title>
      <link>https://bits.houmus.org/2020-02-01/this-goes-to-eleven-pt4</link>
      <description>Decimating Array.Sort with AVX2. I ended up going down the rabbit hole re-implementing array sorting with AVX2 intrinsics. There’s no reason I should go down alone.</description>
      <author> (damageboy)</author>
      <guid>https://bits.houmus.org/2020-02-01/this-goes-to-eleven-pt4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work flow of diagnosing memory performance issues – Part 2 | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/work-flow-of-diagnosing-memory-performance-issues-part-2/</link>
      <description>Work flow of diagnosing memory performance issues – Part 0
Work flow of diagnosing memory performance issues – Part 1
In this blog post I’ll talk a bit about how to spend time wisely and then continue with the analysis. Originally I was going to delve deeper into the GCStats view but I actually just debugged a long suspension issue that I wanted to share 'cause it shows some general ideas of what to do when you hit problems during an analysis.</description>
      <author> (Maoni StephensFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/work-flow-of-diagnosing-memory-performance-issues-part-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 21:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I spent $6 Million On Google Ads Last Year</title>
      <link>https://nicklafferty.com/blog/i-spent-6-million-on-google-ads-last-year-here-s-what-i-learned/</link>
      <description>I spent a lot of money on Google ads last year across Search, Display, Youtube, Discovery, and Gmail. Here's what I learned.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicklafferty.com/blog/i-spent-6-million-on-google-ads-last-year-here-s-what-i-learned/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 21:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>keys.pub - Cryptographic key management, sigchains, user identities, signing, encryption, password manager.</title>
      <link>https://keys.pub/</link>
      <description>Cryptographic key management, saltpack, noise, sigchains, user identities, signing, encryption</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://keys.pub/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 20:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automate multi-container Kubernetes deployments with Azure Pipelines - Learn - Learn</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/deploy-kubernetes/</link>
      <description>Implement a CI/CD pipeline for multiple containers to Kubernetes.</description>
      <author> (tpetchel)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/deploy-kubernetes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 19:06:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building .NET Framework Applications with Github Actions</title>
      <link>https://www.calvinallen.net/building-net-framework-applications-with-github-actions/</link>
      <description>After spending way too much time figuring it all out, I now have a Github Action that can build my .NET Framework web application - and deploy it to Azure!</description>
      <author> (https://www.calvinallen.net/about/)</author>
      <guid>https://www.calvinallen.net/building-net-framework-applications-with-github-actions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 19:06:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Socket Error Codes Depend on Runtime and Operating System - .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/04/27/socket-error-codes-depend-runtime-operating-system/</link>
      <description>This post is the first part of a blog post series that covers different technical challenges that we had to resolve during the migration of the Rider backend process from Mono to .NET Core. By sharing our experiences, we hope … Continue reading →</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/04/27/socket-error-codes-depend-runtime-operating-system/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 18:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Neural Network from Scratch in Python | Fully Connected Feedforward Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b_w4eEiogaE</link>
      <description>In this video we build on last week Multilayer perceptrons to allow for more flexibility in the architecture!


Github: https://github.com/yacineMahdid/artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning/blob/master/Deep%20Learning%20from%20Scratch%20in%20Python/multi_layer_perceptron.ipynb

Backpropagation from scratch video: https://youtu.be/4shguqlkTDM

Understanding Backpropagation video: https://youtu.be/p_domXuoW60


Music found on Youtube music


Making sure a flexible neural network architecture API isn't too difficult. However, we need to be careful about the layer of abstraction we put in place in order to facilitate the work of the user who want to simply fit and predict. Here we make use of the following three concept: Network, Layer and Neuron. These three components will be composed together to make a fully connected feedforward neural network neural network.

For those who don't know a fully connected feedforward neural network is defined as follows (From Wikipedia):
"A feedforward neural network is an artificial neural network wherein connections between the nodes do not form a cycle. As such, it is different from its descendant: recurrent neural networks.
The feedforward neural network was the first and simplest type of artificial neural network devised. In this network, the information moves in only one direction, forward, from the input nodes, through the hidden nodes (if any) and to the output nodes. There are no cycles or loops in the network."



If you have any questions feel free to drop a question down below!</description>
      <author> (CodeThisCodeThat)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b_w4eEiogaE</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 18:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling my A/C with a Gameboy · jg</title>
      <link>http://jg.sn.sg/ir/</link>
      <description>Mon, Apr 27, 2020</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://jg.sn.sg/ir/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 18:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life, part 4</title>
      <link>https://ericlippert.com/2020/04/27/life-part-4/</link>
      <description>Code for this episode can be found here. I have not updated the Life algorithm, but I have added a new feature to the client, namely, you can now resize the form and the display box will resize alo…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ericlippert.com/2020/04/27/life-part-4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 17:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twilio Inspire: Building Cloud City Cakes with ASP.NET and Twilio</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/laylacodesit</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> (LaylaCodesIt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/laylacodesit</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 16:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Release</title>
      <link>https://rust-analyzer.github.io/blog/2020/04/20/first-release.html</link>
      <description>I am pleased to announce the first alpha release of rust-analyzer — a new</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rust-analyzer.github.io/blog/2020/04/20/first-release.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 16:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T E X T F I L E S D O T C O M</title>
      <link>http://www.textfiles.com/</link>
      <description>On deeper inspection, of course, this isn't quite the case. What this site
    offers is a glimpse into the history of writers and artists bound by the
    128 characters that the American Standard Code for Information Interchange
    (ASCII) allowed them. The focus is on mid-1980's textfiles and the world
    as it was then, but even these files are sometime retooled 1960s and 1970s
    works, and offshoots of this culture exist to this day.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.textfiles.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 16:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started : Azure App Services : EP01</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AYQjWE84Bjo</link>
      <description>Hey Coders,
Subscribe here - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCetyodKOWGk5H6FoKoFnkZw 
Talk to us on - https://www.twitch.tv/curiousdrive

Like our page - https://www.facebook.com/curiousdrive/
Follow us on - https://twitter.com/curious_drive
Follow us on - https://www.instagram.com/curiousdrive/ 

Make a donation - https://www.paypal.me/curiousdrive
Be a member - https://www.patreon.com/curiousdrive

BookStores Web API Tutorials - https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4WEkbdagHIQVbiTwos0E38VghMJA06OT

Azure SQL Database - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U6dQqYt3H8M

BookStores API - https://bookstoresapi.azurewebsites.net/swagger/index.html

In this Azure tutorial, I am showing how easy it is to deploy your local app to Azure App Service using visual studio.

1. Sign in with Azure Account in Visual Studio
2. Create a new web deploy publish profile
3. Select FREE hosting plan
4. Configure Azure SQL Database
5. Scaling up from the Azure portal
6. Connection Strings

Happy Coding!!!</description>
      <author> (Curious Drive)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AYQjWE84Bjo</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 14:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have You Been Pwned? - Firewalls Don't Stop Dragons Podcast</title>
      <link>http://podcast.firewallsdontstopdragons.com/2020/04/27/have-you-been-pwned/</link>
      <description>Every time there’s a data breach at a company or service where you do business, there’s a chance that the bad guys will reverse...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://podcast.firewallsdontstopdragons.com/2020/04/27/have-you-been-pwned/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 14:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remove certificate pinning for Australia Goverment Covidsafe Android Application</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/x1sec/8251f846a068fdf8d8731dbe37d3a8fa</link>
      <description>Remove certificate pinning for Australia Goverment Covidsafe Android Application - covidsafe-cert-pin.md</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/x1sec/8251f846a068fdf8d8731dbe37d3a8fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 12:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a-Shell</title>
      <link>https://holzschu.github.io/a-Shell_iOS/</link>
      <description>A text-based user interface for a screen-based platform</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://holzschu.github.io/a-Shell_iOS/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 10:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>