<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Why Blog If Nobody Reads It?</title>
      <link>https://andysblog.uk/why-blog-if-nobody-reads-it/</link>
      <description>What&amp;#39;s the point of blogging?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andysblog.uk/why-blog-if-nobody-reads-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 02:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling with PostgreSQL without boiling the ocean</title>
      <link>https://www.shayon.dev/post/2025/40/scaling-with-postgresql-without-boiling-the-ocean/</link>
      <description>Practical scaling strategies for application developers who don&amp;#39;t have a dedicated database team</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.shayon.dev/post/2025/40/scaling-with-postgresql-without-boiling-the-ocean/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using an LLM to revamp my site</title>
      <link>https://devinlogan.org/2025/02/09/jekyll.html</link>
      <description>This is a meandering post about my personal experience using Claude (just the LLM I happened to be casually using already – I have no affiliation and I also didn’t spend any amount of time trying to pick the “best” LLM for my project) to redesign my site and my broader takeaways on using LLMs for technical projects like this.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devinlogan.org/2025/02/09/jekyll.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Regex to migrate from Fluent Assertions to XUnit Assertions</title>
      <link>https://ilovedotnet.org/blogs/using-regex-to-migrate-from-fluent-assertions-to-xunit-assertions/</link>
      <description>In this post I will teach you how to use regular expression to migrate from Fluent Assertions to XUnit Assertions. All with live working demo.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ilovedotnet.org/blogs/using-regex-to-migrate-from-fluent-assertions-to-xunit-assertions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password Math</title>
      <link>https://www.charlespetzold.com/blog/2025/02/Password-Math.html</link>
      <description>A friend from my PC Magazine days recently posted on Facebook a little mathematics anomaly that he encountered while trying to figure out the number of possible passwords under certain conditions. He began with the stipulation that a four-character password had to be constructed from characters from each of four groups: 26 uppercase letters (which I’ll abbreviate as U), 26 lowercase letters (L), 10 numeric digits (N), and 18 special characters (S), for a total of 80.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.charlespetzold.com/blog/2025/02/Password-Math.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixing Europe&amp;#39;s broken patent system.</title>
      <link>https://josef.cn/blog/europe-patent-reform</link>
      <description>How to Fight Innovation&amp;#39;s Silent Killer | High costs, no flexibility, and lost ideas. Here’s how simple reforms can fix it. By Josef Chen</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://josef.cn/blog/europe-patent-reform</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-langs-in-12-months</title>
      <link>https://mode80.github.io/7-langs-in-12-months.html</link>
      <description>I began last year with a goal to really understand machine learning. I feel utterly lucky to be alive at a time when software is taking its first tentative steps into the realm of intelligence, and I want front row seats to this historic event. Once this has occurred, computers will speak my language. But to see it unfold, I must learn to speak theirs...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mode80.github.io/7-langs-in-12-months.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I&amp;#39;ve learned from a year of CTFs</title>
      <link>https://cqql.site/ctf/what_ive_learned.html</link>
      <description>Home</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cqql.site/ctf/what_ive_learned.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting the KIM-1 to talk to my Mac</title>
      <link>https://blog.jgc.org/2025/02/getting-kim-1-to-talk-to-my-mac.html</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve written before about my 1976 KIM-1  and code I wrote  for a similar one long ago. But I hadn&amp;#39;t done much with the KIM-1 and strongly be...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jgc.org/2025/02/getting-kim-1-to-talk-to-my-mac.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Surface-Stable Fractal Dither on Playdate &amp;#183;  Aras&amp;#39; website</title>
      <link>https://aras-p.info/blog/2025/02/09/Surface-Stable-Fractal-Dither-on-Playdate/</link>
      <description>Rune Skovbo Johansen has a really sweet Surface-Stable Fractal Dithering
technique, where the dither dots “stick” to 3D surfaces, yet the dot density adapts to the view distance and zoom
level.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aras-p.info/blog/2025/02/09/Surface-Stable-Fractal-Dither-on-Playdate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://aaron-blog.onrender.com/post/the-age-of-llms</link>
      <description>2/9/20251 mins read</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aaron-blog.onrender.com/post/the-age-of-llms</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I&amp;#39;m Excited About Nostr</title>
      <link>https://mylessnider.com/articles/why-im-excited-about-nostr</link>
      <description>Social media as it was meant to be. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mylessnider.com/articles/why-im-excited-about-nostr</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Cross-Chain Bridge</title>
      <link>https://blog.anirudha.dev/building-a-cross-chain-bridge</link>
      <description>How to build a decentralised asset bridge</description>
      <author> (https://hashnode.com/@anirudha)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.anirudha.dev/building-a-cross-chain-bridge</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let constraints drive consistency</title>
      <link>https://dimamik.com/posts/general/let_constraints_drive_consistency/</link>
      <description>Best practices, derived from my own experience, that help us to enforce data consistency in a large production database (PostgreSQL and Ecto).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dimamik.com/posts/general/let_constraints_drive_consistency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spec-driven Vibe-coding</title>
      <link>https://vivekhaldar.com/articles/spec-driven-vibe-coding/</link>
      <description>Giving a name to an amorphous new thing is a powerful act. And that’s what Karpathy did, via tweet:

There’s a new kind of coding I call “vibe coding”, where you fully give in to the vibes, embrace exponentials, and forget that the code even exists. It’s possible because the LLMs (e.g. Cursor Composer w Sonnet) are getting too good. Also I just talk to Composer with SuperWhisper so I barely even touch the keyboard. I ask for the dumbest things like “decrease the padding on the sidebar by half” because I’m too lazy to find it. I “Accept All” always, I don’t read the diffs anymore. When I get error messages I just copy paste them in with no comment, usually that fixes it. The code grows beyond my usual comprehension, I’d have to really read through it for a while. Sometimes the LLMs can’t fix a bug so I just work around it or ask for random changes until it goes away. It’s not too bad for throwaway weekend projects, but still quite amusing. I’m building a project or webapp, but it’s not really coding - I just see stuff, say stuff, run stuff, and copy paste stuff, and it mostly works.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vivekhaldar.com/articles/spec-driven-vibe-coding/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&amp;#39;s First Fear - its daniel johns</title>
      <link>https://itsdanieljohns.com/blog/openai-first-fear/</link>
      <description>An exploration of how OpenAI’s fear of public perception led to hesitant decisions, branding confusion, and the importance of bold innovation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://itsdanieljohns.com/blog/openai-first-fear/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I code with LLMs these days</title>
      <link>https://www.phillipcarter.dev/posts/coding-with-llms</link>
      <description>Practical tips for developers looking to use AI coding assistants</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.phillipcarter.dev/posts/coding-with-llms</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>computer graphics, mathematics, shaders, fractals, demoscene and more</title>
      <link>https://iquilezles.org/articles/gpuconditionals/</link>
      <description>Tutorials and articles of Inigo Quilez on computer graphics, fractals, demoscene, shaders and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iquilezles.org/articles/gpuconditionals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 21:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping the World with EF Core: Working with Spatial Data - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/mapping-the-world-with-ef-core-working-with-spatial-data/</link>
      <description>Have you ever needed to store coordinates, track locations, or perform distance calculations in your database? Whether you&amp;#39;re building a ride-sharing app, a location-based service, or an interactive map, working with spatial data is essential. Luckily, EF Core supports spatial data types, allowing you to store, query, and manipulate geographic data seamlessly. No more treating latitude and longitude as simple numbers—let’s bring real GIS (Geographic Information System) power to your EF Core apps!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/mapping-the-world-with-ef-core-working-with-spatial-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 15:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTRODUCTION</title>
      <link>https://thebullshitmachines.com/</link>
      <description>Technologists and publicists gush about how Large Language Models (LLMs) will revolutionize the way we work, learn, play, communicate, create, and connect to another.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thebullshitmachines.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 14:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - xajik/thedeck: The Deck: An Open-Source, Cross-Platform, Mobile, Turn by Turn Card Game Engine in Flutter</title>
      <link>https://github.com/xajik/thedeck</link>
      <description>The Deck: An Open-Source, Cross-Platform, Mobile, Turn by Turn Card Game Engine in Flutter - xajik/thedeck</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/xajik/thedeck</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 07:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI App Builders - Take 1 - Nick&amp;#39;s .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/ai-app-builders-take-1/</link>
      <description>I figured I’d take some of these AI app builders for a run to see how capable they are. To date I’ve mainly just been taking advantage of the AI capabilities that are progressively being added to VS Code and Visual Studio though tooling such as Copilot but I’m hoping that these AI app builders, ... Read more</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/ai-app-builders-take-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 07:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>