<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Forgot that connection string? Get it here!</title>
      <link>https://www.connectionstrings.com/</link>
      <description>All connection strings in one place. Find the syntax for your database connection using ADO.NET, ADO, ODBC, OLEDB, C#, VB, VB.NET, ASP.NET and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.connectionstrings.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 21:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From engineer to manager: what I love, what I hate</title>
      <link>https://thoughtspile.github.io/2024/02/16/eng-to-em/</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s been almost 2 years since I moved to a team lead role, then to a full-time engineering management position after the expansion of our team. I&amp;#39;ve been a front-end developer for 7 years before that, and initially I took the &amp;quot;advanced individual contributor&amp;quot; career track before doing the management turnaround. How&amp;#39;s it been? Bumpy, but fun. In this article, I&amp;#39;ll share the things I love and hate about my current job.</description>
      <author> (Vladimir Klepov)</author>
      <guid>https://thoughtspile.github.io/2024/02/16/eng-to-em/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 21:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Unit Test Improvement using Large Language Models at Meta</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2402.09171</link>
      <description>This paper describes Meta&amp;#39;s TestGen-LLM tool, which uses LLMs to automatically improve existing human-written tests. TestGen-LLM verifies that its generated test classes successfully clear a set of filters that assure measurable improvement over the original test suite, thereby eliminating problems due to LLM hallucination. We describe the deployment of TestGen-LLM at Meta test-a-thons for the Instagram and Facebook platforms. In an evaluation on Reels and Stories products for Instagram, 75% of TestGen-LLM&amp;#39;s test cases built correctly, 57% passed reliably, and 25% increased coverage. During Meta&amp;#39;s Instagram and Facebook test-a-thons, it improved 11.5% of all classes to which it was applied, with 73% of its recommendations being accepted for production deployment by Meta software engineers. We believe this is the first report on industrial scale deployment of LLM-generated code backed by such assurances of code improvement.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 14 Feb 2024])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2402.09171</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 18:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REST002: Standardized Provider Abstraction Spikes</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=gCDo24dJ5Fg</link>
      <description>In this session, we will review some of the work The Standard Community has been doing to implement SPAL (Standardized Providers Abstraction Library) for RES...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=gCDo24dJ5Fg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 17:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add AWS CDK support by vlesierse &amp;#183; Pull Request #2225 &amp;#183; dotnet/aspire</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/2225</link>
      <description>This pull request is intended to gather feedback for supporting AWS CDK with Aspire. It is build upon the work @normj is doing for general AWS with CloudFormation support (#1905 Add AWS CloudFormat...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/2225</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 17:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 things you didn’t know you could do with GitHub Copilot</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/2022-09-14-8-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-copilot/</link>
      <description>Developers all over the world are using GitHub Copilot to help speed up their development and increase developer productivity. With GitHub Copilot available to developers everywhere, we’ve found some fun and useful examples of how developers can use GitHub Copilot for things you may not be thinking about.</description>
      <author> (Rizel Scarlett)</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/2022-09-14-8-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-github-copilot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 17:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Aspire Apache Kafka component - .NET Aspire</title>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/aspire/messaging/kafka-component</link>
      <description>Learn how to use the .NET Aspire Apache Kafka client message-broker component.</description>
      <author> (IEvangelist)</author>
      <guid>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/aspire/messaging/kafka-component</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 17:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considerations for a long-running Raspberry Pi # Chris Dzombak</title>
      <link>https://www.dzombak.com/blog/2023/12/Considerations-for-a-long-running-Raspberry-Pi.html</link>
      <description>Keeping a Raspberry Pi online and working with zero intervention for weeks, months, or years is somewhat of an art form. Several classes of things can go wrong, and you need to consider how your Pi will recover from each of them.</description>
      <author> (Chris Dzombak)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dzombak.com/blog/2023/12/Considerations-for-a-long-running-Raspberry-Pi.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 16:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Pro - Exploring Spatial Computing</title>
      <link>https://willem.com/blog/2024-02-16_vision-pro/</link>
      <description>My thoughts on using Vision Pro to get some real work done, exploring what Spatial Computing means and how it can be useful. </description>
      <author> (Willem L. Middelkoop)</author>
      <guid>https://willem.com/blog/2024-02-16_vision-pro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 12:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Check if a String Contains Only Letters in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-check-if-a-string-contains-only-letters/</link>
      <description>We will meet different alternatives to check if a string contains only letters and, also, discuss their benefits and drawbacks.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-check-if-a-string-contains-only-letters/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 09:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexe&amp;#239; Navalny, l’homme qui d&amp;#233;rangeait Vladimir Poutine, est mort</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Rs46A0gQgPc</link>
      <description>Alexe&amp;#239; Navalny, connu pour avoir d&amp;#233;nonc&amp;#233; le r&amp;#233;gime politique et la corruption du gouvernement russe, est mort dans sa colonie p&amp;#233;nitentiaire de l’Arctique rus...</description>
      <author> (LCI
  
  
  
    LCI
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Rs46A0gQgPc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code to Cloud with .NET Aspire</title>
      <link>https://speakerdeck.com/davidfowl/code-to-cloud-with-net-aspire</link>
      <description>In this session, Distinguished Engineer David Fowler and .NET Product Architect Damian Edwards will talk about how .NET 8 makes building cloud-native apps easier than ever, with powerful new features to turbocharge the development experience.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://speakerdeck.com/davidfowl/code-to-cloud-with-net-aspire</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Chests</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2895/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2895/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing project Kiota a client generator for OpenAPI | .NET Conf 2023</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sQ9Pv-rQ1s8</link>
      <description>Integrating your application with APIs by manually implementing authentication, authorization, serialization, error handling and building requests represents...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sQ9Pv-rQ1s8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 03:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular git config options</title>
      <link>https://jvns.ca/blog/2024/02/16/popular-git-config-options/</link>
      <description>Popular git config options</description>
      <author> (Julia Evans)</author>
      <guid>https://jvns.ca/blog/2024/02/16/popular-git-config-options/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 03:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paying people to work on open source is good actually - Jacob Kaplan-Moss</title>
      <link>https://jacobian.org/2024/feb/16/paying-maintainers-is-good/</link>
      <description>If you have a problem with maintainers getting paid then you have a problem with me and I suggest you let that one marinate.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jacobian.org/2024/feb/16/paying-maintainers-is-good/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Scoped Services From Singletons in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/using-scoped-services-from-singletons-in-aspnetcore</link>
      <description>Did you ever need to inject a scoped service into a singleton service? I&amp;#39;ll explain how you can solve this problem and safely use scoped services from within singletons in ASP.NET Core.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/using-scoped-services-from-singletons-in-aspnetcore</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forgejo forks its own path forward</title>
      <link>https://forgejo.org/2024-02-forking-forward/</link>
      <description>Since its inception, Forgejo (a self-hosted git forge, like GitHub) has been a soft fork of Gitea. Upgrading to it was - and for the time being, remains to be - as simple as changing the URL from which the release is downloaded. Over time, the way Forgejo is governed and developed evolved. To be able to provide stable, secure, reliable releases, Forgejo requires a reasonable effort made at writing tests for each change that goes into the code. This has worked out remarkably well, as it caught both regressions in imported code, and mistakes in proposed changes. Furthermore, Forgejo has accepted features and other changes that are not available in Gitea, and has diverged in other ways already.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://forgejo.org/2024-02-forking-forward/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Continuous Profiler: CPU and Wall Time Profiling</title>
      <link>https://www.datadoghq.com/blog/engineering/dotnet-continuous-profiler-part-2/</link>
      <description>How we implemented CPU and wall time profiling in our .NET continuous profiler.</description>
      <author> ( Datadog )</author>
      <guid>https://www.datadoghq.com/blog/engineering/dotnet-continuous-profiler-part-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Unifi under TrueNAS | BSDbox.</title>
      <link>https://bsdbox.de/en/artikel/unifi</link>
      <description>My Grav Site</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bsdbox.de/en/artikel/unifi</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Risk of Dying Doing What We Love - Soaring - Chess in the Air</title>
      <link>https://chessintheair.com/the-risk-of-dying-doing-what-we-love/</link>
      <description>Many of us participate in activities and sports that are at least somewhat dangerous.&amp;#160; However, most of us also do not have a full appreciation of how risky these activities really are, especially compared to other things that we could be doing instead. We just love our favorite pastime and facing up to its risks … Continue reading &amp;quot;The Risk of Dying Doing What We Love&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chessintheair.com/the-risk-of-dying-doing-what-we-love/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Arduino Language Server With Neovim</title>
      <link>https://ncona.com/2024/02/using-arduino-language-server-with-neovim</link>
      <description>In this post we’re going to configure neovim to work with Arduino Language Server.

Nvim Lsp Config

Neovim comes with an LSP client included, nvim-lspconfig is a plugin that helps us configure the client so it can talk to LSP servers.

This configuration should be enough to get started with Arduino:

1
2
3
4
5
6
return {
  </description>
      <author> (ncona.com)</author>
      <guid>https://ncona.com/2024/02/using-arduino-language-server-with-neovim</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dependency solving in Nix</title>
      <link>http://www.chriswarbo.net/projects/nixos/nix_dependencies.html</link>
      <description>I’ve written a lot about the Nix build
system over the past decade, but one complaint I keep coming across
is that Nix requires dependency constraints to be “solved manually”.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.chriswarbo.net/projects/nixos/nix_dependencies.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version Interfaces, Not Implementations | Gavin D. Howard</title>
      <link>https://gavinhoward.com/2024/02/version-interfaces-not-implementations/</link>
      <description>In which I steal the thunder of a smart man and write a blog post for him showing that we should not version implementations, but interfaces.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gavinhoward.com/2024/02/version-interfaces-not-implementations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Shouldn’t Have The Right to Disrupt Your Life</title>
      <link>https://outlookzen.com/2024/02/16/i-shouldnt-have-the-right-to-disrupt-your-life/</link>
      <description>There are protests, and then there are protests. Some protests are peaceful non-disruptive demonstrations. They gather large groups of people in places where they cause minimal disruption to the li…</description>
      <author> (RP)</author>
      <guid>https://outlookzen.com/2024/02/16/i-shouldnt-have-the-right-to-disrupt-your-life/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual vs text based programming, which is better?</title>
      <link>https://successfulsoftware.net/2024/01/16/visual-vs-text-based-programming-which-is-better/</link>
      <description>Visual programming tools (also called ‘no-code’ or ‘low-code’) have been getting a lot of press recently. This, in turn, has generated a lot of discussion about whether visu…</description>
      <author> (by Andy Brice)</author>
      <guid>https://successfulsoftware.net/2024/01/16/visual-vs-text-based-programming-which-is-better/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bisecting Regressions in Fedora Silverblue – Brno Hat</title>
      <link>https://enblog.eischmann.cz/2024/02/15/bisecting-regressions-in-fedora-silverblue/</link>
      <description>I know that some blog posts on this topic have already been published, but nevertheless I have decided to share my real-life experience of bisecting regressions in Fedora Silverblue.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://enblog.eischmann.cz/2024/02/15/bisecting-regressions-in-fedora-silverblue/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Michael Chinen) &amp;#187; Trying Out Stable Cascade Local Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://michaelchinen.com/2024/02/16/trying-out-stable-cascade-local-image-generation-in-jupyter/</link>
      <description>Stability AI released Stable Cascade on GitHub this week.  It’s very open, and allows not only inference on a number of tasks from text prompting to in-painting but also allows training and fine tuning.  It’s a three stage diffusion model, and they also provide pretrained weights you can download.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://michaelchinen.com/2024/02/16/trying-out-stable-cascade-local-image-generation-in-jupyter/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to feel when your startup feels easy</title>
      <link>https://garethdmm.com/how-to-feel-when-your-startup-feels-easy-1c40b0b4210a</link>
      <description>I did something hard once: I took my startup from zero to $1m in daily volume in 4 months. Something has bothered me ever since: it felt…</description>
      <author> (https://garethdmm.com)</author>
      <guid>https://garethdmm.com/how-to-feel-when-your-startup-feels-easy-1c40b0b4210a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You won&amp;#39;t scale</title>
      <link>https://gomakethings.com/you-wont-scale/</link>
      <description>One of the more common myths I try to debunk around vanilla JavaScript and simpler approaches to web development is that they don’t scale (they do, actually).
So I really enjoyed this post on Mastodon from tante…
 You won’t grow to Google/Amazon scale. It’s fine. Just build a simple solution you can maintain.
 I really wish this was the norm in our industry.
I’m thankfully starting to see the pendulum swing back away from overly complex solutions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gomakethings.com/you-wont-scale/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climbing out of the rabbit hole</title>
      <link>https://ystrickler.com/2023/10/09/climbing-out-of-the-rabbit-hole/</link>
      <description>“Climbing out of the rabbit hole” is a private Google Doc circulated to friends sharing Metalabel’s reflections on the crypto scene. We gave permission to those friends to pass al…</description>
      <author> (Yancey Strickler)</author>
      <guid>https://ystrickler.com/2023/10/09/climbing-out-of-the-rabbit-hole/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EffVer: Version your code by the effort required to upgrade</title>
      <link>https://jacobtomlinson.dev/effver/</link>
      <description>Version numbers are hard to get right. Semantic Versioning (SemVer) communicates backward compatibility via version numbers which often lead to a false sense of security and broken promises.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jacobtomlinson.dev/effver/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting hardware for a server</title>
      <link>https://devraza.duckdns.org/blog/server-hardware-selection/</link>
      <description>I see a lot of people worryingly mistaken about what a server needs (specifically, a home server). Some think that a bland and incredibly ignorant &amp;#39;20% budget for CPU, 30% for GPU, and the rest for the rest&amp;#39; plan for selecting hardware is good enough (at least, before choosing specific items) - you can&amp;#39;t exactly be wrong when choosing hardware, but this is very, very far from right.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devraza.duckdns.org/blog/server-hardware-selection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Selfish GPU</title>
      <link>https://davidlaprade.github.io/the-selfish-gpu</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidlaprade.github.io/the-selfish-gpu</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protip: Notes in your zsh prompt</title>
      <link>https://knezevic.ch/posts/zsh-notes/</link>
      <description>I tend to follow good practices. For example, commit certain things in a
particular git branch, that should be re-based of another branch that
tracks the upstream. However, sometimes I just forget that, especially
after not working on that particular code base for a long time, and do a
commit in a wrong branch. Git is forgiving, but I wanted more, I wanted
to avoid making that mistake in the first place.</description>
      <author> (Nikola Knežević)</author>
      <guid>https://knezevic.ch/posts/zsh-notes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>studiolanes blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.studiolanes.com/posts/how-i-got-the-o1</link>
      <description>Tech blog documenting interesting concepts and ideas in technology</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.studiolanes.com/posts/how-i-got-the-o1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making my first open source contribution</title>
      <link>https://jesusarroyo.com/2024/02/16/first-open-source-contribution.html</link>
      <description>Thoughts on open source contributions</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jesusarroyo.com/2024/02/16/first-open-source-contribution.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alternative BigInt ID identifiers for Rails</title>
      <link>https://nts.strzibny.name/alternative-bigint-id-identifiers-rails/</link>
      <description>Rails comes with default BigInt IDs for your primary keys since version 5.1 (replacing regular Int) and offers UUID v4 as an supported alternative since version 6. But what are the alternatives and what to use in your next app?</description>
      <author> (strzibny)</author>
      <guid>https://nts.strzibny.name/alternative-bigint-id-identifiers-rails/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E2EE on the web: is the web really that bad?</title>
      <link>https://emilymstark.com/2024/02/09/e2ee-on-the-web-is-the-web-really-that-bad.html</link>
      <description>In my last blog post, I discussed why people often view the web as a uniquely unsuited platform for implementing end-to-end encryption (E2EE). This view is that the web doesn’t offer a long-term trustable notion of what the application is. In that earlier post, I explored the idea of treating the application as untrustworthy and isolating sensitive data from it. In this post, I’m going to pontificate on whether web applications are truly less trustworthy than native applications, especially in an E2EE setting, and if so, how we should bridge the gap. The gap is narrower than it appears at first glance, especially with desktop applications. To close it, though, the devil is in the (UX- and deployment-related) details.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://emilymstark.com/2024/02/09/e2ee-on-the-web-is-the-web-really-that-bad.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of self-driving</title>
      <link>https://herman.bearblog.dev/the-future-of-self-driving/</link>
      <description>Modern self-driving technology still has a way to go before it becomes generally safe, and useful enough for broader adoption. While I do believe that at som...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://herman.bearblog.dev/the-future-of-self-driving/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 23:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Working From Home Changed My Life</title>
      <link>https://bitofbinary.com/how-working-from-home-changed-my-life/</link>
      <description>In the profession of software development, the transition to remote work has been a significant shift for many, including myself. My journey into the world of working from home began well before COVID-19.
It started as an experiment with flexibility, gradually transforming from a couple of days a week to a full-time remote work setup. This change of course was because of my managers who showed a level of trust in me.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bitofbinary.com/how-working-from-home-changed-my-life/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 22:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>