<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Seven replies to the viral Apple reasoning paper – and why they fall short</title>
      <link>https://garymarcus.substack.com/p/seven-replies-to-the-viral-apple</link>
      <description>Also: another paper that seals the deal</description>
      <guid>https://garymarcus.substack.com/p/seven-replies-to-the-viral-apple</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On technique: what is it and how do you get it? - Robert Howard - Brisbane Woodworker - Classes in Woodworking and Woodcarving</title>
      <link>https://roberthoward.com.au/on-technique-what-is-it-and-how-do-you-get-it/</link>
      <description>I have spent a good part of the past five years* teaching woodwork. As most teachers probably find, I have learnt as much as my students have. In fact, I am moved to say that if you seriously wish to learn, for example, how to cut a better dovetail, the most efficient way to improve yourself is to attempt to teach someone else how to do it. The great thing about teaching is that you are quickly forced to confront a lot of things that you otherwise might easily ignore, avoid or simply be unaware of.</description>
      <guid>https://roberthoward.com.au/on-technique-what-is-it-and-how-do-you-get-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG Anti-Patterns with Skylar Payne - Jason Liu</title>
      <link>https://jxnl.co/writing/2025/06/11/rag-anti-patterns-with-skylar-payne/</link>
      <description>AI Consulting, RAG, and other personal notes.</description>
      <guid>https://jxnl.co/writing/2025/06/11/rag-anti-patterns-with-skylar-payne/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs Your Agile Process Sucks</title>
      <link>https://www.miserablyemployed.com/blogs/rants/7-signs-your-agile-process-sucks</link>
      <description>Congratulations. You’ve adopted Agile. You have daily standups. You’ve plastered Jira with enough tickets to wallpaper your overpriced open office. You’re doing the thing. But here’s the truth: you’re not Agile. You’re not even mildly flexible. You’re just tired—trapped in a Kafkaesque backlog spiral while pretending t</description>
      <guid>https://www.miserablyemployed.com/blogs/rants/7-signs-your-agile-process-sucks</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A2A Is For UI</title>
      <link>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2025/06/14/a2a</link>
      <description>Sat June 14, 2025</description>
      <guid>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2025/06/14/a2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gap Through Which We Praise the Machine</title>
      <link>https://ferd.ca/the-gap-through-which-we-praise-the-machine.html</link>
      <description>My current theory of agentic programming: people are amazing at adapting the tools they're given and totally underestimate the extent to which they do it, and the amount of skill we build doing that is an incidental consequence of how badly the tools are designed.</description>
      <guid>https://ferd.ca/the-gap-through-which-we-praise-the-machine.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust and Procedural Fetishism</title>
      <link>https://ben-mini.com/2025/trust-and-procedural-fetishism</link>
      <description>I recently finished reading Abundance by Ezra Klein and Derek Thompson. The book explains the various missteps taken by the U.S. government that led us to where we are today: a bureaucratic sludge of policies and regulations that’s caused ambitious projects to go over budget (e.g., Healthcare.gov) or remain unfinished (e.g., California High-Speed Rail). Klein and Thompson propose a renaissance of our public institutions- an invigorated era where government “gets out of the way” of itself and executes on projects only it can do.</description>
      <author> (Ben Wallace)</author>
      <guid>https://ben-mini.com/2025/trust-and-procedural-fetishism</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs, Vibe-Coding, and Where I Draw the Line - ordep.dev</title>
      <link>https://ordep.dev/posts/llms</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://ordep.dev/posts/llms</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Analyzed 16,384 Bundle Combinations (And You Should Too) | blog | puruvj.dev</title>
      <link>https://www.puruvj.dev/blog/neodrag-16k-bundle-combos</link>
      <description>How building a modular drag-and-drop library led me to analyze every possible plugin combination and achieve radical bundle size transparency for developers.</description>
      <guid>https://www.puruvj.dev/blog/neodrag-16k-bundle-combos</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One more reason to choose Postgres over MySQL</title>
      <link>https://tanin.nanakorn.com/one-more-reason-to-use-postgres-vs-mysql/</link>
      <description>Almost always, I'd choose Postgres over any database for a new project because it's flexible and support multi-variances of scenarios that may require different performance characteristics.

However, I don't generally feel strongly about MySQL vs. Postgres. Either seems fine.... until I've learned MySQL doesn't support Transactional DDL. Transactional DDL means</description>
      <guid>https://tanin.nanakorn.com/one-more-reason-to-use-postgres-vs-mysql/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Deploy Schema Changes to a Million Databases</title>
      <link>https://turso.tech/blog/how-to-deploy-schema-changes-to-a-million-databases</link>
      <description>Your SaaS application just hit a major milestone. 100,000 active users, each with their own isolated database. You're celebrating until you realise you need to deploy a schema change. What used to be a simple ALTER TABLE now means coordinating migrations across 100,000 separate databases. And if you're building the next big thing, that number could be heading toward millions.</description>
      <guid>https://turso.tech/blog/how-to-deploy-schema-changes-to-a-million-databases</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fujifilm X half: Is it the perfect family camera ?</title>
      <link>https://arslan.io/2025/06/14/fujifilm-x-half-is-it-the-perfect-family-camera/</link>
      <description>When Fujifilm announced the Fujifilm X half, the internet was literally divided into two halves. Some people were disappointed that it offered limited features for its high price, while others were delighted and found it intriguing. In fact, some even predicted that the X half would sell out quickly. 

As</description>
      <guid>https://arslan.io/2025/06/14/fujifilm-x-half-is-it-the-perfect-family-camera/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - yousef-rafat/miniDiffusion: A reimplementation of Stable Diffusion 3.5 in pure PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://github.com/yousef-rafat/miniDiffusion</link>
      <description>A reimplementation of Stable Diffusion 3.5 in pure PyTorch - yousef-rafat/miniDiffusion</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/yousef-rafat/miniDiffusion</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 21:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endometriosis is an incredibly interesting disease</title>
      <link>https://www.owlposting.com/p/endometriosis-is-an-incredibly-interesting</link>
      <description>5k words, 23 minutes reading time</description>
      <guid>https://www.owlposting.com/p/endometriosis-is-an-incredibly-interesting</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debug Distributed Systems in Minutes Using .NET Aspire</title>
      <link>https://juliocasal.com/blog/debug-distributed-systems-in-minutes-using-net-aspire.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://juliocasal.com/blog/debug-distributed-systems-in-minutes-using-net-aspire.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 16:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aim Labs | Echoleak Blogpost</title>
      <link>https://www.aim.security/lp/aim-labs-echoleak-blogpost</link>
      <description>The first weaponizable zero-click attack chain on an AI agent, resulting in the complete compromise of Copilot data integrity</description>
      <guid>https://www.aim.security/lp/aim-labs-echoleak-blogpost</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 15:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fastest way to detect a vowel in a string</title>
      <link>https://austinhenley.com/blog/vowels.html</link>
      <description>Diving into CPython, bytecode, regex, and algorithmic analysis to find the fastest method.</description>
      <guid>https://austinhenley.com/blog/vowels.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 13:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>