<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Subscribe to read | Financial Times</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/b7a21a16-6a1f-11ea-800d-da70cff6e4d3</link>
      <description>News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the worldʼs leading global business publication</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ft.com/content/b7a21a16-6a1f-11ea-800d-da70cff6e4d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpsAI – OpsAI can help you optimize your infrastructure landscape, improve your security and compliance throughout the IT environment, and eliminates wasteful spending.</title>
      <link>https://www.opsai.com/</link>
      <description>The Cloud Automation Platform</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.opsai.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 02:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home - CLOUDEON</title>
      <link>https://www.cloudeon.com/en/</link>
      <description>Cloudeon is a 100% cloud and digital focused company, delivering innovative digital services and cloud technology.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cloudeon.com/en/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 02:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body Camera Once Again Catches An NYPD Officer Planting Drugs In Someone's Car</title>
      <link>https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20200318/19164444128/body-camera-once-again-catches-nypd-officer-planting-drugs-someones-car.shtml</link>
      <description>If at first you don't get punished, plant, plant again.
 
 
 
 When a police officer in Staten Island was caught by his own body camera in the apparent act of planting marijuana in the car of a group of young men, the video evidence against him...</description>
      <author> (Thu, Mar 19th 2020 11:00am —
Tim Cushing)</author>
      <guid>https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20200318/19164444128/body-camera-once-again-catches-nypd-officer-planting-drugs-someones-car.shtml</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 01:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorful Git Prompt for Azure Cloud Shell and Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/azure/colorful-git-prompt-for-azure-cloud-shell-and-visual-studio-code-3oh4</link>
      <description>A brand new Git prompt for Azure Cloud Shell</description>
      <author> (Michael Crump)</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/azure/colorful-git-prompt-for-azure-cloud-shell-and-visual-studio-code-3oh4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 01:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDC Security Australia - Hack Yourself First with Troy Hunt and Scott Helme</title>
      <link>https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ndc-security-australia-hack-yourself-first-with-troy-hunt-and-scott-helme-tickets-99858553622</link>
      <description>NDC Security Australia - Hack Yourself First Workshop (Online):
Troy Hunt and Scott Helme will be running an online Hack Yourself First Workshop with NDC Conferences through Zoom.us. Please note that the workshop hours are 09:00-17:00 and is scheduled in Canberra / Melbourne / Sydney time (AEDT). The 09:00 start is firm on both days, however, other timings in the schedule below can be fluid based on how long the modules are running for. Troy and Scott will be doing an "unplugged" session together over the lunch breaks both days. Questions can be asked by attendees on any topic and Troy and Scott will both be there responding together. In addition to the unplugged sessions, Troy will hang around at the end of day two for a "virtual mingle" where he will discuss whatever the workshop attendees feel like. 
Online workshop ticket is 800 AUD + GST (total 880 AUD).
Course Description:
Cyber-attacks have become a reality of running software on the web today. We find ourselves under a constant barrage of malicious activity from hacktivists, online criminals and increasingly, nation states. Successful attacks from these adversaries are predominantly via flaws in the software products they target – flaws that could have been prevented by developers understanding how online attackers work and what the appropriate defensive measures are.
"Hack Yourself First" is all about building up defensive skills in developers. It looks at security from the attacker's perspective and takes them through the steps necessary to exploit vulnerable software on the web so that they can experience hacking first hand. Workshop participants are set specific goals they must complete that involve probing for risks and then exploiting discrete vulnerabilities in a specially built vulnerable application. The interactive nature of the workshop means that multiple attack vectors are usually identified across the spectrum of participants and each person contributes their own unique perspective as to how specific risks are exploited.
The Objective
The objective of the workshop is that each person walks away with demonstrated experience across a broad spectrum of specific risks. They not only learn about but also demonstrate practical experience across a range of different vulnerabilities targeted to the specific needs of the group.
Courses run for two days on the following schedule:
Day 1
The first day build fundamental security skills that all technology professionals delivering applications on the web should posses:
- Discovering Risks via the Browser- Using an HTTP proxy - XSS- SQL Injection- CSRF - HTTPS- Framework Disclosure 
Day 2
The second day delves deeper into online risks, covering more advanced topics in greater depth:
- Password Cracking- Account Enumeration - FiddlerScript- Content Security Policy- Session Hijacking- Subresource integrity- Brute Force Attacks- Automating Attacks and Review
What attendees learn
Attendees will get taught the mechanics of each of these risks and of course the defensive patterns required to defend against them. But more than that, they get exposed to how to think about security; how to apply it in depth via multiple defences, how to choose appropriate controls based on the specific risk of the feature and how to have the discussion about what makes sense in different circumstances.
Above all though, security is just one factor in delivering working software and it has to be applied appropriately. Sometimes it comes with a trade-off against usability or cost and decisions have to be made about not what's just most secure, but what's in the overall best interests of the product being built. This workshop helps those who attend have the right discussions about when and where to invest in security.
Intended audience
- Software Developers- System Administrators- Testers
This workshop is aimed at any software developer, system admin or tester who wants to get a better understanding what is going on in cyber space if it comes to hacking and cracking of systems. This workshop enables you to take a pro-active approach and you learn how hackers will try to break your system. This workshop will be an eye opener for most attendees and it is the starting point of becoming a better developer. It all starts with awareness and improving your own habits. So start hacking yourself first, to become a better developer!
Required equipment
Attendees will need to use their own computer with one of following software options installed: Fiddler: http://www.telerik.com/download/fiddler Charles Proxy: http://www.charlesproxy.com/download/ Burp Suite: https://portswigger.net/burp/communitydownload
If possible please also bring your smartphone.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ndc-security-australia-hack-yourself-first-with-troy-hunt-and-scott-helme-tickets-99858553622</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iAnimate.net - Online Animation School</title>
      <link>https://ianimate.net/</link>
      <description>iAnimate.net is an online animation school like no other. We offer a complete set of workshops designed to target all your animation needs</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ianimate.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retweeting Twitter Mentions On Demand with Twilio SMS and ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.twilio.com/blog/retweeting-twitter-mentions-on-demand-twilio-sms-asp-net-core-azure</link>
      <description>Programming tutorial demonstrating how to retweet Twitter mentions on demand from SMS messages sent through Twilio Programmable SMS and the Twitter API using an ASP.NET Core app running on an Azure app service.</description>
      <author> (By David Pine
      2020-03-19)</author>
      <guid>https://www.twilio.com/blog/retweeting-twitter-mentions-on-demand-twilio-sms-asp-net-core-azure</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 22:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Mac Dev Setup</title>
      <link>https://arschles.com/blog/my-mac-dev-setup/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Aaron Schlesinger)</author>
      <guid>https://arschles.com/blog/my-mac-dev-setup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>  Is It Time to Rethink Globalized Supply Chains?</title>
      <link>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-it-time-to-rethink-globalized-supply-chains/</link>
      <description>The COVID-19 pandemic underscores why disaster preparedness is vital for supply chain resilience.</description>
      <author> (Willy Shih)</author>
      <guid>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-it-time-to-rethink-globalized-supply-chains/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 19:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Compiler</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRAdsfhKI4OWNOSfS7EUu5GRAVmze1t2y</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Immo Landwerth
      
      

    
      Immo Landwerth
    

    
    
    
  
        •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRAdsfhKI4OWNOSfS7EUu5GRAVmze1t2y</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 18:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beauty of CSS Design</title>
      <link>http://www.csszengarden.com/</link>
      <description>A demonstration of what can be accomplished visually through CSS-based design.</description>
      <author> (Dave Shea)</author>
      <guid>http://www.csszengarden.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 18:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Reasons Why You As a Developer Should Venture Into Machine Learning Today</title>
      <link>https://www.alexanderslotte.com/5-reasons-why-you-as-a-net-developer-should-venture-into-machine-learning-today/</link>
      <description>I’m fortunate enough to occasionally be invited to speak at conferences around the world about what I’m truly passionate about. Having the opportunity to teach machine learning to groups of highly skilled .NET developers is a privilege and one of the most rewarding things I get to do. I often get questions from developers why they should invest time into learning a completely new domain, and why companies shouldn’t just hire “real” Data Scientists. I wanted to take a moment to write down why I think developers in the .NET community should take an interest, a leap of faith if you will, and venture in the world of machine learning.  </description>
      <author> (Alexander Slotte)</author>
      <guid>https://www.alexanderslotte.com/5-reasons-why-you-as-a-net-developer-should-venture-into-machine-learning-today/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 18:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acheve.Authentication.Events 3.1.3</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Acheve.Authentication.Events/</link>
      <description>Achve.Authentication.Events is a nuget package that implements authentication events with detailed log information and description about the event.
      It´s implemented to be used in learning and debug worflows related to the authentication proccess in Asp.Net Core
      For more information see https://github.com/hbiarge/Acheve.Authentication.Events</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Acheve.Authentication.Events/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 16:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Edge Is The Least Private Browser, Study Finds</title>
      <link>https://fossbytes.com/microsoft-edge-is-the-least-private-browser-study-finds/</link>
      <description>The study examined the unique identifiers, as well as information related to typed URLs which can be used to track down users. Microsoft Edge sent identifiers tied to the device hardware. The unique identifiers, which can be used to link apps on the device, remained the same despite re-installing the browser.</description>
      <author> (Charanjeet Singh)</author>
      <guid>https://fossbytes.com/microsoft-edge-is-the-least-private-browser-study-finds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 15:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing F# 5 preview 1 | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-f-5-preview-1/</link>
      <description>We’re excited to announce that F# 5 preview 1 is now available! Here’s how to get it:  Install .NET 5 preview SDK
Install Jupyter Notebooks for .NET  If you’re using Visual Studio on Windows, you’ll need both the .NET 5 preview SDK and Visual Studio Preview installed.</description>
      <author> (Phillip CarterProgram Manager, .NET and LanguagesFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-f-5-preview-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 13:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collections — Google Arts &amp; Culture</title>
      <link>https://artsandculture.google.com/partner?hl=en</link>
      <description>Google Arts &amp; Culture features content from over 1200 leading museums and archives who have partnered with the Google Cultural Institute to bring the world's treasures online.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://artsandculture.google.com/partner?hl=en</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 12:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual ReCode 1.0 Released - Visual ReCode</title>
      <link>https://visualrecode.com/blog/visual-recode-1-0-available/</link>
      <description>Visual ReCode 1.0 is now available with .NET Framework WCF to .NET Core gRPC migration including basic, full-duplex, and session services as well as an API-c...</description>
      <author> (Mark Rendle
            
            @markrendle)</author>
      <guid>https://visualrecode.com/blog/visual-recode-1-0-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 09:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There is a Serious Lack of Corporate Responsibility During Breach Disclosures</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/there-is-a-serious-lack-of-corporate-responsibility-during-breach-disclosures/</link>
      <description>Subject: Data Breach of [your service] Hi, my name is Troy Hunt and I run the ethical data breach notification service known as Have I Been Pwned: https://haveibeenpwned.com People regularly send me data from compromised systems which are being traded amongst individuals who collect breaches. Recently, a collection</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/there-is-a-serious-lack-of-corporate-responsibility-during-breach-disclosures/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 09:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Floppotron: Sweet Dreams</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oGfkPCZYfFw</link>
      <description>Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/floppotron
Donations: https://paypal.me/floppotron
Eurythmics - Sweet Dreams cover by computer hardware orchestra.
Which song would you like to hear next?
Like it? Share it! https://www.facebook.com/floppotron/
More info on how it works: http://silent.org.pl/home/ .</description>
      <author> (Paweł Zadrożniak)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oGfkPCZYfFw</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 09:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lazily resolving services to fix circular dependencies in .NET Core - Thomas Levesque's .NET blog</title>
      <link>https://thomaslevesque.com/2020/03/18/lazily-resolving-services-to-fix-circular-dependencies-in-net-core/</link>
      <description>The problem with circular dependencies When building an application, good design dictates that you should avoid circular dependencies between your services. A circular dependency is when some components depend on each other, directly or indirectly, e.g. A depends on B which depends on C which depends on A: It is generally agreed that this should … Continue reading Lazily resolving services to fix circular dependencies in .NET Core →</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thomaslevesque.com/2020/03/18/lazily-resolving-services-to-fix-circular-dependencies-in-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Chrome releases</title>
      <link>https://blog.chromium.org/2020/03/upcoming-chrome-releases.html</link>
      <description>Cross-posted from the Chrome Releases Blog   Due to adjusted work schedules at this time, we are pausing upcoming Chrome and Chrome OS relea...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.chromium.org/2020/03/upcoming-chrome-releases.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoid In-Memory Databases for Tests</title>
      <link>https://jimmybogard.com/avoid-in-memory-databases-for-tests/</link>
      <description>A controversial GitHub issue came to my attention a couple of weeks ago around ditching the in-memory provider for Entity Framework Core. This seemed like a no-brainer to me - these database providers are far from trivial to maintain, even for in-memory strategies. It's something our teams learned nearly a</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Bogard)</author>
      <guid>https://jimmybogard.com/avoid-in-memory-databases-for-tests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf: Focus On Xamarin is Next Week! | Xamarin Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xamarin/xamarin-conf-one-week-away/</link>
      <description>We are just one week away from the largest Xamarin digital event of the year, .NET Conf: Focus on Xamarin! Join us live for this free event!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/motzcodes)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xamarin/xamarin-conf-one-week-away/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio for Mac: Become a Productivity Pro | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-for-mac-become-a-productivity-pro/</link>
      <description>Despite continued advancement and innovation in the IDE space, the bottom line is that IDEs are a productivity tool. As a software developer, the value of an IDE is directly related to how much using the tool increases your productivity. Subsequently,</description>
      <author> (Cody BeyerSenior Program Manager, Visual Studio for MacFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-for-mac-become-a-productivity-pro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Staging Phase of Deployment - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/sql/database-devops-sql/the-staging-phase-of-deployment/</link>
      <description>Despite some humorous examples of deployments gone wrong, failures are not funny. William Brewer explains why staging is so important and how it can help avoid the types of disasters he recalls in this article.</description>
      <author> (William Brewer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/sql/database-devops-sql/the-staging-phase-of-deployment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Deploy to Azure extension for Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/new-deploy-to-azure-extension-for-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <description>Organizations and teams that adopt DevOps methodologies are consistently seeing improvements in their ability to deliver high-quality code, with faster release cycles, and ultimately achieve higher levels of satisfaction for their own customers, whether they’re internal or external.</description>
      <author> (Pulkit Agarwal
            Senior Program Manager, Microsoft Azure)</author>
      <guid>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/new-deploy-to-azure-extension-for-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using query strings in ASP.NET Core unit tests</title>
      <link>https://gunnarpeipman.com/aspnet-core-unit-test-query-string/</link>
      <description>Using query string in ASP.NET Core unit tests for controller actions that read query parameters directly from HTTP request.</description>
      <author> (Gunnar Peipman)</author>
      <guid>https://gunnarpeipman.com/aspnet-core-unit-test-query-string/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Foundation</title>
      <link>https://dotnetfoundation.org/blog/2020/03/16/net-foundation-february-march-update</link>
      <description>Here's the February/March 2020 .NET Foundation update. Every month, we'll give you a quick overview of the .NET Open Source landscape, including top project news, events, community links and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetfoundation.org/blog/2020/03/16/net-foundation-february-march-update</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 06:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>