<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>We Need To Rewild The Internet&amp;#160; | NOEMA</title>
      <link>https://www.noemamag.com/we-need-to-rewild-the-internet/</link>
      <description>The internet has become an extractive and fragile monoculture. But we can revitalize it using lessons learned by ecologists.</description>
      <author> (Oliver Milman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.noemamag.com/we-need-to-rewild-the-internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 01:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Isolated Azure Durable Functions: Wait for Any Event and Wait for All the Events</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/04/net-isolated-azure-durable-functions_16.html</link>
      <description>.NET, .NET Core, ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/04/net-isolated-azure-durable-functions_16.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Roll Up an Extension Cord: 4 Tangle-Free Methods</title>
      <link>https://www.bobvila.com/articles/how-to-roll-up-an-extension-cord/</link>
      <description>Even if you know how to roll up an extension cord, there are several ways to do the job. One of these cable-wrapping methods may be more ideal for you.</description>
      <author> (Will Briskin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bobvila.com/articles/how-to-roll-up-an-extension-cord/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise, Marginalization &amp;amp; Return of the Niche Internet</title>
      <link>https://kanfa.macbudkowski.com/niche-internet</link>
      <description>Explore the evolution of the Niche Internet, its role in shaping digital communities and content discovery, and its possible future.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kanfa.macbudkowski.com/niche-internet</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120+ Skills I Use in an SRE / Platform / DevOps Developer Position</title>
      <link>https://nickjanetakis.com/blog/120-skills-i-use-in-an-sre-platform-devops-developer-position</link>
      <description>These are technical topics I&amp;#39;ve actively used or thought about for the last 2 years while working in 1 role.</description>
      <author> (Nick Janetakis)</author>
      <guid>https://nickjanetakis.com/blog/120-skills-i-use-in-an-sre-platform-devops-developer-position</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactive Data Security</title>
      <link>https://www.jayeshs.com/p/proactive-data-security</link>
      <description>While data breaches are not new, something significantly changed in 2020.</description>
      <author> (Jayesh Sidhwani)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jayeshs.com/p/proactive-data-security</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java 23: The New Features are Officially Announced</title>
      <link>https://coderoasis.com/java-23-new-features/</link>
      <description>The newest version of the Java Development Kit 23 (JDK) has four new features in the newest release. The two major features which are noteworthy so far is the Vector API, a second preview of the Stream Gatherers, and a preview of primitive types in patterns – such as instanceof and</description>
      <author> (ExiledTech

Apr 16, 2024
• 6 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://coderoasis.com/java-23-new-features/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The origin story</title>
      <link>https://xmit.dev/posts/origin/</link>
      <description>Host static sites. Sounds trivial, right?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xmit.dev/posts/origin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with perlimports</title>
      <link>https://www.olafalders.com/2024/04/15/getting-started-with-perlimports/</link>
      <description>Improve code quality and dependency management with perlimports</description>
      <author> (Olaf Alders)</author>
      <guid>https://www.olafalders.com/2024/04/15/getting-started-with-perlimports/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Arsenic-in-Rice Scare – 5 years on — Dr Leila Masson</title>
      <link>https://www.drleilamasson.com/blog/removing-arsenic-in-rice-and-reversing-damage</link>
      <description>Exactly 5 years ago the FDA published a report about arsenic in rice. New laboratory testing methods had allowed them to differentiate between organic and inorganic arsenic. Inorganic is more toxic and this Arsenic in Rice was found in dangerous concentrations. The FDA proposed a limit for infant ri</description>
      <author> (Dec 1
            
            Written By Dr Leila Masson M.D., MPH, DTMH, FRACP, FACNEM)</author>
      <guid>https://www.drleilamasson.com/blog/removing-arsenic-in-rice-and-reversing-damage</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On maxing out credit cards and magic money trees</title>
      <link>https://mainlymacro.blogspot.com/2024/03/on-maxing-out-credit-cards-and-magic.html</link>
      <description>&amp;#160; “When you repeat a lie, you spread it.   When you spread a lie, you strengthen it.   When you strengthen a lie, you become an accomplice t...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mainlymacro.blogspot.com/2024/03/on-maxing-out-credit-cards-and-magic.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardest Problem in Computer Science: Centering Things</title>
      <link>https://tonsky.me/blog/centering/</link>
      <description>Somehow we forgot how to center rectangles and must find our way back</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/nikitonsky)</author>
      <guid>https://tonsky.me/blog/centering/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Reaction to Reflection</title>
      <link>https://urth.blog/2024/04/15/from-reaction-to-reflection/</link>
      <description>How to navigate thoughts and feelings for meaningful relationships.</description>
      <author> (Urth)</author>
      <guid>https://urth.blog/2024/04/15/from-reaction-to-reflection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timothy Delille</title>
      <link>https://timothydelille.com/notes/the-game-theory-behind-stock-based-comp</link>
      <description>Personal Website</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://timothydelille.com/notes/the-game-theory-behind-stock-based-comp</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Attention All You Need?</title>
      <link>https://www.mackenziemorehead.com/is-attention-all-you-need/</link>
      <description>Given the ease with which Transformers generalize, scale, and their efficiency on existing hardware, they have become the dominant architecture over the last ~7 years, achieving SoTA in most applications. That’s more true now than ever given that most of the researchers and developers are working on them, all</description>
      <author> (Mackenzie Morehead)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mackenziemorehead.com/is-attention-all-you-need/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to create a Stanford course</title>
      <link>https://saligrama.io/blog/post/infracourse-how-to-setup/</link>
      <description>This is the first post in a three-part retrospective on teaching CS 40.
Last quarter (Winter 2024), Cody Ho and I taught CS 40 Cloud Infrastructure and Scalable Application Deployment at Stanford, a new course we’d been working on creating for nearly a year. CS 40 is Stanford’s first-ever hands-on intro cloud computing course, and with 50 students enrolled, achieving our instructional goals of leaving students with a robust understanding of the material was no easy feat.
Wrapping up the quarter, I’m thrilled with how the course turned out, even given how hectic it was at times. This post is a retrospective on the process of designing the course, getting it approved, and building out course content before the start of the quarter.</description>
      <author> (Aditya Saligrama)</author>
      <guid>https://saligrama.io/blog/post/infracourse-how-to-setup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice is (mostly) a Bad UI</title>
      <link>https://shubhamjain.co/2024/04/16/voice-is-bad-ui/</link>
      <description>
Humane&amp;#39;s AI Pin is in the news and unsurprisingly, it&amp;#39;s been universally [panned by reviewers](https://twitter.com/MKBHD/status/1779641280110161957). I don&amp;#39;t have anything to add there. I appreciate the courage to invent a new paradigm, but there are no excuses for shipping something so pointless after raising hundreds of millions. 

What I want to discuss is voice as an interface. 

Movies like Her have led us to believe that voice is the ultimate user interface. Why bother with a keyboard and mouse, when you can just &amp;quot;talk it out.&amp;quot; Just a few days ago, I heard about a talk where someone was claiming that it&amp;#39;s only a matter of time before every app becomes a voice interface that uses AI agents to accomplish tasks. 

I can&amp;#39;t help but think that these assumptions carry only a surface-level understanding of the human mind.

Of course, voice as input is nowhere near as polished today, but let&amp;#39;s assume it does become so in the near future. Is Voice poised to take over as the universal interface? I don&amp;#39;t believe that for many reasons. 

1. **Voice is inherently incapable of representing abstract thoughts:** When we use tools we heavily use our subconscious mind and abstract thoughts. For eg, writing and researching. Both of these activities heavily use those abilities. I won&amp;#39;t be able to finish any article if I have to narrate everything. That&amp;#39;s because while sometimes I have sentences fully formed in my brain, more often, I only have bits and pieces and I have to take time to string them together. I have to search for the right words, link the right ideas, or find the right research.

    Voice exercises part of the brain that belongs to the &amp;#39;consciousness&amp;#39; category, which limits these capabilities. 

2. **Voice makes quite a few things harder not easier:** Theoretically, saying, &amp;quot;order an Uber to airport&amp;quot; seems like the easiest way to accomplish the task. But is it? What kind of Uber? UberXL, UberGo? There&amp;#39;s a 1.5x surge pricing. Acceptable? Is the pickup point correct? What would be easier, resolving each of those queries through a computer asking questions, or taking a quick look yourself on the app? 

    Another example is food ordering. What would you prefer, going through the menu from tens of restaurants yourself or constantly nudging the AI for the desired option? Technological improvement can only help so much here since users themselves don&amp;#39;t clearly know what you want.

3. **Voice is privacy invading:** Most humans are quite self-conscious and they don&amp;#39;t want to be seen as in public making requests to a computer. Hell, even with friends or a partner, it might get awkward. It&amp;#39;s not just about suspicious requests, people can get paranoid about being judged even for banal ones. Checking messages, for example. This could post questions in mind like: &amp;quot;How frequently this guy wants to check his messages?&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Doesn&amp;#39;t he have anything else to do?&amp;quot;. 

4. **UI is preferable to understand the limits of software**: UI is not a hinderance, it helps us understand the capabilities of software. For eg, Google Maps. Say you want a route that isn&amp;#39;t narrow or bad or a route that takes you through beautiful surroundings. It won&amp;#39;t be able to do that because it doesn&amp;#39;t have that data. Nor, without the UI it&amp;#39;d be easy to discover that you can check the traffic conditions between two locations for a certain departure time.

5. **Users don&amp;#39;t like talking all the time:** Using voice to accomplish simple tasks like setting a timer or an alarm is okay, but to accomplish everything can quickly become annoying. We don&amp;#39;t even realize how many micro-tasks we accomplish throughout the day by familiar interfaces. Checking calendar, emails, messages, browsing. Of course, some of these tasks are a way to kill time, but killing time, too, is an important part of our culture, which isn&amp;#39;t going anywhere.

6. **Voice can&amp;#39;t resolve real-world ambiguities:** There can be tons of ambiguities in an instruction that can&amp;#39;t be easily resolved by a voice-only interface. For example, say you want to sell 500 shares of a certain company, which amounts to 50% of your holdings. But, it was a mistaken assumption, 500 shares represent 100% of your holdings. AI won&amp;#39;t be able to sense what you want to accomplish because it can&amp;#39;t read your brain. 

    Of course, you can make the same mistake on UI, but it would be more difficult since there&amp;#39;s visual feedback about your action. An audio confirmation prompt won&amp;#39;t be that effective as it&amp;#39;s not easy to visualize the numbers in your head.

------------------------------------------

Overall, I am not convinced Voice is the future. There are too many inherent problems in not having a screen you can interact with. And even if you add a screen, Voice makes it harder to achieve many things that can be done more easily with a better UI. I don&amp;#39;t think, even if AI was perfectly capable of understanding human voice and had zero latency, we would reach a future that Humane is envisioning. 

</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shubhamjain.co/2024/04/16/voice-is-bad-ui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLite on Rails | Fractaled Mind</title>
      <link>https://fractaledmind.github.io/2024/04/15/sqlite-on-rails-the-how-and-why-of-optimal-performance/</link>
      <description>This is my personal site, where I write about Ruby, programming, and any of my varied fascinations.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fractaledmind.github.io/2024/04/15/sqlite-on-rails-the-how-and-why-of-optimal-performance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic tabstops - a better way to indent and align code</title>
      <link>https://nick-gravgaard.com/elastic-tabstops/</link>
      <description>Elastic tabstops - a better way to indent and align code</description>
      <author> (Nick Gravgaard)</author>
      <guid>https://nick-gravgaard.com/elastic-tabstops/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;Open Source&amp;quot; Startups - Wayde Gilliam</title>
      <link>https://waydegilliam.com/open-source-startups.html</link>
      <description>In the last couple years there&amp;#39;s been a noticeable increase in startups promoting themselves as being “open source”.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://waydegilliam.com/open-source-startups.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a weather data warehouse part I: Loading a trillion rows of weather data into TimescaleDB</title>
      <link>https://aliramadhan.me/2024/03/31/trillion-rows.html</link>
      <description>Building a weather data warehouse part I: Loading a trillion rows of weather data into TimescaleDB</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aliramadhan.me/2024/03/31/trillion-rows.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build &amp;amp; test resilient apps in .NET with Dev Proxy - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/build-test-resilient-apps-dotnet-dev-proxy/</link>
      <description>Learn how to build and test resilient apps in .NET with Dev Proxy to simulate API failures, different network conditions, and a lot more from your local machine.</description>
      <author> (Waldek Mastykarz)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/build-test-resilient-apps-dotnet-dev-proxy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubious security vulnerability: Program allows its output to be exfiltrated - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240416-00/?p=109668</link>
      <description>Once the output is generated, the program can&amp;#39;t control where it goes.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240416-00/?p=109668</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In search of the Ballmer Peak, and other results from SIGBOVIK 2024 - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240416-01/?p=109672</link>
      <description>Continuing studies in silliness.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240416-01/?p=109672</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is a teenager</title>
      <link>https://pudding.cool/2024/03/teenagers/</link>
      <description>Watch hundreds of teenagers grow up into adults – and see how their lives turn out</description>
      <author> (The Pudding)</author>
      <guid>https://pudding.cool/2024/03/teenagers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you Really Want to Be a Development Team Leader?</title>
      <link>https://ezalii.substack.com/p/do-you-really-want-to-be-a-development</link>
      <description>Ask any up and coming developer what they would like to do in the next year or so and you&amp;#39;ll invariably hear, I&amp;#39;d like to become a Development Team Leader Hopefully most will have actually considered the change of role and be looking for new challenges and ways to contribute more to their chosen profession. However, for some this is an automatic response to a question that is particularly difficult to answer in an industry with no clear career path. For others it&amp;#39;s simply a way to move up the pay scale.</description>
      <author> (Tom Jordell)</author>
      <guid>https://ezalii.substack.com/p/do-you-really-want-to-be-a-development</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ObservableRangeCollection in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/vhugogarcia/observablerangecollection-in-net-maui-k9j</link>
      <description>ObservableRangeCollection is a versatile data structure in C# that offers seamless handling of...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/vhugogarcia/observablerangecollection-in-net-maui-k9j</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hangfire: A Feature-Rich Approach to Task Scheduling in .NET</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/hangfire-feature-rich-approach-task-scheduling-net/</link>
      <description>In the vast landscape of .NET scheduling libraries, Hangfire stands tall as a formidable competitor.


We&amp;#39;ve previously explored the powerful Quartz library in our last article:


From Theory to Practice: Implementing Robust Task Scheduling with Quartz.NETTask scheduling is a backbone feature in modern software development, enabling applications to execute</description>
      <author> (Jonathan Roellinger)</author>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/hangfire-feature-rich-approach-task-scheduling-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 Map Happenings that Rocked our World: Part&amp;#160;9</title>
      <link>https://maphappenings.com/2024/04/11/story-of-etak/</link>
      <description>The Map Happenings series on the hugely impactful events that forever changed our world. This week: the story of a little known company called ‘Etak’. I think you’ll find it a fas…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://maphappenings.com/2024/04/11/story-of-etak/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code It Any Way You Want: Checking Strings for Null</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/04/16/code-it-any-way-you-want-checking-strings-for-null/</link>
      <description>The article discusses best practices for checking strings for null in coding. It outlines three common methods: using == null, is null, or string.IsNullOrEmpty().</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/04/16/code-it-any-way-you-want-checking-strings-for-null/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XZ Utils review notes</title>
      <link>https://tukaani.org/xz-backdoor/review.html</link>
      <description>Trivial commits like updates to THANKS or typo fixes in comments
aren’t mentioned here.</description>
      <author> (Lasse Collin)</author>
      <guid>https://tukaani.org/xz-backdoor/review.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Isolated Azure Durable Functions: Specifying SubOrchestrator Instance Id</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/04/net-isolated-azure-durable-functions.html</link>
      <description>.NET, .NET Core, ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/04/net-isolated-azure-durable-functions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cool Guide to Software Development</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/coolguides/comments/1c4mzes/a_cool_guide_to_software_development/</link>
      <description>Posted in r/coolguides by u/Gooflucky • 1,283 points and 58 comments</description>
      <author> (Gooflucky)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/coolguides/comments/1c4mzes/a_cool_guide_to_software_development/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 08:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Anomaly Detection Using a Neural Autoencoder with C# -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/Articles/2024/04/15/data-anomaly-detection.aspx</link>
      <description>Dr. James McCaffrey of Microsoft Research tackles the process of examining a set of source data to find data items that are different in some way from the majority of the source items.</description>
      <author> (By James McCaffrey04/15/2024)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/Articles/2024/04/15/data-anomaly-detection.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Monoliths and the “Critter Stack”</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/04/15/modular-monoliths-and-the-critter-stack/</link>
      <description>JasperFx Software is open for business and offering consulting services (like helping you craft modular monolith strategies!) and support contracts for both Marten and Wolverine so you know you can…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/04/15/modular-monoliths-and-the-critter-stack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake draft sorting in SQL Server, part 2 - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/databases/sql-server/t-sql-programming-sql-server/snake-draft-sorting-in-sql-server-part-2/</link>
      <description>In my previous post, I showed how to borrow a snake draft concept from fantasy football, or a packing technique from the shipping industry, to distribute</description>
      <author> (Aaron Bertrand)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/databases/sql-server/t-sql-programming-sql-server/snake-draft-sorting-in-sql-server-part-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to build an in-memory Message Bus in TypeScript - Event-Driven.io</title>
      <link>https://event-driven.io/en/inmemory_message_bus_in_typescript/</link>
      <description>Event-Driven by Oskar Dudycz</description>
      <author> (Oskar Dudycz)</author>
      <guid>https://event-driven.io/en/inmemory_message_bus_in_typescript/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New C# Interceptors vs. AOP</title>
      <link>https://mareks-082.medium.com/the-new-c-interceptors-vs-aop-dcbc0d2151a4</link>
      <description>.NET 8 has introduced a new feature called Interceptors — a concept that allows us to rewrite existing code in an intriguing way.</description>
      <author> (https://mareks-082.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://mareks-082.medium.com/the-new-c-interceptors-vs-aop-dcbc0d2151a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implement a secure Blazor Web application using OpenID Connect and security headers</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2024/04/15/implement-a-secure-blazor-web-application-using-openid-connect-and-security-headers/</link>
      <description>This article shows how to implement a secure .NET 8 Blazor Web application using OpenID Connect and security headers with CSP nonces. The NetEscapades.AspNetCore.SecurityHeaders nuget package is us…</description>
      <author> (damienbod)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2024/04/15/implement-a-secure-blazor-web-application-using-openid-connect-and-security-headers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Renovate to update preview versions of NuGet packages</title>
      <link>https://anthonysimmon.com/configure-renovate-update-preview-nuget-packages/</link>
      <description>Renovate doesn&amp;#39;t update preview versions of NuGet packages by default, and your apps might be at risk of using outdated dependencies.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anthonysimmon.com/configure-renovate-update-preview-nuget-packages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services share schema and contract, not class</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/04/15/services-share-schema-and-contract-not-class/</link>
      <description>A reading of the third Don Box tenet, with some commentary.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/04/15/services-share-schema-and-contract-not-class/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing code coverage for a .NET project - G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/computing-code-coverage-for-a-dotnet-project.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to compute code coverage for a .NET project using only the .NET SDK</description>
      <author> (G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/computing-code-coverage-for-a-dotnet-project.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - kevinbentley/Descent3: Descent 3 by Outrage Entertainment</title>
      <link>https://github.com/kevinbentley/Descent3</link>
      <description>Descent 3 by Outrage Entertainment. Contribute to kevinbentley/Descent3 development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (kevinbentley)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/kevinbentley/Descent3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 06:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>