<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Wait Until 8th </title>
      <link>https://www.waituntil8th.org/</link>
      <description>The Wait Until 8th pledge empowers parents to rally together to delay giving children a smartphone until the end of 8th grade.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.waituntil8th.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Essential Tips Every Developer Should Try</title>
      <link>https://malshikay.medium.com/10-essential-tips-every-developer-should-try-0276384c0cb2</link>
      <description>Essential Steps to Elevate Your Development Journey</description>
      <author> (https://malshikay.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://malshikay.medium.com/10-essential-tips-every-developer-should-try-0276384c0cb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To: Formatting the Ancient Hard Drive in a PDP-11</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FOONsywfj-w</link>
      <description>Dave takes you on a trip down Hard Drive memory lane as he shows you how to replace and format the drive in a PDP-11 minicomputer, including getting the drive mounted on RT-11 and RSX-11M.  Free Sample of my Book on the Spectrum: https://amzn.to/3zBinWM

Dave&amp;#39;s Attic - Friday 4PM Podcast - https://www.youtube.com/@UCtb6a_CnmGbSns9G8W2Ny0w 

Follow me for updates!  
Twitter:   @davepl1968 davepl1968
Facebook: fb.com/davepl</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FOONsywfj-w</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform 5.5 - Automated App Packaging, .NET 9 RC2, OpenGL, WebView2 and more</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/5-5/</link>
      <description>Pixel-Perfect Multi-Platform Applications with C# and WinUI for Windows, WebAssembly, iOS, macOS, Android and Linux</description>
      <author> (Uno Platform Team)</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/5-5/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loading State for Images in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/vhugogarcia/loading-state-for-images-in-net-maui-28ng</link>
      <description>Handling the loading state for images can significantly enhance the user experience in any...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/vhugogarcia/loading-state-for-images-in-net-maui-28ng</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Power of GitHub Models in .NET with Semantic Kernel - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/github-ai-models-dotnet-semantic-kernel/</link>
      <description>Explore how to integrate GitHub&amp;#39;s AI models, like GPT, Llama and Phi, into your .NET apps using Microsoft&amp;#39;s Semantic Kernel for intelligent applications</description>
      <author> (Bruno Capuano)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/github-ai-models-dotnet-semantic-kernel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 19:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ref and Out in C#</title>
      <link>https://malshikay.medium.com/ref-and-out-in-c-423c3969eb24</link>
      <description>Understanding the difference between ref and out keywords in C#</description>
      <author> (https://malshikay.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://malshikay.medium.com/ref-and-out-in-c-423c3969eb24</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How One Line of Code Led to Catastrophe:  The Mars Polar Lander</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=9p1amOAn38M</link>
      <description>In December 1999, NASA&amp;#39;s Mars Polar Lander was on a pioneering mission to explore Mars&amp;#39; south pole, aiming to unlock secrets about the planet&amp;#39;s climate and the possibility of water ice beneath its surface. Equipped with cutting-edge technology and years of meticulous planning, the spacecraft represented a significant leap forward in planetary exploration.

But as the lander approached the Martian atmosphere, an unseen flaw lurked within its software—a tiny error buried deep in the code controlling its descent and landing sequence. This subtle glitch caused the lander to misinterpret vibrations from its leg deployment as a confirmation of touchdown while it was still high above the Martian surface. Acting on this false signal, the onboard computer prematurely shut down the descent engines.

With its engines off and no parachute to slow its fall, the Mars Polar Lander plummeted silently to the Red Planet, disappearing without a trace. Back on Earth, engineers and scientists were left in stunned silence, their hopes for groundbreaking discoveries dashed by a single overlooked line of code.

This documentary delves into the intricate world of spacecraft engineering and software development, unraveling how a minor software oversight led to the loss of a $165 million mission. Through expert interviews and detailed analysis, we explore the challenges of designing autonomous systems for space exploration, the critical importance of rigorous testing, and the lessons learned from this poignant failure.

Join us as we journey into the heart of the Mars Polar Lander&amp;#39;s story—a compelling tale of human ambition, technological complexity, and the razor-thin line between triumph and catastrophe in the quest to explore the cosmos.

Free Sample of my Book on the Spectrum: https://amzn.to/3zBinWM

Dave&amp;#39;s Attic - Friday 4PM Podcast - https://www.youtube.com/@UCtb6a_CnmGbSns9G8W2Ny0w 

Follow me for updates!  
Twitter:   @davepl1968 davepl1968
Facebook: fb.com/davepl</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=9p1amOAn38M</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time application with .NET SignalR and Angular #dotnet #csharp #coding #angular</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XCrfa6Kxv74</link>
      <description>We dive into SignalR in .NET 8 combined with Angular to create a real-time shopping list application. I’ll guide you through adding users to SignalR groups and sending notifications for real-time communication between the backend and Angular frontend. Watch as we build seamless, live updates to enhance user experience, allowing instant communication and collaboration within the app.

Perfect for developers looking to integrate real-time functionality into their projects using SignalR!</description>
      <author> (Remigiusz Zalewski)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XCrfa6Kxv74</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind Your Step (by Step): Chain-of-Thought can Reduce Performance on Tasks where Thinking Makes Humans Worse</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2410.21333</link>
      <description>Chain-of-thought (CoT) prompting has become a widely used strategy for working with large language and multimodal models. While CoT has been shown to improve performance across many tasks, determining the settings in which it is effective remains an ongoing effort. In particular, it is still an open question in what settings CoT systematically reduces model performance. In this paper, we seek to identify the characteristics of tasks where CoT reduces performance by drawing inspiration from cognitive psychology, looking at cases where (i) verbal thinking or deliberation hurts performance in humans, and (ii) the constraints governing human performance generalize to language models. Three such cases are implicit statistical learning, visual recognition, and classifying with patterns containing exceptions. In extensive experiments across all three settings, we find that a diverse collection of state-of-the-art models exhibit significant drop-offs in performance (e.g., up to 36.3% absolute accuracy for OpenAI o1-preview compared to GPT-4o) when using inference-time reasoning compared to zero-shot counterparts. We also identify three tasks that satisfy condition (i) but not (ii), and find that while verbal thinking reduces human performance in these tasks, CoT retains or increases model performance. Overall, our results show that while there is not an exact parallel between the cognitive processes of models and those of humans, considering cases where thinking has negative consequences for human performance can help us identify settings where it negatively impacts models. By connecting the literature on human deliberation with evaluations of CoT, we offer a new tool that can be used in understanding the impact of prompt choices and inference-time reasoning.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 27 Oct 2024])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2410.21333</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Use Case of Action #dotnet</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=uagqOqjt7YY</link>
      <description>Here&amp;#39;s a practical use case of the Action class in #csharp</description>
      <author> (Codewrinkles)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=uagqOqjt7YY</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Pizza 2022</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ASMgd-sVw0s</link>
      <description>It was a freudian slip... but now, its a thing #shorts

https://www.twitch.tv/csharpfritz</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ASMgd-sVw0s</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 03:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>