<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - brianmg/voynich-nlp-analysis</title>
      <link>https://github.com/brianmg/voynich-nlp-analysis</link>
      <description>Contribute to brianmg/voynich-nlp-analysis development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/brianmg/voynich-nlp-analysis</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on Software Engineering Handbook</title>
      <link>https://yusufaytas.com/reflecting-on-software-engineering-handbook/</link>
      <description>A brutally honest postmortem on why software engineering handbook sales flopped, marketing misfired, and the unexpected lessons learned.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/yusufaytas)</author>
      <guid>https://yusufaytas.com/reflecting-on-software-engineering-handbook/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM text chat is everywhere. Who’s optimizing its UX?</title>
      <link>https://xenodium.com/llm-text-chat-is-everywhere-whos-optimizing-ux</link>
      <description>When it comes to programming LLM tools, I've seen modes of interaction in the form of code completion, patch application, improvement suggestions, and...</description>
      <guid>https://xenodium.com/llm-text-chat-is-everywhere-whos-optimizing-ux</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why We Think</title>
      <link>https://lilianweng.github.io/posts/2025-05-01-thinking/</link>
      <description>Special thanks to John Schulman for a lot of super valuable feedback and direct edits on this post.
Test time compute (Graves et al. 2016, Ling, et al. 2017, Cobbe et al. 2021) and Chain-of-thought (CoT) (Wei et al. 2022, Nye et al. 2021), have led to significant improvements in model performance, while raising many research questions. This post aims to review recent developments in how to effectively use test-time compute (i.e. “thinking time”) and why it helps.</description>
      <guid>https://lilianweng.github.io/posts/2025-05-01-thinking/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Yelled My MVP Idea and Got a FastAPI Backend in 3 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://rafaelviana.com/posts/yell-to-code</link>
      <description>I build tools to fix my own life — then write about the code, the crashes, and what actually worked.
No growth hacks. No platitudes. Just experiments, LLMs, and digital duct tape.</description>
      <guid>https://rafaelviana.com/posts/yell-to-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Every Generation Thinks It’s the Last One to Feel Real Life</title>
      <link>https://www.clickworlddaily.com/2025/05/why-every-generation-thinks-its-last.html</link>
      <description>This post contains affiliate links Memory plays tricks, but maybe the truth is deeper than that. The boy stares at an old VHS tape like it’s...</description>
      <guid>https://www.clickworlddaily.com/2025/05/why-every-generation-thinks-its-last.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You should not write library style code! (probably) – Wilsons Blog</title>
      <link>https://wilsoniumite.com/2025/05/17/you-should-not-write-library-code-probably/</link>
      <description>When I really got into writing code (big projects, or for work), I really started using libraries. For so many problems, there was already a library that would help me with it. From doing maths fast with numpy to padding strings with left-pad, there was almost always a library that could help. Even now half the time you want to integrate your app with some other application it ships its API as a small library of useful functions. As much as I do like writing code to solve difficult problems, the project manager in my head is telling me “don’t reinvent the wheel”, so naturally I use a lot of libraries.</description>
      <guid>https://wilsoniumite.com/2025/05/17/you-should-not-write-library-code-probably/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RxJourney</title>
      <link>https://www.rxjourney.net/the-butterfly-effect</link>
      <description>The Journey of an Intern Pharmacist</description>
      <guid>https://www.rxjourney.net/the-butterfly-effect</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does the end of mathematics look like?</title>
      <link>https://www.awanderingmind.blog/posts/2025-05-18-what-does-the-end-of-mathematics-look-like.html</link>
      <description>A blog containing essays, of varying cogency, about various things that my mind have wandered to.</description>
      <guid>https://www.awanderingmind.blog/posts/2025-05-18-what-does-the-end-of-mathematics-look-like.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Type Patterns - The Duplicate duck</title>
      <link>https://www.schneems.com/2025/05/07/bad-type-patterns-the-duplicate-duck/</link>
      <description>Why aren’t people writing more types? Perhaps it’s because the intermediate and expert developers deleted the patterns that didn’t work and left no trace for...</description>
      <guid>https://www.schneems.com/2025/05/07/bad-type-patterns-the-duplicate-duck/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Recursion · Choly's Blog</title>
      <link>https://choly.ca/post/agent-recursion/</link>
      <description>Sun, May 18, 2025</description>
      <guid>https://choly.ca/post/agent-recursion/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What would happen if I blocked big search?</title>
      <link>https://www.lkhrs.com/blog/2025/blocking-big-search/</link>
      <description>The major search engines are showing slop summaries first and websites second. They link to sites sometimes, but they’d much prefer searchers stay on the results page and ask followup questions. Engagement numbers and all that.
These companies run mass content scraping campaigns to train their own slop models and provide servers to other slop companies in the same data centers their crawlers operate from. Every word I’ve thrown into this illustrious publication—the reading of which a total of five people have, at various times, expressed mild enjoyment—has been both silently and explicitly declared fair game by the slop companies. The only positive thing I can egotistically hope to grasp about this development is that a distant and diluted abstraction of my words and thoughts could be subtly influencing the thoughts and decisions of people around the world—the same way a pinch of salt would affect the flavor profile of a large vat at the soup factory, or like the breeze under the wings of chaos theory’s cute and frighteningly powerful butterfly mascot.</description>
      <author> (Luke Harris)</author>
      <guid>https://www.lkhrs.com/blog/2025/blocking-big-search/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building my childhood dream PC</title>
      <link>https://fabiensanglard.net/2168/</link>
      <description>May 1, 2025</description>
      <guid>https://fabiensanglard.net/2168/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage your SQL Server database lifecycle with .NET Aspire and the SQL Database Projects hosting extension</title>
      <link>https://erikej.github.io/sql/dacfx/aspire/2025/05/18/sql-aspire-dacfx.html</link>
      <description>.NET Aspire provides tools, templates, and packages to help you build observable, production-ready apps. Delivered through NuGet packages, .NET Aspire simplifies common challenges in modern app development. Today's apps often rely on multiple services like databases, messaging, and caching, many supported by .NET Aspire Integrations, including community extensions in the .NET Aspire Community Toolkit.</description>
      <guid>https://erikej.github.io/sql/dacfx/aspire/2025/05/18/sql-aspire-dacfx.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 18:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spaced Repetition Systems Have Gotten Way Better</title>
      <link>https://domenic.me/fsrs/</link>
      <description>Spaced repetition systems are a well-known way to efficiently learn material. Recent innovations have applied machine learning to greatly improve their scheduling.</description>
      <author> (Domenic Denicola)</author>
      <guid>https://domenic.me/fsrs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 16:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building my childhood dream PC</title>
      <link>https://fabiensanglard.net/2168/index.html</link>
      <description>May 1, 2025</description>
      <guid>https://fabiensanglard.net/2168/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 15:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If nothing is curated, how do we find things?</title>
      <link>https://tadaima.bearblog.dev/if-nothing-is-curated-how-do-we-find-things/</link>
      <description>Bjork is currently promoting a new concert film being released called . She's been releasing new photoshoots and interviews almost every day for the past two...</description>
      <guid>https://tadaima.bearblog.dev/if-nothing-is-curated-how-do-we-find-things/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try AniSora: The Ultimate Anime Video Generation Model</title>
      <link>https://komiko.app/video/AniSora</link>
      <description>Index-AniSora is the most powerful open-source animated video generation model presented by Bilibili. It enables one-click creation of video shots across diverse anime styles including series episodes, Chinese original animations, manga adaptations, VTuber content, anime PVs, mad-style parodies, and more</description>
      <guid>https://komiko.app/video/AniSora</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystical</title>
      <link>https://suberic.net/~dmm/projects/mystical/README.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://suberic.net/~dmm/projects/mystical/README.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O2 VoLTE: locating any customer with a phone call</title>
      <link>https://mastdatabase.co.uk/blog/2025/05/o2-expose-customer-location-call-4g/</link>
      <description>Privacy is dead: For multiple months, any O2 customer has had their location exposed to call initiators without their knowledge.</description>
      <guid>https://mastdatabase.co.uk/blog/2025/05/o2-expose-customer-location-call-4g/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Mario Kart 64" decompilation project reaches 100% completion</title>
      <link>https://gbatemp.net/threads/mario-kart-64-decompilation-project-reaches-100-completion.671104/</link>
      <description>Within the very same week, and in just a span of a few days, we got not one, but two Mario games decompiled, with the first one this week being the very first Gamecube game to get a completed decompilation project with "Mario Party 4", and now another great Mario classic gets a completed...</description>
      <guid>https://gbatemp.net/threads/mario-kart-64-decompilation-project-reaches-100-completion.671104/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 08:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"We would be less confidential than Google" – Proton threatens to quit Switzerland over new surveillance law</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/we-would-be-less-confidential-than-google-proton-threatens-to-quit-switzerland-over-new-surveillance-law</link>
      <description>If passed, new rules would require VPNs and messaging apps to identify and retain users' data</description>
      <guid>https://www.techradar.com/vpn/vpn-privacy-security/we-would-be-less-confidential-than-google-proton-threatens-to-quit-switzerland-over-new-surveillance-law</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>why i don’t want kids - Tasshin</title>
      <link>https://tasshin.com/blog/why-i-dont-want-kids/</link>
      <description>this is an essay about why i, Tasshin Fogleman, do not want kids.</description>
      <guid>https://tasshin.com/blog/why-i-dont-want-kids/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering the Renpho App</title>
      <link>https://neilgaryallen.dev/blog/reverse-engineering-the-renpho-app</link>
      <description>I use Home Assistant to automate my home. This mostly involves turning lights and music on and off but I really like the idea of the dashboard being a sort of hub for my abode.</description>
      <guid>https://neilgaryallen.dev/blog/reverse-engineering-the-renpho-app</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe coding is metaprogramming - foobuzz</title>
      <link>https://blog.valentin.sh/vibe-metacoding/</link>
      <description>I originally wanted to write 2 distinct articles, but realized that they shared the same underlying idea: "Vibe coding", the act of talking to an LLM / LLM-based AI agent to code a full project without writing a line of code manually, is no more than a metaprogramming technique, where a program (the AI agent), produces another program (the code that gets committed). As such, it shares some common characteristics of metaprogramming, notably: 1) The use-case of using metaprogramming when lacking an abstraction. 2) The poor experience of maintaining metaprogramming output when you can't maintain the generator level.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.valentin.sh/vibe-metacoding/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Therapy, part 4: Tending the narrative gardens · Melatonin</title>
      <link>https://melatonin.dev/blog/dev-therapy-part-4-tending-the-narrative-gardens/</link>
      <description>Time to get the story straight.</description>
      <guid>https://melatonin.dev/blog/dev-therapy-part-4-tending-the-narrative-gardens/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pointblank</title>
      <link>https://posit-dev.github.io/pointblank/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://posit-dev.github.io/pointblank/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Would Love to Work With You</title>
      <link>https://robconery.com/life/i-would-love-to-work-with-you/</link>
      <description>Like so many, I was laid off from Microsoft on May 13, 2025. Never good news, but life moves on and I'm still fired up to do fun things with the right group of people.</description>
      <guid>https://robconery.com/life/i-would-love-to-work-with-you/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compiling OCaml to the TI-84+ CE Calculator</title>
      <link>https://farlow.dev/2025/05/17/ocaml-on-calculator</link>
      <description>In this post, I’ll explain how I compiled an OCaml program to run on a TI-84+ CE calculator. 🐪</description>
      <guid>https://farlow.dev/2025/05/17/ocaml-on-calculator</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ingredients of a Productive Monorepo</title>
      <link>https://blog.swgillespie.me/posts/monorepo-ingredients/</link>
      <description>So! Suppose you’re an intrepid engineer in a nascent Developer Productivity
team. Your engineering organization has decided that it wants to
move towards a monorepo. You’ve heard the stories
told of Google, Meta, Uber - each a large technology company with
developer productivity organizations consisting of hundreds of engineers -
and you want to capture some of their magic in a bottle and give it to your
users. You wonder - what work lies ahead of you?</description>
      <guid>https://blog.swgillespie.me/posts/monorepo-ingredients/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>