<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>12 Months of Mandarin</title>
      <link>https://isaak.net/mandarin/</link>
      <description>Estimates for achieving intermediate fluency in Mandarin Chinese range up to spending years and around 4000 total hours (2,200h classroom hours, 1,800 outside). I did it in 1500 hours total and less than a year.[1]






 1. There is a lot of disagreement on language proficiency estimates. They</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://isaak.net/mandarin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 22:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One, a React Framework | Tamagui</title>
      <link>https://onestack.dev/</link>
      <description>One is a React framework focused on simplicity that lets you target both web and native at once with a single Vite plugin.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://onestack.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 21:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting my daily news from a dot matrix printer</title>
      <link>https://aschmelyun.com/blog/getting-my-daily-news-from-a-dot-matrix-printer/</link>
      <description>Instead of doom-scrolling through my phone in the morning, I built an alternative with a Raspberry Pi, a dot matrix printer, and some PHP.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aschmelyun.com/blog/getting-my-daily-news-from-a-dot-matrix-printer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 19:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring .NET MAUI 9: HybridWebView Features</title>
      <link>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/10/04/exploring-dotnet-maui-9-hybridwebview-features/</link>
      <description>.NET MAUI 9 is the next major version of the cross-platform application UI framework. An article detailing the significant features of this version has already been published and can be accessed he…</description>
      <author> (By Vijay Anand E G)</author>
      <guid>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/10/04/exploring-dotnet-maui-9-hybridwebview-features/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Movie Gen</title>
      <link>https://ai.meta.com/research/movie-gen/?_fb_noscript=1</link>
      <description>Meta Movie Gen is our latest research breakthrough that allows you to use simple text inputs to create videos and sounds, edit existing videos or transform your personal image into a unique video.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ai.meta.com/research/movie-gen/?_fb_noscript=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 15:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartographist</title>
      <link>https://szymonkaliski.com/projects/cartographist/</link>
      <description>Web Browser Optimized for Rabbit-Holing</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://szymonkaliski.com/projects/cartographist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Dennard, DRAM Pioneer, Dies at 91</title>
      <link>https://spectrum.ieee.org/in-memoriam-oct-2024</link>
      <description>IEEE also remembers the lives and legacies of other members</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/48576411181)</author>
      <guid>https://spectrum.ieee.org/in-memoriam-oct-2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 10:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Recommits to Hybrid Work Schedule Unlike Amazon | Entrepreneur</title>
      <link>https://www.entrepreneur.com/business-news/google-recommits-to-hybrid-work-schedule-unlike-amazon/480683</link>
      <description>Google won&amp;#39;t be mandating a five-day-a-week return-to-office plan. Employees at the tech giant were concerned about losing their hybrid work schedule after Amazon mandated staff to return to the office five days a week. </description>
      <author> (Erin Davis)</author>
      <guid>https://www.entrepreneur.com/business-news/google-recommits-to-hybrid-work-schedule-unlike-amazon/480683</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 10:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Were RNNs All We Needed?</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2410.01201</link>
      <description>The scalability limitations of Transformers regarding sequence length have renewed interest in recurrent sequence models that are parallelizable during training. As a result, many novel recurrent architectures, such as S4, Mamba, and Aaren, have been proposed that achieve comparable performance. In this work, we revisit traditional recurrent neural networks (RNNs) from over a decade ago: LSTMs (1997) and GRUs (2014). While these models were slow due to requiring to backpropagate through time (BPTT), we show that by removing their hidden state dependencies from their input, forget, and update gates, LSTMs and GRUs no longer need to BPTT and can be efficiently trained in parallel. Building on this, we introduce minimal versions (minLSTMs and minGRUs) that (1) use significantly fewer parameters than their traditional counterparts and (2) are fully parallelizable during training (175x faster for a sequence of length 512). Lastly, we show that these stripped-down versions of decade-old RNNs match the empirical performance of recent sequence models.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 2 Oct 2024])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2410.01201</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 02:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;lt;/&amp;gt; htmx ~ Why Gumroad Didn&amp;#39;t Choose htmx</title>
      <link>https://htmx.org/essays/why-gumroad-didnt-choose-htmx/</link>
      <description>htmx gives you access to AJAX, CSS Transitions, WebSockets and Server Sent Events directly in HTML, using attributes, so you can build modern user interfaces with the simplicity and power of hypertext

    htmx is small (~14k min.gz’d), dependency-free, extendable, IE11 compatible &amp;amp; has reduced code base sizes by 67% when compared with react</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://htmx.org/essays/why-gumroad-didnt-choose-htmx/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>