<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Use XML Literals in Visual Basic .NET to generate TwiML</title>
      <link>https://swimburger.net/blog/dotnet/use-xml-literals-in-visual-basic-dotnet-to-generate-twiml</link>
      <description>Learn how to generate TwiML instructions to respond to texts and voice calls using XML Literals in Visual Basic .NET and ASP.NET Core Minimal APIs.</description>
      <author> (Niels Swimberghe)</author>
      <guid>https://swimburger.net/blog/dotnet/use-xml-literals-in-visual-basic-dotnet-to-generate-twiml</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 01:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Webhook Plugin: Validate your webhooks with the new webhook plugin for the Twilio CLI</title>
      <link>https://swimburger.net/blog/twilio/announcing-the-webhook-plugin</link>
      <description>Emulate webhook requests to test your Twilio webhook applications using the new webhook plugin for the Twilio CLI.</description>
      <author> (Niels Swimberghe)</author>
      <guid>https://swimburger.net/blog/twilio/announcing-the-webhook-plugin</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 01:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Jargon Web3 expliqu&amp;#233; - Doumer&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://doumer.me/le-jargon-web3-explique/</link>
      <description>Nous avons tous entendu parler du bitcoin, d’Ethereum, de Solana, etc. Mais quand quelqu’un dit&amp;#160;qu’il poss&amp;#232;de un bitcoin, ou il vous dit j’ai retir&amp;#233; mes crypto-monnaies de la blockchain vers mon portefeuille, comment ces crypto-monnaies sont-elles repr&amp;#233;sent&amp;#233;es ? Dans le portefeuille ou la blockchain, comment se fait-il que je puisse avoir un portefeuille pour stocker […]READ MORE</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/DamienDoumer)</author>
      <guid>https://doumer.me/le-jargon-web3-explique/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 23:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web3 Terms Explained (Crypto, Wallet, Blockchain...) - Doumer&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://doumer.me/web3-terms-explained/</link>
      <description>Cryptocurrencies, Wallets, Blockchain... What are these Web3 Terms about ? In this article, I explain each of them</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/DamienDoumer)</author>
      <guid>https://doumer.me/web3-terms-explained/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 23:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Monthly Roundup -  February 2023 - .NET 8 Preview 1, New Visual Studio features, and more!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=LPFE-4nO8e0</link>
      <description>&amp;#128198;Welcome to our February .NET Monthly Roundup with Jon Galloway! In just 3 minutes, Jon breaks down the latest news from the month of February 2023 that .NE...</description>
      <author> (stevensandersonuk
  
  
  
    stevensandersonuk
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=LPFE-4nO8e0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 23:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapping to €600k MRR and getting killed by Shopify. The story of Checkout X. </title>
      <link>https://www.leteyski.com/bootstrapping-to-600k-mrr-and-getting-killed-by-shopify-the-story-of-checkout-x</link>
      <description>I’ve been building websites since I was 10 years old and I’ve started multiple companies along the way. I write about Startups, Shopify, and the entrepreneurship journey.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.leteyski.com/bootstrapping-to-600k-mrr-and-getting-killed-by-shopify-the-story-of-checkout-x</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaprogramming in Lean</title>
      <link>https://lakesare.brick.do/metaprogramming-in-lean-BEwZboNyq9ZO</link>
      <description>A post giving an overview of metaprogramming in Lean. There is of course a book on Metaprogramming in Lean, consider this an introductory chapter that I felt I...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lakesare.brick.do/metaprogramming-in-lean-BEwZboNyq9ZO</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LukeHjo&amp;#39;s Dev Log | All about Windows Optimization | Part 1</title>
      <link>https://dev.lukehjo.tech/part-1-understanding-hardware-performance</link>
      <description>This episode explains the different factors that can affect the performance of a Computer, such as RAM, CPU, and the GPU.</description>
      <author> (Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://dev.lukehjo.tech/part-1-understanding-hardware-performance</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan Your Day</title>
      <link>https://mrcn.ski/plan-your-day/</link>
      <description>Keeping a daily todo-list is really quite sufficient for having a productive life. But recently I’ve added a daily planner to my routine to supplement my task list.</description>
      <author> (Marcin S)</author>
      <guid>https://mrcn.ski/plan-your-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architects, Anti-Patterns, and Organizational Fuckery</title>
      <link>https://charity.wtf/2023/03/09/architects-anti-patterns-and-organizational-fuckery/</link>
      <description>I recently wrote a twitter thread on the proper role of architects, or as I put it, tongue-in-cheek-ily, whether or not architect is a “bullshit role”. It got a LOT of reactions (2.5 we…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://charity.wtf/2023/03/09/architects-anti-patterns-and-organizational-fuckery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mathsteroids on hyperbolic surfaces</title>
      <link>https://www.mscroggs.co.uk/blog/102</link>
      <description>A circle of radius \(r\) on a piece of paper can be thought of as a line through all the points on the paper that are a distance \(r\) from the centre of the circle. The length of this line (ie the circumference) is \(2\pi r\).</description>
      <author> (Matthew Scroggs)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mscroggs.co.uk/blog/102</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rationale behind wardleyToGo</title>
      <link>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2023/03/02/rationale-behind-wardleytogo.html</link>
      <description>wardleyToGo is a library and a language to describe Wardley Maps as code/data. This is the rationale behind this library</description>
      <author> (Olivier Wulveryck)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2023/03/02/rationale-behind-wardleytogo.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local History | JetBrains&amp;#160;Rider</title>
      <link>https://www.jetbrains.com/help/rider/local_history.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jetbrains.com/help/rider/local_history.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What would it be like if Italo Calvino and Sun Tzu explained refactoring?</title>
      <link>https://brainrepo.dev/posts/calvino-sun-tzu-refactoring/</link>
      <description>The day has flown by quickly, and I have a headache. I spent the day refactoring the code. Refactoring is not a simple task - there are many things to keep in mind and many things to discover along the way. Now is the time to relax and reread a beautiful book I read many years ago.
Invisible Cities by Italo Calvino.
</description>
      <author> (Mauro Murru)</author>
      <guid>https://brainrepo.dev/posts/calvino-sun-tzu-refactoring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometry in Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>http://akosiorek.github.io/geometry_in_image_diffusion/</link>
      <description>&amp;lt;!– Generative modeling is as old as machine learning. But until recently, generative models were a bit like neural nets pre-2012 when AlexNet came out. P...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://akosiorek.github.io/geometry_in_image_diffusion/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Chat with GPT-4: The River Riddle</title>
      <link>https://www.bramadams.dev/202303141528/</link>
      <description>Can GPT-4 answer the timeless question: How can you safely transport a lion, cabbage, and goat across a river using a boat that can only carry one item at a time?</description>
      <author> (Bram Adams)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bramadams.dev/202303141528/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How migrate an existing Joomla CMS website to a Django Backend</title>
      <link>https://blog.adonissimo.com/how-we-migrate-a-joomla-based-website-to-a-django-backend-with-90-gb-worth-of-data</link>
      <description>How to migrate database and file from a Joomla site running with more than 90 Gb worth of data and 6000+ registered users with all their information.</description>
      <author> (Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.adonissimo.com/how-we-migrate-a-joomla-based-website-to-a-django-backend-with-90-gb-worth-of-data</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the Things We Do Not Know About SVB - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>https://ritholtz.com/2023/03/do-not-know-svb/</link>
      <description>&amp;#160; The news broke Sunday afternoon that depositors would be made whole and would have full access to their accounts and money today; equity investors in the bank would take their losses and senior management are fired. Whatever is left over (if anything) we’ll go to bondholders as new owners for both Silicon Valley Bank…Read More</description>
      <author> (Barry Ritholtz)</author>
      <guid>https://ritholtz.com/2023/03/do-not-know-svb/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My experiments with doing things daily</title>
      <link>https://www.internetvin.tv/my-experiments-with-doing-things-daily/</link>
      <description>In 2017, I started running experiments to see what happens if I do specific things on a daily basis, and over hundreds of days. All of this started with an experiment in making music for 365 days in a row.

The reason I started doing these experiments is because I</description>
      <author> (internetVin
                
                    Mar 14, 2023
                        • 15 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://www.internetvin.tv/my-experiments-with-doing-things-daily/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLx Compile Time Woes</title>
      <link>https://cosmichorror.dev/posts/speeding-up-sqlx-compile-times/</link>
      <description>A curious case of climbing compile-times</description>
      <author> (Cosmic Horror)</author>
      <guid>https://cosmichorror.dev/posts/speeding-up-sqlx-compile-times/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rewiewing is a Contract</title>
      <link>https://bastian.rieck.me/blog/posts/2023/contract/</link>
      <description>It is a beautiful day outside, but I do not feel my usual chipper self.
Huddled in my robe, juiced up on some tea, I nevertheless start doing my
third emergency review for one of the largest machine learning
conferences. And I am not the only one. A good friend and
colleague of mine is an area chair of this conference; he sounds
defeated when he mentions that even as we are way past the deadline for submitting
reviews, there will be at least a couple of papers that will not
receive more than two reviews. Despite what you think about peer review,
this makes an already-tenuous situation even more random. How did we
arrive at this point?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bastian.rieck.me/blog/posts/2023/contract/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monty Hall explained</title>
      <link>https://www.michalpaszkiewicz.co.uk/blog/montyhallexplained/index.html</link>
      <description>explaining the Monty Hall problem to the disbelievers</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.michalpaszkiewicz.co.uk/blog/montyhallexplained/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonas Hietala: Battling burnout</title>
      <link>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2023/03/14/battling_burnout/</link>
      <description>Once again, I’m finding myself trying to recover from burnout, and after about a year I’m finally feeling more like myself.</description>
      <author> (Jonas Hietala)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2023/03/14/battling_burnout/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Your Technology Stack Doesn&amp;#39;t Matter - Here&amp;#39;s What Does</title>
      <link>https://www.msoftwaredev.com/why-your-technology-stack-doesnt-matter-what-really-does/</link>
      <description>Before choosing a technology stack, focus on understanding the problem you&amp;#39;re trying to solve and what functionality the app needs to have.</description>
      <author> (Clint McMahon)</author>
      <guid>https://www.msoftwaredev.com/why-your-technology-stack-doesnt-matter-what-really-does/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans Are Not Turing Machines</title>
      <link>https://joshmpollock.com/blog/external-reprs-llms/</link>
      <description>One criticism of current LLMs is that they can’t reliably do sophisticated math or logic problems out of the box that humans seem to be capable of. In essence, while humans are Turing-complete, today’s LLMs are not.  But wait… are humans even Turing-complete?    We like to think that humans are great at complex reasoning. But put a person in a blank room with nothing to write on, and they’re getting nowhere fast.  Modern human cognition depends on our abilities to write, diagram, or otherwise externalize thought so that we can communicate ideas to others, or simply extend our own working memory.  Disclosure: Some of the links below are affiliate links. This means that, at zero cost to you, I will earn an affiliate commission if you click through the link and finalize a purchase. I wrote this article without affiliate links in mind.             Turing Machines  A Turing Machine has the following pieces:    a tape   a read/write head for the tape   a finite state machine that controls the read/write head   But have you ever wondered where this model came from? I had never read the Turing’s original paper until I came across some commentary about it in the conclusion to Edwin Hutchins’s book about distribute cognition: “Cognition in the Wild.”        This is the key takeaway: Humans are not Turing Machines. Humans paired with pencil and paper are.  Here’s what Turing has to say about his original formalism [Turing 1936]. He is attempting to formalize the process by which human computers calculate numbers.  Tape = Paper     Computing is normally done by writing certain symbols on paper. We may suppose this paper is divided into squares like a child’s arithmetic book. In elementary arithmetic the two-dimensional character of the paper is sometimes used. But such a use is always avoidable, and I think that it will be agreed that the two-dimensional character of paper is no essential of computation. I assume then that the computation is carried out on one-dimensional paper, i.e. on a tape divided into squares. I shall also suppose that the number of symbols which may be printed is finite. If we were to allow an infinity of symbols, then there would be symbols differing to an arbitrarily small extent.    So the tape in a Turing Machine formalizes the role of paper.  Read/Write Head = Eyes &amp;amp; Hand+Pencil     The behaviour of the computer [the person computing!] at any moment is determined by the symbols which he is observing, and his “state of mind” at that moment. We may suppose that there is a bound B to the number of symbols or squares which the computer can observe at one moment. If he wishes to observe more, he must use successive observations.   So the read/write head formalizes the eyes and hand+pencil of the person computing numbers.  Finite State Machine = Human     We will also suppose that the number of states of mind which need be taken into account is finite. The reasons for this are of the same character as those which restrict the number of symbols. If we admitted an infinity of states of mind, some of them will be “arbitrarily close” and will be confused. Again, the restriction is not one which seriously affects computation, since the use of more complicated states of mind can be avoided by writing more symbols on the tape.   So it is only the finite state machine that formalizes the human themselves.     Daniel C. Dennett summarizes the process Turing seems to have gone through when developing the Turing Machine in “Consciousness Explained:”     He was thinking, self-consciously and introspectively, about just how he, a mathematician, went about solving mathematical problems or performing computations, and he took the important step of trying to break down the sequence of his mental acts into their primitive components. “What do I do” he must have asked himself, “when I perform a computation? Well, first I ask myself which rule applies, and then I apply the rule, and then write down the result, and then I look at the result, and then I ask myself what to do next, and…” Turing was an extraordinarily well-organized thinker, but his stream of consciousness, like yours or mine or James Joyce’s, was no doubt a variegated jumble of images, decisions, hunches, reminders, and so forth, out of which he managed to distill the mathematical essence: the bare-bones, minimal sequence of operations that could accomplish the goals he accomplished in the florid and meandering activities of his conscious mind.   How Did We Get Here?  Why do we tend to equate humans and Turing Machines? Here’s Hutchins’s account of it. I don’t fully agree, but it is a decent summary.     Now, here is what I think happened. It was discovered that it is possible to build machines that can manipulate symbols. The computer is nothing more than an automated symbol manipulator. And through symbol manipulation one can not only do things we think of as intelligent, like solving logical proofs or playing chess; we know for a fact that through symbol manipulation of a certain type it is possible to compute any function that can be explicitly specified. So, in principle, the computer could be an intelligent system. The mechanical computers conceived by Charles Babbage to solve the problem of unreliability in human compilers of mathematical and navigational tables were seen by his admirers to have replaced the brain: “The wondrous pulp and fibre of the brain had been substituted by brass and iron; [Babbage] had taught wheelwork to think” (H. W. Buxton, cited in Swade 1993). Of course, a century later it would be vacuum tubes that created the “electronic brain.”    But something got lost in this move. The origin myths of cognitive science place the seminal insights of Alan Turing in his observations of his own actions….    Originally, the model cognitive system was a person actually doing the manipulation of the symbols with his or her hands and eyes. The mathematician or logician was visually and manually interacting with a material world. A person is interacting with the symbols and that interaction does something computational. This is a case of manual manipulation of symbols.    Notice that when the symbols are in the environment of the human, and the human is manipulating the symbols, the cognitive properties of the human are not the same as the properties of the system that is made up of the human in interaction with these symbols. The properties of the human in interaction with the symbols produce some kind of computation. But that does not mean that that computation is happening inside the person’s head.   LangChain, Bing Chat, and the Near Future of LLMs  Humans plus pencil and paper are Turing Machines.  So why do we expect LLMs, like GPT, to both behave like Turing Machines yet also approximate human intelligence? Because they run on computers? Fair, but (at least right now) we can only grant GPT the power of Turing-completeness by giving it access to external representations like web search, a Python REPL, or a database – the modern equivalents of Turing’s pencil and paper.  This is why I’m bullish in the near-term on solutions like Bing chat and LangChain that provide such external representations.  No doubt, LLMs will get better, more accurate, capable of processing longer and longer conversations. Yet no matter how much better they get, the question of correctness will always linger. How can I trust this piece of code will run? Is this argument consistent? Are these facts correct?  I believe we won’t be able to answer such questions without external representations. Sure, the transformer architecture (or at least variations of it) is Turing complete [P&amp;#233;rez et al. 2019]. However, today’s networks don’t typically use their outputs as Turing tapes unless explicitly guided to do so (think step-by-step). And today’s networks cannot search the internet or emulate a Python REPL in reasonable time and space.  With formal, external representations we can better understand the “variegated jumble” of an LLM’s “mind” and build much more powerful tools that we can interrogate and maybe even verify. As Turing showed us back in 1936, it’s just like giving a human some pencil and paper and letting them write. ❏    Thanks to Geoffrey Litt for reviewing this post. If you enjoyed it, you might also like my friend Ajay’s account of our adventure trying to get Bing chat to recommend Dune.</description>
      <author> (Josh Pollock)</author>
      <guid>https://joshmpollock.com/blog/external-reprs-llms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Electricity Storage</title>
      <link>https://jgkramer.github.io/2023/02/28/Storage.html</link>
      <description>Energy storage – both home-scale and utility-scale – has become more relevant as the use of renewable energy for electricity generation proliferates. It is particularly topical recently, as the Inflation Reduction Act includes tax credits specifically targeting energy storage projects. Energy storage (chemical batteries, pumped hydro storage, gravity-based batteries) transports electrical energy through time, from generation earlier to consumption later. Storage works when the aggregate amount of energy generated is adequate to satisfy aggregate demand, but there is a mismatch in the timing of supply and demand. Some basic fact patterns are: Demand More Variable than Supply. As discussed in previous posts, there is both a daily and a seasonal cycle to electricity usage. If a region’s generation is dominated by traditional base-load type power plants with high and constant generation capacity (nuclear, coal) or are quickly dispatchable (natural gas), there are two basic choices for meeting demand: either have enough generation capacity to cover the peak usage at any time, or marry sub-peak generation with the ability to store energy when demand is below supply and then release it for use when demand exceeds capacity. Supply More Variable through time than Demand. Supply can also be more variable than demand. Solar, for instance, generates electricity only during an 8-14 hour period during the daytime. The daily cycle of electricity usage varies but not this much: there is meaningful demand in the evening and through the night. So a grid with significant solar power will likely need to store daytime-generated energy to be deployed at night. Unplanned Intermittancy. A special case of supply variability: power outages due to storms or maintenance, or unfavorable weather conditions for solar / wind, can cause generation to temporarily fall short of demand. This post will illustrate, using real-world electricity demand data and overly simplistic supply models (with no unplanned outages or weather intermittency) what profile of storage could be useful: how much energy capacity is needed and how frequently it is used. In all cases there will be a real-world question of whether it is more efficient to deploy capital in storage solutions or more generation capacity to compensate. A complete answer to that question is beyond the scope of this post, but my analysis provides some indication of feasibility of different architectures. Here’s a summary: In the constant generation model of traditional generation plants, it appears feasible to use battery storage to substitute for power generation that would cover the last ~10 - 20% of peak demand. Somewhat frustratingly, the strong variability of demand still means that this implies generation capacity that is adequate to supply more than 1.5 times the aggregate energy needs. In a variable generation model like predominantly solar,1 there is some benefit in warm climates with mild winters from aligning higher summer generation with higher summer demand. But substantial storage is needed (probably more than is economical) to manage the day-night cycle. As with fixed generation however, there is so much variability of demand over time that the generation capacity measured in GWh needs to be a reasonable multiple of aggregate energy consumed. A combination, heavily weighted towards fixed, can get benefits of both fixed generation (no daily cycle) and solar (more generation with higher summer demand). This post ignores wind power, which is too unpredictable for me to handle at this time.&amp;#160;↩</description>
      <author> (Jared Kramer)</author>
      <guid>https://jgkramer.github.io/2023/02/28/Storage.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 22:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NET 8 Preview 2: QuickGrid, WebAssembly Boost for Blazor -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/03/14/net-8-preview-2.aspx</link>
      <description>Blazor QuickGrid  is &amp;#39;built to be a simple and convenient way to display your data, while still providing powerful features like sorting, filtering, paging and virtualization.&amp;#39;</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel03/14/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/03/14/net-8-preview-2.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 21:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2022 v17.6 Preview 2 is now available - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2022-v17-6-preview-2-is-now-available/</link>
      <description>Preview 2 for Visual Studio 17.6 is now available! If you are a game developer, a mobile developer, or are interested in learning new tricks to better debug your code, check out this latest release. It’s as easy as upgrading your Preview channel in the Visual Studio installer.</description>
      <author> (Marian Luparu)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2022-v17-6-preview-2-is-now-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 21:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Together: Microsoft Graph and .NET week #2 recap and final week overview - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/hack-together-microsoft-graph-dotnet-final-week/</link>
      <description>Join us for Hack Together, our virtual hackathon to learn how to build powerful apps with Microsoft Graph and .NET and win exciting prizes.</description>
      <author> (Ayca Bas)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/hack-together-microsoft-graph-dotnet-final-week/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 21:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Build–Join us May 23–25, 2023</title>
      <link>https://build.microsoft.com/?OCID=Build2020_TWITTER_msdev_spl100003907824971</link>
      <description>Learn to harness what&amp;#39;s next for developers with expert speakers and sessions.</description>
      <author> (Microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://build.microsoft.com/?OCID=Build2020_TWITTER_msdev_spl100003907824971</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 20:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eye4Fraud</title>
      <link>https://eye4fraud.com/statement</link>
      <description>We recently experienced a cybersecurity incident where a backup file that related to
                                certain customers
                                and contained limited information was subject to unauthorized access. We moved to
                                promptly retain
                                cybersecurity experts and outside advisors to assist us in our response. We have
                                notified and are
                                cooperating with law enforcement authorities to investigate the incident.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://eye4fraud.com/statement</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 20:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Build–Join us May 23–25, 2023</title>
      <link>https://build.microsoft.com/</link>
      <description>Learn to harness what&amp;#39;s next for developers with expert speakers and sessions.</description>
      <author> (Microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://build.microsoft.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=KVDnUSH90qI</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
  
    .NET Foundation
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=KVDnUSH90qI</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EF Core 8 Preview 2: Lite and familiar - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-ef8-preview-2/</link>
      <description>Announcing Entity Framework Core 8 (EF8) Preview 2 with support for JSON columns in SQLite and HierarchyId in SQL Server/Azure SQL</description>
      <author> (Arthur Vickers)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-ef8-preview-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - microsoft/hack-together: Hack Together: Microsoft Graph and .NET is a hackathon for .NET developers to learn Microsoft Graph and Microsoft 365.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/hack-together</link>
      <description>Hack Together: Microsoft Graph and .NET is a hackathon for .NET developers to learn Microsoft Graph and Microsoft 365. - GitHub - microsoft/hack-together: Hack Together: Microsoft Graph and .NET is...</description>
      <author> (microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/hack-together</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core updates in .NET 8 Preview 2 - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/asp-net-core-updates-in-dotnet-8-preview-2/</link>
      <description>.NET 8 Preview 2 is now available! Check out what&amp;#39;s new in ASP.NET Core in this update.</description>
      <author> (Daniel Roth)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/asp-net-core-updates-in-dotnet-8-preview-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing .NET 8 Preview 2 - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-8-preview-2/</link>
      <description>.NET 8 Preview 2 contains a few updates/new features from Preview 1, including introspection support for function pointers, as well as some other runtime and libraries improvements.</description>
      <author> (Alexandra Barry)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-8-preview-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET March 2023 Updates – .NET 7.0.4, .NET 6.0.15 - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/march-2023-updates/</link>
      <description>Check out March 2023 updates for .NET 7.0. and .NET 6.0</description>
      <author> (Rahul Bhandari (MSFT))</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/march-2023-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Blazor App Testing with Playwright</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=lJa3YlUliEs</link>
      <description>Learn how to use Playwright to implement end-to-end testing for your Blazor application!Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/blazor-standup-2023-03-14F...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=lJa3YlUliEs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 18:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINQ // Skip and Take</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/ce9ba892-bafe-4a62-8806-7ebf91f28a94</link>
      <description>Skip and Take are used for pagination or limit the number of elements returned by a query.
Since C# 8 you can use Take with a Range. Let&amp;#39;s see some examples.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/ce9ba892-bafe-4a62-8806-7ebf91f28a94</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 17:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Together: Microsoft Graph and .NET week 1 recap and what’s coming - Microsoft 365 Developer Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/hack-together-microsoft-graph-and-dotnet-week-1-recap/</link>
      <description>Last week we launched “Hack Together: Microsoft Graph and .NET” - a virtual hackathon all about building apps with Microsoft Graph and .NET. Here’s what happened last week and what’s still to come.</description>
      <author> (Waldek Mastykarz)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/hack-together-microsoft-graph-and-dotnet-week-1-recap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 17:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft.Bcl.Cryptography 8.0.0-preview.2.23128.3</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Microsoft.Bcl.Cryptography/8.0.0-preview.2.23128.3</link>
      <description>Provides support for some cryptographic primitives for .NET Framework and .NET Standard.

Commonly Used Types:
System.Security.Cryptography.SP800108HmacCounterKdf</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Microsoft.Bcl.Cryptography/8.0.0-preview.2.23128.3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET MAUI Community Standup - Upgrade Assistant - for Mac?!?!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=hx6ifOkbyPg</link>
      <description>Join Maddy Montaquila, David Ortinau, and guest engineer Jeffrey Stedfast for a sneak peek at the latest upgrade assistant developments, coming soon to an op...</description>
      <author> (JyoPat Tech Guru
  
  
  
    JyoPat Tech Guru
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=hx6ifOkbyPg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Vienna ever exist or was it just misinformation? - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230314-00/?p=107937</link>
      <description>It could be neither.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230314-00/?p=107937</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Pi Day - Rebecca Black [Spoof]</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=mIQQp7fF46A</link>
      <description>Of course by now you know of Rebecca Black making her infamous debut with Friday, but what about Pi Day?How come Fridays get so much more love? Friday usuall...</description>
      <author> (Everyday Science
  
  
  
    Everyday Science
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=mIQQp7fF46A</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 13:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>System.Text.Json Serializing Hierarchical Data</title>
      <link>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2023/03/14/system-text-json-serializing-hierarchical-data/</link>
      <description>The System.Text.Json serializer that was introduced with .NET Core 3.0 gets new features with every new .NET version. With .NET 7, features such as type hieararchies, contract customization, and so…</description>
      <author> (Published by
	Christian Nagel)</author>
      <guid>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2023/03/14/system-text-json-serializing-hierarchical-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 11:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn a Hue light red when website is down with IFTTT &amp;amp; elmah.io</title>
      <link>https://blog.elmah.io/turn-a-hue-light-red-when-website-is-down-with-ifttt-elmah-io/</link>
      <description>Learn how to use IFTTT and elmah.io to turn your Philips Hue light red when your website is down, ensuring you never miss a critical alert!</description>
      <author> (Written by Thomas Ardal, March 14, 2023)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.elmah.io/turn-a-hue-light-red-when-website-is-down-with-ifttt-elmah-io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 11:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Classes In C# And How to Use Them - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-partial-classes-and-how-to-use-them/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to talk about partial classes in C# and how we should use them with a practical example.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-partial-classes-and-how-to-use-them/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 09:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the Builder Design Pattern in .NET</title>
      <link>https://im5tu.io/article/2023/03/using-the-builder-design-pattern-in-.net/</link>
      <description>Discover how to use the Builder pattern in C#/.NET to create more maintainable and flexible code. Learn implementation tips and answers to FAQs in this comprehensive guide. Improve your .NET development skills and create reusable code today.</description>
      <author> (Stuart Blackler)</author>
      <guid>https://im5tu.io/article/2023/03/using-the-builder-design-pattern-in-.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 09:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting password security! Pwned Passwords, zxcvbn, and more!</title>
      <link>https://scotthelme.co.uk/boosting-account-security-pwned-passwords-and-zxcvbn/</link>
      <description>As we&amp;#39;re constantly working to improve Report URI, time is not always spent on new features and bug fixes. We always want to offer the most secure service we can and recently, we made some upgrades that will help our users keep their accounts more secure!





Existing Measures

Of course,</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/scott.helme)</author>
      <guid>https://scotthelme.co.uk/boosting-account-security-pwned-passwords-and-zxcvbn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 09:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring the ChatGPT model into our applications</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/modern-work-app-consult-blog/bring-the-chatgpt-model-into-our-applications/ba-p/3766574</link>
      <description>In the first two posts of this series we have developed an Outlook add-in that, using the Open AI models, helps users to generate professional business mails starting from a simple sentence.&amp;#160;In the first post, we achieved this goal by directly using the OpenAI APIs;&amp;#160;in the second one, instead, we ha...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/44595)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/modern-work-app-consult-blog/bring-the-chatgpt-model-into-our-applications/ba-p/3766574</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 06:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - microsoft/visual-chatgpt: Official repo for the paper: Visual ChatGPT: Talking, Drawing and Editing with Visual Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/visual-chatgpt</link>
      <description>Official repo for the paper: Visual ChatGPT: Talking, Drawing and Editing with Visual Foundation Models - GitHub - microsoft/visual-chatgpt: Official repo for the paper: Visual ChatGPT: Talking, Dr...</description>
      <author> (microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/visual-chatgpt</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 06:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL HotChocolate - Method overloading for queries</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/03/graphql-hotchocolate-method-overloading.html</link>
      <description>When building my GraphQL schema with HotChocolate , I typically use the code first or annotation first approach.   Annotation-based example ...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/03/graphql-hotchocolate-method-overloading.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 06:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence from Facade Tests</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2023/03/13/confidence-from-facade-tests/</link>
      <description>Recycling an old neologism of mine, I try to illustrate a point about the epistemology of testing function composition.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2023/03/13/confidence-from-facade-tests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 06:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is there a strategy for keeping .Net versions up to date on servers and in ASP applications?</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/dotnet/comments/11q6c8v/is_there_a_strategy_for_keeping_net_versions_up/</link>
      <description>I’m working on a large application landscape, spread out over 50+ microservices on 10+ servers per environment. We want to keep all these...</description>
      <author> (imdabestmangideedeed)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/dotnet/comments/11q6c8v/is_there_a_strategy_for_keeping_net_versions_up/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>