<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Web Components Will Outlive Your JavaScript Framework | jakelazaroff.com</title>
      <link>https://jakelazaroff.com/words/web-components-will-outlive-your-javascript-framework/</link>
      <description>If we&amp;#39;re building things that we want to work in five or ten or even 20 years, we need to avoid dependencies and use the web with no layers in between.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jakelazaroff.com/words/web-components-will-outlive-your-javascript-framework/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 22:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have I Been Pwned: API v3</title>
      <link>https://haveibeenpwned.com/API/v3#License</link>
      <description>Have I Been Pwned allows you to search across multiple data breaches to see if your email address or phone number has been compromised.</description>
      <author> (Authorisation)</author>
      <guid>https://haveibeenpwned.com/API/v3#License</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 22:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&amp;#39;s 2023, here is why your web design sucks.</title>
      <link>https://heather-buchel.com/blog/2023/10/why-your-web-design-sucks/</link>
      <description>Exploring the reasons why we no longer have web designers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://heather-buchel.com/blog/2023/10/why-your-web-design-sucks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firstborn</title>
      <link>https://www.sonyasupposedly.com/firstborn/</link>
      <description>On bearing a child and becoming a mother.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sonyasupposedly.com/firstborn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting boring APIs: lessons learned from implementing fallback handlers in Pavex | Luca Palmieri</title>
      <link>https://www.lpalmieri.com/posts/api-design-should-be-boring/</link>
      <description>APIs should not surprise: we see what it takes to apply this design principle to the API router for Pavex, a Rust web framework</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lpalmieri.com/posts/api-design-should-be-boring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>axo blog - System dependencies are hard (so we made them easier)</title>
      <link>https://blog.axo.dev/2023/10/dependencies</link>
      <description>About cargo-dist&amp;#39;s new tooling for installing and introspecting system dependencies</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.axo.dev/2023/10/dependencies</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iLeakage: Browser-based Timerless Speculative Execution Attacks on Apple Devices</title>
      <link>https://ileakage.com/</link>
      <description>We present iLeakage, a transient execution side channel targeting the Safari web browser present on Macs, iPads and
						iPhones. iLeakage shows that the Spectre attack is still
						relevant and exploitable, even after nearly 6 years of effort to mitigate it since its discovery.
						We show how an attacker can induce Safari to render an arbitrary webpage, subsequently
						recovering sensitive information present within it using speculative execution. In particular,
						we demonstrate how Safari allows a malicious webpage to recover secrets from popular high-value
						targets, such as Gmail inbox content. Finally, we demonstrate the recovery of passwords, in case
						these are autofilled by credential managers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ileakage.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity Killed Modern Proprietary Gaming For Me</title>
      <link>https://jaylittle.com/post/view/2023/9/unity-killed-modern-proprietary-gaming-for-me</link>
      <description>As some of you undoubtedly have heard Unity, the company behind one of the most prolific game engines of our time called Unity Engine, recently announced some changes to their pricing.  On the surface this may sound like quite a big nothing burger if you aren&amp;#39;t familiar with the process of how software is made, let me assure you: This announcement is rocking the entire gaming world.</description>
      <author> (Jay Little)</author>
      <guid>https://jaylittle.com/post/view/2023/9/unity-killed-modern-proprietary-gaming-for-me</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 2023 all-flash ZFS NAS (Network Storage) build</title>
      <link>https://michael.stapelberg.ch/posts/2023-10-25-my-all-flash-zfs-network-storage-build/</link>
      <description>For over 10 years now, I run two self-built NAS (Network Storage) devices which serve media (currently via Jellyfin) and run daily backups of all my PCs and servers.
In this article, I describe my goals, which hardware I picked for my new build (and why) and how I set it up.</description>
      <author> (Michael Stapelberg)</author>
      <guid>https://michael.stapelberg.ch/posts/2023-10-25-my-all-flash-zfs-network-storage-build/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automattic&amp;#39;s Tumblr/ActivityPub integration reportedly shelved</title>
      <link>https://notes.ghed.in/posts/2023/tumblr-activitypub-integration/</link>
      <description>When Twitter changed hands and Mastodon had its 15 minutes of fame, on October 2022, it seemed that we were on the verge of a digital revolution based on Act...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.ghed.in/posts/2023/tumblr-activitypub-integration/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Databases Store and Retrieve Data with B-Trees</title>
      <link>https://www.lucavall.in/blog/how-databases-store-and-retrieve-data-with-b-trees</link>
      <description>Learning about data storage and B-Trees from &amp;quot;Database Internals: A Deep Dive Into How Distributed Data Systems Work&amp;quot; by Alex Petrov (O&amp;#39;Reilly Media).</description>
      <author> (Luca Cavallin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.lucavall.in/blog/how-databases-store-and-retrieve-data-with-b-trees</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Linking Bookmarks</title>
      <link>https://joshleeb.com/posts/linking-bookmarks.html</link>
      <description>Published on
2023-10-25
to joshleeb&amp;#39;s blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joshleeb.com/posts/linking-bookmarks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triggering `entr`</title>
      <link>https://huijzer.xyz/posts/entr-trigger/</link>
      <description>Executing commands automatically upon file changes.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://huijzer.xyz/posts/entr-trigger/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoiding addictions</title>
      <link>https://josem.co/avoiding-addictions/</link>
      <description>Capitalism is great at giving people what they demand and making them even want things they don’t need. Once a company creates a product or service, the industry streamlines its production, distribution, and sales to maximize efficiency. The more they sell, the better it is for the business.
Living in a market-driven society is a blessing if you want to buy a good fork or a reliable car. However, there’s a flip side to this coin: an entire sector focuses on enticing consumers with addictive products and services, and that’s where the danger begins.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://josem.co/avoiding-addictions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&amp;#39;s Fucking Impossible to Stay Healthy</title>
      <link>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2023-10-24-its_impossible_to_stay_healthy/</link>
      <description>My college physical life was a bit strange. I worked out(weights) nearly every day, except that I basically didn’t move from my chair at any other point in time. Food was a block away, and I nearly never went to class. The few times I did, I would use an electric scooter. It wasn’t like I was a health nut, but I generally kept my weight between 175-180lb as a 6&amp;#39;0 male.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2023-10-24-its_impossible_to_stay_healthy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you talking or speaking?</title>
      <link>https://rory.codes/talking-or-speaking/</link>
      <description>A brief guide to listening.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rory.codes/talking-or-speaking/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integration Testing GraphQL Endpoints with Alba</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/10/25/integration-testing-graphql-endpoints-with-alba/</link>
      <description>I’m helping a JasperFx Software client get a new system off the ground that’s using both Hot Chocolate for GraphQL and Marten for event sourcing and general persistence. That’s le…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/10/25/integration-testing-graphql-endpoints-with-alba/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:05:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Java Jockeys Get OpenAI Playground -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/10/25/azure-openai-java.aspx</link>
      <description>Microsoft&amp;#39;s dev team for Java on Azure tooling announced support for the Azure OpenAI Service and associated Playground, enabling new AI-based scenarios based on advanced tech from Microsoft partner OpenAI, creator of ChatGPT.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel10/25/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/10/25/azure-openai-java.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of a .NET devcontainer</title>
      <link>https://timheuer.com/blog/anatomy-of-a-dotnet-devcontainer/</link>
      <description>Wondering how the new .NET Codespaces environment is configured? Check out the devcontainer definition to learn more and how you can do this too!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://timheuer.com/blog/anatomy-of-a-dotnet-devcontainer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a web API with ASP.NET Core and MongoDB</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/create-a-web-api-with-aspnet-core-and-mongodb/</link>
      <description>This post is about configuring Mongo DB and creating ASP.NET Core Web API to work with Mongo DB using MongoDB.EntityFrameworkCore nuget package. Recently MongoDB team announced a EF Core provider for MongoDB. Earlier this year I blogged about MongoDB and ASP.NET Core using MongoFramework nuget package. In this blog post we are using MongoDB.EntityFrameworkCore nuget package which is from MongoDB.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/create-a-web-api-with-aspnet-core-and-mongodb/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyal workers are selectively and ironically targeted for exploitation</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0022103122001615</link>
      <description>Loyalty is often touted as a moral principle, or virtue, worth exemplifying in social and business relations. But is it always beneficial to be loyal?…</description>
      <author> (J. Dungan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0022103122001615</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Shawn Wildermuth: Web Service APIs in .NET 7 - Episode 266</title>
      <link>http://feed.azuredevops.show/shawn-wildermuth-web-service-apis-in-net-7-episode-266/</link>
      <description>Shawn Wildermuth has been tinkering with computers and software since he got a VIC-20 back in the early ’80s. He has been a Microsoft MVP, Pluralsight Author, and filmmaker. You can reach him at his blog at  and he makes films at . &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [5:34] What got Shawn excited about coding? [9:26] How should developers be thinking about just the concept of an API? What are the categories that they should be aware of? [16:04] Shawn’s first steps in designing an API. [18:37] What are the newer concepts and newer advances that are worth taking a look at? [19:10] Maturing minimal APIs. [24:53] Endpoint filtering. [27:01] Does the core logic need to be aware that it might be in a caching workflow, or does caching as a concept belong to the interface for the application programming? [31:45] Shawn’s favorite method for testing the complete set of web service APIs. [34:59] Helping young developers not get lost along the way of feeling the need to be perfect. [39:25] How developers make the decision of where and how to run the applications they built. &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode: YARP     — New Video Podcast! Email us at .  (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!  — Follow to stay informed about future events!   &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://feed.azuredevops.show/shawn-wildermuth-web-service-apis-in-net-7-episode-266/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 16:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libsyn Podcast Player</title>
      <link>https://play.libsyn.com/embed/episode/id/28249835/theme/modern/tdest_id/768876</link>
      <description>Libsyn Podcast Player</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://play.libsyn.com/embed/episode/id/28249835/theme/modern/tdest_id/768876</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 16:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The format of icon resources, revisited - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231025-00/?p=108925</link>
      <description>Filling in some gaps.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231025-00/?p=108925</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 16:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Maeda’s Cozy AI Kitchen: AI-copiloted Career Advising with guest Kevin Bethune</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/vEXTWilW_sU?feature=shared</link>
      <description>John Maeda is Microsoft’s VP of Design and AI. He also enjoys cooking up some warm and wonderful AI goodies in his kitchen.  John’s guest today is Kevin Buth...</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Developer
  
  
  
    Microsoft Developer
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/vEXTWilW_sU?feature=shared</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 15:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - AndrewWalsh/openapi-devtools: Effortlessly discover API behaviour with a Chrome extension that automatically generates OpenAPI specifications in real time for any app or website</title>
      <link>https://github.com/AndrewWalsh/openapi-devtools</link>
      <description>Effortlessly discover API behaviour with a Chrome extension that automatically generates OpenAPI specifications in real time for any app or website - GitHub - AndrewWalsh/openapi-devtools: Effortle...</description>
      <author> (AndrewWalsh)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/AndrewWalsh/openapi-devtools</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 15:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Master the Art of Reflection in CSharp and Boost Your Programming Skills</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/10/25/how-to-master-the-art-of-reflection-in-csharp-and-boost-your-programming-skills/</link>
      <description>Learn about reflection in CSharp and how it can be used. See how reflection in C# allows you to explore and modify objects, classes, and assemblies at runtime.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/10/25/how-to-master-the-art-of-reflection-in-csharp-and-boost-your-programming-skills/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarsnap has given 2^18 dollars to open source</title>
      <link>https://www.daemonology.net/blog/2023-10-25-2%5E18-dollars-to-open-source.html</link>
      <description>Yesterday I read a great article from Sentry entitled
&amp;quot;We
Just Gave $500,000 to Open Source Maintainers&amp;quot;, and it made me wonder
just how much Tarsnap had spent
on supporting open source software over the years.  Ever since
December 2009
Tarsnap has spent 100% of its December operating profits on supporting
open source software — which, since needs for support aren&amp;#39;t limited
to December, means that Tarsnap hands out money throughout the year, and
at the end of the year (when I know how much profit Tarsnap made in
December) I send whatever is left in the &amp;quot;budget&amp;quot; to the
FreeBSD Foundation.
Going through 14 years of accounting spreadsheets brought me to a total
of $274,482 — or in binary terms, slightly over 2^18 USD.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.daemonology.net/blog/2023-10-25-2%5E18-dollars-to-open-source.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daylight Saving Choice</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2846/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2846/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Validate Your Application Settings with Data Annotations #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=KUhAclofBoY</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=KUhAclofBoY</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interfaces vs Abstract Classes</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=PPZ_vZcF2AU</link>
      <description>A popular C# interview question is to explain the differences between interfaces and abstract classes, why use an interface over an abstract class or an abst...</description>
      <author> (Raw Coding
  
  
  
    Raw Coding
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=PPZ_vZcF2AU</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamically Adding Rows on a Form in Razor Pages - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/dynamically-adding-rows-form-razor-pages/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will understand how to add and remove rows in Razor Pages Form in ASP.NET Core dynamically.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/dynamically-adding-rows-form-razor-pages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Friday - Learn about the Azure cloud with this free weekly educational video podcast with Scott Hanselman and Friends!</title>
      <link>https://azurefriday.com/</link>
      <description>Azure Friday - Search through past episodes of the Azure Friday cloud video podcast with Scott Hanselman and learn more about the Azure Cloud!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://azurefriday.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release v0.3.0 &amp;#183; cgillum/azure-functions-openai-extension</title>
      <link>https://github.com/cgillum/azure-functions-openai-extension/releases/tag/v0.3.0</link>
      <description>This release contains full support for Azure OpenAI deployments, allowing users to safely interact with OpenAI&amp;#39;s advanced models without exposing any data to OpenAI.
NuGet Packages
The following Nu...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/cgillum/azure-functions-openai-extension/releases/tag/v0.3.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#160;Accelerate your software engineering career by tracking your work</title>
      <link>https://blog.3d-logic.com/2023/10/24/accelerate-your-software-engineering-career-by-tracking-your-work/</link>
      <description>Your manager doesn’t know what you’re doing. They do know about things you should be doing they care about but you’re doing much more than that. You’re probably doing much more than even you think …</description>
      <author> (moozzyk)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.3d-logic.com/2023/10/24/accelerate-your-software-engineering-career-by-tracking-your-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform Live Coding: Porting WinUI 3 code!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=iHqjFAqpSBY</link>
      <description>Today we embark on a new adventure of porting the newly published WinUI 3 code to C# and Uno Platform!</description>
      <author> (The Meltzone Podcast
  
  
  
    The Meltzone Podcast
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=iHqjFAqpSBY</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft .NET Code Analysis: Consider Using String.Contains() Instead of String.IndexOf()</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/10/25/microsoft-net-code-analysis-consider-using-string-contains-instead-of-string-indexof/</link>
      <description>In this article, we explore Microsoft’s recommendation to utilize the String.Contains() method instead of String.IndexOf() for improved code readability. We provide code examples to illustrat…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave
		

		
			I live in San Diego, Ca USA			
				View all posts by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/10/25/microsoft-net-code-analysis-consider-using-string-contains-instead-of-string-indexof/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interfaces can have private methods</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/03957748-73b3-40f9-a9f7-cc95501a3a8e</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s drop some &amp;quot;useless&amp;quot; knowledge here. Interfaces can have private methods. This comes with the C# 8 feature: &amp;quot;Default interface methods&amp;quot;.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/03957748-73b3-40f9-a9f7-cc95501a3a8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React Basics: How to Use Cookies in React</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/react-basics-how-to-use-cookies</link>
      <description>Cookies are a common way to store and retrieve data on the client side in web applications. See some examples of setting and using cookies in React.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/react-basics-how-to-use-cookies</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Service Virtualization Capability from Scratch (Part 2)</title>
      <link>https://www.codeproject.com/Articles/5367440/Creating-a-Service-Virtualization-Capability-from</link>
      <description>A case study in building a cloud tool to perform service virtualization using LocalStack (AWS), minimal APIs, and Terraform</description>
      <author> (Pete O&amp;#39;Hanlon)</author>
      <guid>https://www.codeproject.com/Articles/5367440/Creating-a-Service-Virtualization-Capability-from</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Service Virtualization Capability from Scratch (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://www.codeproject.com/Articles/5366987/Creating-a-Service-Virtualization-Capability-fro-2</link>
      <description>A case study in building a cloud tool to perform service virtualization using LocalStack (AWS), minimal APIs, and Terraform</description>
      <author> (Pete O&amp;#39;Hanlon)</author>
      <guid>https://www.codeproject.com/Articles/5366987/Creating-a-Service-Virtualization-Capability-fro-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Testcontainers with .NET Unit Tests | The .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/10/24/how-to-use-testcontainers-with-dotnet-unit-tests/</link>
      <description>With Testcontainers, you can spin up and tear down Docker containers as part of your automated tests. For example, if you need a database, you don&amp;#39;t need to mock it: your xUnit, NUnit, and MSTest code can launch an actual database against which you can validate your code.</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/10/24/how-to-use-testcontainers-with-dotnet-unit-tests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Decorators: What They Are and When to Use Them — SitePoint</title>
      <link>https://www.sitepoint.com/javascript-decorators-what-they-are/</link>
      <description>Learn about decorators in JavaScript: what they are, how they work, what they&amp;#39;re useful for, their pros and cons, and how to use them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sitepoint.com/javascript-decorators-what-they-are/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Endpoint Filters with ASP.NET Core Minimal APIs</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/global-endpoint-filters-with-aspnet-core-minimal-apis</link>
      <description>Minimal API endpoint filters for ALL the Minimal API endpoints</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/global-endpoint-filters-with-aspnet-core-minimal-apis</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to v4 Azure Functions Node.js with TypeScript | johnnyreilly</title>
      <link>https://johnnyreilly.com/migrating-azure-functions-node-js-v4-typescript</link>
      <description>Learn how to migrate a TypeScript Azure Functions app to the v4 Node.js programming model.</description>
      <author> (https://johnnyreilly.com/about)</author>
      <guid>https://johnnyreilly.com/migrating-azure-functions-node-js-v4-typescript</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metalama Source Code Available | PostSharp Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.postsharp.net/post/source-available.html</link>
      <description>It is important to note that “source-available” does not equate to “open source” as defined by the Open Source Initiative (OSI). If you need more features than those provided by Metalama Free, you will still need to acquire a license for Metalama.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.postsharp.net/post/source-available.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# Record Explained - NDepend Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.ndepend.com/c-record-explained/</link>
      <description>Unlock the power of C# records with this comprehensive guide. Explore their features, syntaxes, applications and benefits.</description>
      <author> (NDepend)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ndepend.com/c-record-explained/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 8 Top 10 New Features - NDepend Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.ndepend.com/net-8-top-10-new-features/</link>
      <description>Explore the Top 10 New Features in .NET 8 - Uncover the latest enhancements and innovations in this game-changing release.</description>
      <author> (NDepend)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ndepend.com/net-8-top-10-new-features/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Developer Workflow with Pieces.App&amp;#39;s Tsavo Knott</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselminutes.com/913/redefining-developer-workflow-with-piecesapps-tsavo-knott</link>
      <description>Tsavo Knott and the team at Pieces have an app that smooths the spaces between your developer tools. It makes you smarter and makes your workflow more seamless as you move code context from ide to web, from browser tab to clipboard, through your entire tool chain. How does Pieces promise to redefine atomic productivity for developers? Scott finds out of they will take code snippets to the next level on this episode.</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/552706617)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselminutes.com/913/redefining-developer-workflow-with-piecesapps-tsavo-knott</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 03:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Maeda’s Cozy AI Kitchen: AI-copiloted Design Thinking with guest Ben Sheppard</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/6Jr6z_YvJhc</link>
      <description>Welcome to the first episode of Mr. Maeda’s Cozy AI Kitchen.   First off, please note we had a bit of an issue with the audio inside of our refrigerator for ...</description>
      <author> (ONETUG
  
  
  
    ONETUG
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/6Jr6z_YvJhc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 03:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That Time the City of Seattle Accidentally Gave Me 32m Emails for 40 Dollars</title>
      <link>https://mchap.io/that-time-the-city-of-seattle-accidentally-gave-me-32m-emails-for-40-dollars4997.html</link>
      <description>October 19, 2018 — 
Matt Chapman</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mchap.io/that-time-the-city-of-seattle-accidentally-gave-me-32m-emails-for-40-dollars4997.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 03:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>