<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Niklaus Wirth was right and that is a problem – bowero</title>
      <link>https://bowero.nl/blog/2020/07/31/niklaus-wirth-was-right-and-that-is-a-problem/</link>
      <description>Wirth’s law is not really a law. Actually, none of them ever are laws. They are adages:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bowero.nl/blog/2020/07/31/niklaus-wirth-was-right-and-that-is-a-problem/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 22:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Big Crackdown is upon us – NEWS FROM UNDERGROUND</title>
      <link>http://markcrispinmiller.com/2020/07/the-big-crackdown-is-upon-us/</link>
      <description>From Kevin Barry:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://markcrispinmiller.com/2020/07/the-big-crackdown-is-upon-us/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>swyx Writing | Slack is Fumbling Developers</title>
      <link>https://www.swyx.io/writing/slack-fumble/</link>
      <description>Reflecting on the sudden switch away from Slack for Developer communities</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.swyx.io/writing/slack-fumble/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 22:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Cloudflare Workers to prevent attackers from bypassing your Cloudflare WAF</title>
      <link>https://sandrino.dev/blog/forcing-traffic-through-cloudflare</link>
      <description>A long standing challenge with Cloudflare is the ability to bypass all protections by attacking the Origin IP directly. Cloudflare Workers could provide a simple way to solve this issue once and for all.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sandrino.dev/blog/forcing-traffic-through-cloudflare</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What makes Paul Graham a great writer?</title>
      <link>https://ellenrhymes.com/paul-graham/</link>
      <description>Paul Graham, besides being an entrepreneur &amp; investor, is among today's most widely admired essayists. What makes his writing so great? Here are some clues.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ellenrhymes.com/paul-graham/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 22:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple’s bulls**t narrative on the App Store</title>
      <link>https://scrambleuphill.com/2020/07/31/apples-bullst-narrative-on-the-app-store/</link>
      <description>“The only apps that are subject to a commission are those where the developer acquires a customer on an Apple device and where the features or services would be experienced and consumed on an…</description>
      <author> (scramblinguphill)</author>
      <guid>https://scrambleuphill.com/2020/07/31/apples-bullst-narrative-on-the-app-store/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Spent 2 Days Chasing a Bug that Didn't Exist</title>
      <link>https://figbert.com/posts/pebkac-txtodo/</link>
      <description>&lt;p class="text-sm preview"&gt;Post-&lt;a class="underline" href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc20/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;WWDC2020&lt;/a&gt;, I decided to rewrite the backend of txtodo in SwiftUI using the new &lt;a class="underline" href="https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2020/10037/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;App and Scene structure&lt;/a&gt;. Rebuilding the app from scratch may have not been the best choice, but during that process I have massively simplified the app's data structure, despaghettified some messy UI code, and spent two full days trying to solve a problem that didn't exist. This is the story of that last bit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <author> (FIGBERT)</author>
      <guid>https://figbert.com/posts/pebkac-txtodo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 22:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build and deploy GitHub Pages from any branch beta The GitHub Blog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/changelog/2020-07-31-build-and-deploy-github-pages-from-any-branch-beta/</link>
      <description>Build and deploy GitHub Pages from any branch beta</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/changelog/2020-07-31-build-and-deploy-github-pages-from-any-branch-beta/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 21:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenTelemetry .NET Beta Released!</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/opentelemetry/opentelemetry-net-beta-released-e1b070f0a5bc</link>
      <description>Today, we are happy to announce that the OpenTelemetry .NET SDK has reached beta. This means that you can now begin integrating the…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@ank3it)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/opentelemetry/opentelemetry-net-beta-released-e1b070f0a5bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 21:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>trozler/whereAmI</title>
      <link>https://github.com/trozler/whereAmI</link>
      <description>A one line shell script that returns you your ip address and its geolocation. - trozler/whereAmI</description>
      <author> (trozler)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/trozler/whereAmI</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 21:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zello Security Notice – July 31, 2020</title>
      <link>https://support.zello.com/hc/en-us/articles/360046709192-Zello-Security-Notice-July-31-2020</link>
      <description>On July 8, 2020, we discovered unusual activity on one of our servers. We immediately initiated an investigation, notified law enforcement and engaged a leading independent forensics firm to help. ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://support.zello.com/hc/en-us/articles/360046709192-Zello-Security-Notice-July-31-2020</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 21:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackbaud's Bizarre Ransomware Attack Notification</title>
      <link>https://www.bankinfosecurity.com/blogs/blackbauds-insane-ransomware-attack-notification-p-2929</link>
      <description>How many different shades of bizarre is the data breach notification issued by software vendor Blackbaud? Over the course of three paragraphs, Blackbaud normalizes hacking, congratulates its amazing cybersecurity team, and says it cares so much for its customers that it paid a ransom to attackers.</description>
      <author> (Mathew J. Schwartz)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bankinfosecurity.com/blogs/blackbauds-insane-ransomware-attack-notification-p-2929</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 21:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET R&amp;D Digest (July, 2020)</title>
      <link>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2020/07/31/net-rd-digest-july-2020/</link>
      <description>This issue of .NET R&amp;D Digest includes bits of computer science (even a link to a paper!), software development and a few learning resources which you can use to learn something new! Ah, yeah, …</description>
      <author> (Oleg Karasik)</author>
      <guid>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2020/07/31/net-rd-digest-july-2020/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 21:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read function arguments from .NET applications with .NET ProfilingAPI</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/gabbersepp/read-function-arguments-from-net-applications-with-net-profilingapi-c64</link>
      <description>I show you how you can extend your profiler in order to read function parameters within a FunctionEnter event</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/gabbersepp/read-function-arguments-from-net-applications-with-net-profilingapi-c64</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 20:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News Releases | Washington State Department of Agriculture</title>
      <link>https://agr.wa.gov/about-wsda/news-and-media-relations/news-releases?article=31413</link>
      <description>Contact Number:
                                360-902-2178</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://agr.wa.gov/about-wsda/news-and-media-relations/news-releases?article=31413</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 19:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Resource Scheduling Errors and How to Mitigate Them - DZone Agile</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/7-resource-scheduling-errors-how-to-mitigate-them</link>
      <description>Resource scheduling is essential part of project management. Here’s a read on common scheduling errors most businesses commit, and how to resolve them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dzone.com/articles/7-resource-scheduling-errors-how-to-mitigate-them</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 19:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Release v0.20.0 · microsoft/PowerToys</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/PowerToys/releases/tag/v0.20.0</link>
      <description>Our goals for 0.20 release cycle were to focus on adding in a few new features along with a heavy focus on stability / quality fixes. Martin Chrzan helped contribute a new utility that was in our 2...</description>
      <author> (microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/PowerToys/releases/tag/v0.20.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 17:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade to pip 20.2, plus, changes coming in 20.3</title>
      <link>https://blog.python.org/2020/07/upgrade-pip-20-2-changes-20-3.html</link>
      <description>On behalf of the Python Packaging Authority, I am pleased to announce that we have just released pip 20.2, a new version of pip. You can install it by running</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.python.org/2020/07/upgrade-pip-20-2-changes-20-3.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 17:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kushner’s Shadow Task Force Appears to Violate Multiple Laws - CREW</title>
      <link>https://www.citizensforethics.org/press-release/kushners-shadow-task-force-violate-multiple-laws/</link>
      <description>Jared Kushner’s shadow coronavirus task force appears to be violating both the Presidential Records Act and Federal Advisory Committee Act.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.citizensforethics.org/press-release/kushners-shadow-task-force-violate-multiple-laws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 17:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf - Focus on Microservices</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/visualstudio?utm_campaign=liveworkshop&amp;utm_source=dotnet&amp;utm_medium=twitter</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/visualstudio?utm_campaign=liveworkshop&amp;utm_source=dotnet&amp;utm_medium=twitter</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 17:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer News - Visual Studio Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=MadsKristensen.DeveloperNews</link>
      <description>Extension for Visual Studio - Always stay up to date with developer news from the Visual Studio team and other sources right within Visual Studio or your default browser.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=MadsKristensen.DeveloperNews</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 16:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor GameDev - part 6: mouse input - Davide Guida</title>
      <link>https://www.davideguida.com/blazor-gamedev-part-6-mouse-input/</link>
      <description>Hi All! Welcome back to part 6 of our Blazor 2d Gamedev series. Today we'll see how we can start detecting user interaction and mouse input.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/davide.guida)</author>
      <guid>https://www.davideguida.com/blazor-gamedev-part-6-mouse-input/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 16:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Thursday - August 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/nl-NL/Azure-Thursdays/events/271139367/</link>
      <description>do 6 aug. 2020 19:00: Join on:https://events.azurethursday.com## Schedule (Time in CEST)18:30- 19:00 - Get ready!19:00 - 19:45 – Barbara Forbes - When powers combine: Azure Function Apps &amp; PowerShell1</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/nl-NL/Azure-Thursdays/events/271139367/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 15:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring demystified: A guide for logging, tracing, metrics | TechBeacon</title>
      <link>https://techbeacon.com/enterprise-it/monitoring-demystified-guide-logging-tracing-metrics</link>
      <description>Here are the top 38 online resources to teach you how to do observability operations well.</description>
      <author> (Mitch Pronschinske)</author>
      <guid>https://techbeacon.com/enterprise-it/monitoring-demystified-guide-logging-tracing-metrics</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 15:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philosophers On GPT-3 (updated with replies by GPT-3) - Daily Nous</title>
      <link>http://dailynous.com/2020/07/30/philosophers-gpt-3/</link>
      <description>Nine philosophers explore the various issues and questions raised by the newly released language model, GPT-3, in this edition of Philosophers On, guest edited by Annette Zimmermann. Introduction Annette Zimmermann, guest editor GPT-3, a powerful, 175 billion parameter language model developed recently by OpenAI, has been galvanizing public debate and controversy. As the MIT Technology Review puts it: “OpenAI’s new language generator GPT-3 is shockingly good—and completely mindless”. Parts of the technology community hope (and fear) that GPT-3 could brings us one step closer to the hypothetical future possibility of human-like, highly sophisticated artificial general intelligence (AGI). Meanwhile, others (including OpenAI’s own CEO) have critiqued claims about GPT-3’s ostensible proximity to AGI, arguing that they are vastly overstated. Why the hype? As is turns out, GPT-3 is unlike other natural language processing (NLP) systems, the latter of which often struggle with what comes comparatively easily to humans: performing entirely new language tasks based on a few simple instructions and examples. Instead, NLP systems usually have to be pre-trained on a large corpus of text, and then fine-tuned in order to successfully perform a specific task. GPT-3, by contrast, does not require fine tuning of this kind: it seems to be able to perform a whole range of tasks reasonably well, from producing fiction, poetry, and press releases to functioning code, and from music, jokes, and technical manuals, to “news articles which human evaluators have difficulty distinguishing from articles written by humans”. The Philosophers On series contains group posts on issues of current interest, with the aim being to show what the careful thinking characteristic of philosophers (and occasionally scholars in related fields) can bring to popular ongoing conversations. Contributors present not fully worked out position papers but rather brief thoughts that can serve as prompts for further reflection and discussion. The contributors to this installment of “Philosophers On” are Amanda Askell (Research Scientist, OpenAI), David Chalmers (Professor of Philosophy, New York University), Justin Khoo (Associate Professor of Philosophy, Massachusetts Institute of Technology), Carlos Montemayor (Professor of Philosophy, San Francisco State University), C. Thi Nguyen (Associate Professor of Philosophy, University of Utah), Regina Rini (Canada Research Chair in Philosophy of Moral and Social Cognition, York University), Henry Shevlin (Research Associate, Leverhulme Centre for..</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://dailynous.com/2020/07/30/philosophers-gpt-3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 15:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Jared Kushner’s Secret Testing Plan “Went Poof Into Thin Air”</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/07/how-jared-kushners-secret-testing-plan-went-poof-into-thin-air</link>
      <description>This spring, a team working under the president's son-in-law produced a plan for an aggressive, coordinated national COVID-19 response that could have brought the pandemic under control. So why did the White House spike it in favor of a shambolic 50-state response?</description>
      <author> (Katherine Eban)</author>
      <guid>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/07/how-jared-kushners-secret-testing-plan-went-poof-into-thin-air</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 14:33:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add a Blazor sample by ADefWebserver · Pull Request #30 · richorama/IronBlock</title>
      <link>https://github.com/richorama/IronBlock/pull/30</link>
      <description>Have a question about this project? Sign up for a free GitHub account to open an issue and contact its maintainers and the community.</description>
      <author> (richorama)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/richorama/IronBlock/pull/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 14:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Maze Weekly #36 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-36/</link>
      <description>This week we’ve seen articles on all kinds of different topics. From .NET to frontend to AI and some interesting real-world stuff that we can all relate to. Check out this week’s selection, pick your favorite place to read and enjoy: .NET and C# Detecting duplicate routes in ASP.NET Core [andrewlock.net] In the fifth part […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-36/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 14:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn on &amp; manage community contributions</title>
      <link>https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/6052538</link>
      <description>Community contributions going away soon Community contributions will be discontinued across all channels after September 28, 2020. Community contributions allowed viewers to add closed captions,</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/6052538</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 14:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Timelapse</title>
      <link>https://earthengine.google.com/timelapse/</link>
      <description>Explore the dynamics of our changing planet over the past three and a half decades.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://earthengine.google.com/timelapse/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 12:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 202</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-202/</link>
      <description>Unfortunately, our run of good luck here down in Aus has taken a bit of a turn COVID wise. Not so much in my home state, but the southern states have been copping it so this week, I pulled the pin on snowboarding. For folks overseas, that might sound like</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt's Picture)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-202/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 09:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the brightness() CSS Filter to generically highlight Content</title>
      <link>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2020/Jul/28/Using-the-brightness-CSS-Filter-to-generically-highlight-Content</link>
      <description>Filters are not new in CSS, but their often overlooked for providing some useful generic behaviors for things like hover styling or nice background effects. In this post I discuss how to use the brightness() filter to create a generic button hover behavior and also briefly discuss the newish `backdrop-filter` property.</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/rickstrahl)</author>
      <guid>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2020/Jul/28/Using-the-brightness-CSS-Filter-to-generically-highlight-Content</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 09:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angular Language Service for Visual Studio   — NoWaySheCodes</title>
      <link>https://www.nowayshecodes.com/blog-tech/angular-language-service-for-visual-studio</link>
      <description>Great news everyone: The Angular Language Service is coming to Visual Studio!</description>
      <author> (Jul 29
            
            Written By Gabrielle Crevecoeur)</author>
      <guid>https://www.nowayshecodes.com/blog-tech/angular-language-service-for-visual-studio</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 08:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September DDD by Night</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/DDD-Melbourne-By-Night/events/272205392/</link>
      <description>Thu, Sep 10, 2020, 6:00 PM: We have started planning DDD by Night September and now looking for speakers.The evening will be hosted by the DDD Melbourne crew and consists ofshort &amp; sharp presentations</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/DDD-Melbourne-By-Night/events/272205392/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 08:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Your Daily Ride or Make Money Driving Now</title>
      <link>https://swvl.com/</link>
      <description>Number one Transportation App With Fixed Line and Fare. Get Your Ride In Minutes.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://swvl.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 08:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we migrated Dropbox from Nginx to Envoy</title>
      <link>https://dropbox.tech/infrastructure/how-we-migrated-dropbox-from-nginx-to-envoy</link>
      <description>In this blogpost we’ll talk about the old Nginx-based traffic infrastructure, its pain points, and the benefits we gained by migrating to Envoy. We’ll compare Nginx to Envoy across many software engineering and operational dimensions. We’ll also briefly touch on the migration process, its current state, and some of the problems encountered on the way.</description>
      <author> (Alexey Ivanov)</author>
      <guid>https://dropbox.tech/infrastructure/how-we-migrated-dropbox-from-nginx-to-envoy</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 07:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egyptian bus operator Swvl hit by data breach</title>
      <link>https://portswigger.net/daily-swig/egyptian-bus-operator-swvl-hit-by-data-breach</link>
      <description>Swvl claims only names, email addresses, and phone numbers were accessed</description>
      <author> (Adam Bannister
        
    
        
            @Ad_Nauseum74)</author>
      <guid>https://portswigger.net/daily-swig/egyptian-bus-operator-swvl-hit-by-data-breach</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 07:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run Blazor-based .NET Web applications on AWS Serverless | Amazon Web Services</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/run-blazor-based-net-web-applications-on-aws-serverless/</link>
      <description>Blazor WebAssembly is a new client-side web development framework that lets developers to use C# to create application front end. Blazor can run client-side C# code directly in the browser, using WebAssembly. Blazor WebAssembly runs on .NET Core and it is an open source and cross-platform web framework for building single-page application using .NET and […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/run-blazor-based-net-web-applications-on-aws-serverless/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 06:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TDD is an antidote for uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2020/07/29/tdd-is-an-antidote-for-uncertainty/</link>
      <description>Everyone on a team has to buy into TDD for it to work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2020/07/29/tdd-is-an-antidote-for-uncertainty/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fix .NET Core's 'Unable to obtain lock file access' error on Red Hat OpenShift - Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2020/07/30/how-to-fix-net-cores-unable-to-obtain-lock-file-access-error-on-red-hat-openshift/</link>
      <description>Well, it finally happened. Despite the added assurances of working with containers and Kubernetes, the old “It works on my machine” scenario reared its ugly head in my .NET Core (C#) code. The image that I created worked fine on my local PC—a Fedora 32 machine—but it crashed when I tried running it in my …</description>
      <author> (By Don Schenck July 30, 2020July 30, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2020/07/30/how-to-fix-net-cores-unable-to-obtain-lock-file-access-error-on-red-hat-openshift/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 06:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integration testing your Polly policies with HttpClient Interception</title>
      <link>http://josephwoodward.co.uk/2020/07/integration-testing-polly-policies-httpclient-interception</link>
      <description>In my previous post I introduced HttpClientInterception, a hugely versatile .NET library that I've had great success with. In the post I demonstrated how you can use it to stub remote HTTP service dependencies within your application to ease testing. Towards the end of the post I demonstrated how it integrated with IHttpClientFactory via the IHttpMessageHandlerBuilderFilter interface, enabling you to apply additional HttpMessageHandlers to your HttpClients generated via IHttpClientFactory.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://josephwoodward.co.uk/2020/07/integration-testing-polly-policies-httpclient-interception</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 06:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I find which directory my .NET Core console application was started in or is running from?</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/HowDoIFindWhichDirectoryMyNETCoreConsoleApplicationWasStartedInOrIsRunningFrom.aspx</link>
      <description>I got a great question emailed to me today. And while I could find the answer and email them back, I also have a ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/HowDoIFindWhichDirectoryMyNETCoreConsoleApplicationWasStartedInOrIsRunningFrom.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 06:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTIC TR JUMPER INDEX</title>
      <link>https://apps.dtic.mil/dtic/tr/fulltext/</link>
      <description>Jump Page 2     20181109</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://apps.dtic.mil/dtic/tr/fulltext/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 06:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing launch configurations support for SAM debugging in the AWS Toolkit for VS Code | Amazon Web Services</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/introducing-launch-configurations-support-for-sam-debugging-in-the-aws-toolkit-for-vs-code/</link>
      <description>The AWS Toolkit for Visual Studio Code implements a new SAM debugging experience based on VS Code launch configurations. This new experience replaces the old Run Locally | Debug Locally experience. To try the SAM debugging experience for VS Code, install the AWS Toolkit from the VS Code Marketplace. The new experience embraces VS Code’s […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/introducing-launch-configurations-support-for-sam-debugging-in-the-aws-toolkit-for-vs-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 06:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to Basics #2: Binding Markup - Nick's .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/back-to-basics-2-binding-markup/</link>
      <description>The next post in the series originally written by Beatriz Stollnitz. Original post available on Github. What does “{Binding}” mean? Most Bindings you see in samples have the Source and Path properties set. The Source property specifies the object you’re binding to and the Path specifies a property in that object whose value you’re interested … Continue reading "Back to Basics #2: Binding Markup"</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/back-to-basics-2-binding-markup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 06:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotnet-presentations/dotNETConf</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet-presentations/dotNETConf/tree/master/2020/FocusOnMicroservices</link>
      <description>Creative and technical content for running a .NET Conf local event in your community - dotnet-presentations/dotNETConf</description>
      <author> (dotnet-presentations)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet-presentations/dotNETConf/tree/master/2020/FocusOnMicroservices</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 05:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rynowak/link-a-thon</title>
      <link>https://github.com/rynowak/link-a-thon/blob/master/src/ApiTemplate/Linker.xml</link>
      <description>Contribute to rynowak/link-a-thon development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (rynowak)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/rynowak/link-a-thon/blob/master/src/ApiTemplate/Linker.xml</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 04:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotnet/designs</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/designs/blob/master/accepted/2020/linking-libraries.md</link>
      <description>This repo is used for reviewing new .NET designs. Contribute to dotnet/designs development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/designs/blob/master/accepted/2020/linking-libraries.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 04:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Era of DNA Database Hacks Is Here</title>
      <link>https://onezero.medium.com/the-era-of-dna-database-hacks-is-here-85a860190622?source=social---tw.onezero&amp;gi=sd</link>
      <description>A major data breach shows genetic information is vulnerable to attack</description>
      <author> (https://onezero.medium.com/@emilymullin)</author>
      <guid>https://onezero.medium.com/the-era-of-dna-database-hacks-is-here-85a860190622?source=social---tw.onezero&amp;gi=sd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 03:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour party has data compromised following Blackbaud hack | ITV News</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2020-07-30/labour-party-has-data-compromised-following-blackbaud-hack</link>
      <description>The party is among growing number of organisations to have their data breached following a cyber-attack on cloud computing provider BlackBaud.  </description>
      <author> (Shehab Khan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.itv.com/news/2020-07-30/labour-party-has-data-compromised-following-blackbaud-hack</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 02:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token authentication requirements for API and Git operations - The GitHub Blog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/2020-07-30-token-authentication-requirements-for-api-and-git-operations/</link>
      <description>Beginning November 13th, 2020, we will no longer accept account passwords when authenticating with the GitHub REST API. In the future, we will similarly no longer accept account passwords when authenticating Git operations.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/2020-07-30-token-authentication-requirements-for-api-and-git-operations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 01:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s problems are bigger than just the antitrust case</title>
      <link>https://www.economist.com/briefing/2020/07/30/googles-problems-are-bigger-than-just-the-antitrust-case</link>
      <description>As the computing conglomerate has grown, so too have the risks that it becomes more like a conventional company</description>
      <author> (Jul 30th 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://www.economist.com/briefing/2020/07/30/googles-problems-are-bigger-than-just-the-antitrust-case</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure/CloudShell</title>
      <link>https://github.com/azure/cloudshell</link>
      <description>Container Image for Azure Cloud Shell (https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/features/cloud-shell/) - Azure/CloudShell</description>
      <author> (Azure)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/azure/cloudshell</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libraries lend books, and must continue to lend books: Internet Archive responds to publishers’ lawsuit - Internet Archive Blogs</title>
      <link>https://blog.archive.org/2020/07/29/internet-archive-responds-to-publishers-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>Yesterday, the Internet Archive filed our response to the lawsuit brought by four commercial publishers to end the practice of Controlled Digital Lending (CDL), the digital equivalent of traditional library lending. CDL is a respectful and secure way to bring the breadth of our library collections to digital learners. Commercial ebooks, while useful, only cover […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.archive.org/2020/07/29/internet-archive-responds-to-publishers-lawsuit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 23:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Windows 10 Insider Preview Build 20170 | Windows Experience Blog</title>
      <link>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2020/07/15/announcing-windows-10-insider-preview-build-20170/</link>
      <description>Hello Windows Insiders, today we’re releasing Windows 10 Insider Preview Build 20170 to Windows Insiders in the Dev Channel. PLEASE NOTE: Windows Insiders with PCs that have AMD processors will not be offered this build today due to a bug impacting overall usability of these PCs. The issue should be fixed for the next flight. …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2020/07/15/announcing-windows-10-insider-preview-build-20170/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>