<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Synchronise using Queues or Semaphores?</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=okXbHqRQ6Mo</link>
      <description>Never used Queue&amp;#39;s for synchronisation? would you like to know when to use one over a Semaphore?Support my Work  &amp;#129309; https://www.patreon.com/raw_codingBuy my ...</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Mechanics
  
  
  
    Microsoft Mechanics
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=okXbHqRQ6Mo</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is Jepsen Written in Clojure?</title>
      <link>https://aphyr.com/posts/367-why-is-jepsen-written-in-clojure</link>
      <description>People keep asking why Jepsen is written in Clojure, so I figure it’s worth having a referencable answer. I’ve programmed in something like twenty languages. Why choose a Weird Lisp?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aphyr.com/posts/367-why-is-jepsen-written-in-clojure</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 13:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchmarkDotNet v0.13.11 &amp;#183; dotnet/BenchmarkDotNet &amp;#183; Discussion #2479</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/BenchmarkDotNet/discussions/2479</link>
      <description>Full changelog: https://benchmarkdotnet.org/changelog/v0.13.11.html In the v0.13.11 scope, 4 issues were resolved and 8 pull requests were merged. This release includes 28 commits by 7 contributors...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/BenchmarkDotNet/discussions/2479</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 12:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your GitHub pull request workflow is slowing everyone down</title>
      <link>https://graphite.dev/blog/your-github-pr-workflow-is-slow</link>
      <description> Optimize your GitHub pull request workflow with this step-by-step guide. Improve collaboration &amp;amp; code review.</description>
      <author> (Written by)</author>
      <guid>https://graphite.dev/blog/your-github-pr-workflow-is-slow</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf 2023 Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://dotnetconf.study4.tw/</link>
      <description>這一年一次的 .NET Conf 世界級盛會台灣不會缺席！由 STUDY4 組織的台灣 .NET Conf 開發人員線上活動，快來慶祝並了解新版本帶來的優秀開發體驗吧！</description>
      <author> (STUDY4)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetconf.study4.tw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLite Forum: JSONB has landed</title>
      <link>https://sqlite.org/forum/forumpost/fa6f64e3dc1a5d97</link>
      <description>JSONB is a rewrite of the SQLite JSON functions
that, depending on usage patterns, could be several times faster
than the original JSON functions.  This enhancement has now
landed on trunk.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sqlite.org/forum/forumpost/fa6f64e3dc1a5d97</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Switch Between .NET SDK Versions</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/dotnet-switch-between-sdk-versions/</link>
      <description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll learn how to switch between .NET SDK versions in our projects using global.json for explicit version control.</description>
      <author> (Lennart Pries)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/dotnet-switch-between-sdk-versions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arnold Schwarzenegger Sings About Rainbows</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=K_XwseDwmuQ&amp;si=zDE6LjTuBrj4loPz</link>
      <description>Arnold Schwarzenegger used to live in KansasVoice by @JoeGaudet For more vids follow BrianMonarch on Insta :)For parody use only.</description>
      <author> (brianmonarch
  
  
  
    brianmonarch
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=K_XwseDwmuQ&amp;si=zDE6LjTuBrj4loPz</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy a SpringBoot 3 API on AWS Lambda in 10 minutes</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HQQD4dndDpE</link>
      <description>SpringBoot is the most widely used application framework in Java, but did you know you can your SpringBoot 3 applications built with Java 21 on AWS Lambda in...</description>
      <author> (Rust Dublin
  
  
  
    Rust Dublin
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HQQD4dndDpE</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a JavaScript Master: Essential 10 Tips for Mastery the Language!</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/educator-developer-blog/become-a-javascript-master-essential-10-tips-for-mastery-the/ba-p/3996356</link>
      <description>JavaScript is a programming language that has been gaining many followers year after year! In this article I will be giving some fundamental tips on how you..</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/321336)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/educator-developer-blog/become-a-javascript-master-essential-10-tips-for-mastery-the/ba-p/3996356</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build and deploy .NET 8 Blazor WASM apps with serverless APIs using Azure Static Web Apps</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/build-and-deploy-net-8-blazor-wasm-apps-with-serverless-apis/ba-p/3988412</link>
      <description>With .NET 8, we can build and host full-stack .NET 8 applications with Blazor WASM and serverless Functions APIs on Azure Static Web Apps.&amp;#160;In this article,..</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/1310795)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/build-and-deploy-net-8-blazor-wasm-apps-with-serverless-apis/ba-p/3988412</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#129302; Does Functional Programming Matter To You?</title>
      <link>https://robconery.com/software-design/does-functional-programming-still-matter/</link>
      <description>Learning Elixir changed me as a programmer, and learning functional concepts changed the way I think about writing software. How about you? Is functional proogramming a useful thing to learn?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robconery.com/software-design/does-functional-programming-still-matter/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Regular Expressions and Match Evaluators in .NET</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/how-to-use-regular-expressions-and-match-evaluators-in-dotnet</link>
      <description>Using the RegEx.Replace method with MatchEvaluator</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/how-to-use-regular-expressions-and-match-evaluators-in-dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sneaky async void Leads to ASP.NET Core Crash</title>
      <link>https://joshthecoder.com/2023/12/01/sneaky-async-void-leads-to-aspnetcore-crash.html</link>
      <description>I had a production issue at work recently where an ASP.NET Core application would crash periodically. It was a fairly tricky issue because it appeared to be crashing due to an unhandled exception in a Controller method - which shouldn’t crash the app pool, it should be handled by ASP.NET Core and return an error to the browser. Setup To start, I’ll create a web API service with: dotnet new webapi --use-controllers -o CrashyApi Now I’ll create a class that has an HttpClient as a dependency: public class SpecialService { private readonly HttpClient _httpClient; public SpecialService(HttpClient httpClient) { _httpClient = httpClient; } } Then I’ll add the class to DI: builder.Services.AddTransient&amp;lt;SpecialService&amp;gt;(); Next, I’m going to configure an anonymous factory method that fills out the base address of the HttpClient from appsettings.json. This is to keep things simple in the class - calls can use relative URIs, rather than needing to specify the full target domain: builder.Services.AddHttpClient&amp;lt;SpecialService&amp;gt;((provider, client) =&amp;gt; { using var scope = provider.CreateScope(); var config = scope.ServiceProvider.GetRequiredService&amp;lt;IConfiguration&amp;gt;(); var baseUrl = config[&amp;quot;SpecialBaseUrl&amp;quot;]; if (string.IsNullOrWhiteSpace(baseUrl)) return; client.BaseAddress = new Uri(baseUrl); }); That factory method will get called any time the DI container is asked to resolve an instance of the SpecialService class. Finally, I have a Controller endpoint that calls a method on my service, which just returns the configured base address (for simplicity’s sake): [ApiController] [Route(&amp;quot;[controller]&amp;quot;)] public class TestController : ControllerBase { private readonly SpecialService _specialService; public TestController(SpecialService specialService) { _specialService = specialService; } [HttpGet(Name = &amp;quot;GetBaseAddress&amp;quot;)] public string Get() { return _specialService.GetBaseAddress(); } } This works great, I can test it in the Swagger UI: Feature Change Now we have decided to get the base address from a DB instead of a configuration file. That’s an easy code change, in principle. We have EF Core, so we can resolve the context instead of the IConfiguration, and then query the DB. The updated factory code looks like this: builder.Services.AddHttpClient&amp;lt;SpecialService&amp;gt;(async (provider, client) =&amp;gt; { using var scope = provider.CreateScope(); using var context = scope.ServiceProvider.GetRequiredService&amp;lt;DefaultEFContext&amp;gt;(); var setting = await context.Settings.SingleAsync(s =&amp;gt; s.SettingName == &amp;quot;SpecialBaseUrl&amp;quot;); var baseUrl = setting.SettingValue; if (string.IsNullOrWhiteSpace(baseUrl)) return; client.BaseAddress = new Uri(baseUrl); }); I’ll also make everything on the consuming side async, to more accurately match the real scenario: [HttpGet(Name = &amp;quot;GetBaseAddress&amp;quot;)] public async Task&amp;lt;string&amp;gt; Get() { return await _specialService.GetBaseAddressAsync(); } This also works fine! Swagger UI results look the same (I won’t bother repeating the screenshot). However, if the SQL Server is unavailable for any reason, that query in the factory method will throw an Exception (as one would expect). Something that’s not necessarily obvious from the code there is that the anonymous method is an async void method, which will crash the entire process (if you’re running in IIS, that’s the w3wp.exe process hosting the .NET application) in the face of an unhandled Exception. This is pretty bad news, as often a SQL Server error can be transient - especially running in the cloud, where flaky networks and slow disks abound. About async void Any unhandled Exception can crash a process. However, when working with ASP.NET Core, it’s easy to expect that normal user requests hitting controller endpoints are not vulnerable to this. The framework will eventually handle the Exception and return a 500 error response. An async void method violates this expectation, because it runs on a separate thread, and thus try-catch blocks in the calling code can’t catch Exceptions thrown from the method (the calling method has already moved on). This is explained in the documentation, as well as why a Task-returning method does work normally with Exception handling: The caller of a void-returning async method can’t catch exceptions thrown from the method. Such unhandled exceptions are likely to cause your application to fail. If a method that returns a Task or Task&amp;lt;TResult&amp;gt; throws an exception, the exception is stored in the returned task. The exception is rethrown when the task is awaited. Make sure that any async method that can produce an exception has a return type of Task or Task&amp;lt;TResult&amp;gt; and that calls to the method are awaited. Fixing You can avoid this problem by: wrapping the contents of the anonymous method in a try-catch block using the synchronous APIs instead, and removing the async-await from the anonymous method I went with the second approach, as there is really no need for that factory to be async - it was just made that way out of a habit of using the async EF Core APIs. Here’s the updated code: builder.Services.AddHttpClient&amp;lt;SpecialService&amp;gt;((provider, client) =&amp;gt; { using var scope = provider.CreateScope(); using var context = scope.ServiceProvider.GetRequiredService&amp;lt;DefaultEFContext&amp;gt;(); var setting = context.Settings.Single(s =&amp;gt; s.SettingName == &amp;quot;SpecialBaseUrl&amp;quot;); var baseUrl = setting.SettingValue; if (string.IsNullOrWhiteSpace(baseUrl)) return; client.BaseAddress = new Uri(baseUrl); }); Now, if even if there is an issue contacting the SQL Server, the browser will just get a 500 error, which the application can handle (by allowing a retry, showing an error message, etc.): Summary Avoid async void like the plague. It’s confusing and awful. Be especially careful when using APIs that accept an Action as a parameter, as these are void-returning delegates, are easy to make async, and it’s not nearly as obvious that you need to deal with the caveats of async void when this comes up.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joshthecoder.com/2023/12/01/sneaky-async-void-leads-to-aspnetcore-crash.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting C# Ranges</title>
      <link>https://humbletoolsmith.com/2023/12/03/dissecting-csharp-ranges/</link>
      <description>Technical Web Development Blog</description>
      <author> (Eric Potter)</author>
      <guid>https://humbletoolsmith.com/2023/12/03/dissecting-csharp-ranges/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and Trust - Schneier on Security</title>
      <link>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/12/ai-and-trust.html</link>
      <description>I trusted a lot today. I trusted my phone to wake me on time. I trusted Uber to arrange a taxi for me, and the driver to get me to the airport safely. I trusted thousands of other drivers on the road not to ram my car on the way. At the airport, I trusted ticket agents and maintenance engineers and everyone else who keeps airlines operating. And the pilot of the plane I flew in. And thousands of other people at the airport and on the plane, any of which could have attacked me. And all the people that prepared and served my breakfast, and the entire food supply chain—any of them could have poisoned me. When I landed here, I trusted thousands more people: at the airport, on the road, in this building, in this room. And that was all before 10:30 this morning.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/12/ai-and-trust.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Highland Song for Nintendo Switch - Nintendo Official Site</title>
      <link>https://www.nintendo.com/us/store/products/a-highland-song-switch/</link>
      <description>Buy A Highland Song and shop other great Nintendo products online at the official My Nintendo Store.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nintendo.com/us/store/products/a-highland-song-switch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>avoid allocations for TLS handshake by wfurt &amp;#183; Pull Request #87874 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/87874#event-11161738561</link>
      <description>There are several places where we use Span.ToArray() to get data returned by native layer to something we can write to underlying stream. One day, we may write Memory&amp;lt;byte&amp;gt; wrapper but for now I re...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/87874#event-11161738561</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Functions Flex Consumption (Private Preview)</title>
      <link>https://forms.office.com/pages/responsepage.aspx?id=v4j5cvGGr0GRqy180BHbR7G0fdH_ORJPojP1kEoyvuBUOENZU0M1UTUwMTJRWURNOElSN1pLQk5aTy4u</link>
      <description>Flex Consumption is a new Azure Functions hosting option that builds on the consumption &amp;#39;pay for what you use&amp;#39; serverless billing model and gives users more flexibility and customizability without compromising on available features.&amp;#160;The service is currently in private preview, with public preview scheduled before the end of 2023 (tentative). Please use this form if you would like to be onboarded for the preview.This feature preview has no SLA provided during the preview. Please DO NOT use the preview features in any production or critical environments.&amp;#160;Participation requires transferring your data to other countries in which Microsoft operates, including the United States.&amp;#160; By submitting this form, you agree to the transfer of your data outside your country. Microsoft Privacy Statement&amp;#160;https://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=521839. For questions and feedback, please reach out to us here&amp;#160;flexconsumptionprev@microsoft.com</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://forms.office.com/pages/responsepage.aspx?id=v4j5cvGGr0GRqy180BHbR7G0fdH_ORJPojP1kEoyvuBUOENZU0M1UTUwMTJRWURNOElSN1pLQk5aTy4u</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C++ From Scratch</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLxNPSjHT5qvvIGGhRnFOGA4CbX1oTrt6z</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (CoffeeBeforeArch
  
  
  
    CoffeeBeforeArch
  






    •
    6.3K views • 1 year ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLxNPSjHT5qvvIGGhRnFOGA4CbX1oTrt6z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DasBlog’s upgrade to .NET 8 is ready!</title>
      <link>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/dasblogs-upgrade-to-net-8-is-ready</link>
      <description>I am pleased to share that DasBlog has been upgraded to support .NET 8! It has ...</description>
      <author> (Mark Downie)</author>
      <guid>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/dasblogs-upgrade-to-net-8-is-ready</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine Tuning Mistral 7B on Magic the Gathering Drafts</title>
      <link>https://generallyintelligent.substack.com/p/fine-tuning-mistral-7b-on-magic-the</link>
      <description>Tips, examples, and thoughts from an exploration of the world of fine tuning</description>
      <author> (David Hershey)</author>
      <guid>https://generallyintelligent.substack.com/p/fine-tuning-mistral-7b-on-magic-the</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 02:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Truncation and Wrapping in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://askxammy.com/text-truncation-and-wrapping-in-net-maui/</link>
      <description>Imagine an app without text; it would be practically non-functional, wouldn&amp;#39;t it? &amp;#129335;‍♀️ Text is an essential element in any application, and handling it appropriately according to different requirements is very important. In this article, we will focus on techniques for truncating and wrapping text using the LineBreakMode property to enhance the readability of our text. Let&amp;#39;s get started! &amp;#128640;

Let’s start!
What is the LineBreakMode?
This property allows you to control the wrapping and truncation of the text. Accepts an enumeration as a value, which contains the following values:
➖ NoWrap
Its responsibility is to display only the text that fits on the device’s first line. This means the amount of text visible on the first line may vary depending on the size device. – [It’s the default value].



➖ WordWrap
These values automatically move text to the next line at the word boundary. This prevents words from being cut off at the end of a line, enhancing readability and allowing text to adapt to various screen sizes.



➖ CharacterWrap
Unlike the WordWrap function, this setting automatically transfers text to the next line based on a character limit. This sometimes results in line breaks that do not align with entire words.




➖ HeadTruncation
It omits the beginning of the text, presenting only the final part in a single line. It’s best used when the text’s conclusion is most relevant to the reader, ensuring focus on the most pertinent information.




➖ MiddleTruncation
Unify the beginning and end of the text to fit within a single line, replacing the middle section with an ellipsis, which consists of three dots (...)



➖ TailTruncation


It omits the end of the text, presenting only the initial part on a single line.








And our article is completed! &amp;#160;.
Thanks for ready! &amp;#128075; See you next time! &amp;#128154;&amp;#128149;
Spanish post:



➖ https://es.askxammy.com/truncamiento-y-ajuste-de-texto-en-net-maui/
Reference:
➖ https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/maui/user-interface/controls/label?view=net-maui-8.0?WT.mc_id=DT-MVP-50033
</description>
      <author> (About Leomaris Reyes)</author>
      <guid>https://askxammy.com/text-truncation-and-wrapping-in-net-maui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to Note Before Migrating Servers</title>
      <link>https://blog.akshaykaushik.eu.org/things-to-note-before-migrating-servers</link>
      <description>Learn how to migrate servers like a pro with this comprehensive guide. Covers everything from assessing infrastructure to deploying applications.</description>
      <author> (Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.akshaykaushik.eu.org/things-to-note-before-migrating-servers</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Text Editor: the Gap Buffer</title>
      <link>https://workdad.dev/posts/building-a-text-editor-the-gap-buffer/</link>
      <description>Prologue: The Agon 8-bit computer In December of 2022 I came across a new 8-bit computer called Agon. It was built around the eZ80 CPU, a modern version of the venerable Z80 processor that was popular in many 1980s microcomputers, and an ESP32 microcontroller for video generation using FabGL (now vdp-gl, a fork of FabGL maintained by me). The original Z80 was an 8 bit CPU with a 16 bit address bus, allowing it to access up to 64KiB of memory at a time.</description>
      <author> (Igor Cananea)</author>
      <guid>https://workdad.dev/posts/building-a-text-editor-the-gap-buffer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Startups are Empathetic</title>
      <link>https://www.ch3ngl0rd.com/empathy/</link>
      <description>TLDR: Success in startups hinges on empathy and truly understanding user needs, while setting aside ego.
It&amp;#39;s an open secret in the startup world that succes...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ch3ngl0rd.com/empathy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;m Not Participating in This Year&amp;#39;s Advent of Code For Very Good Reasons</title>
      <link>https://www.jasonscheirer.com/weblog/not-participating-in-advent-of-code/</link>
      <description>I’m exhausted. I’ve been guilted/peer pressured into participating in the AoC for at least 5 years. I’m tired, I’m defeated, I’m unable to meet its weird expectations consistently and still I remain a competent software engineer.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jasonscheirer.com/weblog/not-participating-in-advent-of-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arnold Schwarzenegger Sings About Rainbows</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/K_XwseDwmuQ</link>
      <description>Arnold Schwarzenegger used to live in KansasVoice by @JoeGaudet For more vids follow BrianMonarch on Insta :)For parody use only.</description>
      <author> (brianmonarch
  
  
  
    brianmonarch
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/K_XwseDwmuQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Responds to Fine Woven Case Problem</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/eMEahWU4mrM</link>
      <description>Apple responds to complaints about the new iPhone 15 Fine Woven case scratching easily. Turns out it’s not that fine at all!Apple Responds to iPhone Bending:...</description>
      <author> (CNBC Television
  
  
  
    CNBC Television
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/eMEahWU4mrM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arnold Schwarzenegger Sings About Rainbows</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=K_XwseDwmuQ</link>
      <description>Arnold Schwarzenegger used to live in KansasVoice by @JoeGaudet For more vids follow BrianMonarch on Insta :)For parody use only.</description>
      <author> (brianmonarch
  
  
  
    brianmonarch
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=K_XwseDwmuQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Explores a &amp;#39;Reboot of Compute&amp;#39; in Cloud with WebAssembly -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/12/05/wasm-cloud.aspx</link>
      <description>WebAssembly made Microsoft&amp;#39;s Blazor framework possible by enabling C#-based web development, and now the company wants it to completely remake cloud computing.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel12/05/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/12/05/wasm-cloud.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Online Malware Analysis Sandbox - ANY.RUN</title>
      <link>https://app.any.run/</link>
      <description>Cloud-based malware analysis service. Take your information security to the next level. Analyze suspicious and malicious activities using our innovative tools.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://app.any.run/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 22:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Responds to Fine Woven Case Problem</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=eMEahWU4mrM&amp;si=XSNKBalbR3L5i-vw</link>
      <description>Apple responds to complaints about the new iPhone 15 Fine Woven case scratching easily. Turns out it’s not that fine at all!Apple Responds to iPhone Bending:...</description>
      <author> (Andrew Clare
  
  
  
    Andrew Clare
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=eMEahWU4mrM&amp;si=XSNKBalbR3L5i-vw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 22:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Updates for .NET Devs | .NET Conf 2023</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Ki4Wv-neAsw</link>
      <description>There&amp;#39;s so much new good stuff in Visual Studio for .NET developers - Endpoint Explorer, Dev Tunnels, REST endpoint testing with .http files, and more!Repo -...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Ki4Wv-neAsw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 22:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iMessage, explained</title>
      <link>https://jjtech.dev/reverse-engineering/imessage-explained/</link>
      <description>This blog post is going to be a cursory overview of the internals iMessage, as I’ve discovered during my work on pypush, an open source project that reimplements iMessage.</description>
      <author> (JJTech)</author>
      <guid>https://jjtech.dev/reverse-engineering/imessage-explained/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 22:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women In Linux</title>
      <link>https://inv.vern.cc/channel/UCRaYM8wu6KPp1AFsU6bZqdw</link>
      <description>Women In Linux is a non-profit organization supporting women in Linux-centric tech careers who want to obtain and sustain a thriving career in tech.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://inv.vern.cc/channel/UCRaYM8wu6KPp1AFsU6bZqdw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 22:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET R&amp;amp;D Digest (November, 2023)</title>
      <link>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2023/12/04/net-rd-digest-november-2023/</link>
      <description>This issue includes bits of AI,&amp;#160;stories, operating systems, diagnostics, low-level optimisations, IaC, videos and .NET.</description>
      <author> (Oleg Karasik)</author>
      <guid>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2023/12/04/net-rd-digest-november-2023/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and Mass Spying - Schneier on Security</title>
      <link>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/12/ai-and-mass-spying.html</link>
      <description>Spying and surveillance are different but related things. If I hired a private detective to spy on you, that detective could hide a bug in your home or car, tap your phone, and listen to what you said. At the end, I would get a report of all the conversations you had and the contents of those conversations. If I hired that same private detective to put you under surveillance, I would get a different report: where you went, whom you talked to, what you purchased, what you did.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/12/ai-and-mass-spying.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform Live Stream</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=i68wLprbuCg</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Uno Platform
  
  
  
    Uno Platform
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=i68wLprbuCg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beeper Mini - iMessage on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.beeper.com/</link>
      <description>Finally, get blue bubbles on Android! Your Android phone number is now blue. Join iPhone-only group chats, send full size media and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.beeper.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What was the code name for 64-bit Windows? - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231205-00/?p=109103</link>
      <description>Sundown, which was a hidden jab at the competition.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231205-00/?p=109103</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 18:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox on the&amp;#160;brink? | BryceWray.com</title>
      <link>https://www.brycewray.com/posts/2023/11/firefox-brink/</link>
      <description>The Big&amp;#160;Three may effectively be&amp;#160;down to&amp;#160;a Big&amp;#160;Two, and&amp;#160;right&amp;#160;quick.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.brycewray.com/posts/2023/11/firefox-brink/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 17:03:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>q3k :blobcatcoffee: (@q3k@hackerspace.pl)</title>
      <link>https://social.hackerspace.pl/@q3k/111528162462505087</link>
      <description>Attached: 1 image

I can finally reveal some research I&amp;#39;ve been involved with over the past year or so.

We (@redford@infosec.exchange, @mrtick@infosec.exchange and I) have reverse engineered the PLC code of NEWAG Impuls EMUs. These trains were locking up for arbitrary reasons after being serviced at third-party workshops. The manufacturer argued that this was because of malpractice by these workshops, and that they should be serviced by them instead of third parties.

1/4</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://social.hackerspace.pl/@q3k/111528162462505087</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating the first year of Copilot with significant new innovations - The Official Microsoft Blog</title>
      <link>https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/12/05/celebrating-the-first-year-of-copilot-with-significant-new-innovations/</link>
      <description>This year will be remembered as the moment that we, as individuals, began to harness the power of AI in our daily lives. The last 10 months reflect years of AI research, close partnerships, and breakthrough innovations coming together. This culmination is now unifying our product vision to empower every person and every organization on...</description>
      <author> (Yusuf Medhi)</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/12/05/celebrating-the-first-year-of-copilot-with-significant-new-innovations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - bradygaster/AugmentR: Sample showing how to do Retrieval Augmented Generation using .NET Aspire, Semantic Kernel, and OpenAI.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/bradygaster/AugmentR</link>
      <description>Sample showing how to do Retrieval Augmented Generation using .NET Aspire, Semantic Kernel, and OpenAI. - GitHub - bradygaster/AugmentR: Sample showing how to do Retrieval Augmented Generation usin...</description>
      <author> (bradygaster)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/bradygaster/AugmentR</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Build Resilient Cloud Applications With .NET 8</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pgeHRp2Otlc</link>
      <description>&amp;#128187;Join me on Patreon to get the source code: https://www.patreon.com/juliocasal&amp;#128293;My Free .NET Backend Developer Roadmap: https://juliocasal.com/roadmapIf you...</description>
      <author> (Julio Casal
  
  
  
    Julio Casal
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pgeHRp2Otlc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to (and how not to) design REST APIs</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=60F8rzP5nQo</link>
      <description>Everyone seems to love best practices or rules around how to design REST APIs. But is all this guidance good advice? Well, let&amp;#39;s find out.&amp;#128279; EventStoreDBhttp...</description>
      <author> (Lee Robinson
  
  
  
    Lee Robinson
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=60F8rzP5nQo</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inline Snapshot testing in .NET - G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/inline-snapshot-testing-in-dotnet.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to use Inline Snapshot testing in .NET. Inline Snapshot testing is a technique that allows you to write tests that assert the output of a method or function. The output is stored in a snapshot file. The next time the test is run, the output is compared to the snapshot file. If the output is different, the test fails. If the output is the same, the test passes.&amp;quot;
</description>
      <author> (G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/inline-snapshot-testing-in-dotnet.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instrumenting .NET Kafka Clients with OpenTelemetry and KafkaFlow</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HOivyibM-04</link>
      <description>How can we instrument Apache Kafka Producers and Consumers on our .NET applications? In this video, I show you how to use the KafkaFlow OpenTelemetry package...</description>
      <author> (NDC Conferences
  
  
  
    NDC Conferences
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HOivyibM-04</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examples Of The Visitor Pattern In C# – A Practical Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/12/05/examples-of-the-visitor-pattern-in-c-a-practical-guide/</link>
      <description>The Visitor Pattern is a very handy design pattern! Check out the examples of the visitor pattern in C# in this article to solidify your understanding!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/12/05/examples-of-the-visitor-pattern-in-c-a-practical-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fetching and Publishing Settings for Azure Functions with Azure Functions Core Tools Command Line</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/fetching-and-publishing-settings-for-azure-functions-with-azure-functions-core-tools-command-line-4akj</link>
      <description>During my daily activities I develop a lot of Azure Functions. Every time I struggle to synchronize...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/fetching-and-publishing-settings-for-azure-functions-with-azure-functions-core-tools-command-line-4akj</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>