<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Blur All the Way Down</title>
      <link>https://www.osar.fr/notes/motionblur/</link>
      <description>Pierre Cusa &amp;lt;pierre@osar.fr&amp;gt;
				
				November 2022  (history)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.osar.fr/notes/motionblur/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 16:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the next generation of Claude</title>
      <link>https://www.anthropic.com/news/claude-3-family</link>
      <description>Anthropic is an AI safety and research company that&amp;#39;s working to build reliable, interpretable, and steerable AI systems.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.anthropic.com/news/claude-3-family</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 16:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Run Your Benchmarks - 2 Ways To Run BenchmarkDotNet</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Hqeq9ycqteQ</link>
      <description>BenchmarkDotNet is the gold standard for being able to benchmark our C# code. It greatly simplified the process of creating a benchmark for C# code we&amp;#39;re int...</description>
      <author> (Jeff Geerling
  
  
  
    Jeff Geerling
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Hqeq9ycqteQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET MAUI: painfully slow debugging resolved with speedscope</title>
      <link>https://www.sharpnado.com/net-maui-painfully-slow-debugging/</link>
      <description>If you experiment long painful startup times, or even very long view construction times during your app lifetime when debugging, you can enable XAMLC again by setting a hidden property.</description>
      <author> (Jean-Marie Alfonsi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sharpnado.com/net-maui-painfully-slow-debugging/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 8  &amp;#128165;  - ASP.NET Core Web API Filters</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ZvxXK0AuFIQ</link>
      <description>In this video we will be going to be exploring Filters in ASP.Net core, will discuss different types of Filters and how we can utilise ordering.Support me on...</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand
  
  
  
    Mohamad Lawand
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ZvxXK0AuFIQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 14:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Operators in C#: How To Simplify Type Conversions</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/04/implicit-operators-in-c-how-to-simplify-type-conversions/</link>
      <description>Learn how to perform implicit conversions by using implicit operators in C#. This is a helpful feature that can enhance readability when done with care.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/04/implicit-operators-in-c-how-to-simplify-type-conversions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 14:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Way To Append Arrays in C#</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=R5Shxt1dx58</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=R5Shxt1dx58</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 13:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Court Issues Damages Award for Violation of GPL</title>
      <link>https://heathermeeker.com/2024/02/17/french-court-issues-damages-award-for-violation-of-gpl/</link>
      <description>On February 14, 2024, the Court of Appeal of Paris issued an order stating that Orange, a major French telecom provider, had infringed the copyight of Entr’Ouvert’s Lasso software and violate…</description>
      <author> (Author: heatherjmeeker)</author>
      <guid>https://heathermeeker.com/2024/02/17/french-court-issues-damages-award-for-violation-of-gpl/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interesting ideas in Observable Framework</title>
      <link>https://simonwillison.net/2024/Mar/3/interesting-ideas-in-observable-framework/</link>
      <description>Mike Bostock, Announcing: Observable Framework: Today we’re launching Observable 2.0 with a bold new vision: an open-source static site generator for building fast, beautiful data apps, dashboards, and reports. Our …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://simonwillison.net/2024/Mar/3/interesting-ideas-in-observable-framework/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 09:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The hater’s guide to Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://paulbutler.org/2024/the-haters-guide-to-kubernetes/</link>
      <description>Among a certain tech set, Kubernetes has earned a reputation as an unnecessarily complicated time-sink that startups should avoid. Using Kubernetes with a small team is seen as a sign of over-engineering.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://paulbutler.org/2024/the-haters-guide-to-kubernetes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 09:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marten 7.0 is Released!</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/03/03/marten-7-0-is-released/</link>
      <description>Marten 7.0 is released to the wild as of right now! Before getting into the highlights of what’s improved in this release, let’s go right to thanking some of the folks who made big cont…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/03/03/marten-7-0-is-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 06:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Init for ASP.NET Core Compared to VS or VS Code Extensions</title>
      <link>http://thedatafarm.com/docker/docker-init-for-asp-net-core-compared-to-vs-or-vs-code-extensions/</link>
      <description>Docker began introducing a new CLI command, docker init, allowing us to easily build stake-in-the-ground Dockerfile, docker-compose and .dockerignore files for a project. As the documentation says,…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://thedatafarm.com/docker/docker-init-for-asp-net-core-compared-to-vs-or-vs-code-extensions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 06:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why F# is a fun programming language</title>
      <link>https://hamy.xyz/labs/2024-02_fsharp-is-fun</link>
      <description>F# is often described as a fun programming language. I&amp;#39;ve personally described it thus many times.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hamy.xyz/labs/2024-02_fsharp-is-fun</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 06:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Log in, log out</title>
      <link>https://blog.mavnn.co.uk/2024/03/01/dev_journal_4.html</link>
      <description>This post is part of the &amp;quot;Dev Journal&amp;quot; series. Part 1 contains the series index, while the DevJournal4 tag for the CalDance project in GitLab holds the state of the repository as described here.</description>
      <author> (Michael Newton)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.mavnn.co.uk/2024/03/01/dev_journal_4.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 06:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS for printing to paper</title>
      <link>https://voussoir.net/writing/css_for_printing</link>
      <description>Back to writing</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://voussoir.net/writing/css_for_printing</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 06:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maybe possible bug in std::shared_mutex on Windows</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/cpp/comments/1b55686/maybe_possible_bug_in_stdshared_mutex_on_windows/</link>
      <description>A team at my company ran into a peculiar and unexpected behavior with `std::shared_mutex`. This behavior only occurs on Windows w/ MSVC. It does...</description>
      <author> (forrestthewoods)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/cpp/comments/1b55686/maybe_possible_bug_in_stdshared_mutex_on_windows/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 04:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposal: `TimeSpan` literals &amp;#183; dotnet/csharplang &amp;#183; Discussion #7982</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/csharplang/discussions/7982</link>
      <description>Intro: ubiquitous and rock solid There&amp;#39;s a common value type that has become ubiquitous when working with anything from database calls, network calls, rest/graphql apis, caches, delays, timeouts an...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/csharplang/discussions/7982</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 04:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standalone Aspire dashboard sample app - Code Samples</title>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/samples/dotnet/aspire-samples/aspire-standalone-dashboard/</link>
      <description>A sample of using the Aspire dashboard to view telemetry from non-Aspire apps.</description>
      <author> (VSC-Service-Account)</author>
      <guid>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/samples/dotnet/aspire-samples/aspire-standalone-dashboard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 04:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Feature Will Make Your Code Safer</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dfT8UwS9PAw</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dfT8UwS9PAw</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 01:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Lessons I learned the hard way from 6 years as a software engineer</title>
      <link>https://careercutler.substack.com/p/5-lessons-i-learned-the-hard-way</link>
      <description>Hey there, Jordan here &amp;#128075;. You’re probably familiar with most of my articles being a “how-to” guide. Those guides come from my real-world experience and lessons I learned—usually from mistakes I made. This article is going to cover the 5 biggest lessons</description>
      <author> (Jordan Cutler)</author>
      <guid>https://careercutler.substack.com/p/5-lessons-i-learned-the-hard-way</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to build a SaaS micro startup in 31 hours</title>
      <link>https://marclou.beehiiv.com/p/how-to-build-a-saas-micro-startup-in-days</link>
      <description>Here&amp;#39;s my solopreneur experience from getting SaaS ideas to launching and getting the first customer.</description>
      <author> (Marc Lou)</author>
      <guid>https://marclou.beehiiv.com/p/how-to-build-a-saas-micro-startup-in-days</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The unreasonable effectiveness of i3, or: ten years of a boring desktop environment</title>
      <link>https://blog.waleson.com/2024/03/the-unreasonable-effectiveness-of-i3-or.html</link>
      <description>My wife uses Windows and over the years I&amp;#39;ve helped her move things to new systems. Win8, 10 and now 11. With every change the UI changes. N...</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.waleson.com/2024/03/the-unreasonable-effectiveness-of-i3-or.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Issue 50: Reset your Social Media Annually</title>
      <link>https://www.bramadams.dev/issue-50/</link>
      <description>On the controlled burn of online profiles</description>
      <author> (Bram Adams)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bramadams.dev/issue-50/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fog of War: or, when being vague is useful</title>
      <link>https://blog.waleson.com/2024/03/the-fog-of-war-or-when-being-vague-is.html</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve always been a straight shooter. Perhaps it&amp;#39;s the Dutch culture or the protestant roots, but mystery, rituals and concepts annoy me. If ...</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.waleson.com/2024/03/the-fog-of-war-or-when-being-vague-is.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Math of Card Shuffling</title>
      <link>https://fredhohman.com/card-shuffling/</link>
      <description>Riffling from factory order to complete randomness.</description>
      <author> (By: Fred Hohman)</author>
      <guid>https://fredhohman.com/card-shuffling/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>37 Pieces of Career Advice I Wish I’d Known Earlier - RyanHoliday.net</title>
      <link>https://ryanholiday.net/37-pieces-of-career-advice-i-wish-id-known-earlier/</link>
      <description>From my first desk job working at my college newspaper. My first job was working at a small deli and grocery store in Lake Tahoe when I was 15. It was a job that came full circle some twenty years later when my wife and I bought a place called ​Tracy’s Drive-In Grocery​ in 2021, a little place that’s been in business since 1940. I’ve had my fair share of gigs in between. I worked in fast food. I was the director of marketing for a publicly traded company. I’ve been a lifeguard. I dropped out of college to be a research assistant to an author. I worked a desk at a talent agency in Beverly Hills. I’ve started multiple businesses. I’ve freelanced. I’ve been lucky enough to speak and consult with multi-billion dollar companies and Super Bowl winning sports franchises, family offices and law firms. I wouldn’t say I’ve done it all because that’s one thing you learn–how much you have left to learn–but I have done a lot. I’ve had to think a lot about how to be a good employee as well as how to be a good boss. I’ve seen what makes good companies succeed and bad companies fail. I’ve seen how people get ahead…and how people get stuff. I’ve also written a lot about this over the years, as I was figuring it out. In fact, many times I had to talk to bosses about this “little thing I do on the side” which was writing until eventually, the business stuff itself because of the stuff I do on the side. And now I have to have the conversation the other way with the people who work for me at ​Daily Stoic​ or ​Brass Check​ or at ​The Painted Porch​ or at ​Tracy’s​: Ok, but what do you really want to do and how can I help you get there? Anyway, this post is about that. The best of those lessons—things I wish I’d been told when I was just starting and things I still tell myself. Some of them might be exactly what you need to hear right now. Some might not apply to you yet, or ever. That’s okay. Whether you’re just starting out, looking to make a big change, or aiming to reach new heights in your current role, I hope you’ll find something here that helps you navigate your own unique path. Be quiet, work hard, and stay healthy. It’s not ambition or skill that is going to set you apart but sanity. I remember once I called Dov Charney, founder of American Apparel, about some little success I’d had on some project. He was very busy and frustrated that I’d interrupted, but politely, he said, “Ryan, you are calling me to tell me that you did your job.” I thought of that conversation when I saw that famous scene in Mad Men where Peggy complains that Don never says thank you. “That’s what the money is for!” he tells her. The thing that’s wrong about imposter syndrome is that for the most part no one is thinking about you at all. They’re too busy with their own doubts and their own work. When I was starting out as an assistant in Hollywood, someone told me that the best thing I could do was make my boss look good. Don’t worry about credit, they said. Forget credit so hard that you’re glad when other people get it instead of you. It ended up being pretty decent advice, but it was nowhere near the right wording. I think a better way to express it would be: ​Find canvases for other people to paint on​. Come up with ideas to hand over to your boss. Find people, thinkers, up and comers to introduce them to. Cross wires to create new sparks. Find what nobody else wants to do and do it. Find inefficiency and waste and redundancies. Identify leaks and patches to free up resources for new areas. Produce more than everyone else and give your ideas away. The person who clears the path ultimately controls its direction, just as the canvas shapes the painting. Very rarely have I ever let anyone go because they did not have the skills to do their job. It’s almost always their unwillingness to learn those skills or their inability to take feedback. When I was 20 years old, I was working at this talent agency in Hollywood, and I got invited to this important meeting. As they were talking about stuff, I interjected and said something. My mentor took me aside after and he said, why did you say that? Did you think it actually needed to be said or did you just feel like you wanted to have something to say? I think about that all the time. It’s in ​The 48 Laws of Power​ — Always say less than necessary. Saying less than necessary, not interjecting at every chance we get—this is actually the mark not just of a self-disciplined person, but also a very smart and wise person. The boss/mentor/biz can’t want you to succeed more than you want it. You have to be the driver of your own life/career/advancement. I was working full time at American Apparel but planning my next move, saving my money and thinking about writing a book. Over lunch one day, Robert Greene told me, Ryan, while people wait for the right moment, ​there are two types of time​: Dead time—where they are passive and biding and Alive time—where they are learning and acting and getting the most out of every second. Which will this be for you? When you’re lacking motivation, remind yourself: discipline now, freedom later. The labor will pass, and the rewards will last. When I first moved to Austin in 2013, I went out to lunch—fittingly—with a writer named Austin Kleon. I was a longtime fan of his book ​Steal Like an Artist​ (his book ​Keep Going​ is another favorite). After we ate, [...]</description>
      <author> (Ryan Holiday)</author>
      <guid>https://ryanholiday.net/37-pieces-of-career-advice-i-wish-id-known-earlier/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factfulness: A Paradigm Shift in Perceiving the World &amp;#128218;</title>
      <link>https://pooriat.com/posts/20240222/post1/</link>
      <description>Book Recommendation</description>
      <author> (Pooria Taghdiri)</author>
      <guid>https://pooriat.com/posts/20240222/post1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writers can write anything. Programmers can&amp;#39;t.</title>
      <link>https://www.mahendraker.com/blog/writing</link>
      <description>The difference between writing and coding.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mahendraker.com/blog/writing</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamming’s Reflection</title>
      <link>https://sameerismail.org/hamming</link>
      <description>Hamming’s Reflection</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sameerismail.org/hamming</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saved by NixOS Integration Tests, Surprisingly</title>
      <link>https://boinkor.net/2024/02/saved-by-nixos-integration-tests-surprisingly/</link>
      <description>Recently, tsnsrv has been getting a lot of high-quality
contributions
that add better support for Headscale and custom certificates, among
other things. As they always do when things change, bugs crept
in, and
frustratingly, not in a way that existing tests could have caught:
Instead of the go code (which has mildly decent test coverage), it was
bugs in the nixos module!
This was a great opportunity to investigate if we can test the tsnsrv
NixOS module, and maybe improve the baseline quality of the codebase
as a whole.
A recent blog post series on the NixOS test driver
(part1, part2) made the rounds
showing off what it can do, so this felt like a tractable project to
take on. Here’s my experience with it.</description>
      <author> (Andreas Fuchs)</author>
      <guid>https://boinkor.net/2024/02/saved-by-nixos-integration-tests-surprisingly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blameless culture should be a standard in the engineering industry</title>
      <link>https://newsletter.eng-leadership.com/p/blameless-culture-should-be-a-standard</link>
      <description>&amp;#127873; Incident Retrospective Template included!</description>
      <author> (Gregor Ojstersek)</author>
      <guid>https://newsletter.eng-leadership.com/p/blameless-culture-should-be-a-standard</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve resources page performance with many resources by JamesNK &amp;#183; Pull Request #2556 &amp;#183; dotnet/aspire</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/2556</link>
      <description>The dashboard resource&amp;#39;s page subscribes to resource updates. Along with the subscription is a collection of initial data that were cached resources.
This didn&amp;#39;t work quite as intended. The subscri...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/2556</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confronting Imposter Syndrome: The Reality of Feeling Inadequate in Software Development</title>
      <link>https://soumowatitallah1.substack.com/p/confronting-imposter-syndrome-the?triedRedirect=true</link>
      <description>Whether you call it imposter syndrome or simply your jerkbrain acting up, we all have our moments of feeling like a fake and that, someday, everyone will find out. And at it turns out, one of the professions most prone to imposter syndrome is software development.</description>
      <author> (Sharon Fisher)</author>
      <guid>https://soumowatitallah1.substack.com/p/confronting-imposter-syndrome-the?triedRedirect=true</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 17:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using ChatGPT and GitHub Copilot to Generate the XAML for your Windows application - Nick&amp;#39;s .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/chatgpt-copilot-xaml/</link>
      <description>In this post I’m going to experiment using ChatGPT and Copilot to help generate the XAML for pages in a Windows application. Since we’ll be using WinUI and the Windows App SDK, the application can be extended to support other platforms via the&amp;#160;Uno Platform.&amp;#160; ChatGPT We’ll start by using ChatGPT (in this case ChatGPT v3.5) ... Read more</description>
      <author> (Nick)</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/chatgpt-copilot-xaml/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 17:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>