<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Hunt: &amp;#39;De Adobe-breach kwam precies goed uit voor Have I been Pwned&amp;#39;</title>
      <link>https://tweakers.net/reviews/8620/troy-hunt-de-adobe-breach-kwam-precies-goed-uit-voor-have-i-been-pwned.html</link>
      <description>Troy Hunt is oprichter en enige beheerder van Have I Been Pwned, met miljarden records en tienduizenden bezoekers per dag. Hoe onderhoud je zoiets naast je werk?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tweakers.net/reviews/8620/troy-hunt-de-adobe-breach-kwam-precies-goed-uit-voor-have-i-been-pwned.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 08:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 228</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-228/</link>
      <description>Well, it kinda feels like we&amp;#39;re back to the new normal that is 2021. I&amp;#39;m home, the kids are back at school and we&amp;#39;re all still getting breached. We&amp;#39;re breached so much that even when we&amp;#39;re not breached but someone says we&amp;#39;re breached, it genuinely looks like we&amp;#39;re breached. Ok,</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-228/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 08:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Short Interest Stocks : All exchanges : Showing 1</title>
      <link>https://www.highshortinterest.com/all/</link>
      <description>Comprehensive database of high short interest stocks listed on the Nasdaq Stock Market, New York Stock Exchange, and American Stock Exchange.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.highshortinterest.com/all/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 07:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I&amp;#39;m losing faith in UX</title>
      <link>https://creativegood.com/blog/21/losing-faith-in-ux.html</link>
      <description>Digital design increasingly exploits users.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://creativegood.com/blog/21/losing-faith-in-ux.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 07:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-Driven on Azure: Part 1 – Why you should consider an event-driven architecture</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/event-driven-on-azure-part-1-why-you-should-consider-an-event/ba-p/2106983</link>
      <description>Event-driven architecture has become popular for its ability to ingest, process, and react to events in real-time. Event-driven is not a new paradigm however the proliferation of microservices and serverless computing has led to its ability to fully realize the benefit of its loosely coupled design ...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/790749)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/event-driven-on-azure-part-1-why-you-should-consider-an-event/ba-p/2106983</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using fetch with TypeScript</title>
      <link>https://kentcdodds.com/blog/using-fetch-with-type-script/</link>
      <description>How to make HTTP requests with fetch and TypeScript
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kentcdodds.com/blog/using-fetch-with-type-script/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Docker images *quickly* with GitHub Actions self-hosted runners</title>
      <link>https://blog.sixeyed.com/build-docker-images-quickly-with-github-actions-and-a-self-hosted-runner/</link>
      <description>Bring your own VM to run GitHub Actions jobs, using your Docker build cache. Stop and start the VM in the workflow, so you only pay when you&amp;#39;re building.</description>
      <author> (Written by Elton Stoneman)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sixeyed.com/build-docker-images-quickly-with-github-actions-and-a-self-hosted-runner/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bliki: RefinementCodeReview</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/RefinementCodeReview.html</link>
      <description>Code review isn&amp;#39;t just explicit process steps, it can also be regular refinement of the code.</description>
      <author> (Martin Fowler)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/RefinementCodeReview.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automate application lifecycle management with GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/automate-application-lifecycle-management-with-github-actions/</link>
      <description>In 2021, each month we will be releasing a monthly blog covering the webinar of the month for the Low-code Application Development (LCAD) on Azure solution.</description>
      <author> (Ricardo  Duncan
            Product Marketing Manager)</author>
      <guid>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/automate-application-lifecycle-management-with-github-actions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET GC Internals – the Mark phase – TooSlowException</title>
      <link>https://tooslowexception.com/net-gc-internals-the-mark-phase/</link>
      <description>Hi and welcome to the second episode of the .NET GC internals! Yesterday is was 1.5h of talking about the (non-concurrent) Mark phase. The one responsible for discovering which object are “reachable” and which may be garbage collected. I’ve covered topics like object graph traversal algorithm, the pinning and marking flag, the mark stack and mark list data structures. And obviously, some deep dive into the gc.cpp at the end.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tooslowexception.com/net-gc-internals-the-mark-phase/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bliki: PullRequest</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/PullRequest.html</link>
      <description>A mechanism supporting Feature Branching and Pre-Integration Review, at the cost of integration friction</description>
      <author> (Martin Fowler)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/PullRequest.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying AWS Lambdas across environments - Octopus Deploy</title>
      <link>https://octopus.com/blog/deploying-lambdas</link>
      <description>Learn how to progress Lambda deployments across environments using CloudFormation</description>
      <author> (Octopus Deploy)</author>
      <guid>https://octopus.com/blog/deploying-lambdas</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://www.apple.com/privacy/docs/A_Day_in_the_Life_of_Your_Data.pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/privacy/docs/A_Day_in_the_Life_of_Your_Data.pdf</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/privacy/docs/A_Day_in_the_Life_of_Your_Data.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DBA in training: SQL Server under the hood - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/sql/sql-training/dba-training-sql-server-hood/</link>
      <description>In this article of the series, Pamela Mooney explains the architecture of SQL Server under the hood, including some query anti-patterns to avoid.</description>
      <author> (Pamela Mooney)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/sql/sql-training/dba-training-sql-server-hood/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Select Tag Helper in ASP.NET Core MVC</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/select-tag-helper-asp-net-core-mvc</link>
      <description>In this article, explore tag helpers: what they are, which ones are built in, select tag helper, setting selected options, disabling options and option groups. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/select-tag-helper-asp-net-core-mvc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 06:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A/B Testing with Azure App Service</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/ab-testing-azure-app-service/</link>
      <description>A/B Testing feature helps you to test new website content, processes, workflows, etc. by routing the traffic into multiple slots. At a very high level, you route your users into different two deployments of code and measure the success of each version of the site based on your requirements. Azure App Service helps us to set up it very quickly with the help of Deployment Slots.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/ab-testing-azure-app-service/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 05:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Stocks Out Of Your Robinhood Account | Robinhood</title>
      <link>https://robinhood.com/us/en/support/articles/transfer-stocks-out-of-your-robinhood-account/</link>
      <description>Transfer Stocks Out Of Your Robinhood Account</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robinhood.com/us/en/support/articles/transfer-stocks-out-of-your-robinhood-account/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 04:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why You ACTUALLY Need Math for Programming</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/7H30s7xE4jU</link>
      <description>I recently came across a video from Joma Tech called &amp;quot;why you NEED math for programming&amp;quot; (https://youtu.be/sW9npZVpiMI). I think this video is yet another fa...</description>
      <author> (Aidan Glickman
  
  
    

    
      
    Aidan Glickman
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/7H30s7xE4jU</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 03:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood - Investment &amp;amp; Trading, Commission-free - Apps on Google Play</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.robinhood.android&amp;showAllReviews=true&amp;showAllReviews=true&amp;1=</link>
      <description>Invest in stocks, options, and funds with Robinhood Financial. Buy and sell cryptocurrencies with Robinhood Crypto. All commission-free.
Other fees may apply. View Robinhood Financial&amp;#39;s fee schedule at rbnhd.co/fees to learn more.

Invest in the stock market, and earn money on your uninvested cash. Here&amp;#39;s what you get when you join Robinhood:

Finance Explained - We’ll help you understand financial markets so you can invest in the stock market and buy funds, shares and options, all commission-free. 

Trading Tools - Before you buy funds, Bitcoin, or other investment options, you can access real-time market data, read relevant news, and get notified about important events to manage your portfolio.

Plus, we’ve got a full range of products to help make your money work harder for you.

INVESTING MADE EASY
New to investing? We have the tools and services to empower investors like you to participate in the financial market. Learn how to invest and trade smartly and get in-depth financial info - in lingo that makes sense. To get you started, get your first stock on us. Certain limitations apply.

STOCKS, FUNDS, OPTIONS AND CRYPTO
With Robinhood Financial, you can invest in stocks, funds, and options. You can also buy and sell cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), and Dogecoin (DOGE) with Robinhood Crypto.

SECURE AND TRUSTED
Your security is our priority. Robinhood uses cutting-edge security measures to help protect investor assets and personal information.

CASH MANAGEMENT
Earn money with competitive interest* on your uninvested cash and get more flexibility with your brokerage account.

Disclosures

*Cash Management is an added feature to your Robinhood Financial LLC brokerage account. The Annual Percentage Yield (APY) is paid by program banks and may change at any time at the program banks’ discretion. Interest is earned on uninvested cash swept from the brokerage account to the program banks. Neither Robinhood Financial LLC nor any of its affiliates are banks. The debit card is issued by Sutton Bank, member FDIC, pursuant to license by Mastercard&amp;#174; International Incorporated.

Securities trading offered through Robinhood Financial LLC, member SIPC and FINRA. See our Customer Relationship Summary at http://rbnhd.co/crs.

Cryptocurrency trading offered through Robinhood Crypto, LLC. Robinhood Crypto is licensed to engage in virtual currency business activity by the New York State Department of Financial Services and is not a member of FINRA or SIPC. Cryptocurrencies are not stocks and your cryptocurrency investments are not products protected by either the FDIC or SIPC.

The free stock offer is available to new users only, subject to the terms and conditions at rbnhd.co/freestock. Free stock randomly chosen from the program’s inventory. Individuals must sign up through promotional page advertisement to be eligible. Neither receipt of a share of stock through this program nor identification of a particular security in communications related to this program constitutes a solicitation of the security or a recommendation to buy, sell, or hold the security. Robinhood Financial does not provide investment advice and does not hereby recommend any security or transaction.

All investments involve risk, including the possible loss of principal. Investors should consider their investment objectives and risks carefully before investing.

Recurring investments do not ensure a profit or guarantee against loss. Not all securities on Robinhood are eligible for recurring investments. Recurring investments may result in a purchase of fractional shares, which are illiquid outside of Robinhood and not transferable. For a complete explanation of conditions, restrictions and limitations associated with fractional shares, visit www.robinhood.com.

Robinhood Financial LLC and Robinhood Crypto, LLC are wholly-owned subsidiaries of Robinhood Markets, Inc.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.robinhood.android&amp;showAllReviews=true&amp;showAllReviews=true&amp;1=</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 01:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps for ASP.NET Developers: Hosting NuGet Packages</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/DevOps-for-ASPNET-Developers-Hosting-NuGet-Packages</link>
      <description>NuGet defines how packages for .NET are created, hosted, and consumed. Using NuGet feeds, you can make your packages publicly available or limit them to an audience, such as your internal team. In thi</description>
      <author> (by Cecil Phillip, Jeremy Likness)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/DevOps-for-ASPNET-Developers-Hosting-NuGet-Packages</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 01:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Actions (Xamarin.Essentials API of the Week)</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/App-Actions-XamarinEssentials-API-of-the-Week</link>
      <description>Xamarin.Essentials provides developers with cross-platform APIs for their mobile applications. On this week&amp;#39;s Essential API of the week we take a look at App Actions, that allows you to add shortcuts </description>
      <author> (by James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/App-Actions-XamarinEssentials-API-of-the-Week</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 01:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-performance Services with gRPC: What&amp;#39;s new in .NET 5</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EJ8M2Em5Zzc</link>
      <description>gRPC is a high-performance RPC framework used by developers around the world to build fast apps. In this talk you will learn about what&amp;#39;s new in gRPC for .NE...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EJ8M2Em5Zzc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 01:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring My .bashrc In 2021</title>
      <link>https://thesoloadmin.com/exploring-my-bashrc-in-2021/</link>
      <description>I figure the beginning of the year is as good a time as any to take a walk through my personal .bashrc file and see if I can remember what everything does</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thesoloadmin.com/exploring-my-bashrc-in-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to properly store a password in the Database | Petre Popescu</title>
      <link>https://petrepopescu.tech/2021/01/how-to-properly-store-a-password-in-the-database/</link>
      <description>Learn how to securely store passwords in the database when building a website or web-app. Java code sample for storing passwords securely.</description>
      <author> (by     
Petre Popescu

&amp;#183;
Published January 16, 2021
&amp;#183; Updated January 28, 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://petrepopescu.tech/2021/01/how-to-properly-store-a-password-in-the-database/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Main Advantage Of TailwindCSS</title>
      <link>https://planflow.dev/blog/the-main-advantage-of-tailwindcss/</link>
      <description>The primary benefit of using Tailwind is that it leads to a massive increase in productivity. This post explores how.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://planflow.dev/blog/the-main-advantage-of-tailwindcss/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Recommendations for a New VC</title>
      <link>https://lifeinbeta.home.blog/2021/01/24/vcreadinglist/</link>
      <description>I recently caught up with someone who is moving into an investing role at a venture capital firm – she asked me for any book recommendations that could help her get up to speed faster I&amp;amp;#8217…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lifeinbeta.home.blog/2021/01/24/vcreadinglist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Gamestop a Win for the Little Guy? - Benjamin Tseng</title>
      <link>https://benjamintseng.com/2021/01/is-gamestop-a-win-for-the-little-guy/</link>
      <description>The narrative that this is Main Street winning over Wall Street is overblown.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://benjamintseng.com/2021/01/is-gamestop-a-win-for-the-little-guy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lithuanian Lawmaker Valdas Rakutis Outrageously Blames Jews for Holocaust — Stop Antisemitism</title>
      <link>https://www.stopantisemitism.org/antisemitic-incidents-64/lithuanian-lawmaker-valdas-rakutis-outrageously-blames-jews-partially-for-holocaust</link>
      <description>&amp;quot;There was no shortage of Holocaust perpetrators among the Jews themselves, especially in the ghetto self-government structures.&amp;quot; - Valdas Rakutis</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.stopantisemitism.org/antisemitic-incidents-64/lithuanian-lawmaker-valdas-rakutis-outrageously-blames-jews-partially-for-holocaust</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Code with Infrastructure as Code</title>
      <link>https://www.leebriggs.co.uk/blog/2021/01/27/learn-to-code-with-iac.html</link>
      <description>Engineering, DevOps &amp;amp; Cloud Computing</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.leebriggs.co.uk/blog/2021/01/27/learn-to-code-with-iac.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The life of a Web Component - Initialization</title>
      <link>https://hugodaniel.com/posts/the-life-of-a-web-component/</link>
      <description>This post is a quick write-up on some of my learnings in experimenting with Web Components. It focuses mostly on the small subset of their life-cycle methods that deal with initialization.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hugodaniel.com/posts/the-life-of-a-web-component/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if GitHub is the devil?</title>
      <link>https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2021/01/28/what-if-github-is-the-devil/</link>
      <description>Some critics think the curl project shouldn’t use GitHub. The reasons for being against GitHub hosting tend to be one or more of:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2021/01/28/what-if-github-is-the-devil/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Youtube Dislike Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://phzoe.com/2021/01/27/white-house-youtube-dislike-manipulation/</link>
      <description>I’ve seen screenshots of YouTube modifying dislikes of White House videos. I decided I would do a thorough analysis myself. I wrote a script to check video stats every 80 seconds for 24 hours…</description>
      <author> (Published by Zoe Phin		
	
	
		https://phzoe.com		
			View more posts)</author>
      <guid>https://phzoe.com/2021/01/27/white-house-youtube-dislike-manipulation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the software becomes unmaintainable? – a practical example</title>
      <link>https://kmitov.com/posts/how-the-software-becomes-unmaintainable-a-practical-example/</link>
      <description>(Everyday Code – instead of keeping our knowledge in a README.md let’s share it with the internet)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kmitov.com/posts/how-the-software-becomes-unmaintainable-a-practical-example/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivering with empathy</title>
      <link>https://www.adammalone.net/post/delivering-with-empathy/</link>
      <description>I remember learning about the difference between sympathy and empathy in middle school.  Sympathy: feelings of pity and sorrow for someone else&amp;#39;s misfortune. Empathy: the ability to understand and share the feelings of another.Pretty damn simple to understand the difference when you read each of the above definitions, but</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.adammalone.net/post/delivering-with-empathy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp and the domestication of users</title>
      <link>https://seirdy.one/2021/01/27/whatsapp-and-the-domestication-of-users.html</link>
      <description>WhatsApp&amp;#39;s rise and recent PR efforts highlight a class of business models that I call &amp;quot;user domestication&amp;quot;.</description>
      <author> (Rohan Kumar)</author>
      <guid>https://seirdy.one/2021/01/27/whatsapp-and-the-domestication-of-users.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The myth of turning your hobby into a job with writer Aley Arion | Hanselminutes with Scott Hanselman</title>
      <link>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/the-myth-of-turning-your-hobby-into-a-job-with-writer-aley-arion-hSx11_DR</link>
      <description>One day multi-hyphenate creative Aley Arion tweeted &amp;quot;one day I’m going to talk about the myth of turning your hobby into a job &amp;amp; how it can actually create a disconnect between you &amp;amp; that thing you once did for fun because it became work.&amp;quot; Today is that day! Aley talks to Scott about how the challenges of attaching your creative outlets to your rent. Is it possible and is it healthy?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/the-myth-of-turning-your-hobby-into-a-job-with-writer-aley-arion-hSx11_DR</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 23:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon have cut 95K jobs in five years | Light Reading</title>
      <link>https://www.lightreading.com/aiautomation/atandt-and-verizon-have-cut-95k-jobs-in-five-years/d/d-id/766984#.YBMsXyU2S00.twitter</link>
      <description>About a fifth of jobs at the US operators have vanished in the last five years and the layoffs will probably continue.</description>
      <author> (News Analysis
                Iain Morris, International Editor
                1/28/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://www.lightreading.com/aiautomation/atandt-and-verizon-have-cut-95k-jobs-in-five-years/d/d-id/766984#.YBMsXyU2S00.twitter</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 23:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Johnny Still, Still Can&amp;#39;t Encrypt: Evaluating the Usability of a Modern PGP Client</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/1510.08555</link>
      <description>This paper presents the results of a laboratory study involving Mailvelope, a
modern PGP client that integrates tightly with existing webmail providers. In
our study, we brought in pairs of participants and had them attempt to use
Mailvelope to communicate with each other. Our results shown that more than a
decade and a half after 	extit{Why Johnny Can&amp;#39;t Encrypt}, modern PGP tools are
still unusable for the masses. We finish with a discussion of pain points
encountered using Mailvelope, and discuss what might be done to address them in
future PGP systems.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 29 Oct 2015 (v1), last revised 13 Jan 2016 (this version, v2)])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/1510.08555</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 23:04:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood Hit With Class Action Lawsuit After Halting GameStop Stock - IGN</title>
      <link>https://www.ign.com/articles/robinhood-hit-with-class-action-lawsuit-after-halting-gamestop-stock</link>
      <description>Stock trading app Robinhood has been hit with a class-action lawsuit after halting trades on GameStop, other stocks it says are &amp;quot;volatile.&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> (By&amp;#160;Matt T.M. KimUpdated: 28 Jan 2021 11:44 amPosted: 28 Jan 2021 11:33 am)</author>
      <guid>https://www.ign.com/articles/robinhood-hit-with-class-action-lawsuit-after-halting-gamestop-stock</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 23:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase announces proposed direct listing</title>
      <link>https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-announces-proposed-direct-listing-3a52c4298ccc</link>
      <description>Coinbase Global, Inc. today announced its intent to become a publicly-traded company pursuant to a proposed direct listing of its Class A…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@coinbaseblog)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-announces-proposed-direct-listing-3a52c4298ccc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 23:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# with CSharpFritz S2 E4 - APIs with ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y_hTutN7yOw</link>
      <description>In this week&amp;#39;s session, Fritz walks through the basics of building RESTful APIs with ASP.NET Core.  We look at the base template, writing an API with minimal...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y_hTutN7yOw</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 22:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[1] Complaint</title>
      <link>https://www.yumpu.com/en/document/read/65257553/1-complaint</link>
      <description>Case 1:21-cv-00777 Document 1 Filed 01/28/21 Page 1 of 9UNITED STATES DISTRICT COURTSOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW</description>
      <author> (Yumpu.com)</author>
      <guid>https://www.yumpu.com/en/document/read/65257553/1-complaint</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 21:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asynchronous Messaging, Part 4: Retrieve Results</title>
      <link>https://blog.stephencleary.com/2021/01/asynchronous-messaging-4-retrieve-results.html</link>
      <description>When you do and do not need to retrieve results in an asynchronous messaging solution, and methods for doing so.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.stephencleary.com/2021/01/asynchronous-messaging-4-retrieve-results.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 21:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enriching Excel with higher-order functional programming</title>
      <link>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/research/blog/lambda-the-ultimatae-excel-worksheet-function/?OCID=msr_blog_lambda_tw</link>
      <description>Microsoft Excel the programming language is evolving. With the recent release of LAMBDA, users can now define new functions in the program’s formula language. Learn about the capability and its role in the transformation of spreadsheet formulas.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/research/blog/lambda-the-ultimatae-excel-worksheet-function/?OCID=msr_blog_lambda_tw</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 21:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First comes the slop, then the good stuff</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2021/01/28/first-comes-the-slop-then-the-good-stuff/</link>
      <description>Do you ever struggle with your code? Like, you know the answer is there somewhere, but whatever is popping out onto the IDE from the keyboard is definitely not it? After a few times of this, you fi…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2021/01/28/first-comes-the-slop-then-the-good-stuff/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood - Investment &amp;amp; Trading, Commission-free - Apps on Google Play</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.robinhood.android&amp;showAllReviews=true</link>
      <description>Invest in stocks, options, and funds with Robinhood Financial. Buy and sell cryptocurrencies with Robinhood Crypto. All commission-free.
Other fees may apply. View Robinhood Financial&amp;#39;s fee schedule at rbnhd.co/fees to learn more.

Invest in the stock market, and earn money on your uninvested cash. Here&amp;#39;s what you get when you join Robinhood:

Finance Explained - We’ll help you understand financial markets so you can invest in the stock market and buy funds, shares and options, all commission-free. 

Trading Tools - Before you buy funds, Bitcoin, or other investment options, you can access real-time market data, read relevant news, and get notified about important events to manage your portfolio.

Plus, we’ve got a full range of products to help make your money work harder for you.

INVESTING MADE EASY
New to investing? We have the tools and services to empower investors like you to participate in the financial market. Learn how to invest and trade smartly and get in-depth financial info - in lingo that makes sense. To get you started, get your first stock on us. Certain limitations apply.

STOCKS, FUNDS, OPTIONS AND CRYPTO
With Robinhood Financial, you can invest in stocks, funds, and options. You can also buy and sell cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), and Dogecoin (DOGE) with Robinhood Crypto.

SECURE AND TRUSTED
Your security is our priority. Robinhood uses cutting-edge security measures to help protect investor assets and personal information.

CASH MANAGEMENT
Earn money with competitive interest* on your uninvested cash and get more flexibility with your brokerage account.

Disclosures

*Cash Management is an added feature to your Robinhood Financial LLC brokerage account. The Annual Percentage Yield (APY) is paid by program banks and may change at any time at the program banks’ discretion. Interest is earned on uninvested cash swept from the brokerage account to the program banks. Neither Robinhood Financial LLC nor any of its affiliates are banks. The debit card is issued by Sutton Bank, member FDIC, pursuant to license by Mastercard&amp;#174; International Incorporated.

Securities trading offered through Robinhood Financial LLC, member SIPC and FINRA. See our Customer Relationship Summary at http://rbnhd.co/crs.

Cryptocurrency trading offered through Robinhood Crypto, LLC. Robinhood Crypto is licensed to engage in virtual currency business activity by the New York State Department of Financial Services and is not a member of FINRA or SIPC. Cryptocurrencies are not stocks and your cryptocurrency investments are not products protected by either the FDIC or SIPC.

The free stock offer is available to new users only, subject to the terms and conditions at rbnhd.co/freestock. Free stock randomly chosen from the program’s inventory. Individuals must sign up through promotional page advertisement to be eligible. Neither receipt of a share of stock through this program nor identification of a particular security in communications related to this program constitutes a solicitation of the security or a recommendation to buy, sell, or hold the security. Robinhood Financial does not provide investment advice and does not hereby recommend any security or transaction.

All investments involve risk, including the possible loss of principal. Investors should consider their investment objectives and risks carefully before investing.

Recurring investments do not ensure a profit or guarantee against loss. Not all securities on Robinhood are eligible for recurring investments. Recurring investments may result in a purchase of fractional shares, which are illiquid outside of Robinhood and not transferable. For a complete explanation of conditions, restrictions and limitations associated with fractional shares, visit www.robinhood.com.

Robinhood Financial LLC and Robinhood Crypto, LLC are wholly-owned subsidiaries of Robinhood Markets, Inc.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.robinhood.android&amp;showAllReviews=true</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 20:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pascalw/kindle-dash</title>
      <link>https://github.com/pascalw/kindle-dash</link>
      <description>Power efficient dashboard for Kindle 4 NT devices. Contribute to pascalw/kindle-dash development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (pascalw)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/pascalw/kindle-dash</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 20:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protocols, Not Platforms: A Technological Approach to Free Speech</title>
      <link>https://knightcolumbia.org/content/protocols-not-platforms-a-technological-approach-to-free-speech</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (By
              Mike Masnick)</author>
      <guid>https://knightcolumbia.org/content/protocols-not-platforms-a-technological-approach-to-free-speech</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:06:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WE are Preparing a Class Action LAWSUIT against Robinhood!</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/l6yrs3/we_are_preparing_a_class_action_lawsuit_against/</link>
      <description>Hey everyone, &amp;amp;#x200B; We all just got screwed by Robinhood&amp;#39;s screwup here. I&amp;#39;m friends with a lawyer who says we have a good case for a class...</description>
      <author> (jartek)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/l6yrs3/we_are_preparing_a_class_action_lawsuit_against/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:06:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the front page of the internet</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/</link>
      <description>Reddit gives you the best of the internet in one place. Get a constantly updating feed of breaking news, fun stories, pics, memes, and videos just for you. Passionate about something niche? Reddit has thousands of vibrant communities with people that share your interests. Alternatively, find out what’s trending across all of Reddit on r/popular. Reddit is also anonymous so you can be yourself, with your Reddit profile and persona disconnected from your real-world identity.</description>
      <author> (Bundaga)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents&amp;#39; income, not smarts, key to entrepreneurship - study</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/parents-income-not-smarts-key-to-entrepreneurship-study-657058</link>
      <description>Research like this is an early part of a process that can eventually turn into government planning.</description>
      <author> (By  ZEV STUB
            &amp;#160;
            JANUARY 28, 2021 17:09)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/parents-income-not-smarts-key-to-entrepreneurship-study-657058</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Terminal Preview 1.6 Release | Windows Command Line</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/windows-terminal-preview-1-6-release/</link>
      <description>Welcome to our first Windows Terminal release of 2021! This release brings new features to Windows Terminal Preview version 1.6 as well as moves Windows Terminal to version 1.5, which includes the features from this previous blog post. You can download both versions from the Microsoft Store or from the GitHub releases page.</description>
      <author> (Kayla Cinnamon Program Manager, Windows Terminal, Console, Command Line, &amp;amp; Cascadia Code Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/windows-terminal-preview-1-6-release/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:05:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Spotify Patent Involves Monitoring Users’ Speech to Recommend Music</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/new-spotify-patent-involves-monitoring-users-speech-to-recommend-music/</link>
      <description>The streaming platform is interested in extracting data points like emotional state, gender, age, and accent to hone its recommendations</description>
      <author> (Noah Yoo)</author>
      <guid>https://pitchfork.com/news/new-spotify-patent-involves-monitoring-users-speech-to-recommend-music/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authentication options in ASP.NET 5 and ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/LKTDZG6</link>
      <description>Take this survey powered by surveymonkey.com. Create your own surveys for free.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/LKTDZG6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>reddit: the front page of the internet</title>
      <link>https://i.reddit.com/</link>
      <description>reddit: the front page of the internet</description>
      <author> (Bundaga)</author>
      <guid>https://i.reddit.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:05:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tour of SQL Workshops</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Data-Exposed/A-Tour-of-SQL-Workshops</link>
      <description>Join Anna Hoffman and Buck Woody as they take a tour of the incredible learning resource the Microsoft Engineering team has put together. From labs to full hands-on workshops and much more, you&amp;#39;ll fin</description>
      <author> (by Marisa Brasile)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Data-Exposed/A-Tour-of-SQL-Workshops</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ynpmIT-DlO0</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io/</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
    

    
      
    .NET Foundation
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ynpmIT-DlO0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>windows sound effect (acapella)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4AZB64VBJfA</link>
      <description>windows sound effect (acapella)Music arranged by MaytreeVideo directed by Napkins music#window #microsoft #humaneffect</description>
      <author> (MayTree
  
  
    

    
      
    MayTree
  
    



  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4AZB64VBJfA</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 17:10:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Real-Time Communications (WebRTC) transforms the communications landscape; becomes a World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) Recommendation and multiple Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF) standards</title>
      <link>https://www.w3.org/2021/01/pressrelease-webrtc-rec.html.en</link>
      <description>For immediate release</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.w3.org/2021/01/pressrelease-webrtc-rec.html.en</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 17:05:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers spend most of their time figuring the system out</title>
      <link>https://blog.feenk.com/developers-spend-most-of-their-time-figuri-7aj1ocjhe765vvlln8qqbuhto/</link>
      <description>What does it mean when we say that developers spend most of their time figuring the system out? 

Why is it important?

And how else could we look at this problem?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.feenk.com/developers-spend-most-of-their-time-figuri-7aj1ocjhe765vvlln8qqbuhto/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 17:05:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a ServiceLifetime</title>
      <link>https://jimmybogard.com/choosing-a-servicelifetime/</link>
      <description>A subtle source of errors and less-than-subtle source of frustration is understanding and using service lifetimes appropriately with .NET Core dependency injection. Service lifetimes, while complicated on the surface, can help developers that need to share state across different lifetimes of an application. Typically, a long-running application has three service</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Bogard)</author>
      <guid>https://jimmybogard.com/choosing-a-servicelifetime/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 17:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>/r/wallstreetbets vs. WallStreet: It&amp;#39;s not about the money anymore!!</title>
      <link>https://thinkingthrough.substack.com/p/rwallstreetbets-vs-wallstreet-its</link>
      <description>(3 Min Read)</description>
      <author> (Mayank Verma)</author>
      <guid>https://thinkingthrough.substack.com/p/rwallstreetbets-vs-wallstreet-its</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 16:07:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoscrolling on drag, part 4: Dynamic autoscroll based on escape velocity | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210128-00/?p=104768</link>
      <description>Last time, we noted some problems with autoscroll based on the distance from the mouse to the window. An alternate design is to use the speed with which the mouse exited the window to establish the autoscroll speed. This no longer penalizes people with small screens or windows near the edge of the screen.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210128-00/?p=104768</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 16:07:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stack Overflow 2019 hack was guided by advice from none other than... Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2021/01/27/stack_overflow_2019_hack_was/</link>
      <description>Vulnerabilities in build systems, secrets in source code: developer environments are an attack target</description>
      <author> (Tim Anderson
            Wed&amp;#160;27&amp;#160;Jan&amp;#160;2021 // 19:31&amp;#160;UTC)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2021/01/27/stack_overflow_2019_hack_was/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 15:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks! vNext</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1724</link>
      <description>.NET Rocks! is a weekly talk show for anyone interested in programming on the Microsoft .NET platform. The shows range from introductory information to hardcore geekiness.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1724</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 15:05:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>benbjohnson/litestream</title>
      <link>https://github.com/benbjohnson/litestream#open-source-not-open-contribution</link>
      <description>Streaming S3 replication for SQLite. Contribute to benbjohnson/litestream development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (benbjohnson)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/benbjohnson/litestream#open-source-not-open-contribution</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 15:05:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take Your Online Presence to the Next Level with Hashnode</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bJ1C5-kXfLU</link>
      <description>Your online presence can help get you your first/next job as a developer. Having a good online presence isn&amp;#39;t required, but it can make a huge difference. I&amp;#39;...</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick
  
  
    

    
      
    James Q Quick
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bJ1C5-kXfLU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 15:05:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use FastReport Open Source in ASP.NET Core Web application</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/how-to-use-fastreport-open-source-in-aspnetcore/</link>
      <description>If you’re coming from VB6 / Winforms world, one of the challenge in ASP.NET Core is lack of reporting tools. In VB6, Crystal reports was there. And if I am not wrong it was part of some Visual Studio versions. I was exploring a free reporting tool for one of old companies as they were planning to move their VB6 app to ASP.NET Core and Cloud. So lets explore Fast Report Open Source.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/how-to-use-fastreport-open-source-in-aspnetcore/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 15:05:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JaaS: the Team that Builds Jitsi Can Now Also Run it for You! - Jitsi</title>
      <link>https://jitsi.org/blog/jaas-the-team-that-builds-jitsi-can-now-also-run-it-for-you/</link>
      <description>TL;DR The Jitsi team at 8&amp;#215;8 are proud to announce the brand new and awesome Jitsi as a Service: world’s easiest way to embed video meetings in your apps and websites! All the power of […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jitsi.org/blog/jaas-the-team-that-builds-jitsi-can-now-also-run-it-for-you/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 14:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EU must protect the right to privacy and not attack end-to-end encryption</title>
      <link>https://protonmail.com/blog/joint-statement-eu-encryption/</link>
      <description>Along with Threema, Tresorit, and Tutanota, we are releasing a joint statement calling on the EU to reject any ban or attack on end-to-end encryption.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://protonmail.com/blog/joint-statement-eu-encryption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 14:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab removes its &amp;#39;starter&amp;#39; tier: Users must either pay 5x more or lose features</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/AMP/2021/01/27/gitlab_removes_starter_tier/</link>
      <description>Customer: &amp;#39;It feels like a bit of a kick in the teeth&amp;#39;</description>
      <author> (Tim Anderson
                    
                        Wed&amp;#160;27&amp;#160;Jan&amp;#160;2021&amp;#160;//&amp;#160;13:00&amp;#160;UTC)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/AMP/2021/01/27/gitlab_removes_starter_tier/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 13:05:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.woodlandtrust.org.uk/security-incident/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Woodland Trust)</author>
      <guid>https://www.woodlandtrust.org.uk/security-incident/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 13:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a social media platform without going bankrupt: Part IV–Caching and distribution</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/193029-C/building-a-social-media-platform-without-going-bankrupt-part-iv-caching-and-distribution?Key=99bbaa12-88f7-4ae3-91ae-84922bedb1b7</link>
      <description>In my previous post we looked at the process in which we process a request for a batch of posts and get their results. The code made no assumptions about whe...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/193029-C/building-a-social-media-platform-without-going-bankrupt-part-iv-caching-and-distribution?Key=99bbaa12-88f7-4ae3-91ae-84922bedb1b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 13:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Actions Breaking Change:&amp;#160;.NET Core 3.0 will be removed from macOS and Ubuntu images - GitHub Changelog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-01-28-github-actions-breaking-change-net-core-3-0-will-be-removed-from-macos-and-ubuntu-images/</link>
      <description>GitHub Actions Breaking Change:&amp;#160;.NET Core 3.0 will be removed from macOS and Ubuntu images</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/changelog/2021-01-28-github-actions-breaking-change-net-core-3-0-will-be-removed-from-macos-and-ubuntu-images/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 12:07:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans of Infosec - Troy Hunt</title>
      <link>https://audioboom.com/posts/7777178-humans-of-infosec-troy-hunt</link>
      <description>An episode by Infosecurity Europe Podcasts</description>
      <author> (Infosecurity Europe Podcasts)</author>
      <guid>https://audioboom.com/posts/7777178-humans-of-infosec-troy-hunt</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 11:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Privacy Day 2021 - Looking ahead at the always on, always secure, always private Internet</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/data-privacy-day-2021-looking-ahead-at-the-always-on-always-secure-always-private-internet/</link>
      <description>2020 was a big year for data protection, so what does 2021 have in store? On this Data Privacy Day, we talk about the key role data localization and encryption technologies will play in data protection this year.</description>
      <author> (Emily Hancock)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/data-privacy-day-2021-looking-ahead-at-the-always-on-always-secure-always-private-internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 09:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-01-28</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/01/app-developer-links-2021-01-28/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/01/app-developer-links-2021-01-28/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 09:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implement OAUTH Device Code Flow with Azure AD and ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2021/01/28/implement-oauth-device-code-flow-with-azure-ad-and-asp-net-core/</link>
      <description>The post shows how the Device Code flow (RFC 8628) could be implemented in an ASP.NET Core web application which uses Azure AD as an identity provider. An Azure App registration is used to setup th…</description>
      <author> (damienbod)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2021/01/28/implement-oauth-device-code-flow-with-azure-ad-and-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 09:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET GC Internals - 03. Concurrent Mark phase</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wSHisrMt6-8</link>
      <description>The third episode of the .NET GC Internals series explaining a real in-depth knowledge how .NET GC works. This episode is about the Concurrent Mark phase, di...</description>
      <author> (Dotnetos
  
  
    

    
      
    Dotnetos
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wSHisrMt6-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 09:05:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>