<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code Dev Team Eyes Long-Requested Testing Support -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/05/vs-code-1-53.aspx</link>
      <description>  Of course, testing is possible in VS Code via numerous extensions, but Microsoft is seeking to spearhead a more structured, comprehensive approach.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel02/05/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/05/vs-code-1-53.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 23:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s Crack Zodiac - Episode 5 - The 340 Is Solved!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-1oQLPRE21o</link>
      <description>On December 3rd, 2020, an international three-person team of codebreakers made a breakthrough with the Zodiac Killer&amp;#39;s unsolved 340-character cipher.By Decem...</description>
      <author> (David Oranchak
  
  
    

    
      
    David Oranchak
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-1oQLPRE21o</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 23:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl LV on Cloudflare’s Radar</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-super-bowl-lv/</link>
      <description>Super Bowl LV, the most watched US sports broadcast, is just around the corner. All through Super Bowl weekend and especially while the game between the Tampa Bay Buccaneers and the Kansas City Chiefs is on we expect a visible impact on Internet usage.</description>
      <author> (Marc Lamik)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-super-bowl-lv/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 23:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Vaccine - LessWrong</title>
      <link>https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/niQ3heWwF6SydhS7R/making-vaccine</link>
      <description>Back in December, I asked how hard it would be to make a vaccine for oneself.
Several people pointed to radvac. It was a best-case scenario: an open-source
vaccine design, made for self-experimenters, dead simple to make with
readily-available materials, well-explained reasoning about the design, and with
the name of one of the world’s more competent biologists (who I already knew of
beforehand) stamped on the whitepaper. My girlfriend and I made a batch a week
ago and took our first booster yesterday.

This post talks a bit about the process, a bit about our plan, and a bit about
motivations. Bear in mind that we may have made mistakes - if something seems
off, leave a comment.

THE PROCESS
All of the materials and equipment to make the vaccine cost us about $1000. We
did not need any special licenses or anything like that. I do have a little
wetlab experience from my undergrad days, but the skills required were pretty
minimal.

One vial of custom peptide - that little pile of white powder at the bottom.The
large majority of the cost (about $850) was the peptides. These are the main
active ingredients of the vaccine: short segments of proteins from the COVID
virus. They’re all &amp;lt;25 amino acids, so far too small to have any likely function
as proteins (for comparison, COVID’s spike protein has 1273 amino acids).
They’re just meant to be recognized by the immune system: the immune system
learns to recognize these sequences, and that’s what provides immunity.

Each of six peptides came in two vials of 4.5 mg each. These are the half we
haven&amp;#39;t dissolved; we keep them in the freezer as backups.The peptides were
custom synthesized. There are companies which synthesize any (short) peptide
sequence you want - you can find dozens of them online. The cheapest options
suffice for the vaccine - the peptides don’t need to be “purified” (this just
means removing partial sequences), they don’t need any special modifications,
and very small amounts suffice. The minimum order size </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/niQ3heWwF6SydhS7R/making-vaccine</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 23:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fecal transplant turns cancer immunotherapy non-responders into responders</title>
      <link>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-02/uop-ftt012921.php</link>
      <description>A phase II clinical trial shows that changing the gut microbiome through fecal transplant can transform cancer patients who never responded to immunotherapy into patients who do.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-02/uop-ftt012921.php</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 22:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac utility Homebrew finally gets native Apple Silicon and M1 support</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/02/mac-utility-homebrew-finally-gets-native-apple-silicon-and-m1-support/?utm_social-type=owned</link>
      <description>There aren&amp;#39;t bottles for every package yet, but the work is in progress.</description>
      <author> (Samuel Axon
    -  2/5/2021, 1:47 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/02/mac-utility-homebrew-finally-gets-native-apple-silicon-and-m1-support/?utm_social-type=owned</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 22:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoHistory for EF Core - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/77/autohistory-for-ef-core</link>
      <description>A plugin for Microsoft.EntityFrameworkCore to support automatically recording data changes history. Comes in handy when you want to create a log of data changes over time. Think blog post revisions, etc.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/77/autohistory-for-ef-core</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 22:06:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firewalls Don&amp;#39;t Stop Dragons Podcast - Don&amp;#39;t Get Caught With Your Drawbridge Down!</title>
      <link>https://podcast.firewallsdontstopdragons.com/</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t Get Caught With Your Drawbridge Down!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://podcast.firewallsdontstopdragons.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 21:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elements of Computing Systems, Second Edition</title>
      <link>https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/elements-computing-systems-second-edition</link>
      <description>A new and extensively revised edition of a popular textbook used in universities, coding boot camps, hacker clubs, and online courses.
                The best way to understand how computers work is to build one from scratch, and this textbook leads learners through twelve chapters and projects that gradually build the hardware platform and software hierarchy for a simple but powerful computer system. In the process, learners gain hands-on knowledge of hardware, architecture, operating systems, programming languages, compilers, data structures and algorithms, and software engineering. Using this constructive approach, the book introduces learners to a significant body of computer science knowledge and demonstrates how theoretical and applied techniques taught in other computer science courses fit into the overall picture. The outcome of these efforts is known as Nand to Tetris: a journey that starts with the most elementary logic gate, called Nand, and ends, twelve projects later, with a general-purpose computer system capable of running Tetris.
                    The first edition of this popular textbook inspired Nand to Tetris classes in universities, coding boot camps, hacker clubs, and online course platforms. This second edition has been extensively revised. It has been restructured into two distinct parts—part I, Hardware, and part II, Software—with six projects in each part. All chapters and projects have been rewritten, with an emphasis on separating abstraction from implementation, and many new sections, figures, and examples have been added. Substantial new appendixes offer focused presentation on technical and theoretical topics.</description>
      <author> (By Noam Nisan and  Shimon Schocken)</author>
      <guid>https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/elements-computing-systems-second-edition</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 20:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major corporations say they will stop donating to members of Congress who tried to overturn the election</title>
      <link>https://popular.info/p/three-major-corporations-say-they</link>
      <description>On January 6, a violent mob stormed the Capitol of the United States, disrupting the joint session to confirm Joe Biden&amp;#39;s victory. The incident left five people dead, including a member of the Capitol police who was crushed to death in the mele.</description>
      <author> (Judd Legum)</author>
      <guid>https://popular.info/p/three-major-corporations-say-they</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 20:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gift Egwuenu (Gift Egwuenu)</title>
      <link>https://mvp.microsoft.com/en-us/PublicProfile/5004152?fullName=Gift%20Egwuenu</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mvp.microsoft.com/en-us/PublicProfile/5004152?fullName=Gift%20Egwuenu</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 20:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Maze Weekly #63 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-63/</link>
      <description>Not many technologies are exciting as soon as they come out. Blazor was and still is an exciting toy to play with, and we’re thrilled to see it grow and that people are adopting it steadily. So give it a chance. Or pick some of the awesome topics we’ve prepared for you this time. Take […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-63/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 19:06:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2021 - Schedule</title>
      <link>https://fosdem.org/2021/schedule/</link>
      <description>Every year, FOSDEM hosts a wide variety of activities.
  This page gives an overview with links to further information about
  scheduled events. All times CET (UTC+1).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fosdem.org/2021/schedule/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 17:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn off that camera during virtual meetings, environmental study says</title>
      <link>https://www.purdue.edu/newsroom/releases/2021/Q1/turn-off-that-camera-during-virtual-meetings,-environmental-study-says.html</link>
      <description>It’s not just to hide clutter anymore – add “saving the planet” to the reasons you leave the camera off during your next virtual meeting.</description>
      <author> (Purdue News Service)</author>
      <guid>https://www.purdue.edu/newsroom/releases/2021/Q1/turn-off-that-camera-during-virtual-meetings,-environmental-study-says.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 17:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atkinson Hyperlegible Font May Be Pretty Good If Your Granny Can&amp;#39;t See Well</title>
      <link>https://christiantietze.de/posts/2021/01/hyperlegible-font/</link>
      <description>My grandmother approves of Atkinson Hyperlegible free font for her phone book printout</description>
      <author> (Christian Tietze)</author>
      <guid>https://christiantietze.de/posts/2021/01/hyperlegible-font/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 16:07:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The .NET Docs Show - Using Source Generators for Fun (and Maybe Profit)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mIo_HTz2viI</link>
      <description>Tired of writing code? Community MVP Jason Bock joins the panel to show us how to automate ourselves out of a job!Featuring: Jason Bock (@jasonbock)#source-g...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mIo_HTz2viI</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 16:07:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 69 - The Risks of Third Party Code With Niels Tanis</title>
      <link>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-69-the-risks-of-third-party-code-with-niels-anis/</link>
      <description>In this episode of The .NET Core Podcast we talked with Niels Tanis about some of the inherent risks with third party code</description>
      <author> (RJJ Software)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-69-the-risks-of-third-party-code-with-niels-anis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 15:07:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Streaming | gRPC in .NET 5</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wY4nMSUF9e0</link>
      <description>Subscribe: http://bit.ly/ChapsasSubBecome a Patreon and get source code access: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsasHello everybody I&amp;#39;m Nick and in this video...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
    

    
      
    Nick Chapsas
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wY4nMSUF9e0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 15:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.0.0</title>
      <link>https://brew.sh/2021/02/05/homebrew-3.0.0/</link>
      <description>Today I’d like to announce Homebrew 3.0.0. The most significant changes since 2.7.0 are official Apple Silicon support and a new bottle format in formulae.</description>
      <author> (MikeMcQuaid)</author>
      <guid>https://brew.sh/2021/02/05/homebrew-3.0.0/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 15:06:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a social media platform without going bankrupt: Part X–Optimizing for whales</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/193062-A/building-a-social-media-platform-without-going-bankrupt-part-x-optimizing-for-whales?Key=718095b6-a3fd-472c-aa28-6112d985f66f</link>
      <description>Unless I get good feedback / questions on the other posts in the series, this is likely to be the last post on the topic. I was trying to show what kind of s...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/193062-A/building-a-social-media-platform-without-going-bankrupt-part-x-optimizing-for-whales?Key=718095b6-a3fd-472c-aa28-6112d985f66f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 15:06:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I get a foothold in the neutral apartment? | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210205-00/?p=104801</link>
      <description>The neutral apartment is a mysterious beast. You cannot initialize a thread in the neutral apartment, because the neutral apartment isn’t tied to a thread. Instead, the neutral apartment takes over any thread it can find: If you are on an existing thread and call an object that lives in the neutral apartment,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210205-00/?p=104801</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 15:06:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New report on Apple’s VR headset: 8K in each eye, potential $3,000 price tag</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/02/new-report-on-apples-vr-headset-8k-in-each-eye-potential-3000-price-tag/</link>
      <description>Plus, our analysis: How legit is this idea, anyway?</description>
      <author> (Samuel Axon
    -  2/4/2021, 12:46 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/02/new-report-on-apples-vr-headset-8k-in-each-eye-potential-3000-price-tag/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 14:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Big: Three Months in at Elastic - Steve Gordon - Code with Steve</title>
      <link>https://www.stevejgordon.co.uk/dream-big-three-months-in-at-elastic</link>
      <description>In this post, I share my thoughts on imposter syndrome, career development and my journey to starting work at Elastic.</description>
      <author> (Steve Gordon)</author>
      <guid>https://www.stevejgordon.co.uk/dream-big-three-months-in-at-elastic</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 13:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disqus, the dark commenting system</title>
      <link>https://supunkavinda.blog/disqus</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m explaining why Disqus is a great example for &amp;amp;amp;amp;quot;if you&amp;#39;re not paying for it, you become the product&amp;amp;amp;amp;quot;.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://supunkavinda.blog/disqus</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 13:05:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightingale REST API Client - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/189/nightingale-rest-api-client</link>
      <description>I was inspired to build Nightingale after seeing a lack of full-fledged REST API clients on the Microsoft Store. Additionally, I realized that while other clients were incredibly powerful, they used nearly 500MB of memory even when performing simple HTTP request tasks. 

Thus, Nightingale was cre…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/189/nightingale-rest-api-client</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 12:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man who produced Steve Jobs’ keynotes for 20 years.</title>
      <link>https://www.cake.co/conversations/jNZlq6j/the-man-who-produced-steve-jobs-keynotes-for-20-years</link>
      <description>Wayne Goodrich was the producer for every keynote Steve gave after his return to Apple. Before that, Wayne helped him create presentations at NeXT and Pixar. He is writing a book about what it was …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cake.co/conversations/jNZlq6j/the-man-who-produced-steve-jobs-keynotes-for-20-years</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 12:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Free Hyperlegible Typeface from the Braille Institute</title>
      <link>https://kottke.org/20/10/a-free-hyperlegible-typeface-from-the-braille-institute</link>
      <description>

Atkinson Hyperlegible is a free typeface developed by the Braille Institute and Applied Design Works that makes text more readab</description>
      <author> (posted by Jason Kottke &amp;#160; Oct 15, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://kottke.org/20/10/a-free-hyperlegible-typeface-from-the-braille-institute</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 09:07:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How hackers are finding creative ways to steal gift cards using artificial intelligence.</title>
      <link>https://deceptive.medium.com/how-hackers-are-finding-creative-ways-to-steal-gift-cards-using-artificial-intelligence-8a0544a54c6f</link>
      <description>Hackers are finding extraordinary ways to obtain gift cards for stores of high demand using artificial intelligence and phone providers.</description>
      <author> (https://deceptive.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://deceptive.medium.com/how-hackers-are-finding-creative-ways-to-steal-gift-cards-using-artificial-intelligence-8a0544a54c6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 09:07:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-02-05</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/02/app-developer-links-2021-02-05/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/02/app-developer-links-2021-02-05/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 09:06:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 229</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-229/</link>
      <description>This week&amp;#39;s update comes to you amongst the noisy backdrop of the garden being literally chopped up by high pressure hose (which I think my beautiful Rhode Broadcaster mic successfully excluded). As I say in the intro, it appears the horticulture industry is a little like the software one where</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-229/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 08:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helium Scraper - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/211/helium-scraper</link>
      <description>This is the third version of Helium Scraper, a web scraper that now uses CefSharp as a built in browser and can run many parallel off-screen browsers and uses a minimalist language, as well as ready-to-go wizards to configure extraction agents. It has a 10 day trial.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/211/helium-scraper</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 08:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to hire senior developers: Give them more autonomy</title>
      <link>https://hiringengineersbook.com/post/autonomy/</link>
      <description>Let me ask you a question: How much value do you think your source code has?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hiringengineersbook.com/post/autonomy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 08:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compiling DirectShow.Net for use in .NET 5</title>
      <link>https://weblogs.asp.net/rweigelt/compiling-directshow-net-for-use-in-net-5</link>
      <description>In a previous blog post, I wrote about how to access webcam properties from C# using DirectShow.Net. The last release of the library is version 2.1 from February 2010, with project files for Visual&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#8230;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://weblogs.asp.net/rweigelt/compiling-directshow-net-for-use-in-net-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 06:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here, I made a thing to save time building all projects in a solution</title>
      <link>https://www.mrlacey.com/2021/02/here-i-made-thing-to-save-time-building.html</link>
      <description>Compilers are complicated. They don&amp;#39;t always behave the way you&amp;#39;d expect. For instance, if you have a resource that has the Copy to Output D...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mrlacey.com/2021/02/here-i-made-thing-to-save-time-building.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 06:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the first six months of health care professionals replacing police officers, no one they encountered was arrested</title>
      <link>https://denverite.com/2021/02/02/in-the-first-six-months-of-health-care-professionals-replacing-police-officers-no-one-they-encountered-was-arrested/</link>
      <description>DPD Chief Pazen, who is fond of the STAR program, says it frees up officers to do their jobs: fight crime.</description>
      <author> (By  David Sachs)</author>
      <guid>https://denverite.com/2021/02/02/in-the-first-six-months-of-health-care-professionals-replacing-police-officers-no-one-they-encountered-was-arrested/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening an Admin Windows Terminal from Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2021/Feb/04/Opening-an-Admin-Windows-Terminal-from-Visual-Studio</link>
      <description>Opening Windows Terminal from another application is a bit of a pain. In particular I wanted to open Windows Terminal as an External Tool from Visual Studio and found it wasn&amp;#39;t as easy as referencing the `wt.exe` executable. Opening as an Administrator adds additional complexity. In this post I&amp;#39;ll talk about the use case of an External Tools and the settings to launch both a regular and admin Windows Terminal instance from External Tools.</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/rickstrahl)</author>
      <guid>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2021/Feb/04/Opening-an-Admin-Windows-Terminal-from-Visual-Studio</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConcurrentDictionaryExtensions.cs</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/davidfowl/3dac8f7b3d141ae87abf770d5781feed</link>
      <description>GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/davidfowl/3dac8f7b3d141ae87abf770d5781feed</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Critic - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/217/fantasy-critic</link>
      <description>Fantasy Critic is essentially fantasy football, for video games. A group of people form a league, and then create their own virtual video game “Publishers”. Each player then will assemble a roster of the games they believe will review the best. Similar to fantasy football, the players will alternat…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/217/fantasy-critic</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Profiling - Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/performance-profiling-introduction</link>
      <description>If you are not sure what to do once you start experiencing performance issues ...</description>
      <author> (Mark Downie)</author>
      <guid>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/performance-profiling-introduction</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rust-analyzer/rust-analyzer</title>
      <link>https://github.com/rust-analyzer/rust-analyzer/blob/master/docs/dev/architecture.md</link>
      <description>An experimental Rust compiler front-end for IDEs. Contribute to rust-analyzer/rust-analyzer development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (rust-analyzer)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/rust-analyzer/rust-analyzer/blob/master/docs/dev/architecture.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s Dunant subsea cable is now ready for service | Google Cloud Blog</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/infrastructure/googles-dunant-subsea-cable-is-now-ready-for-service</link>
      <description>The Dunant submarine cable system, crossing the Atlantic Ocean between Virginia Beach in the U.S. and Saint-Hilaire-de-Riez on the French Atlantic coast, has been deployed and tested and is now ready for service.</description>
      <author> (Chris Ciauri  President, EMEA, Google Cloud)</author>
      <guid>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/infrastructure/googles-dunant-subsea-cable-is-now-ready-for-service</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 03:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with SSL Certificate in Azure App Service</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/working-with-ssl-certificate-azure-app-service/</link>
      <description>This article shows you how to work with SSL certificates in Azure App Service. Last year I wrote a blog post on how to use Azure App Service managed certificates. If you’re using App service managed certificates, you don’t need to worry about the expiry, it will get renewed automatically by Azure. If you’re using custom domain names for Azure App service you will be able to configure SSL certificates to the custom domain name. To create custom TLS/SSL bindings for your App Service app, your App Service plan must be in the Basic, Standard, Premium, or Isolated tier.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/working-with-ssl-certificate-azure-app-service/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 03:05:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Templated Controls are Awesome | The Xamarin Show</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/Templated-Controls-are-Awesome--The-Xamarin-Show</link>
      <description>This week, James is joined again by Javier Su&amp;#225;rez, Developer on Xamarin.Forms, who explains what control templates are, why they are awesome, and how you can create amazing things with them. You don&amp;#39;t</description>
      <author> (by James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/Templated-Controls-are-Awesome--The-Xamarin-Show</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Suspender gets flagged for malware by Google Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.windowscentral.com/great-suspender-gets-pulled-chrome-web-store</link>
      <description>Users of The Great Suspender extension now see a message that flags it for containing malware. The popular extension was sold to new ownership last year and has been accused of adding malware in the past.</description>
      <author> (Sean Endicott)</author>
      <guid>https://www.windowscentral.com/great-suspender-gets-pulled-chrome-web-store</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxfam Australia investigating suspected data incident | Media Oxfam Australia</title>
      <link>https://media.oxfam.org.au/2021/02/oxfam-australia-investigating-suspected-data-incident/</link>
      <description>Late last week, Oxfam Australia was alerted to a suspected data incident. Oxfam immediately launched an investigation and engaged market leading experts to assist in identifying whether data may have</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://media.oxfam.org.au/2021/02/oxfam-australia-investigating-suspected-data-incident/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ideas That Created the Future</title>
      <link>https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/ideas-created-future?hss_channel=tw-20774514</link>
      <description>Classic papers by thinkers ranging from Aristotle and Leibniz to Norbert Wiener and Gordon Moore that chart the evolution of computer science.
                
                    Ideas That Created the Future collects forty-six classic papers in computer science that map the evolution of the field. It covers all aspects of computer science: theory and practice, architectures and algorithms, and logic and software systems, with an emphasis on the period of 1936–1980 but also including important earlier work. Offering papers by thinkers ranging from Aristotle and Leibniz to Alan Turing and Nobert Wiener, the book documents the discoveries and inventions that created today&amp;#39;s digital world. A brief essay by volume editor Harry Lewis, offering historical and intellectual context, accompanies each paper.Readers will learn that we owe to Aristotle the realization that fixed rules of logic can apply to different phenomena—that logic provides a general framework for reasoning—and that Leibniz recognized the merits of binary notation. They can read Ada Lovelace&amp;#39;s notes on L. F. Menabrea&amp;#39;s sketch of an analytical engine, George Boole&amp;#39;s attempt to capture the rules of reason in mathematical form, David Hilbert&amp;#39;s famous 1900 address, “Mathematical Problems,” and Alan Turing&amp;#39;s illumination of a metamathematical world. Later papers document the “Cambrian era” of 1950s computer design, Maurice Wilkes&amp;#39;s invention of microcode, Grace Hopper&amp;#39;s vision of a computer&amp;#39;s “education,” Ivan Sutherland&amp;#39;s invention of computer graphics at MIT, Whitfield Diffie and Martin Hellman&amp;#39;s pioneering work on encryption, and much more. Lewis&amp;#39;s guided tour of a burgeoning field is especially welcome at a time when computer education is increasingly specialized.</description>
      <author> (Edited by Harry R. Lewis)</author>
      <guid>https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/ideas-created-future?hss_channel=tw-20774514</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Knowledge Online</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Sharing-Knowledge-Online</link>
      <description>Want to share your knowledge and experiences with others online? David Giard, host of the Technology and Friends and GCast channels on YouTube, shows you how to get started.  Check out David&amp;#39;s videos </description>
      <author> (by Robert Green)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Sharing-Knowledge-Online</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity Framework Community Standup - Introducing MSBuild.Sdk.SqlProj</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lmHU1zD2mvA</link>
      <description>MSBuild.Sdk.SqlProj is a new open source project that allows you to build SQL Server Database Projects (.sqlproj) using the new SDK-style projects cross-plat...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lmHU1zD2mvA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safia Abdalla &amp;#183; The ReadME Project</title>
      <link>https://github.com/readme/safia-abdalla</link>
      <description>&amp;#128075; I’m Safia, also known online as [@captainsafia](https://github.com/captainsafia). I’m a full-time software engineer at Microsoft, a writer, and an [open source maintainer](https://github.blog/201...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/readme/safia-abdalla</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>