<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=channel%2FUCiaZbznpWV1o-KLxj8zqR6A</link>
      <description>Enjoy the videos and music you love, upload original content, and share it all with friends, family, and the world on YouTube.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=channel%2FUCiaZbznpWV1o-KLxj8zqR6A</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - haampie/libtree: ldd as a tree with an option to bundle dependencies into a single folder</title>
      <link>https://github.com/haampie/libtree</link>
      <description>ldd as a tree with an option to bundle dependencies into a single folder - GitHub - haampie/libtree: ldd as a tree with an option to bundle dependencies into a single folder</description>
      <author> (haampie)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/haampie/libtree</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 15:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An alarming trend in K-12 math education: a guest post and an open letter</title>
      <link>https://scottaaronson.blog/?p=6146</link>
      <description>Today, I’m turning over Shtetl-Optimized to an extremely important guest post by theoretical computer scientists Boaz Barak of Harvard and Edith Cohen of Google (cross-posted on the windows o…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scottaaronson.blog/?p=6146</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 15:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 UI/UX Tips &amp;amp; Tricks</title>
      <link>https://akcium.gumroad.com/l/ui-ux-tips</link>
      <description>What this book is about?For the whole year, I&amp;#39;ve been tweeting and collecting UI/UX tips. I end up with more than 120+ of them.Not all of them are good, some are controversial, some are opinionated.So I removed the worse and compiled the rest in 100 tips that I put in a few categories. Almost every tip has an illustration, as well as a description. Apart from that, I tried to provide some external resources that are related to the tip or that provide some proof. In total there are more than 50+ additional links complementing this book.&amp;#128073; You can download a free preview hereWho is this book for?Basically for everyone interested in user interfaces.It might be especially useful for developers, founders and aspiring designers.What&amp;#39;s inside?Exactly 100 UI/UX tips. Every tip takes exactly 1 page, so they are concise and easy to digest because almost all of them are illustrated.A few examples are in the gallery above.What do other people say?“Learning UI can be tricking, but seeing and understanding tips like these can help you level up, I enjoyed reading this book, lots of wisdom that took me years to learn here.”— Adrian Twarog (@adrian_twarog)&amp;quot;This book is seriously impressive. It features tons of high quality, actionable UI/UX tips with visual &amp;quot;do&amp;#39;s and don&amp;#39;ts&amp;quot; to help you design and build awesome applications - even if you&amp;#39;re not a designer yourself. Victor has packaged everything together neatly without any fluff, so I highly recommend picking up this book to level up your practical design skills.&amp;quot;— Mads Brodt (@madsbrodt)&amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ve been following Victor for quite a while and remember him posting all these UI/UX tips. What I can say is that you don&amp;#39;t need a design degree to make decent interfaces. Especially if you are bootstrapped founder and don&amp;#39;t have money for a designer. This book might help you much with that.&amp;quot;— Simon H&amp;#248;iberg (@SimonHoiberg)&amp;quot;What I liked about this book is that it&amp;#39;s easy to read. I&amp;#39;m a Frontend Engineer and sometimes it takes ages for me to make UI looks good. Among these tips, I found quite a few that I hadn&amp;#39;t thought about earlier.&amp;quot;— Dimitri Ivashchuk (@DivDev_)What is the option with a spreadsheet?Since most of the tips were published on Twitter, people left some comments agreeing or disagreeing with every tip. Sometimes they might have provided a better solution or an interesting idea.Plus, not all of the tips are in this book, I didn&amp;#39;t include some of them.The spreadsheet is a .xlsx file that contains ~120 links to my tips.Apart from this, I&amp;#39;ve included big threads, that are dedicated to a specific topic, e.g. validation of sign-up forms. One thread has about 50+ curated links related to designing different UI controls, that got more than 10K likes.For every tweet, I&amp;#39;ve also put the number of likes and retweets, which might be an indirect cue of how good it is. Or a least popular.This is how it looks like &amp;#128071;What is the option with a review?Besides tweeting UI/UX tips, I also did quite a few UI/UX reviews in different formats. At first, I made them for free, but then I realized that it takes quite a lot of time and effort to make them. After I got some positive reviews, I decided that I need to charge some money. Well, it will increase the quality of the review after all.So a review is basically a Loom video, usually ~30-50 minutes long, where I go through your interface and try to point out all the mistakes I see. Before I do this, I go through the interface myself.In some cases, the UI already looks good enough, so I got nothing much to add. In this case, I&amp;#39;ll either try to go deeper or just make a refund. You can also send me a message with your site upfront so that I check it and say if I&amp;#39;m able to help or not.How will I get the review?There is a .txt file with my email and Twitter. You should send me a link to your site or design or whatever you need to review, and I&amp;#39;ll record a video within a few days.You can send me your site upfront on Twitter: https://twitter.com/vponamariov.UI/UX Review testimonialsFree Review Threads</description>
      <author> (ByVictor)</author>
      <guid>https://akcium.gumroad.com/l/ui-ux-tips</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 14:54:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t Make My Mistakes: Common Infrastructure Errors I&amp;#39;ve Made</title>
      <link>https://matduggan.com/mistakes/</link>
      <description>One surreal experience as my career has progressed is the intense feeling of deja vu you get hit with during meetings. From time to time, someone will mention something and you&amp;#39;ll flash back to the same meeting you had about this a few jobs ago. A decision was made then,</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matduggan.com/mistakes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 14:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Advent Calendar - .NET Advent Calendar 2021, Day 4</title>
      <link>https://dotnet.christmas/2021/4</link>
      <description>One blog post every day until Christmas.</description>
      <author> (Dustin Moris Gorski)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnet.christmas/2021/4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 14:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webb</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2550/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2550/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 05:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality has a surprising amount of detail</title>
      <link>http://johnsalvatier.org/blog/2017/reality-has-a-surprising-amount-of-detail</link>
      <description>My dad emigrated from Colombia to North America when he was 18 looking looking for a better life. For my brother and I that meant a lot of standing outside in the cold. My dad’s preferred method of improving his lot was improving lots, and my brother and I were “voluntarily” recruited to help working on the buildings we owned.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://johnsalvatier.org/blog/2017/reality-has-a-surprising-amount-of-detail</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 03:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add RateLimiting APIs by BrennanConroy &amp;#183; Pull Request #61788 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/61788</link>
      <description>Part of dotnet/aspnetcore#37385
Moves the current non-generic APIs and two rate limiter implementations from https://github.com/aspnet/AspLabs/tree/main/src/RateLimiting.
There were a couple minor ...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/61788</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a web UI with ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YnU1FckB2s4</link>
      <description>Starting Monday, November 15, 2021 (PST), join Scott Hanselman, Maira Wenzel, Jeff Fritz, Jon Galloway, James Montemagno, and Matt Soucoup live on Learn TV f...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YnU1FckB2s4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Steps on MAUI Beach</title>
      <link>https://blog.taranissoftware.com/first-steps-on-maui-beach</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s time to set sail for .NET MAUI! This article documents my experiences starting a new cross platform app using .NET MAUI Preview 10.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.taranissoftware.com/first-steps-on-maui-beach</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never Use Black by Ian Storm Taylor</title>
      <link>https://ianstormtaylor.com/design-tip-never-use-black/</link>
      <description>One of the most important color tricks I’ve ever learned was to avoid using the color black in my work. Mrs. Zamula, my childhood art teacher, first warned me about black when I was in middle school. And I heard the same again multiple times at RISD. It sounds weird at first, but it’s good advice.</description>
      <author> (Ian Storm Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://ianstormtaylor.com/design-tip-never-use-black/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercharged high-resolution ocean simulation with JAX | dionhaefner.github.io</title>
      <link>https://dionhaefner.github.io/2021/12/supercharged-high-resolution-ocean-simulation-with-jax/</link>
      <description>Our Python ocean model Veros (which I maintain) now fully supports JAX as its computational backend. As a result, Veros has much better performance than before on both CPU and GPU, while all model code is still written in Python. In fact, we can now do high-resolution ocean simulations on …</description>
      <author> (Dion)</author>
      <guid>https://dionhaefner.github.io/2021/12/supercharged-high-resolution-ocean-simulation-with-jax/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tips on Adding JSON Output to Your CLI App - Brazil&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.kellybrazil.com/2021/12/03/tips-on-adding-json-output-to-your-cli-app/</link>
      <description>Best practices when adding a JSON output option to your command-line application.</description>
      <author> (Published by kellyjonbrazil)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.kellybrazil.com/2021/12/03/tips-on-adding-json-output-to-your-cli-app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So you want an iconic logo like Apple or Nike? / wesjones.co</title>
      <link>https://www.wesjones.co/ideas/iconic-logos</link>
      <description>Follow these five design principles to have the best chance at getting a logo people remember.</description>
      <author> (Nov 12
            
            Written By Wes Jones)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wesjones.co/ideas/iconic-logos</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep A Log</title>
      <link>https://bruno-oliveira.github.io/techblog/Keep-a-log/</link>
      <description>One of the most underrated things in the industry, especially when you’re working as a full-time developer, is the power of keeping a “knowledge stash” handy. There’s this perception that knowledge comes through experience, time, or simply osmosis, and, while that can be true over a long enough period of time and for the more superficial knowledge, there are just too many layers in a professional codebase that it’s impossible to grok it immediately.

</description>
      <author> (Bruno Oliveira)</author>
      <guid>https://bruno-oliveira.github.io/techblog/Keep-a-log/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Twitter was Hacked.</title>
      <link>https://jerseyfonseca.com/blogs/my-twitter-was-hacked</link>
      <description>My Twitter was hacked. It&amp;#39;s a shame because I spent a few months building up an audience of 2,000 followers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jerseyfonseca.com/blogs/my-twitter-was-hacked</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chromium Foundation | Gabriel&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabrielsimmer.com/posts/chromium-foundation/</link>
      <description>We need to divorce Chromium from Google   The world of browsers is pretty bleak. We essentially have one viable player, Chromium, flanked by the smaller players of Firefox, spiraling in a slow painful self destruction, and Safari, a browser well optimized for Apple products.
 note: We&amp;#39;re specifically discussing browsers, but you can roughly equate the arguments I make later with the browser&amp;#39;s respective engines.
 The current state of browsers is a difficult one.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.gabrielsimmer.com/posts/chromium-foundation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webrise</title>
      <link>https://bkardell.com/blog/Webrise.html</link>
      <description>Something in a recent piece by Jeremy Keith really clicked with something I’ve been thinking about, so I thought I’d write about it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bkardell.com/blog/Webrise.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind The Spotify Wrapped API Scenes</title>
      <link>https://den.dev/blog/spotify-wrapped/</link>
      <description>Understanding the components to the Spotify Wrapped generated story.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://den.dev/blog/spotify-wrapped/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I wrote my book</title>
      <link>https://www.kevinwmcconnell.com/writing/how-i-wrote-my-book</link>
      <description>Earlier this month I released a book. This post is about how I wrote it, the tools I used, and what I learned.
I&amp;#39;ve also shared a link to a repo containing all the settings, themes and file structure that I used, which you can take as a starting point for your own writing project.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.kevinwmcconnell.com/writing/how-i-wrote-my-book</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube is Auto-Deleting 100% of my Comments @YouTube #YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=43wp_EUk2ho</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (KingK
  
  
  
    KingK
  






    •
  
  
    
      113K views
    
      2 days ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=43wp_EUk2ho</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 23:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Templates in Visual Studio 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9kuA6jKzdw4</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s use Custom Project Templates in VS2022! In this demo, Sayed Hashimi will give you some key tips and tricks for both template users and template authors...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •
  
  
    
      12K views
    
      3 weeks ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9kuA6jKzdw4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 22:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Analyzers Via a Project Reference &amp;#183; Issue #18093 &amp;#183; dotnet/roslyn</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/roslyn/issues/18093</link>
      <description>Version Used: Visual Studio 2017 (though this applies to 2015 as well) Steps to Reproduce: I&amp;amp;#39;d like to be able to add analyzers to a project via a project reference. For example, let&amp;amp;#39;s say ...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/roslyn/issues/18093</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 22:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>while True: learn()</title>
      <link>https://www.gog.com/game/while_true_learn</link>
      <description>Save 10% when purchasing while True: learn(), while True: learn() Art Pack, while True: l</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.gog.com/game/while_true_learn</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 21:50:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Forms Lives On in .NET 6 -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/12/03/winforms-net-6.aspx</link>
      <description>Windows Forms would like you to know that the reports of its death are greatly exaggerated.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel12/03/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/12/03/winforms-net-6.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 21:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMP4300 - Game Programming - Lecture 01 - Course Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LpEdZbUdDe4</link>
      <description>00:00 - Welcome &amp;amp; Introduction06:52 - Course Syllabus31:39 - Game Programming / ECS Lecture43:46 - What is ECS?Memorial University - Computer Science 4300 - ...</description>
      <author> (Strange Loop Conference
  
  
  
    Strange Loop Conference
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LpEdZbUdDe4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 21:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>  3.0 — blender.org</title>
      <link>https://www.blender.org/download/releases/3-0/</link>
      <description>21 years after Blender 2.0, version 3.0 brings unprecedented
performance on a robust yet light package.</description>
      <author> (Blender Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.blender.org/download/releases/3-0/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 20:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pg_graphql: A GraphQL extension for PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://supabase.com/blog/2021/12/03/pg-graphql</link>
      <description>GraphQL support is in development for PostgreSQL + Supabase.</description>
      <author> (https://github.com/olirice)</author>
      <guid>https://supabase.com/blog/2021/12/03/pg-graphql</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 20:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Grinch Bot is Stealing Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/grinch-bot/</link>
      <description>Bots moved quickly this holiday season, launching over 1 trillion requests on Black Friday but quickly receding after the weekend.</description>
      <author> (Ben Solomon)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/grinch-bot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 19:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Michael Washington on Blazor in .NET 6 - Episode 168</title>
      <link>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/michael-washington-on-blazor-in-net-6-episode-168</link>
      <description>This week, Michael Washington is once again joining the podcast to discuss all things Blazor! He previously joined the podcast on episode 88, where he discussed the state of Blazor back in May 2020. &amp;amp;nbsp; Michael is an ASP.NET and C# programmer who has extensive knowledge in process improvement, billing systems, and student information systems. He also is the founder of two websites, AiHelpWebsite.com and BlazorHelpWebsite.com — both fantastic resources that help empower developers. Michael resides in Los Angeles, California, with his son Zachary and wife, Valerie. &amp;amp;nbsp; Hot off the heels of .NET Conf, there is tons to discuss regarding Blazor and .NET 6! Michael shares the key announcement that developers should be looking out for, the announcements he was personally most excited for, and his advice for those looking to just get started with Blazor. He also speaks about some of his recently published books on the topics of Blazor Oqtane and Blazor WebAssembly, speaks about the current state of third-party UI controls and components, and where you can go to take an even deeper dive into everything he discusses today. &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [:36] About The Azure DevOps Podcast, Clear Measure; the new video podcast Architect Tips; and Jeffrey’s offer to speak at virtual user groups. [1:11] About today’s episode with Michael Washington. [1:37] Jeffrey welcomes Michael back to the podcast! [1:58] Michael introduces himself, shares his career background, and what led him to focus on Blazor. [4:45] Michael speaks about Azure Communication Services and how to make it work with Blazor. [7:51] The #1 announcement Michael was most excited for at .NET Conf: hot reload. [11:38] Michael highlights some of the other key announcements at the recent .NET Conf. [14:58] A word from Azure DevOps Podcast’s sponsor: Clear Measure. [15:32] Michael speaks about the different types of Blazor applications (beyond serverside and WebAssembly) and gives an overview of the landscape of Blazor going into 2022. [20:00] Why Michael urges listeners to give Blazor a try if you have not already. [22:27] Michael shares his insights on WebAssembly and what he currently uses it for. [25:34] About Michael’s recent ebooks, Custom Blazor Oqtane Modules Succinctly and Blazor WebAssembly Succinctly. [28:27] The current state of the third-party UI controls and components. [31:34] Michael shares some parting advice on what developers should know about when it comes to .NET 6 and Blazor. [34:06] Jeffrey thanks Michael for joining The Azure DevOps Podcast once again! &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:  — New video podcast!   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!  — Click here to download the .NET DevOps for Azure ebook!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!  — Dec. 7th‒9th in Las Vegas, Nevada (Use discount code: PALERMO)                           &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/michael-washington-on-blazor-in-net-6-episode-168</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 19:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>