<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Exploring the ABP web app framework</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/vMWM-_ihjwM</link>
      <description>ABP Framework is a complete infrastructure to create modern web applications by following the software development best practices and conventions. Join ABP t...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/vMWM-_ihjwM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 16:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People don&amp;#39;t work as much as you think</title>
      <link>https://drmaciver.substack.com/p/people-dont-work-as-much-as-you-think</link>
      <description>There is a persistent idea that people work 40 hours a week. They don&amp;#39;t, and if you try to do this it will break you. Here are some more reasonable guidelines.</description>
      <author> (David R. MacIver)</author>
      <guid>https://drmaciver.substack.com/p/people-dont-work-as-much-as-you-think</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 15:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Tips and Tricks for Better Development Lifecycle</title>
      <link>https://codewithshadman.com/top-5-tips-and-tricks-for-better-development/</link>
      <description>Creating a secure SDLC process demands dedication and effort in each phase, from a collection of requirements to deployment and maintenance. It requires a change of mind in the development team to focus on security at every project stage rather than focusing only on functionality.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/shadman.kudchikar)</author>
      <guid>https://codewithshadman.com/top-5-tips-and-tricks-for-better-development/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 09:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketplace Office Hours (Business and Technical)- Register Now for February Sessions</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/marketplace-office-hours-business-and-technical-register-now-for-february-sessions/</link>
      <description>The commercial marketplace services team in Azure engineering has upcoming&amp;#160;Marketplace Office Hours&amp;#160;on business and technical topics; providing publishers with the information and resources to successfully publish their solutions to the Microsoft Commercial Marketplace.&amp;#160;&amp;#160;Register for one of the following Marketplace Office hours sessions now: Marketplace Office Hours: Resources and best practices to accelerate publishing your solution to the commercial marketplace Join us for an overview of the three different transactable offer types in the Microsoft marketplace. &amp;#160;</description>
      <author> (Developer Support)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/marketplace-office-hours-business-and-technical-register-now-for-february-sessions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 09:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wire • Secure Messenger | F-Droid - Free and Open Source Android App Repository</title>
      <link>https://f-droid.org/en/packages/com.wire/</link>
      <description>Wire offers highly secure communication – anywhere and anytime.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://f-droid.org/en/packages/com.wire/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 08:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams 2.0 will use half the memory, dropping Electron...</title>
      <link>https://tomtalks.blog/microsoft-teams-2-0-will-use-half-the-memory-dropping-electron-for-edge-webview2/</link>
      <description>Credit to Brad Sams for first reporting on this, Alongside the Windows 11 announcement today, Rish Tandon, the CVP Engineering for Microsoft Teams, posted on Twitter about changes coming to Microsoft Teams architecture. It gave a lot of useful insight into what is coming. Microsoft Teams is...</description>
      <author> (Tom Arbuthnot)</author>
      <guid>https://tomtalks.blog/microsoft-teams-2-0-will-use-half-the-memory-dropping-electron-for-edge-webview2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 05:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - stenh0use/docker-machine-for-mac: Docker Machine for Mac - an alternative to Docker for Mac</title>
      <link>https://github.com/stenh0use/docker-machine-for-mac</link>
      <description>Docker Machine for Mac - an alternative to Docker for Mac - GitHub - stenh0use/docker-machine-for-mac: Docker Machine for Mac - an alternative to Docker for Mac</description>
      <author> (stenh0use)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/stenh0use/docker-machine-for-mac</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 05:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare color photos from the Second World War, 1941-1945 - Rare Historical Photos</title>
      <link>https://rarehistoricalphotos.com/color-photos-from-second-world-war/</link>
      <description>These are rarely seen color pictures from the Second World War featured in the book “The Second World War in Colour” by the Imperial War Museum.</description>
      <author> (Jim
				
					September 30, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://rarehistoricalphotos.com/color-photos-from-second-world-war/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 05:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piped</title>
      <link>https://youtube.censors.us/shorts/-dlvxucMy-8</link>
      <description>An alternative privacy-friendly YouTube frontend which is efficient by design.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.censors.us/shorts/-dlvxucMy-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 04:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoresponder</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2574/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2574/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 03:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trying to vlog #crypto #vlog #shorts</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-dlvxucMy-8</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (David Wong
  
  
  
    David Wong
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-dlvxucMy-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 01:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed up your .NET app with the .NET memory profilers in Visual Studio 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x8mRttvzJBs</link>
      <description>The profiling tools in Visual Studio 2022 are the tools you need to improve the performance of your app. In this video we look at some of the new features in...</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Visual Studio
  
  
  
    Microsoft Visual Studio
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x8mRttvzJBs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 01:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA GPUs Enable Simulation of a Living Cell | NVIDIA Blog</title>
      <link>https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2022/01/20/living-cell-simulation/</link>
      <description>Researchers from the University of Illinois developed GPU-accelerated software to simulate a cell that metabolizes and grows like a living cell.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2022/01/20/living-cell-simulation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 01:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCaml - Generalized algebraic datatypes</title>
      <link>https://ocaml.org/manual/gadts-tutorial.html#c%3Agadts-tutorial</link>
      <description>Generalized algebraic datatypes, or GADTs, extend usual sum types in
two ways: constraints on type parameters may change depending on the
value constructor, and some type variables may be existentially
quantified.
Adding constraints is done by giving an explicit return type, where type
parameters are instantiated:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ocaml.org/manual/gadts-tutorial.html#c%3Agadts-tutorial</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 01:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>| Avoiding Conflicts on Social Media Might Make Things WorseMichele Coscia</title>
      <link>https://www.michelecoscia.com/?p=2082</link>
      <description>Look, I get it. Sometimes you really don’t want to get mired in a Facebook discussion with that uncle of yours who thinks that the moon doesn’t exist. It’s easier to block, unfriend, ignore, rather than engage. However, have you considered that avoiding conflicts might make things worse? This is a question Luca Rossi and I asked ourselves as a part of our research on polarization on social media. Part of the answer comes from an Agent Based Model (ABM) we have recently published on Plos One in the paper “How Minimizing Conflicts Could Lead to Polarization on Social Media: an Agent-Based Model Investigation.”</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.michelecoscia.com/?p=2082</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In defense of NIR</title>
      <link>https://www.jlekstrand.net/jason/blog/2022/01/in-defense-of-nir/</link>
      <description>NIR has been an integral part of the Mesa driver stack for about six or seven years now (depending on how you count) and a lot has changed since NIR first landed at the end of 2014 and I wrote my initial NIR notes. Also, for various reasons, I’ve had to give my NIR elevator pitch a few times lately. I think it’s time for a new post. This time on why, after working on this mess for seven years, I still think NIR was the right call.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jlekstrand.net/jason/blog/2022/01/in-defense-of-nir/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teleporting thru Information Space</title>
      <link>http://evanlh.com/posts/personal_information_environment/</link>
      <description>I’m really excited by the research effort proposed in Towards a Dynamic Multiscale Personal Information Space, a 2020 paper advocating more ‘convivial’1 information spaces. As the authors describe it, when a user interacts with the computer:
 The system offers a novel interface to her digital information, consolidating her data (e.g., email, messages, calendars, web pages, notes, sketches, and analyses and visualizations) across applications. When she interacts with the information in her workspace, it seems to be alive, aware of when and how it was last used, and sometimes even why she was using it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://evanlh.com/posts/personal_information_environment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Man Yells at Cloud</title>
      <link>https://pxlnv.com/blog/old-man-yells-at-cloud/</link>
      <description>Hinted at earlier this week and made official today, MacOS 12.3 will be dropping support for the kernel extension used by cloud storage providers like Dropbox and Microsoft OneDrive. They will instead be required to use Apple’s File Provider extension, originally created for iOS’ Files app and integrated into MacOS since Catalina. It is a […]</description>
      <author> (Nick Heer)</author>
      <guid>https://pxlnv.com/blog/old-man-yells-at-cloud/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suggestions for onboarding remote Software Engineers</title>
      <link>https://zohaib.me/suggestions-for-onboarding-remote-engineers/</link>
      <description>Onboarding remote Software Engineers can be challenging. Here are some suggestions from my experience of onboarding multiple engineers remotely to make them become part of team.</description>
      <author> (Zohaib Rauf)</author>
      <guid>https://zohaib.me/suggestions-for-onboarding-remote-engineers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fun with Node experimental modules and loaders</title>
      <link>https://raphael.medaer.me/2022/01/28/fun-with-node-experimental-modules-and-loaders.html</link>
      <description>If you are a front-end or a fullstack developer, you maybe already imported CSS files from a Javascript or a Typescript file. For instance: import styles from &amp;quot;./styles.css&amp;quot; A few months ago it would not have been possible out of the shelf. Indeed you would need a bundler (such as WebPack, Rollup,…) to “inline” the CSS file as a string in your Javascript file. Nowadays it’s possible thanks to the “CSS Modules” (to not confuse with the homonym open-source project).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://raphael.medaer.me/2022/01/28/fun-with-node-experimental-modules-and-loaders.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 21 best StumbleUpon alternatives of 2022</title>
      <link>https://blog.kovah.de/en/2022/best-stumbleupon-alternatives-2022/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Kevin Woblick)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.kovah.de/en/2022/best-stumbleupon-alternatives-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reclaiming the lost art of Linux server administration</title>
      <link>https://www.pietrorea.com/2022/01/28/reclaiming-the-lost-art-of-linux-server-administration/</link>
      <description>One of the skills I wish I&amp;#39;d learned earlier in my career is basic Linux server administration. Specifically in relation to hosting something on the web, either a web app or API that I wrote myself, or something from the thriving self-hosted community, such as Wordpress. Managing servers is increasingly seen as the &amp;#39;older way&amp;#39; of doing things, so it&amp;#39;s easy to become a software developer and never learn to set up a VPS, set up remote access, stand up a firewall, etc.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pietrorea.com/2022/01/28/reclaiming-the-lost-art-of-linux-server-administration/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 23:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marijuana Deals Nearby | Find 420 Deals &amp;amp; Discounts | Leafly</title>
      <link>https://www.leafly.com/deals</link>
      <description>Find great deals on marijuana and cannabis products for 4/20 at recreational cannabis stores and medical dispensaries near you.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.leafly.com/deals</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 22:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brand New! Azure Functions OpenAPI Extension on .NET 6</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=exFObKITBaQ</link>
      <description>Since //Build 2021 where the Azure Functions OpenAPI extension was officially announced as a preview, it&amp;#39;s now GA with the full support of .NET 6.Because Azu...</description>
      <author> (Dapr
  
  
  
    Dapr
  






    •
  
  
    
      4.5K views
    
      3 months ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=exFObKITBaQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 22:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps requires TLS 1.2 on all connections including Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/azure-devops-requires-tls-1-2-on-all-connections-including-visual-studio/</link>
      <description>Starting Monday January 31st, Azure DevOps will no longer accept connections coming over TLS 1.0 and 1.1 due to security vulnerabilities in those protocols. Developers have increasingly become the target of hackers and these protocols have known security vulnerabilities not specific to Microsoft’s implementation.</description>
      <author> (Ruben Rios)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/azure-devops-requires-tls-1-2-on-all-connections-including-visual-studio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 21:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making the web better. With blocks!</title>
      <link>https://www.joelonsoftware.com/2022/01/27/making-the-web-better-with-blocks/</link>
      <description>You’ve probably seen web editors based on the idea of blocks. I’m typing this in WordPress, which has a little + button that brings up a long list of potential blocks that you can inser…</description>
      <author> (About the author.)</author>
      <guid>https://www.joelonsoftware.com/2022/01/27/making-the-web-better-with-blocks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 21:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 280</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/vsEGdYmG5g8</link>
      <description>That Azure Bill</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt
  
  
  
    Troy Hunt
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/vsEGdYmG5g8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 19:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be a Cognizant Software Developer #shorts</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dytt3nQ0hVk</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t accept the status quo. Be cognizant and aware of what doesn&amp;#39;t feel &amp;quot;right&amp;quot; during your day to day development.  Don&amp;#39;t accept &amp;quot;that&amp;#39;s how it is&amp;quot;.#softwa...</description>
      <author> (DevTown
  
  
  
    DevTown
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dytt3nQ0hVk</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 19:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January 7, 2021 - Building a PowerBI report, CSS Ribbon, and Azure functions</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wf3kY5G1NnY</link>
      <description>KlipTok is growing and Fritz needs a way to monitor growth and how folks are using the application.  In this video, he starts building a PowerBI dashboard to...</description>
      <author> (Pragmatic Works
  
  
  
    Pragmatic Works
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wf3kY5G1NnY</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 17:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January 10, 2021 - Tab-based notation with TAML, ServiceBus with KlipTok and MORE!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wqcpJimAEPg</link>
      <description>Fritz starts this stream by revisiting a markup language he invented that is ONLY tabs called TAML.Information about TAML can be found at https://github.com/...</description>
      <author> (Zeneca&amp;#39;s NFT Academy
  
  
  
    Zeneca&amp;#39;s NFT Academy
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wqcpJimAEPg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 17:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did we get from .NET Framework to just .NET?</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RbbPLCyHTts</link>
      <description>A simple question for @csharpfritz , that traces a little .NET history: How did we get from .NET Framework to just .NET?All your .NET Docs are at https://msf...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •
  
  
    
      155K views
    
      2 months ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RbbPLCyHTts</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 17:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS Monterey 12.3 Beta Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://developer.apple.com/documentation/macos-release-notes/macos-12_3-release-notes#Python</link>
      <description>Update your apps to use new features, and test your apps against API changes.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developer.apple.com/documentation/macos-release-notes/macos-12_3-release-notes#Python</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 17:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>