<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Atlas of Space</title>
      <link>https://atlasof.space/</link>
      <description>The Atlas of Space</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://atlasof.space/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 22:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fidget</title>
      <link>https://www.mattkeeter.com/projects/fidget/</link>
      <description>Fidget is a library for representing,
compiling, and evaluating large-scale math expressions, i.e. hundreds or
thousands of arithmetic clauses.  It&amp;#39;s mainly designed as a backend for
implicit surfaces, but the
library is flexible enough for many different uses!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mattkeeter.com/projects/fidget/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 20:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollama is Awesome!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=gv8fJWKrfIs</link>
      <description>In this edition of #tech on ice, I talk about #ollama and how it makes running #ai #llm models simple. Awesome stuff!
#technology #developer #programming #coldplunge</description>
      <author> (Isaac Levin)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=gv8fJWKrfIs</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 19:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired From Meta After 1 Week: Here’s All The Dirt I Got</title>
      <link>https://sebastiancarlos.com/fired-from-meta-after-1-week-heres-all-the-dirt-i-got-855e4e5a0d65</link>
      <description>This is not just another story of a disgruntled ex-employee. I’m not shying away from the serious corporate espionage or the ethical…</description>
      <author> (https://sebastiancarlos.com)</author>
      <guid>https://sebastiancarlos.com/fired-from-meta-after-1-week-heres-all-the-dirt-i-got-855e4e5a0d65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 18:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How We Cracked a 512-Bit DKIM Key for Less Than $8 in the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://dmarcchecker.app/articles/crack-512-bit-dkim-rsa-key</link>
      <description>In our study on the SPF, DKIM, and DMARC records of the top 1M websites, we were surprised to uncover more than 1,700 public DKIM keys that were shorter than 1,024 bits in length. This finding was unexpected, as RSA keys shorter than 1,024 bits are considered insecure, and their use in DKIM has been deprecated since the introduction of RFC 8301 in 2018.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dmarcchecker.app/articles/crack-512-bit-dkim-rsa-key</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 16:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Ultra Long Range TOSLINK
</title>
      <link>https://blog.benjojo.co.uk/post/sfp-experiment-ultra-long-range-toslink</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.benjojo.co.uk/post/sfp-experiment-ultra-long-range-toslink</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 15:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Backbone of Digital Communication: Understanding the Client-Server Model - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/the-backbone-of-digital-communication-understanding-the-client-server-model/</link>
      <description>The client-server model, a ubiquitous presence in our digital universe, is the invisible framework that powers nearly every online interaction you experience. From the seamless streaming of your favorite shows to the lightning-fast loading of websites, this model is the architectural masterpiece orchestrating how devices exchange information in a networked world. It’s the quiet genius behind the scenes, ensuring your digital life feels effortless.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/the-backbone-of-digital-communication-understanding-the-client-server-model/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 14:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switching Tech Jobs: What To Consider As A Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=fRdqUBDjhX8</link>
      <description>At some point in your software engineering career, you&amp;#39;ll be faced with the debate:

Stick with the current job or take on some risk with a new role.

How will you decide? Which factors should you consider?

----
&amp;#128273; Membership &amp;amp; Subscriptions:
- &amp;#128232; Weekly Newsletter: https://weekly.devleader.ca
- &amp;#127960;️ Private Discord Community: https://sidestack.io/devleader

&amp;#129504; Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Get Promoted As A Software Engineer: https://dometrain.com/course/career-getting-promoted-as-a-software-engineer/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?ref=nick-cosentino
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

&amp;#128483;️ Social Media &amp;amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs:  @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp;amp; Products/Services That I Love:
- @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper Opus Clip: https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----

#softwareengineering #softwaredeveloper #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=fRdqUBDjhX8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StackOverflow Dec 2024 stats</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/hopeseekr/f522e380e35745bd5bdc3269a9f0b132</link>
      <description>StackOverflow Dec 2024 stats. GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/hopeseekr/f522e380e35745bd5bdc3269a9f0b132</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operating System in 1,000 Lines</title>
      <link>https://operating-system-in-1000-lines.vercel.app/en</link>
      <description>Hey there! In this book, we&amp;#39;re going to build a small operating system from scratch, step by step.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://operating-system-in-1000-lines.vercel.app/en</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft disguises Bing as Google to fool inattentive searchers</title>
      <link>https://www.pcworld.com/article/2568916/microsoft-disguises-bing-as-google-to-fool-inattentive-searchers.html</link>
      <description>If you can&amp;#39;t beat Google, trick your users into thinking that they&amp;#39;re using Google. That seems to be Microsoft&amp;#39;s sneaky new approach to Bing search.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pcworld.com/article/2568916/microsoft-disguises-bing-as-google-to-fool-inattentive-searchers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 06:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burdens of type 2 diabetes and cardiovascular disease attributable to sugar-sweetened beverages in 184 countries - Nature Medicine</title>
      <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03345-4</link>
      <description>Estimates from the Global Dietary Database indicated that 2.2 million new type 2 diabetes and 1.2 million new cardiovascular disease cases were attributable to sugar-sweetened beverages worldwide in 2020, with the highest burdens in sub-Saharan Africa, Latin America and the Caribbean.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03345-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 05:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistakes engineers make in large established codebases</title>
      <link>https://www.seangoedecke.com/large-established-codebases/</link>
      <description>What I&amp;#39;ve learned from ten years working on projects like this</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.seangoedecke.com/large-established-codebases/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 04:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude plays GeoGuessr</title>
      <link>https://www.jerrywei.net/blog/claude-plays-geoguessr</link>
      <description>Claude plays GeoGuessr
Jerry Wei
January 06, 2025.
Constantly seeking ways to evaluate and benchmark the capabilities of our AI models helps us understand their current performance and drives future development and improvements. In this spirit, I recently examined a fun task: How well can Claude</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jerrywei.net/blog/claude-plays-geoguessr</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street-fighting RAG: Chain-of-thought prompting</title>
      <link>https://www.sgnt.ai/p/street-fighting-rag-chain-of-thought</link>
      <description>or, reducing hallucination and making in-generation adjustments to LLM responses</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sgnt.ai/p/street-fighting-rag-chain-of-thought</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The good, the bad, and the ugly of Gemini’s structured outputs – Dylan Castillo</title>
      <link>https://dylancastillo.co/posts/gemini-structured-outputs.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dylancastillo.co/posts/gemini-structured-outputs.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do the obvious next thing</title>
      <link>https://www.sonyasupposedly.com/do-the-obvious-next-thing/</link>
      <description>Letting gravity be my guide, like water.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sonyasupposedly.com/do-the-obvious-next-thing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Audience Matters</title>
      <link>https://shubhamjain.co/2025/01/07/the-audience-matters/</link>
      <description>
There&amp;#39;s an interesting story behind making DDLJ (*Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge*). For the unaware, it&amp;#39;s an extremely successful Bollywood film with the longest theatrical run in history. I always considered it to be the epitome of clich&amp;#233;d Bollywood—a lazy, formulaic crowd-pleaser. I am not being harsh here. Aditya Chopra, the director himself, admits:

&amp;gt; My film is not different. I’m making the most commercial, clich&amp;#233;d, tapori (pedestrian) movie. I’m making the oldest story in the world.

DDLJ is an ordinary bollywood movie, but its success was no accident. It was born from nearly a decade of research—hard, deliberate work to [understand the Indian audience](https://www.reddit.com/r/BollyBlindsNGossip/comments/116qx6g/aditya_chopra_appreciation_post/)

&amp;gt; He (Aditya Chopra) saw every movie in the theatre FDFS (First Day, First Show) since he was 12 - just to study almost clinically what the audience thought, where they laughed, where they left. He tracked the BO numbers. He did the analysis, put in the hard work, and studied the business of cinema quite literally. He used those insights to inform his filmmaking process and predict what’s next. He understands the psychology of people in general, of Indian people very deeply, and what connects with them and what doesn’t.

This method is a far cry from the creative projects I’ve always admired—the &amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t care about the audience&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Ship something you want to see&amp;quot; kind of projects. The movies, shows, and video games I have admired have all been driven by a wild, passionate vision to make something great, not how the audience is going to react.

Aditya flipped this approach on its head. Well before committing to a project, he wanted to understand what makes the Indian audience tick. Make no mistake, he was still creative—the locations, dialogues, songs were all well-thought. However, he worked within the bounds of what he believed would eventually succeed.

## Caring About Something That Works

Rick Rubin is a big advocate of letting your creative spirit do the work. You care and everything else will fall in place. In his book _The Creative Act_, [he says](https://www.goodreads.com/work/quotes/96114890-the-creative-act-a-way-of-being):

&amp;gt; In terms of priority, inspiration comes first. You come next. The audience comes last.
&amp;gt;
&amp;gt; All that matters is that you are making something you love, to the best of your ability, here and now.

It’s a beautiful idea. But here’s the problem. Sooner or later, you need to create something the audience cares about. That&amp;#39;s because, without their validation, you’ll struggle to make money and sustain what you love. 

Sure, you can ignore the audience and create only for yourself. There are enough success stories to make free-spirited creativity sound like a tempting idea. However, there are just as many failures. The basic fact can&amp;#39;t be ignored: to have a shot at making money, you need to build something people are willing to pay for. You need to care about the audience. 

The other approach is to figure out what is working in the market, and create something with that in mind. The most successful indie-hackers I’ve seen do this very well. [LevelsIO](https://x.com/levelsio?lang=en), for example, has been pretty amazing in spotting trends and building something valuable around them. When Generative AI was just taking off, he created Interior.ai and it quickly succeeded in becoming a $50k MRR side project. 

Danny Postma entire approach to product-building centers around researching what [people are already searching](https://www.dannypostma.com/seo-course) for via SEO tools, selecting the ones with money-making potential, then slowly building your website to rank well for those keywords.

Of course, you still need creativity. It&amp;#39;s not easy to sell junk. But by focusing your creativity on something with a better chance of success—something people already want—you can drastically improve your odds at making money. You treat creativity as a tool, not the goal.

</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shubhamjain.co/2025/01/07/the-audience-matters/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take the pedals off the bike</title>
      <link>https://www.fortressofdoors.com/take-the-pedals-off-the-bike/</link>
      <description>Apparently if you want to teach kids how to ride a bike you&amp;#39;re supposed to take the pedals off first, and now my mind will never be the same again.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.fortressofdoors.com/take-the-pedals-off-the-bike/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How LLMs are secretly reshaping the code of tomorrow, and what to do about it</title>
      <link>https://nathanpeck.com/how-llms-of-today-are-secretly-shaping-the-code-of-tomorrow/</link>
      <description>The next revolutionary programming framework might be dead before you even discover it. AI coding assistants are reshaping software development practices in some unexpected ways.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nathanpeck.com/how-llms-of-today-are-secretly-shaping-the-code-of-tomorrow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruising a VPS at OpenBSD Amsterdam</title>
      <link>https://www.tumfatig.net/2025/cruising-a-vps-at-openbsd-amsterdam/</link>
      <description>When it comes to getting an OpenBSD virtual machine, you can go to your preferred Linux VPS provider and hack its rescue mode to install OpenBSD. Or you can go to a VPS provider that offers booting from an ISO file and getting access to the console. In that case, you’d probably get an OpenBSD VM running on KVM. Which is not that bad.
But you can also book your VM from OpenBSD Amsterdam and let the 100% OpenBSD journey begin.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tumfatig.net/2025/cruising-a-vps-at-openbsd-amsterdam/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Syndication - The Missing Internet&amp;#160;Protocol</title>
      <link>http://tautvilas.lt/decentralized-syndication-the-missing-internet-protocol/</link>
      <description>The Internet is decentralized by design. It came into being not at once, but in parts. New protocols were added on top of previous ones, but one crucial protocol is still missing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://tautvilas.lt/decentralized-syndication-the-missing-internet-protocol/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a new role</title>
      <link>https://chrisshort.net/micro/looking-for-a-new-role-2025/</link>
      <description>From Red Hat to AWS, I&amp;#39;ve done developer advocacy, technical marketing, and product marketing. This is in addition to the upstream work I do for Kubernetes. I welcome new opportunities.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chrisshort.net/micro/looking-for-a-new-role-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iain Schmitt</title>
      <link>https://iainschmitt.com/post/the-strangest-carrier-southern-linc</link>
      <description>Any firm&amp;#39;s contingency plans or redundant infrastructure says a lot about the business that they are in and what tradeoffs they are faced with. As an example, if your company&amp;#39;s HR software vendor was inaccessible for a day because of an AWS availability zone failure, you probably have bigger problems that day. Beside the point that AWS customers are far likelier to bring an outage on themselves, the impact to a company of HR software being inaccessible for a work day is not an &amp;quot;everything grids to a halt&amp;quot; situation. Some offer letters will be sent out late and any pending changes in benefits wouldn&amp;#39;t be acted on, but it isn&amp;#39;t the end of the world. Lattice is the first company that came to mind here, and if Lattice engineering leadership is trying to prioritise between a) lift-and-shift capabilities to another public cloud vendor and b) new features that will differentiate the product in the marketplace, it&amp;#39;s pretty clear that they should go for the latter.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iainschmitt.com/post/the-strangest-carrier-southern-linc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsing JSON in C &amp;amp; C++: Singleton Tax</title>
      <link>https://ashvardanian.com/posts/parsing-json-with-allocators-cpp/</link>
      <description>I’d argue that almost every open-source developer gets an extra spark of joy when someone reads the documentation and uses their tool in a way that goes beyond the classic 101 examples. It’s a rare treat even for popular projects like JSON parsers, but if you are building high-throughput software, such as analyzing millions of network packets per second, you’ll have to dig deeper.
The first thing I generally check in such libraries is the memory usage pattern and whether I can override the default memory allocator. It is the most common singleton of them all!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ashvardanian.com/posts/parsing-json-with-allocators-cpp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero to One Hundred Thousand Tests</title>
      <link>https://etodd.io/2025/01/06/zero-to-one-hundred-thousand-tests/</link>
      <description>When I started at StrongDM five years ago (woah), we had zero automated tests. Last year we had 50,000 tests. Today, around 70% of our code is covered by over 100,000 tests, most of which run on every pull request.
What follows is my personal opinion about what constitutes a “good” automated test based on my observation of this colossal increase in test coverage. The goal is not to convince you I’m right, but to draw some contrasts and provoke you to question assumptions and form your own opinions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://etodd.io/2025/01/06/zero-to-one-hundred-thousand-tests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning data into calendar feeds</title>
      <link>https://mattrossman.com/2025/01/06/turning-data-into-calendar-feeds/</link>
      <description>I rely on Google Calendar and macOS Calendar to remind me of time commitments.
Some events I care about are managed by other people, making them hard to track
in my calendar apps.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mattrossman.com/2025/01/06/turning-data-into-calendar-feeds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an LVGL Touchscreen App with Zig</title>
      <link>https://lupyuen.org/articles/lvgl.html</link>
      <description>Can we use Zig to build an LVGL Touchscreen App for Apache NuttX RTOS? Also wrap the LVGL API in Zig to build simpler, safer LVGL Apps? Let&amp;#39;s find out!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lupyuen.org/articles/lvgl.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic/Tragic Email Links: Don&amp;#39;t make them the only option</title>
      <link>https://recyclebin.zip/posts/annoyinglinks/</link>
      <description>Subscription websites now like to use magic email links for login. They are extremely annoying.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://recyclebin.zip/posts/annoyinglinks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLC | Microserving LLM engines</title>
      <link>https://blog.mlc.ai/2025/01/07/microserving-llm-engines</link>
      <description>Jan 7, 2025
        
        
        •</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.mlc.ai/2025/01/07/microserving-llm-engines</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dermatology AI that can reason like a doctor</title>
      <link>https://mdme.ai/blog/2025/01/06/dermatology-ai-that-can-reason-like-a-doctor</link>
      <description>Human clinicians have traditionally had a definitive edge over traditional computer vision programs because humans can combine information from images and text. Here, we demonstrate the capability of large language model technology, in particular GPT4o, to convincingly use clinical context to enhance dermatological image interpretation in ways analogous to the semantic reasoning of a real dermatologist. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mdme.ai/blog/2025/01/06/dermatology-ai-that-can-reason-like-a-doctor</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving SVG chart interactivity with Voronoi diagrams</title>
      <link>https://tomhazledine.com/improving-svg-chart-interactivity-with-voronoi-diagrams/</link>
      <description>How I used Delaunay triangulation and Voronoi diagrams to fix hover issues in my SVG charts (with React and D3.js).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tomhazledine.com/improving-svg-chart-interactivity-with-voronoi-diagrams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing Post-Training Techniques from Recent Open LLMs | Brian Fitzgerald</title>
      <link>https://brianfitzgerald.xyz/dpo-review/</link>
      <description>header</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://brianfitzgerald.xyz/dpo-review/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#220;llar Maasik - Learning Laravel by building a postal code finder</title>
      <link>https://usrme.xyz/posts/learning-laravel-by-building-a-postal-code-finder/</link>
      <description>January 5, 2025</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://usrme.xyz/posts/learning-laravel-by-building-a-postal-code-finder/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When will we fix the tools that run the world?</title>
      <link>https://www.cgustavo.com/blog/tools</link>
      <description>Gustavo Cid (@_cgustavo) |</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cgustavo.com/blog/tools</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Web Was Made For Surfing Not Scrolling</title>
      <link>https://orbiter.host/blog/the-web-was-meant-for-surfing-not-scrolling/</link>
      <description>The web was once a fun and open place where people would wander and wonder. Social media has negatively impacted that.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://orbiter.host/blog/the-web-was-meant-for-surfing-not-scrolling/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Years of Generative AI Slop</title>
      <link>https://bauer.codes/post/2025/01/10-years-of-genai-slop/</link>
      <description>Paul Bauer, computer programmer working at Datadog, has professional interest in: resilient software engineering, functional programming, databases, profiling, remote work, personal knowledge management.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bauer.codes/post/2025/01/10-years-of-genai-slop/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I use the notes field in my password manager</title>
      <link>https://alexwlchan.net/2025/password-notes/</link>
      <description>I use notes as a mini-changelog to track the context and history of my online accounts. I write down why I created accounts, made changes, or chose particular settings. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alexwlchan.net/2025/password-notes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 02:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern C# Part 2 – Accessing via Implicit Index</title>
      <link>https://jesseliberty.com/2025/01/07/modern-c-part-2-accessing-via-implicit-index/</link>
      <description>Until now, if you wanted to access the last item in a list you had to use a slightly cumbersome syntax. C# 13 introduces the “hat” operator (^) where ^1 is the last element in your collection, ^2 is the penultimate member, etc.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jesseliberty.com/2025/01/07/modern-c-part-2-accessing-via-implicit-index/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 23:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>