<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse engineering an Arctis Pro Wireless Headset</title>
      <link>https://chameth.com/reverse-engineering-arctis-pro-wireless-headset/</link>
      <description>In which we go from &amp;amp;#34;is it on or not?&amp;amp;#34; to &amp;amp;#34;can it play gifs?&amp;amp;#34;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chameth.com/reverse-engineering-arctis-pro-wireless-headset/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Big is Tether?</title>
      <link>https://bennettftomlin.com/2021/06/10/how-big-is-tether/</link>
      <description>I have been following Tether for about three and a half years and still I struggle to really grasp how large it is. It is so absurdly large that it has started warping my perception of other huge a…</description>
      <author> (Published by Bennett Tomlin)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettftomlin.com/2021/06/10/how-big-is-tether/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Source of Water</title>
      <link>https://jamesgill.net/waterword/</link>
      <description>Did you know vodka in Russian means &amp;quot;little water&amp;quot;?The origins of the modern words for &amp;quot;water&amp;quot; in the western world are ancient. There are two main roots for the names we have water: ap and wed. A</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jamesgill.net/waterword/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some people just won&amp;#39;t get it - Blog by Amir Bolous</title>
      <link>https://amirbolous.com/posts/advice/</link>
      <description>Not all advice is good advice. How do you determine what constitutes bad advice?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://amirbolous.com/posts/advice/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The value of code</title>
      <link>https://janikvonrotz.ch/2021/06/11/the-value-of-code/</link>
      <description>Being a disciple to the Open Source movement I often have to explain why it is better to make code public than private. Apart from the usual arguments such as “access to better security”, “trust through transparency” or “the design is the intellectual property”, I came up with the argument of true value. Let me explain.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://janikvonrotz.ch/2021/06/11/the-value-of-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile air conditioning sucks - Imre Jonk</title>
      <link>https://www.imrejonk.nl/mobile-ac-sucks/</link>
      <description>Mobile A/C units may seem attractive, but they&amp;#39;re incredibly inefficient. A bit of background and tips on staying cool.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.imrejonk.nl/mobile-ac-sucks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attempts at solving the online social media</title>
      <link>https://ashutosh.blog/attempts-at-solving-the-online-social-media</link>
      <description>After graduation, I’ve always been mindful of my social media consumption. I had permanently deleted Facebook and Instagram accounts. I’ve...</description>
      <author> (https://ashutosh.blog)</author>
      <guid>https://ashutosh.blog/attempts-at-solving-the-online-social-media</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treating employees like business partners - for fun and profit</title>
      <link>https://www.riknieu.com/employees-as-business-partners/</link>
      <description>Post-pandemic, there seems to an acceleration in the already growing trend of employers trying to squeeze every ounce of life and value from their employees with no regard to their health, happiness or sense of wellbeing.</description>
      <author> (Rik Nieu)</author>
      <guid>https://www.riknieu.com/employees-as-business-partners/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I don&amp;#39;t think where I work</title>
      <link>https://jakobgreenfeld.com/deep-thinking</link>
      <description>Unlike in a normal job, the hours I sit at my desk don’t matter. All that counts is my output.

</description>
      <author> (Jakob Greenfeld)</author>
      <guid>https://jakobgreenfeld.com/deep-thinking</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why you need bundle size monitoring – Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.tommoor.com/posts/monitoring-bundle-size</link>
      <description>June 11th, 2021</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tommoor.com/posts/monitoring-bundle-size</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why does storing a set take the same space as storing a list?</title>
      <link>https://bahadirtuluce.com/why-does-storing-a-set-take-the-same-space-as-storing-a-list</link>
      <description>In a typical serialization library, encoding a collection gets carried out in the same way for lists (ordered) and sets (order-agnostic). Regardless of the collection type, the elements are simply written one after the other. This means that the encoded bytes implicitly carry the information of the order of elements. Is it possible to isolate this information, eliminate it from the encoding, therefore end up with a more compact byte representation? ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bahadirtuluce.com/why-does-storing-a-set-take-the-same-space-as-storing-a-list</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does a fighter jet lock onto and keep track of an enemy aircraft? Can an aircraft detect that it has been locked onto, or is it just a convenient plot device in movies?</title>
      <link>https://www.quora.com/How-does-a-fighter-jet-lock-onto-and-keep-track-of-an-enemy-aircraft-Can-an-aircraft-detect-that-it-has-been-locked-onto-or-is-it-just-a-convenient-plot-device-in-movies?share=1</link>
      <description>The primary technology that a military aircraft uses to lock and track an enemy aircraft is its onboard radar.  Aircraft radars typically have two modes: search and track.  In search mode, the radar sweeps a radio beam across the sky in a zig-zag pattern.  When the radio beam is reflected by a target aircraft, an indication is shown on the radar display.  In search mode, no single aircraft is being tracked, but the pilot can usually tell generally what a particular radar return is doing because with each successive sweep, the radar return moves slightly. This is an example of the fire control radar display for an F-16 Fighting Falcon when the radar is in a search mode:   Each white brick is a radar return.  Because the radar is only scanning, not tracking, no other information is available about the radar targets.  (There is one exception: The Doppler shift of the radar return can be measured, to estimate how fast the aircraft traveling towards or away from you, much like the pitch of an oncoming train&amp;#39;s whistle can tell you how fast it&amp;#39;s coming at you.  This is displayed as the small white trend line originating from each brick.) Note that the cursors are over the bottom-most brick (closest to our aircraft).  The pilot is ready to lock up this target.  This will put the radar into a track mode.  In track mode, the radar focuses its energy on a particular target.  Because the radar is actually tracking a target, and not just displaying bricks when it gets a reflection back, it can tell the pilot a lot more about the target.  This is what the F-16&amp;#39;s fire control radar display looks like when a target is locked:   Along the top we have a lot of information about what our radar target is doing: Its aspect angle (angle between its nose position and our nose position) is 160&amp;#176; to the left,its heading is 190&amp;#176;,its airspeed is 450 knots,and our closure rate is 828 knots.With this information, the pilot gets a much better idea of what the aircraft is doing, but at the expense of information about other aircraft in the area. Note that in the above picture, the bottom-most (closest) target is locked (circle around it), the two targets further away are tracked (yellow squares), and there are two radar returns even further away (white bricks).  This is demonstrating an advanced feature of modern radars, situational awareness modes.  A radar in SAM combines both tracking and scanning to allow a pilot to track one or a small number of &amp;quot;interesting&amp;quot; targets while not losing the big picture of what other targets are doing.  In this mode, the radar beam sweeps the sky, while briefly and regularly pausing its scan to check up on a locked target. Note that all of this comes with tradeoffs.  In the end, a radar is only as powerful as it is, and you can put a lot of radar energy on one target, or spread it out weakly throughout the sky, or some compromise in between.  In the above photo you can see two vertical bars spanning the height of the display -- these are the azimuth scan limits.  It&amp;#39;s the aircraft&amp;#39;s way of telling you, &amp;quot;OK, I can both track this target, and scan for other targets, but in return, I&amp;#39;m only going to scan a 40&amp;#176; wide cone in front of the aircraft, instead of the usual 60&amp;#176;.  Radar, like life, is full of tradeoffs. An important thing to note is that a radar lock is not always required to launch weapons at a target.  For guns kills, if the aircraft has a radar lock on a target, it can accurately gauge range to the target, and provide the pilot with the appropriate corrections for lead and gravity drop, to get an accurate guns kill.  Without the radar, the pilot&amp;#39;s own judgement must be used. As an example of that, let&amp;#39;s take a look at the F-16&amp;#39;s HUD (heads-up display) when in the process of employing guns at a radar-locked target:    It becomes really simple: That small circle labeled &amp;quot;bullets at target range&amp;quot; is called the &amp;quot;death dot&amp;quot; by F-16 pilots.  Basically, it represents where the cannon rounds would land if you fired right now, and the rounds traveled the distance between you and the locked target.  In other words, if you want a solid guns kill, simply fly the death dot onto the airplane.  Super simple. But what if there&amp;#39;s no radar lock?  Well now the HUD looks like this:   No death dot -- but you still have the funnel.  The funnel represents the path the cannon rounds would travel out in front of you if you fired right now.  The width of the funnel is equal to the apparent width of a predetermined wingspan at that particular range.  So, if you didn&amp;#39;t have a lock on your target, but you knew it had a wingspan of 35 feet, you could dial in 35 feet, then fly the funnel until the width exactly lined up with the width of the enemy aircraft&amp;#39;s wings, then squeeze the trigger. And what about missiles?  Again, a radar lock is not required.  For heat-seeking missiles, a radar lock is only used to train the seeker head onto the target.  Without a radar lock, the seeker head scans the sky looking for &amp;quot;bright&amp;quot; (hot) objects, and when it finds one, it plays a distinctive whining tone to the pilot.  The pilot does not need radar in this case, he just needs to maneuver his aircraft until he has &amp;quot;good tone,&amp;quot; and then fire the missile.  The radar only makes this process faster. Now, radar-guided missiles come in two varieties: passive and active.  Passive radar missiles do require a radar lock, because these missiles use the aircraft&amp;#39;s reflected radar energy to track the target. Active radar missiles however have their own onboard radar, which locks and tracks a target.  But this radar is on a one-way trip, so it&amp;#39;s considerably less expensive (and less powerful) than the aircraft&amp;#39;s radar.  So, these missiles normally get some guidance help from the launching aircraft until they fly close enough to the target where they can turn on their own radar and &amp;quot;go active.&amp;quot;  (This allows the launching aircraft to turn away and defend itself.)  It is possible to fire an active radar missile with no radar lock (so-called &amp;quot;maddog&amp;quot;); in this case, the missile will fly until it&amp;#39;s nearly out of fuel, and then it will turn on its radar and pursue the first target it sees.  This is not a recommended strategy if there are friendly aircraft in close proximity to the enemy. As to the last part of your question -- yes, an aircraft can tell if a radar is painting it or locked onto it.  Radar is just radio waves, and just as your FM radio converts radio waves into sound, so can an aircraft analyze incoming radio signals to figure out who&amp;#39;s doing what.  This is called an RWR, or radar warning receiver, and has both a video and audio component.  This is a typical RWR display:   Although an aircraft&amp;#39;s radar can only scan out in front of the aircraft, an aircraft can listen for incoming radar signals in any direction, so the scope is 360&amp;#176;.  A digital signal processor looks for recognizable radio &amp;quot;chirps&amp;quot; that correspond to known radars, and displays their azimuth on the scope.  A chirp is a distinctive waveform that a radio uses.  See, if two radios use the same waveform simultaneously, they&amp;#39;ll confuse each other, because each radio won&amp;#39;t know which radar returns are from its own transmitter.  To prevent this, different radios tend to use distinct waveforms.  This can also be used by the target aircraft to identify the type of radar being used, and therefore possibly, the type of aircraft. In this display, the RWR has detected an F-15 (15 with a hat on it indicating aircraft) at the 7-o&amp;#39;clock position.  The strength of the radar is plotted as distance from the center -- the closer to the center, the stronger the detected radar signal, and therefore possibly the closer the transmitting aircraft. Detected at the 12- to 1-o&amp;#39;clock position are two surface-to-air missile (SAM) sites, an SA-5 &amp;quot;Gammon&amp;quot; and an SA-6 &amp;quot;Gainful&amp;quot;.  These are Russian SAM launching radars and represent a serious threat.  The RWR computer has determined the SA-6 to be the highest priority threat in the area, and thus has enclosed it with a diamond. RWR also has an audio component.  Each time a new radar signal is detected, it is converted into an audio wave and played for the pilot.  Because different radars &amp;quot;sound&amp;quot; different, pilots learn to recognize different airborne or surface threats by their distinctive tones.  The sound is also an important cue to tell the pilot what the radar is doing: If the sound plays once, or intermittently, it means the radar is only painting our aircraft (in search mode).  If a sound plays continuously, the radar has locked onto our aircraft and is in track mode, and thus the pilot&amp;#39;s immediate attention is demanded.  In some cases, the RWR can tell if the radar is in launch mode (sending radar data to a passive radar-guided missile), or if the radar is that of an active radar-guided missile.  In either of these cases, a distinctive missile launch tone is played and the pilot is advised to immediately act to counter the threat.  Note that the RWR has no way of knowing if a heat-seeking missile is on its way to our aircraft. Aside from radar, there are other technologies that are used to lock on to enemy aircraft and ground targets.  A targeting pod is a very powerful camera mounted on an articulating swivel that allows it to look in nearly every direction.  This camera is connected to image processor that is able to tell apart vehicles and buildings from surrounding terrain, and track moving targets.  This is the SNIPER XR targeting pod:   And this is what the pilot sees when he operates it:   The pod is able to track vehicles day and night, using visual or infra-red cameras.  Heat-seeking missiles obviously use this same technology to home in on aircraft, and electro-optical missiles use this technology to track ground targets. Lastly, there are laser-guided missiles as well.  These &amp;quot;beam riders&amp;quot; follow a laser beam emanating from the aircraft to the target.  Many ground vehicles use laser rangefinders as well, and some aircraft include a laser warning system (LWS) that works similarly to an RWR, but displays incoming laser signals instead.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.quora.com/How-does-a-fighter-jet-lock-onto-and-keep-track-of-an-enemy-aircraft-Can-an-aircraft-detect-that-it-has-been-locked-onto-or-is-it-just-a-convenient-plot-device-in-movies?share=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:09:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Win At Risk By Using Systems Thinking</title>
      <link>https://thesystemisdown.substack.com/p/how-to-win-at-risk-every-time-by</link>
      <description>Systems Thinking gives you an advantage in almost every area of life - even the game of Risk.</description>
      <author> (Andy Patton)</author>
      <guid>https://thesystemisdown.substack.com/p/how-to-win-at-risk-every-time-by</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 20:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Fighter Jets Lock On (and How the Targets Know)</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/how-fighter-jets-lock-on-and-how-the-targets-know-1644871272</link>
      <description>The primary technology that a military aircraft uses to lock and track an enemy aircraft is its onboard radar.  Aircraft radars typically have two modes: search and track.  In search mode, the radar sweeps a radio beam across the sky in a zig-zag pattern.  When the radio beam is reflected by a target aircraft, an…</description>
      <author> (Tim Morgan - Quora)</author>
      <guid>https://gizmodo.com/how-fighter-jets-lock-on-and-how-the-targets-know-1644871272</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 19:05:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>180e57971e7cabc0a15c76112f8d37a942bc8d61 - chromium/src - Git at Google</title>
      <link>https://chromium.googlesource.com/chromium/src/+/180e57971e7cabc0a15c76112f8d37a942bc8d61</link>
      <description>Chromium is an open-source browser project that aims to build a safer, faster, and more stable way for all users to experience the web.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chromium.googlesource.com/chromium/src/+/180e57971e7cabc0a15c76112f8d37a942bc8d61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 14:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What you do when you are a “Developer Advocate” #career #job #programming #tech #work</title>
      <link>https://www.tiktok.com/@vscode/video/6972295318805155078</link>
      <description>Visual Studio Code (@vscode) has created a short video on TikTok with music original sound. | What you do when you are a “Developer Advocate” #career #job #programming #tech #work</description>
      <author> (vscodeVisual Studio Code &amp;#183; 1d ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiktok.com/@vscode/video/6972295318805155078</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 13:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 5 Dependency Injection</title>
      <link>https://ytprivate.com/watch?v=0x2KW-dJDQU</link>
      <description>Since the release of .NET Core (now.NET 5), more developers are making use of dependency injection by using the default Microsoft Dependency Injection contai...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ytprivate.com/watch?v=0x2KW-dJDQU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 13:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do You Need Redis? PostgreSQL Does Queuing, Locking, &amp;amp; Pub/Sub</title>
      <link>https://spin.atomicobject.com/2021/02/04/redis-postgresql/</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s a common architecture to have PostgreSQL and Redis serve as the backbone of your app, but PostgreSQL may be capable of everything you use Redis for.</description>
      <author> (By: Chris Farber)</author>
      <guid>https://spin.atomicobject.com/2021/02/04/redis-postgresql/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 12:05:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a Static Web App via Azure DevOps Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/deploying-a-static-webapp-via-azure-devops-pipeline/</link>
      <description>This article will discuss about deploying Azure Static Web apps from Azure DevOps Pipeline. Azure Static Web Apps is a service that automatically builds and deploys full stack web apps to Azure from a code repository.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/deploying-a-static-webapp-via-azure-devops-pipeline/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 11:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Xamarin App</title>
      <link>https://weeklyxamarin.github.io/website/</link>
      <description>Weekly Xamarin App for iOS and Android</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://weeklyxamarin.github.io/website/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 11:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion |It’s Time to Break Up the Ivy League Cartel</title>
      <link>https://www.chronicle.com/article/how-meritocracy-became-trickle-down-education</link>
      <description>Democracy requires something more than a handful of super-rich universities.</description>
      <author> (https://www.chronicle.com/author/sam-haselby)</author>
      <guid>https://www.chronicle.com/article/how-meritocracy-became-trickle-down-education</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 09:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#39;I was completely inside&amp;#39;: Lobster diver swallowed by humpback whale off Provincetown</title>
      <link>https://www.capecodtimes.com/story/news/2021/06/11/humpback-whale-catches-michael-packard-lobster-driver-mouth-proviencetown-cape-cod/7653838002/</link>
      <description>“I was completely inside (the whale); it was completely black,” said Michael Packard of Wellfleet as people compare him to Jonah and the whale.</description>
      <author> (Doug Fraser)</author>
      <guid>https://www.capecodtimes.com/story/news/2021/06/11/humpback-whale-catches-michael-packard-lobster-driver-mouth-proviencetown-cape-cod/7653838002/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 06:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code v1.57 (May 2021 Update) Adds Terminal Tabs, Integrates Edge Dev Tools -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/06/11/vs-code-may-2021.aspx</link>
      <description>  Visual Studio Code v1.57, the May update, includes a bunch of new features that were previewed earlier, including terminal tabs, Workspace Trust, remote repositories (RemoteHub) and more.
</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel06/11/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/06/11/vs-code-may-2021.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 01:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wormhole: Instant Encrypted File-Sharing Powered by WebTorrent * TorrentFreak</title>
      <link>https://torrentfreak.com/wormhole-instant-encrypted-file-sharing-powered-by-webtorrent-210611/</link>
      <description>Wormhole is a free browser-based tool that allows people to instantly share files with end-to-end encryption using BitTorrent.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://torrentfreak.com/wormhole-instant-encrypted-file-sharing-powered-by-webtorrent-210611/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 23:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The .NET Docs Show - Making Phone Calls &amp;#128222; from Blazor WebAssembly with Twilio Voice</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e8DX7HdSmkU</link>
      <description>Combine Blazor WASM, JavaScript Interop, Twilio&amp;#39;s client library, ngrok for ASP.NET Core WebAPI, and Twilio back end. Featuring: Niels Swimberghe (@RealSwimb...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e8DX7HdSmkU</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 23:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Person Does Not Exist</title>
      <link>https://thispersondoesnotexist.com/</link>
      <description>This Person Does Not Exist</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thispersondoesnotexist.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 22:07:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Can Find My Devices? Security and Privacy of Apple&amp;#39;s Crowd-Sourced Bluetooth Location Tracking System</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2103.02282</link>
      <description>Overnight, Apple has turned its hundreds-of-million-device ecosystem into the
world&amp;#39;s largest crowd-sourced location tracking network called offline finding
(OF). OF leverages online finder devices to detect the presence of missing
offline devices using Bluetooth and report an approximate location back to the
owner via the Internet. While OF is not the first system of its kind, it is the
first to commit to strong privacy goals. In particular, OF aims to ensure
finder anonymity, untrackability of owner devices, and confidentiality of
location reports. This paper presents the first comprehensive security and
privacy analysis of OF. To this end, we recover the specifications of the
closed-source OF protocols by means of reverse engineering. We experimentally
show that unauthorized access to the location reports allows for accurate
device tracking and retrieving a user&amp;#39;s top locations with an error in the
order of 10 meters in urban areas. While we find that OF&amp;#39;s design achieves its
privacy goals, we discover two distinct design and implementation flaws that
can lead to a location correlation attack and unauthorized access to the
location history of the past seven days, which could deanonymize users. Apple
has partially addressed the issues following our responsible disclosure.
Finally, we make our research artifacts publicly available.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 3 Mar 2021])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2103.02282</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 22:07:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI Faces – Avatars for design mockups</title>
      <link>https://uifaces.co/</link>
      <description>UI Faces aggregates various free avatar placeholder sources that you can use in your design mockups by copy—paste, API, plugins for Sketch, Adobe XD and Figma.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://uifaces.co/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 22:07:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generated Photos | Unique, worry-free model photos</title>
      <link>https://generated.photos/</link>
      <description>AI-generated images have never looked better. Explore and download our diverse, copyright-free headshot images from our production-ready database.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://generated.photos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 22:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>