<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Exoplanet System</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3103/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3103/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 19:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working on databases from prison: How I got here, part 2.</title>
      <link>https://turso.tech/blog/working-on-databases-from-prison</link>
      <description>I'm very excited to announce that I have recently joined Turso as a software engineer. For many in the field, including myself, getting to work on databases and solve unique challenges with such a talented team would be a dream job, but it is that much more special to me because of my unusual and unlikely circumstances. As difficult as it might be to believe, I am currently incarcerated and I landed this job from my cell in state prison. If you don’t know me, let me tell you more about how I got here.</description>
      <guid>https://turso.tech/blog/working-on-databases-from-prison</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start your own Internet Resiliency Club – Bow Shock Systems Consulting</title>
      <link>https://bowshock.nl/irc/</link>
      <description>Thanks to war, geopolitics, and climate change, Europe will have more
frequent and more severe internet
disruptions
in the very near future. Governments and businesses need to prepare
for catastrophic loss of communications. Unfortunately, the necessary
changes are risky and expensive, which means they won’t do it until a
crisis is already here. However, small
groups of volunteers with a little bit of time and money can provide
crucial initial leadership to bootstrap recovery.</description>
      <guid>https://bowshock.nl/irc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 13:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Standards and Name Changes in the Browser Wars</title>
      <link>https://tim.dierks.org/2014/05/security-standards-and-name-changes-in.html</link>
      <description>The Netscape/Microsoft browser wars in the mid-90's were really vicious and competitive. They really had it out for each other. Netscape had...</description>
      <guid>https://tim.dierks.org/2014/05/security-standards-and-name-changes-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>blog/posts/2025-06-03.md at master · frankmcsherry/blog</title>
      <link>https://github.com/frankmcsherry/blog/blob/master/posts/2025-06-03.md</link>
      <description>Some notes on things I find interesting and important. - frankmcsherry/blog</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/frankmcsherry/blog/blob/master/posts/2025-06-03.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 04:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to modify Starlink Mini to run without the built-in WiFi router – Oleg Kutkov personal blog</title>
      <link>https://olegkutkov.me/2025/06/15/how-to-modify-starlink-mini-to-run-without-the-built-in-wifi-router/</link>
      <description>The Starlink Mini terminal is designed as a compact, all-in-one solution with an integrated Wi-Fi router. While this design is ideal for typical consumer use, certain applications—such as custom networking setups, embedded installations, or power-constrained environments—may benefit from removing the internal router entirely. In this article, I’ll detail the process of physically removing the built-in Wi-Fi router board from the Starlink Mini, allowing the terminal to operate solely via Ethernet and offering greater flexibility for advanced users.</description>
      <guid>https://olegkutkov.me/2025/06/15/how-to-modify-starlink-mini-to-run-without-the-built-in-wifi-router/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 01:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>