<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf 2023: Call for Speakers</title>
      <link>https://sessionize.com/dotnetconf-2023/</link>
      <description>.NET Conf is a free, three-day, virtual developer event that celebrates the major releases of the .NET development platform. It is co-organized by the...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sessionize.com/dotnetconf-2023/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 18:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>shouldn&amp;#39;t very very distant objects appear magnified?</title>
      <link>https://astronomy.stackexchange.com/questions/54499/shouldnt-very-very-distant-objects-appear-magnified</link>
      <description>My understanding of the expansion of space itself is very shaky,
but if space itself is expanding,
then shouldn&amp;#39;t very very distant objects appear magnified?
For example these James Webb Space Tele...</description>
      <author> (orion elenzilorion elenzil
        
            32311 gold badge22 silver badges55 bronze badges)</author>
      <guid>https://astronomy.stackexchange.com/questions/54499/shouldnt-very-very-distant-objects-appear-magnified</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 18:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Frontend Programming While Having Fun and Building Something Real</title>
      <link>https://robconery.com/frontend-accelerator/</link>
      <description>JavaScript client frameworks are powerful and help you create an amazing experience for your end user. Unfortunately, learning how to use them sucks.</description>
      <author> (Webestica.com)</author>
      <guid>https://robconery.com/frontend-accelerator/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 18:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logging guidance for .NET library authors - .NET</title>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/core/extensions/logging-library-authors</link>
      <description>Learn how to expose logging as a library author in .NET. Follow the guidance to ensure your library is correctly exposed to consumers.</description>
      <author> (IEvangelist)</author>
      <guid>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/core/extensions/logging-library-authors</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 18:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The endpoint of Web Environment Integrity is a closed Web</title>
      <link>https://educatedguesswork.org/posts/wei/</link>
      <description>We had to destroy the Web in order to save it</description>
      <author> (Posted by ekr on 18 Aug 2023)</author>
      <guid>https://educatedguesswork.org/posts/wei/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 18:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An announcement regarding Kris N&amp;#243;va</title>
      <link>https://nivenly.org/blog/2023/08/19/an-announcement-regarding-kris-n%C3%B3va/</link>
      <description>An announcement from Nivenly about Kris N&amp;#243;va</description>
      <author> (By dma (@dma) |
Saturday, August 19, 2023)</author>
      <guid>https://nivenly.org/blog/2023/08/19/an-announcement-regarding-kris-n%C3%B3va/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 17:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive Function Theft</title>
      <link>https://hedgehoglibrarian.com/2023/08/14/executive-function-theft/</link>
      <description>The phrase arrived in my head so completely formed and concrete that I couldn’t believe it wasn’t already established in the lexicon, but at least preliminary searches suggest it is not…</description>
      <author> (Author: Abigail Goben)</author>
      <guid>https://hedgehoglibrarian.com/2023/08/14/executive-function-theft/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 17:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Suspected in New Wave of Malicious npm Packages</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/north-korean-hackers-suspected-in-new.html</link>
      <description>&amp;#128230; Developers, beware! Nine npm packages uploaded between Aug 9-12, 2023 have caught the attention of security experts.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/thehackernews)</author>
      <guid>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/north-korean-hackers-suspected-in-new.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 17:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kolide Device Trust Demo</title>
      <link>https://lp.kolide.co/demo</link>
      <description>Watch an on-demand video to see how Kolide Device Trust integrates with Okta to keep untrusted devices from accessing your company&amp;#39;s apps.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lp.kolide.co/demo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 16:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 361</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=gkbYfZ3wH9Y</link>
      <description>Lessons From 2 Weeks of the New HIBP Subscription Service; Pulling HIBP Domain Search Data into Splunk; Breaches - More Breaches; Sponsored by Kolidehttps://...</description>
      <author> (MissLizHeart
  
  
  
    MissLizHeart
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=gkbYfZ3wH9Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 16:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MassTransit #2: In-memory Mediator pattern basics</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/masstransit-inmemory-mediator-basics/</link>
      <description>MassTransit is a free, open-source distributed application framework for .NET. This library facilitates service-to-service communication and helps developers build decoupled applications that can scale and manage failure scenarios effectively.

One of its key features is the implementation of the mediator pattern which this article will cover in depth.

The mediator</description>
      <author> (Pierre Belin)</author>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/masstransit-inmemory-mediator-basics/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 16:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manipulated Caiman: The Sophisticated Snare of Mexico&amp;#39;s Banking Predators - Perception Point</title>
      <link>https://perception-point.io/blog/manipulated-caiman-the-sophisticated-snare-of-mexicos-banking-predators-technical-edition/</link>
      <description>Perception Point researchers have identified a complex phishing operation they dubbed “Manipulated Caiman.”</description>
      <author> (Joanna Wayburn)</author>
      <guid>https://perception-point.io/blog/manipulated-caiman-the-sophisticated-snare-of-mexicos-banking-predators-technical-edition/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 16:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the power curve of the Cucconi test</title>
      <link>https://aakinshin.net/posts/cucconi-power/</link>
      <description>The Cucconi test is a nonparametric two-sample test that compares both location and scale. It is a classic example of the family of tests that perform such a comparison simultaneously instead of combining the results of a location test and a scale test. Int...</description>
      <author> (Andrey Akinshin)</author>
      <guid>https://aakinshin.net/posts/cucconi-power/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 16:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying ASP.NET Core WebAPI to AWS App Runner - Super Fast Deployments via ECR and GitHub</title>
      <link>https://codewithmukesh.com/blog/deploying-aspnet-core-webapi-to-aws-app-runner/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to explore yet another deployment option from AWS, which is Deploying ASP.NET Core WebAPI to AWS App Runner, which is the latest</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/iammukeshm)</author>
      <guid>https://codewithmukesh.com/blog/deploying-aspnet-core-webapi-to-aws-app-runner/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 15:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving performance and memory use while accessing APIs using HTTPClient in dotnet</title>
      <link>https://ilovedotnet.org/blogs/improving-performance-and-memory-use-while-accessing-apis-using-http-client-in-dotnet/</link>
      <description>In this post I will teach how to unit test hosted services in ASP.NET web api. All with live working demo.</description>
      <author> (Abdul Rahman Shabeek Mohamed)</author>
      <guid>https://ilovedotnet.org/blogs/improving-performance-and-memory-use-while-accessing-apis-using-http-client-in-dotnet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 15:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Dependency Injection A Mess? Here&amp;#39;s How To Fix It #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=oYGcsl6AZP4</link>
      <description>&amp;#128204; Check out my Pragmatic Clean Architecture course: https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/pragmatic-clean-architecture&amp;#128640; Join 770+ engineers in my  Patreon commun...</description>
      <author> (AWS Events
  
  
  
    AWS Events
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=oYGcsl6AZP4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 12:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolving the Game: A clientless streaming tool for reMarkable 2</title>
      <link>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2023/07/25/evolving-the-game-a-clientless-streaming-tool-for-remarkable-2.html</link>
      <description>In this article, I expose the new version of the streaming tool for my reMarkable tablet.
Originally crafted in 2021, this tool allowed me to stream sketches during video calls.
Aiming for more user-friendliness, I revamped the design to a clientless implementation. This articles describes the implementation with some code illustrations in Javascript and Go on how to

get the picture and to display it in a canvas
optimize the flow by playing with uint4 and RLE

</description>
      <author> (Olivier Wulveryck)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2023/07/25/evolving-the-game-a-clientless-streaming-tool-for-remarkable-2.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 12:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellebrite asks cops to keep its phone hacking tech ‘hush hush’ | TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2023/08/19/cellebrite-asks-cops-to-keep-its-phone-hacking-tech-hush-hush/</link>
      <description>For years, cops and other government authorities all over the world have been using phone hacking technology provided by Cellebrite to unlock phones and In a leaked video, a Cellebrite employee urges law enforcement customers to keep their use of its phone hacking technology secret.</description>
      <author> (Lorenzo Franceschi-Bicchierai)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2023/08/19/cellebrite-asks-cops-to-keep-its-phone-hacking-tech-hush-hush/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 11:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clone-a Lisa &amp;#127912;⏱️ art forgery game</title>
      <link>https://vole.wtf/clone-a-lisa/</link>
      <description>One minute to copy Leonardo da Vinci’s Mona Lisa.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vole.wtf/clone-a-lisa/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 08:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - rivet-gg/rivet: Open-source solution to deploy, scale, and operate your multiplayer game</title>
      <link>https://github.com/rivet-gg/rivet</link>
      <description>Open-source solution to deploy, scale, and operate your multiplayer game - GitHub - rivet-gg/rivet: Open-source solution to deploy, scale, and operate your multiplayer game</description>
      <author> (rivet-gg)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/rivet-gg/rivet</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>flipreps</title>
      <link>https://carloslagoa.com/blog/flipreps/flipreps.html</link>
      <description>Howdy! I’m Carlos and I like tech and planes (among other things like
          having massive servings of pasta). I’m currently studying for my
          commercial license in Europe. So far most of my flight training has
          happened on a Piper PA28 (the -180 variant)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://carloslagoa.com/blog/flipreps/flipreps.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>using serde_derive without precompiled binary &amp;#183; Issue #2538 &amp;#183; serde-rs/serde</title>
      <link>https://github.com/serde-rs/serde/issues/2538</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m working on packaging serde for Fedora Linux, and I noticed that recent versions of serde_derive ship a precompiled binary now. This is problematic for us, since we cannot, under no circumstance...</description>
      <author> (serde-rs)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/serde-rs/serde/issues/2538</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Old Books Smell So Good?</title>
      <link>https://scienceswitch.com/2023/08/19/why-do-old-books-smell-so-good/</link>
      <description>The distinctive scent of old books comes from volatile organic compounds released as the materials decay over time. Scientists analyze these chemical clues to reveal secrets about a historical tome…</description>
      <author> (Author: ScienceSwitch)</author>
      <guid>https://scienceswitch.com/2023/08/19/why-do-old-books-smell-so-good/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - leejet/stable-diffusion.cpp: Stable Diffusion in pure C/C++</title>
      <link>https://github.com/leejet/stable-diffusion.cpp</link>
      <description>Stable Diffusion in pure C/C++. Contribute to leejet/stable-diffusion.cpp development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (leejet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/leejet/stable-diffusion.cpp</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 23:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hahaha we live in hell</title>
      <link>https://cohost.org/cathoderaydude/post/2521077-hahaha-we-live-in-he</link>
      <description>sitting in my car in a Seattle parking lot. there&amp;#39;s a knock on my window. it&amp;#39;s an old lady, who asks me &amp;quot;how do we pay for parking?&amp;quot;

----------------------------------------

she&amp;#39;s taking her husband to the hospital to see his doctor, but there&amp;#39;s a massive road project that has cut off access for months, no end in sight, so she&amp;#39;s parked a few blocks away. almost every parking lot in town removed their pay stations years ago. she has a smartphone but no idea how to handle this situation.

she never would have figured it out. her words, and I don&amp;#39;t doubt her.

the lot has three signs hung up with instructions on how to pay, because every single lot in town supports one to five different competing parking lot apps. there&amp;#39;s one sign that says you can use Park Mobile, and gives a lot ID, and then on another wall there&amp;#39;s a sign that says you can use PayByPhone, with a different lot ID, and then there&amp;#39;s a huge sign with a QR code that encourages you to Scan Here To Park, as if it&amp;#39;s the official primary method for doing so. It is not, it&amp;#39;s just another app.

I&amp;#39;ve scanned these before and gotten an &amp;quot;Instant App.&amp;quot; I figure this is minimal friction for this person, so I suggest she do so. she pulls up a QR Scanner app - either because she&amp;#39;s been bamboozled into believing that&amp;#39;s the only way to get QR support, or because her particular Android phone actually does not have it built into the camera for God knows what reason; I didn&amp;#39;t have time to figure out which.

at first she struggles to figure out how to change cameras, but this turns out to be only because she&amp;#39;s used to every camera app opening with the front facing selected by default; it has actually selected the rear camera, so I help her get it aimed right, and it goes bleep, and then... pops up an ad. i have to stop her before she hits open on whatever sludge is trying to put itself on her device

then we get a screen with 30 different elements on it describing different qualities of the QR code. the most prominent is a &amp;quot;Search The Web&amp;quot; button, which would have dumped the scanned URL into Google for some reason and produced irrelevant results; i have to direct her to tap the tiny blue link.

that link opens Instant App. Google play prints a huge permissions message; I direct her to accept it. it installs a 16mb app; so what was the point of Instant here, exactly?

well, that&amp;#39;s moot anyway, because as soon as it opens, it asks for permission, and then simply installs the normal version of the app, 24mb.

we get into that. it asks for the street address of the lot. I have never seen this information printed on any parking lot in my life. it suggests several &amp;quot;nearby&amp;quot; options; they are actually half a mile away.

unable to figure this conundrum out even for myself, i sigh and walk her through installing Park Mobile, which I know works. i help her find the lot ID. it asks for duration. she picks two hours. it asks for payment. she gets out her CC and types in the info.

proceeding to checkout, it then... selects google pay. even though she just put in a CC. she hits proceed, and i go &amp;quot;is that the right card?&amp;quot; and she double takes and goes &amp;quot;...no.&amp;quot; i maybe just saved this woman from losing $30 in overdrafts.

I direct her to tap the payment options field. nothing. i sigh. &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m sorry, it looks like you have to tap that tiny pencil icon in the CORNER of the field.&amp;quot; yep. finally she&amp;#39;s able to select her credit card. she hits proceed.

it now pops up the duration selector again. what???? why????? it&amp;#39;s back at the default of 1 hour, and she tries to pick two again, but it just won&amp;#39;t do it. I happen to know this UI pretty well, so I know that if parking time was actually limited to 1 hour, it wouldn&amp;#39;t show the option at all. This is just completely glitched out.

with no other options, she just picks one hour, and successfully pays. we both breathe a sigh of relief, and I advise her that if she needs more time, she should be able to just tap a button in the app to extend her parking. I really hope it actually works like I described.

throughout all this we had to grant Location permissions at least three times, and each time you have to decide between three options, none of which are &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot; the one you want is &amp;quot;while the app is open&amp;quot; but there is no way to know this, and nobody alive has ever picked either of the other options. nobody would.

i have struggled to write an ending to this post three times. words genuinely fail me.</description>
      <author> (https://cohost.org/cathoderaydude)</author>
      <guid>https://cohost.org/cathoderaydude/post/2521077-hahaha-we-live-in-he</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 22:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So, your friend has a startup idea, huh?</title>
      <link>https://kevinlestarge.com/2023/08/14/so-your-friend-has-a-startup-idea-huh/</link>
      <description>The Scenario If you are a software engineer, then the following scenario inevitably happens to you: Your friend (or relative, neighbor, acquaintance, etc) learns you are a software engineer. She te…</description>
      <author> (Kevin LeStarge)</author>
      <guid>https://kevinlestarge.com/2023/08/14/so-your-friend-has-a-startup-idea-huh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precision and Recall are just filtered accuracies</title>
      <link>https://shubhanshu.com/blog/accuracy-precision-recall.html#accuracy-precision-recall?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</link>
      <description>In this post I will show how precision and recall are related to accuracy and how they can be thought of as filtered versions of accuracy. Accuracy&amp;#182;Accuracy is a fundamental concept in evaluating every day systems. In simple terms, accuracy is defined as proportion of times the predictions of our system matched the true outcome (assuming the true outcome exists). For this post lets follow the scikit-learn convention and define y_true</description>
      <author> (https://shubhanshu.com/blog/author/shubhanshu-mishra.html)</author>
      <guid>https://shubhanshu.com/blog/accuracy-precision-recall.html#accuracy-precision-recall?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a USB Mute Button for Online Meetings - ClickedyClick</title>
      <link>https://gergely.imreh.net/blog/2023/08/making-a-usb-mute-button-for-online-meetings/</link>
      <description>Since Google Meet teases us to add a USB device to controll calls, let&amp;#39;s learn how to teach an Arduino clone to act like a phone mute button, and thus ultimately being capable to act like an infinite variety of peripheral devices.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/gergely.imreh)</author>
      <guid>https://gergely.imreh.net/blog/2023/08/making-a-usb-mute-button-for-online-meetings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s build a website using XML!</title>
      <link>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2023/08/lets-build-a-website-using-xml/</link>
      <description>It is 2023. XHTML is dead and buried. HTML is a &amp;quot;living standard&amp;quot; with billions of users. So what kind of idiot would want to build a website using XML? Me. I am that idiot. Last year, I launched a &amp;quot;web page&amp;quot; which didn&amp;#39;t use HTML. Called, appropriately enough, &amp;quot;YOU DON&amp;#39;T NEED HTML!&amp;quot; That (ab)used [...]</description>
      <author> (https://shkspr.mobi/blog/author/admin/)</author>
      <guid>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2023/08/lets-build-a-website-using-xml/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Conference Organisers Everywhere… – Arun Raghavan</title>
      <link>https://arunraghavan.net/2023/08/to-conference-organisers-everywhere/</link>
      <description>(well, not exactly everywhere …)</description>
      <author> (Arun)</author>
      <guid>https://arunraghavan.net/2023/08/to-conference-organisers-everywhere/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ninx | Blog</title>
      <link>https://ninx.xyz/blog/dont-be-yourself</link>
      <description>Added on 1/8/2023, Written by Lubwama Abdul Muswawir</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ninx.xyz/blog/dont-be-yourself</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Visual Database Query Plans from a CLI</title>
      <link>https://davidgomes.com/analyzing-visual-query-plans-from-a-cli/</link>
      <description>tl;dr: we’ve created new SQL commands ( SHOW PROFILE UI, EXPLAIN UI and SHOW PLAN UI) that allow developers to more easily visualize their SingleStoreDB query plans. It’s the little things!

I recently tried to define Database Developer Experience, which is where I’ve been spending most of</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidgomes.com/analyzing-visual-query-plans-from-a-cli/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scourge of 00UB | Gavin D. Howard</title>
      <link>https://gavinhoward.com/2023/08/the-scourge-of-00ub/</link>
      <description>Compiler authors claim that the possibility of UB is a license to kill. They are not James Bond.</description>
      <author> (Compiler Author vs. Language User)</author>
      <guid>https://gavinhoward.com/2023/08/the-scourge-of-00ub/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Matters</title>
      <link>https://martinrue.com/nothing-matters/</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s far too easy to be passive and experience life as the default, but it&amp;#39;s clear to me that it works the other way around.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martinrue.com/nothing-matters/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>