<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How many photons are received per bit transmitted from Voyager 1?</title>
      <link>https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/816698/how-many-photons-are-received-per-bit-transmitted-from-voyager-1</link>
      <description>As of 2024, according to https://voyager.jpl.nasa.gov/ , Voyager 1 is around one light&amp;#183;day away from Earth and still in radio contact. When Voyager 1 sends messages to Earth, roughly how many photo...</description>
      <author> (Jos BergervoetJos Bergervoet
        
            3,7501010 silver badges2323 bronze badges)</author>
      <guid>https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/816698/how-many-photons-are-received-per-bit-transmitted-from-voyager-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 15:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority for chat control possible – Users who refuse scanning to be prevented from sharing photos and links</title>
      <link>https://www.patrick-breyer.de/en/majority-for-chat-control-possible-users-who-refuse-scanning-to-be-prevented-from-sharing-photos-and-links/</link>
      <description>The highly controversial indiscriminate child sexual abuse regulation (so-called chat control) could still be endorsed by EU governments after all, as France could give up its previous veto. This is reported by Euractiv and confirmed by internal documents. France considers the new &amp;quot;upload moderation</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.patrick-breyer.de/en/majority-for-chat-control-possible-users-who-refuse-scanning-to-be-prevented-from-sharing-photos-and-links/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 14:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More on harmful overuse of std::move - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240603-00/?p=109842</link>
      <description>Could we expand copy elision to cover the harmful cases?</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240603-00/?p=109842</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 14:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;m forking Ladybird and stepping down as SerenityOS BDFL</title>
      <link>https://awesomekling.substack.com/p/forking-ladybird-and-stepping-down-serenityos</link>
      <description>In 2018, I created the SerenityOS project after completing a drug rehab program. I needed something to soak up my free time while learning to live a normal life, and it turned out that building a new operating system was a task of just the right proportions.</description>
      <author> (Andreas Kling)</author>
      <guid>https://awesomekling.substack.com/p/forking-ladybird-and-stepping-down-serenityos</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 12:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serializing Objects: Efficient Serialization and Deserialization of Collections with JsonSerializer</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/06/03/serializing-objects-efficient-serialization-and-deserialization-of-collections-with-jsonserializer/</link>
      <description>The article demonstrates the ease of serializing and deserializing collections using JsonSerializer.</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/06/03/serializing-objects-efficient-serialization-and-deserialization-of-collections-with-jsonserializer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 09:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing Quality Method Docs</title>
      <link>https://thoughtbot.com/blog/writing-quality-method-docs</link>
      <description>Things I think about when putting together effective method-level documentation.</description>
      <author> (Jo&amp;#235;l Quenneville

        
          May 31, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://thoughtbot.com/blog/writing-quality-method-docs</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A beginner&amp;#39;s guide to the Git reftable format</title>
      <link>https://about.gitlab.com/blog/2024/05/30/a-beginners-guide-to-the-git-reftable-format/</link>
      <description>In Git 2.45.0, GitLab upstreamed the reftable backend to Git, which completely changes how references are stored. Get an in-depth look at the inner workings of this new format.</description>
      <author> (Patrick Steinhardt)</author>
      <guid>https://about.gitlab.com/blog/2024/05/30/a-beginners-guide-to-the-git-reftable-format/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Intuitive Guide to Maxwell’s Equations</title>
      <link>https://photonlines.substack.com/p/an-intuitive-guide-to-maxwells-equations</link>
      <description>An Intuitive and Visual Guide to Maxwell&amp;#39;s Equations</description>
      <author> (Nick M)</author>
      <guid>https://photonlines.substack.com/p/an-intuitive-guide-to-maxwells-equations</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a Jenkins pipeline to deploy Desktop Apps as MSIX - Part 2: Packaging a Visual Studio solutio</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/modern-work-app-consult-blog/create-a-jenkins-pipeline-to-deploy-desktop-apps-as-msix-part-2/ba-p/4157259</link>
      <description>&amp;#160;
In this second part, it is described how to setup Jenkins pipeline to package a Visual Studio solution with a Windows Forms application and a&amp;#160;Windows..</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/258734)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/modern-work-app-consult-blog/create-a-jenkins-pipeline-to-deploy-desktop-apps-as-msix-part-2/ba-p/4157259</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metalama Status Update, May 2024</title>
      <link>https://blog.postsharp.net/metalama-status-update-2024-05</link>
      <description>In May 2024 we mainly worked on type and constructor introductions, with our first successful implementations of the Memento pattern. We also added tons of smaller features to the Metalama API. We started a new blog, the Timeless .NET Engineer.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.postsharp.net/metalama-status-update-2024-05</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failed to start Dapr - file does not exist</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/05/failed-to-start-dapr-file-does-not-exist.html</link>
      <description>A short post today; I’ll share an issue a encountered when trying to run a Dapr enabled application. This blog post wouldn’t add much value ...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/05/failed-to-start-dapr-file-does-not-exist.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s new in the Windows Subsystem for Linux in May 2024</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/whats-new-in-the-windows-subsystem-for-linux-in-may-2024/</link>
      <description>For this year’s Microsoft BUILD conference, we are thrilled to announce significant updates to WSL. This blog post will provide an overview of these enhancements and the recent developments in WSL. Memory, storage and networking improvements WSL Settings GUI application coming soon WSL Zero Trust Manage WSL in Dev Home,</description>
      <author> (Craig Loewen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/whats-new-in-the-windows-subsystem-for-linux-in-may-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECMAScript 2024 features: resizing and transferring ArrayBuffers</title>
      <link>https://2ality.com/2024/06/array-buffers-es2024.html</link>
      <description>In this blog post, we examine ArrayBuffer features that were introduced in ECMAScript 2024: “In-place resizable ArrayBuffers”, proposed by Shu-yu Guo “ArrayBuffer.prototype.transfer and friends” proposed by Shu-yu Guo, Jordan Harband and Yagiz Nizipli</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2ality.com/2024/06/array-buffers-es2024.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting to grips with an extra thumb</title>
      <link>https://www.cam.ac.uk/stories/third-thumb</link>
      <description>Members of the public have little trouble in learning very quickly how to use a third thumb – a controllable, prosthetic extra thumb – to pick up and manipulate objects. </description>
      <author> (Craig Brierley)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cam.ac.uk/stories/third-thumb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lizzy Banks. This story must be heard.</title>
      <link>https://lizzybanks.co.uk/2024/05/15/hello-world/</link>
      <description>The short story In order to fully understand everything that has happened, I strongly encourage you to read the full article below, but this is a very short summary of what I want to say. On 28th J…</description>
      <author> (Lizzy)</author>
      <guid>https://lizzybanks.co.uk/2024/05/15/hello-world/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measure schools on student growth</title>
      <link>https://brettcvz.com/posts/137-measure-schools-on-student-growth</link>
      <description>School accountability frameworks measure schools on the aggregate performance of current  students on standardized tests rather than the growth students demonstrate between years. As a result, “school quality” measures can fluctuate up or down based on the preparedness of incoming students even if the actual instructional quality remains constant.
Every spring, students across the country take high-stakes, summative assessments to demonstrate what they‘ve learned. These assessments are the single largest factor in how schools are measured, graded, and compared to one another, but there is a key structural flaw in how individual student results are aggregated into school-level results: school results vary based on &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;incoming student preparedness.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;
This is not a theoretical concern - this exact situation is playing out in some of our schools at Summit. In California, we are able to request from the state the prior test scores of our current students, including tests taken before the students enrolled with us. This allows us to better tailor the supports we give incoming students and to measure student growth over time; it also has pointed out that the proficiency levels of some of our schools’ incoming classes are low and &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;falling&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;. The students are starting further behind when they first walk in our doors; even if our schools do a great job helping students grow, it’s almost certain these schools’ grade level aggregates will decline. As a result, these schools will be under greater scrutiny and face contentious charter renewals.
Here’s what this looks like in practice - let’s say for a particular middle school, only 40 out of the 100 incoming sixth graders scored “proficient” on the tests they took just four months before. If that middle school does an amazing job, they can help 10 (16%) of the below-proficient students close the gap, so by the end of sixth grade 50 out of 100 students test as proficient. I would point to this as a great school, even though half its students are “below proficient”!
But we can go a step further: each year a new batch of sixth graders rolls in, and say in year two now the number of incoming sixth graders scored “proficient” when they were in fifth grade &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;decreases&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; to 25 out of 100. Seeing the greater need, the teachers at the school work extra hard and are able to help 15 (20%) of the below proficient students close the gap, so by the end of the second year 40 out of 100 students test as proficient. I would point to this as a school that is doing a commendable job serving high-need students and getting better over time.
Unfortunately, that perspective is the &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;opposite&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; of how this school would be seen in state accountability systems that look at simple aggregates of grade level results. In California for example, this school would be seen as a low performing school (because only 40% are proficient) that is getting worse (because last year 50% were proficient). This school would likely be put under strict oversight, the administration and staff would be told that they were failing kids, and if it were a charter school it would likely be shut down. Despite the fact that this middle school is exactly the type of school we need more of: a school that’s not only helping students close the gap, but one that’s actually getting better over time!
The solution is straightforward and easy for states to implement: measure schools based by individual student growth, not single-year snapshots. Celebrate the schools where students make greater than one year’s worth of growth and put pressure on those that cause students to fall behind in the first place. The current system harms the very schools that are doing the most to help.
Putting aside the debate about whether high-stakes summative assessments are the right way to measure school quality, fixing this structural flaw in school accountability metrics would go a long way to making sure we’re measuring schools based on what we care about most: helping students grow.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://brettcvz.com/posts/137-measure-schools-on-student-growth</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ctrl-Z Exhaustion - 6 Proven Methods to Overcome Mental Fatigue and Reclaim Your Energy - Sparrow&amp;#39;s Digital Garden</title>
      <link>https://garden.sparrow.zone/Ctrl-Z+Exhaustion+-+6+Proven+Methods+to+Overcome+Mental+Fatigue+and+Reclaim+Your+Energy</link>
      <description>Ctrl-Z Exhaustion - 6 Proven Methods to Overcome Mental Fatigue and Reclaim Your Energy - Sparrow&amp;#39;s Digital Garden</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://garden.sparrow.zone/Ctrl-Z+Exhaustion+-+6+Proven+Methods+to+Overcome+Mental+Fatigue+and+Reclaim+Your+Energy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Chrome go brrrrrr....</title>
      <link>https://datosh.github.io/post/hardware_accelerate_chrome/</link>
      <description>Everything started with a simple question: “Why does my laptop get hot watching YouTube?</description>
      <author> (DaTosh)</author>
      <guid>https://datosh.github.io/post/hardware_accelerate_chrome/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating PostgreSQL backups to Digital Ocean Spaces with Kamal</title>
      <link>https://nts.strzibny.name/automating-postgresql-backups-do-spaces-kamal/</link>
      <description>Here’s a short tutorial on how I set up automated PostgreSQL backups to a DO Spaces bucket with Kamal.</description>
      <author> (strzibny)</author>
      <guid>https://nts.strzibny.name/automating-postgresql-backups-do-spaces-kamal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs as Programming Language Runtimes, or Why Monolithic Text Prompts Are a Mistake &amp;#183; Sibylline.dev</title>
      <link>https://sibylline.dev/2024/06/02/llms-as-programming-language-runtimes/</link>
      <description>02 Jun 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sibylline.dev/2024/06/02/llms-as-programming-language-runtimes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fansite of Kumdor</title>
      <link>https://lynn.github.io/kumdor/</link>
      <description>“The Sword of
          Kumdor” (クムドールの剣) is a touch-typing RPG for the
          NEC&amp;#160;PC‑98, created by Michiaki Tsubaki in 1991. You play as
          the Milky&amp;#160;Way&amp;#39;s #1&amp;#160;typist, summoned to planet Kumdor to
          fight mysterious monsters by typing spells — but you lose all your
          keyboard keys and your QWERTY skills in a crash landing. Can
          you recover your talents and save the world??</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lynn.github.io/kumdor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Hunter – Aspire and more</title>
      <link>https://jesseliberty.com/2024/06/02/scott-hunter-aspire-and-more/</link>
      <description>Scott Hunter (VP Microsoft) joins Yet Another Podcast’s reboot to talk about Aspire, Azure and much more. Do not miss this episode… Aspire will blow you away!</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://jesseliberty.com/2024/06/02/scott-hunter-aspire-and-more/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 16:06:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>