<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Choose Your Status Game Wisely – Of Dollars And Data</title>
      <link>https://ofdollarsanddata.com/choose-your-status-game-wisely/</link>
      <description>On status games and how to outsmart them.</description>
      <author> (Posted March 29, 2022 by Nick Maggiulli)</author>
      <guid>https://ofdollarsanddata.com/choose-your-status-game-wisely/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 12:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDD South West 2022 Call for Papers Now Open</title>
      <link>https://dddsouthwest.com/news/14/ddd-south-west-2022-cfp-now-open</link>
      <description>The DDD South West 2022 call for papers is now open! This year our event takes place on Saturday 25th June at The Engine Shed, Temple Meads, Bristol, BS1 6QH. (See venue)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dddsouthwest.com/news/14/ddd-south-west-2022-cfp-now-open</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 11:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Convert String to Title Case in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-convert-string-title-case/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to learn how to convert string to title case in C# with different examples that will help us in a process.</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-convert-string-title-case/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 09:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Principal Engineering Community</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/landing_pages/principal-engineer-hiring?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202204</link>
      <description>Amazon’s Principal Engineer Community sets the standard for engineering excellence at Amazon.&amp;#160; The community comprises Principal, Senior Principal, and Distinguished Engineers who are responsible for driving Amazon’s overall technical architecture. Principal Engineers at Amazon are pragmatic visionaries. They make a lasting impact that echoes through the technology, the product, and the company. They work on Amazon’s hardest problems, building high quality, architecturally sound systems that are aligned with our business needs. They remain hands-on and lead by example. By being close to the details, they earn the respect needed to be effective technical leaders. Principal Engineers bring clarity to complexity and demonstrate smart ways to simplify. They are leaders and mentors, setting excellent examples for their local teams and the entire Amazon engineering community. They meet regularly&amp;#160;to question each other’s assumptions, illuminate pitfalls, and foster shared understanding across all groups at Amazon. Amazon&amp;#39;s Principal Engineering Community created a set of tenets to articulate and perpetuate the guiding values and expectations of Principal Engineers at Amazon!&amp;#160;Click here to learn more about the tenets.&amp;#160;

Amazon continues to expand our Principal Engineer Community and we are actively looking for senior technical individual contributors across every business at Amazon!

If you are interested in pursuing a senior individual contributor role at Amazon, please contact the Senior Technical Talent Recruiting team using this email alias: principal-engineer-hiring@amazon.com

The Senior Technical Talent Recruiting Team is the dedicated talent acquisition team responsible for hiring Principal, Senior Principal and Distinguished Engineers across the globe. We focus on finding the right role fit for senior level technical individual contributors at Amazon.&amp;#160;

Amazon celebrates International Women&amp;#39;s Day&amp;#160;

Amazon will be celebrating International Women&amp;#39;s Day globally. Individually, we&amp;#39;re all responsible for our own thoughts and actions - all day, every day. We can break the bias in our communities. We can break the bias in our workplaces. We can break the bias in our schools, colleges and universities. Together, we can all break the bias - on International Women&amp;#39;s Day and beyond.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.jobs/en/landing_pages/principal-engineer-hiring?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202204</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 07:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - benbjohnson/postlite: Postgres wire compatible SQLite proxy.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/benbjohnson/postlite</link>
      <description>Postgres wire compatible SQLite proxy. Contribute to benbjohnson/postlite development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (benbjohnson)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/benbjohnson/postlite</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 04:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A database for 2022</title>
      <link>https://tailscale.com/blog/database-for-2022/</link>
      <description>Hi, it’s us again, the ones who used to store our database in a single JSON file on disk, and then moved to etcd. Time for another change! We’re going to put everything in a single file on disk again.</description>
      <author> (Tailscale)</author>
      <guid>https://tailscale.com/blog/database-for-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 04:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFC 9225: Software Defects Considered Harmful</title>
      <link>https://www.rfc-editor.org/rfc/rfc9225.html</link>
      <description>This document discourages the practice of introducing software defects in general and in network protocol implementations specifically. 
        Software defects are one of the largest cost drivers for the networking industry.
        This document is intended to clarify the best current practice in this regard.</description>
      <author> (Remco van Mook)</author>
      <guid>https://www.rfc-editor.org/rfc/rfc9225.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 02:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2022 Now Does GitHub Copilot, the &amp;#39;AI Pair Programmer&amp;#39; -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/04/01/vs2022-copilot.aspx</link>
      <description>The potentially game-changing tech drew many &amp;#39;ooohs&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;aaahs&amp;#39; from the developer community -- and a fair amount of debate about ethics and security -- when it was unveiled last summer for Visual Studio Code.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel04/01/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/04/01/vs2022-copilot.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 01:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Sold My Newsletter: Andrew Kamphey - Paved Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.paved.com/blog/how-i-sold-my-newsletter-andrew-kamphey/</link>
      <description>Andrew Kamphey is an entrepreneur and content creator who’s launched a variety of projects, from web apps to online courses. He founded and later sold Influence Weekly, a newsletter aimed at curating influencer marketing research and analyzing the influencer marketing industry. In January 2022, Andrew started working here at Paved as a publisher success manager.</description>
      <author> (Emily Wong)</author>
      <guid>https://www.paved.com/blog/how-i-sold-my-newsletter-andrew-kamphey/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned with Elm | 20Y</title>
      <link>https://20y.hu/journal/elm-lessons-learned/</link>
      <description>I’ve been working with Elm for more than a year now. I’m was new to the language and to staticly typed functional programming too. I come from a PHP, Emacs Lisp, Python, JavaScript background. Hereby I’m collecting my insights and the lessons I’ve learned along the way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://20y.hu/journal/elm-lessons-learned/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers for software engineers - Made of Bugs</title>
      <link>https://blog.nelhage.com/post/transformers-for-software-engineers/</link>
      <description>Ever since its introduction in the 2017 paper, Attention is All You Need, the Transformer model architecture has taken the deep-learning world by storm. Initially introduced for machine translation, it has become the tool of choice for a wide range of domains, including text, audio, video, and others. Transformers have also driven most of the massive increases in model scale and capability in the last few years. OpenAI’s GPT-3 and Codex models are Transformers, as are DeepMind’s Gopher models and many others.</description>
      <author> (Nelson Elhage)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.nelhage.com/post/transformers-for-software-engineers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Reminder Trick &amp;#183; Jens Oliver Meiert</title>
      <link>https://meiert.com/en/blog/reminders/</link>
      <description>This tool is so powerful and at the same time so trivial to make a routine that I ask everyone who regularly employs it to transcend their disappointment—I’m mentioning it for the people I meet who don’t&amp;#160;use it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://meiert.com/en/blog/reminders/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I love Elm</title>
      <link>https://blog.auryn.dev/posts/starting-with-elm/</link>
      <description>My first projects in Elm</description>
      <author> (Auryn Engel)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.auryn.dev/posts/starting-with-elm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Free Automatic Diary – DeUmbra</title>
      <link>https://deumbra.com/2022/04/introducing-thoughtlog-the-free-automatic-diary/</link>
      <description>Our thoughts are our experience in this world, and our worries, memories, and plans are the only real testimony to our existence. Moment by moment, it feels like we are thinking about what’s naturally important, but in reality we each focus only on a minuscule subset. Equally surprising is that we dwell on different subsets from those around us—each of us lives a unique internal life. Our thoughts are partially under our control and partially not, but they are all we really have, and they just pass through.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://deumbra.com/2022/04/introducing-thoughtlog-the-free-automatic-diary/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A year of README reviews</title>
      <link>https://blog.liw.fi/posts/2022/03/31/readmes/</link>
      <description>A year ago I published an offer to review the README of free and open source projects. I didn’t expect much interest, but someone posted the link to Hacker News, and I got enough requests that it was a little overwhelming. I’ve now reviewed 196 READMEs, my queue is empty, and I’m suspending the offer for now, even if it has been fun.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.liw.fi/posts/2022/03/31/readmes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutting down my baby | fabiandietrich.com</title>
      <link>https://www.fabiandietrich.com/blog/shutting-down-my-baby.html</link>
      <description>[07-2021 / English / 1688 words]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.fabiandietrich.com/blog/shutting-down-my-baby.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I ❤️ Microscopes • Hillel Wayne</title>
      <link>https://www.hillelwayne.com/post/microscopy/</link>
      <description>To celebrate April Fools, some friends and I made content outside our normal brands. You can see the full list of pieces here!
Also, CW: grody gross-up pictures of bugs.
I’ve always loved science. At one time, I thought it’d be my career: I got BAs in math and physics with the hope of eventually becoming a physicist. But my friend’s horror stories of grad school scared me off and I instead left academia and got a job programming.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hillelwayne.com/post/microscopy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total Functions and Partial Functions</title>
      <link>https://nickdrozd.github.io/2022/04/01/total-partial-functions.html</link>
      <description>Given a function and an input for which that function is defined, does the function return an answer? Functions that always return answers are called total, and functions that don’t are called partial.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nickdrozd.github.io/2022/04/01/total-partial-functions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python in VS Code Team Is Breaking Up Big Extension -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/04/01/vs-code-python-apr22.aspx</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s by far the most popular tool in the marketplace with more than 53 million installs, nearly 20 million more than any other extension.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel04/01/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/04/01/vs-code-python-apr22.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 23:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sof&amp;#237;a Celi - cryptographer</title>
      <link>https://sofiaceli.com/2022/03/12/loading.html</link>
      <description>Sof&amp;#237;a Celi - Cryptography</description>
      <author> (Sof&amp;#237;a Celi)</author>
      <guid>https://sofiaceli.com/2022/03/12/loading.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Issues &amp;#183; dotnet/aspnetcore</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspnetcore/labels/feature-minimal-actions</link>
      <description>ASP.NET Core is a cross-platform .NET framework for building modern cloud-based web applications on Windows, Mac, or Linux. - Issues &amp;#183; dotnet/aspnetcore</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspnetcore/labels/feature-minimal-actions</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 21:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xkcd: Instructions</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2601/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2601/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 21:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support Ukraine &amp;#128155;&amp;#128153; Ukrainian Borscht | Ievgen Klopotenko</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/gOrE-3ISQ3I</link>
      <description>Hi! My team and I are working to help Ukraine. ✔ We’re providing culinary support to Ukrainians: sharing recipes made with currently available ingredients, a...</description>
      <author> (Ievgen Klopotenko
  
  
  
    Ievgen Klopotenko
  




  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/gOrE-3ISQ3I</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 20:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preparing CIFAR Image Data for PyTorch -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/04/01/preparing-cifar-data.aspx</link>
      <description>CIFAR-10 problems analyze crude 32 x 32 color images to predict which of 10 classes the image is. Here, Dr. James McCaffrey of Microsoft Research explains how to get the raw source CIFAR-10 data, convert it from binary to text and save it as a text file that can be used to train a PyTorch neural network classifier.</description>
      <author> (By James McCaffrey04/01/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/04/01/preparing-cifar-data.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 19:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinite Mac: An Instant-Booting Quadra in Your Browser</title>
      <link>https://blog.persistent.info/2022/03/blog-post.html</link>
      <description>I’ve extended James Friend’s in-browser Basilisk II port to create a full-featured classic 68K Mac in your browser. You can see it in action at system7.app or macos8.app. For a taste, see also this screencast:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.persistent.info/2022/03/blog-post.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 19:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET | Open-source web framework for .NET</title>
      <link>https://dotnet.microsoft.com/en-us/apps/aspnet</link>
      <description>Build web apps and services that run on Windows, Linux, and macOS using C#, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Get started for free on Windows, Linux, or macOS.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnet.microsoft.com/en-us/apps/aspnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 19:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>docopt.net 0.8.0</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/docopt.net/0.8.0</link>
      <description>docopt.net is the .net version of the docopt python beautiful command line parser.  docopt.net helps you define an interface for your command-line app, and automatically generate a parser for it. docopt.net is based on conventions that have been used for decades in help messages and man pages for program interface description.  Interface description in docopt.net is such a help message, but formalized. Check out http://docopt.org for a more detailed explanation.
        Quick example:
            var arguments = new Docopt().Apply(&amp;quot;Usage: prog [-a] [-b] FILE&amp;quot;, args);
            if (arguments[&amp;quot;-a&amp;quot;].IsTrue) {{ ... }}</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/docopt.net/0.8.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 18:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A few things to know before stealing my 914</title>
      <link>https://www.hagerty.com/media/advice/a-few-things-to-know-before-you-steal-my-914/</link>
      <description>If you&amp;#39;re going to make a getaway in Norman Garrett&amp;#39;s Porsche 914, he&amp;#39;s got some tips to help grease the wheels, as it were.</description>
      <author> (Norman Garrett					
					
						31 March 2022)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hagerty.com/media/advice/a-few-things-to-know-before-you-steal-my-914/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 17:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlaKE12</title>
      <link>https://blake12.org/</link>
      <description>BlaKE12</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blake12.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 17:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GOV.UK Design System is now live - Government Digital Service</title>
      <link>https://gds.blog.gov.uk/2022/03/31/the-gov-uk-design-system-is-now-live/</link>
      <description>GDS is leading the digital transformation of the UK government.</description>
      <author> (Trang Erskine, Senior Product Manager, Government Digital Service)</author>
      <guid>https://gds.blog.gov.uk/2022/03/31/the-gov-uk-design-system-is-now-live/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 17:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Cosmos DB Conf April 2022 - Events</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learntv/azure-cosmos-db-april-2022/</link>
      <description>Join us LIVE on April 19 – 20, 2022 for the second Azure Cosmos DB Conf on Learn TV. Azure Cosmos DB Conf is a free, virtual developer event organized in collaboration with the Azure Cosmos DB community and Microsoft. The event will be streamed in three, 3-hour live segments with 25-minute sessions. Each livestream will have its own unique content, so feel free to attend more than one stream or view the content on-demand after the event ends.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learntv/azure-cosmos-db-april-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 16:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time to get on trend</title>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.blog/2022/03/31/time-to-get-on-trend-filters/</link>
      <description>Question: who&amp;#39;s got a new lewk? Answer: Oh, you know</description>
      <author> (Ben Popper and Ryan Donovan)</author>
      <guid>https://stackoverflow.blog/2022/03/31/time-to-get-on-trend-filters/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 15:03:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>April 1, 2022</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220401-00/</link>
      <description>Inspiring a new level of code obfuscation.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220401-00/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 15:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beginning gRPC with ASP.NET Core 6: Build Applications using ASP.NET Core Razor Pages, Angular, and Best Practices in .NET 6: Giretti, Anthony: 9781484280072: Amazon.com: Books</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/Beginning-gRPC-ASP-NET-Core-Applications/dp/1484280075/ref=sr_1_8?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202204</link>
      <description>Beginning gRPC with ASP.NET Core 6: Build Applications using ASP.NET Core Razor Pages, Angular, and Best Practices in .NET 6 [Giretti, Anthony] on Amazon.com. *FREE* shipping on qualifying offers. Beginning gRPC with ASP.NET Core 6: Build Applications using ASP.NET Core Razor Pages, Angular, and Best Practices in .NET 6</description>
      <author> (Share                                    &amp;lt;Embed&amp;gt;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/Beginning-gRPC-ASP-NET-Core-Applications/dp/1484280075/ref=sr_1_8?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202204</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 14:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The end of the road for Cloudflare CAPTCHAs</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/end-cloudflare-captcha/</link>
      <description>We decided we’re going to stop using CAPTCHAs</description>
      <author> (Reid Tatoris)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/end-cloudflare-captcha/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 14:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the .NET Community Toolkit - MVVM, Performance, Diagnostics, &amp;amp; More</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/oKMZiDA9ogM</link>
      <description>This week James is joined by Sergio Pedri, a software engineer on the Microsoft Store client team and contributor to the .NET Community Toolkit to talk about...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •
  
  
    
      4.8K views
    
      8 days ago)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/oKMZiDA9ogM</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 13:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAF mitigations for Spring4Shell</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/waf-mitigations-spring4shell/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare Managed Ruleset updates for the recent vulnerabilities affecting the Java Spring framework and related software components</description>
      <author> (Michael Tremante)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/waf-mitigations-spring4shell/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 13:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>