<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Aspire を デプロイする - Qiita</title>
      <link>https://qiita.com/takashiuesaka/items/3da744d0511f29270299</link>
      <description>はじめにこの記事は .NET Aspire に関する一連の記事の一部です。.NET Aspire って何？ - 概要.NET Aspire を使ってみる.NET Aspire をデプロイする.NET Aspire で Prometheus, Jaeger, Grafana を使…</description>
      <author> (by okazuki)</author>
      <guid>https://qiita.com/takashiuesaka/items/3da744d0511f29270299</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 07:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A year of making you more productive using Git in Visual Studio - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/a-year-of-making-you-more-productive-using-git-in-visual-studio/</link>
      <description>Our team has been dedicated to increasing GitHub integration, boosting productivity, and addressing valuable feedback from Developer Community.</description>
      <author> (Jessie Houghton)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/a-year-of-making-you-more-productive-using-git-in-visual-studio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 06:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compiling Success: My Aspirations for a Transformative Year Ahead - Chris Woodruff&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/compiling-success-my-aspirations-for-a-transformative-year-ahead/</link>
      <description>Introduction As we step into 2024, I find myself reflecting on the journey I&amp;#39;ve embarked upon in the ever-evolving field of software development and architecture. This year, I am setting 10 ambitious goals to grow and expand my life and expertise. I believe that setting clear, achievable objectives is crucial in one’s professional and personal</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/compiling-success-my-aspirations-for-a-transformative-year-ahead/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical Introduction to Deep Learning: Methods, Implementations, and Theory</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2310.20360</link>
      <description>This book aims to provide an introduction to the topic of deep learning algorithms. We review essential components of deep learning algorithms in full mathematical detail including different artificial neural network (ANN) architectures (such as fully-connected feedforward ANNs, convolutional ANNs, recurrent ANNs, residual ANNs, and ANNs with batch normalization) and different optimization algorithms (such as the basic stochastic gradient descent (SGD) method, accelerated methods, and adaptive methods). We also cover several theoretical aspects of deep learning algorithms such as approximation capacities of ANNs (including a calculus for ANNs), optimization theory (including Kurdyka-Łojasiewicz inequalities), and generalization errors. In the last part of the book some deep learning approximation methods for PDEs are reviewed including physics-informed neural networks (PINNs) and deep Galerkin methods. We hope that this book will be useful for students and scientists who do not yet have any background in deep learning at all and would like to gain a solid foundation as well as for practitioners who would like to obtain a firmer mathematical understanding of the objects and methods considered in deep learning.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 31 Oct 2023])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2310.20360</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Dive into Conversions in C# With the Convert Class - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-conversions-convert-class/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will learn how to utilize different types of conversions in C# and convert C# types interchangeably.</description>
      <author> (Kamil Pakula)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-conversions-convert-class/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 01:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman with rectifier and car 1912</title>
      <link>https://nyheritage.contentdm.oclc.org/digital/collection/p16694coll20/id/35/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nyheritage.contentdm.oclc.org/digital/collection/p16694coll20/id/35/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All DMCA Notices Filed Against TorrentFreak in 2023 Were Bogus * TorrentFreak</title>
      <link>https://torrentfreak.com/all-dmca-notices-filed-against-torrentfreak-in-2023-were-bogus-240101/</link>
      <description>In 2023, anti-piracy companies continued to file DMCA notices against TorrentFreak both directly and with Google. All 100% bogus.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://torrentfreak.com/all-dmca-notices-filed-against-torrentfreak-in-2023-were-bogus-240101/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenVoice: Versatile Instant Voice Cloning</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2312.01479</link>
      <description>We introduce OpenVoice, a versatile voice cloning approach that requires only a short audio clip from the reference speaker to replicate their voice and generate speech in multiple languages. OpenVoice represents a significant advancement in addressing the following open challenges in the field: 1) Flexible Voice Style Control. OpenVoice enables granular control over voice styles, including emotion, accent, rhythm, pauses, and intonation, in addition to replicating the tone color of the reference speaker. The voice styles are not directly copied from and constrained by the style of the reference speaker. Previous approaches lacked the ability to flexibly manipulate voice styles after cloning. 2) Zero-Shot Cross-Lingual Voice Cloning. OpenVoice achieves zero-shot cross-lingual voice cloning for languages not included in the massive-speaker training set. Unlike previous approaches, which typically require extensive massive-speaker multi-lingual (MSML) dataset for all languages, OpenVoice can clone voices into a new language without any massive-speaker training data for that language. OpenVoice is also computationally efficient, costing tens of times less than commercially available APIs that offer even inferior performance. To foster further research in the field, we have made the source code and trained model publicly accessible. We also provide qualitative results in our demo website. Prior to its public release, our internal version of OpenVoice was used tens of millions of times by users worldwide between May and October 2023, serving as the backend of MyShell.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 3 Dec 2023 (v1), last revised 21 Dec 2023 (this version, v4)])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2312.01479</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Spatial Geometries for Clustering Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://bramcohen.com/p/better-spatial-geometries-for-clustering</link>
      <description>Everybody please start using this</description>
      <author> (Bram Cohen)</author>
      <guid>https://bramcohen.com/p/better-spatial-geometries-for-clustering</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from Securing FreeRDP</title>
      <link>https://eyalitkin.wordpress.com/2024/01/01/lessons-from-securing-freerdp/</link>
      <description>Introduction The story behind this 2-part blog series started quite a while ago, on September 2018, when I started a vulnerability research on a (then) novel attack vector: “Reverse RDP&amp;amp;#8221…</description>
      <author> (Author: Eyal Itkin

		
			Former white hat security researcher.			
				View all posts by Eyal Itkin)</author>
      <guid>https://eyalitkin.wordpress.com/2024/01/01/lessons-from-securing-freerdp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY I AM USING WINDOWS 7 MACHINE AS A DAILY DRIVER IN 2024?</title>
      <link>https://trackerninja.codeberg.page/post/why-i-am-using-windows-7-machine-as-a-daily-driver-in-2024/</link>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2024-01-01

Added some links and fixed typos here and there.

VERSION: alpha 02</description>
      <author> (About Unlisted Slacker
	
	
		Vintage computer retrograde interested in many aspects of life)</author>
      <guid>https://trackerninja.codeberg.page/post/why-i-am-using-windows-7-machine-as-a-daily-driver-in-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This year in LLVM (2023)</title>
      <link>https://www.npopov.com/2024/01/01/This-year-in-LLVM-2023.html</link>
      <description>This is my second year working on LLVM at Red Hat. Similar to last year’s blog post, I want to summarize some of the things I’ve worked on this year.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.npopov.com/2024/01/01/This-year-in-LLVM-2023.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects - .NET Foundation Project Trends</title>
      <link>https://dnfprojects.org/</link>
      <description>This site is running on Microsoft Azure and was developed by the experts at Devessence using Oqtane, a CMS and application framework for Blazor and .NET MAUI.Check out the open source project on GitHub!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dnfprojects.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What You Should Know About Linear Markov Chains</title>
      <link>https://win-vector.com/2024/01/01/linear-markov-chain-facts/</link>
      <description>I want to collect some “great things to know about linear Markov chains.” For this note we are working with a Markov chain on states that are the integers 0 through k (k &amp;gt; 0). A Mark…</description>
      <author> (John Mount)</author>
      <guid>https://win-vector.com/2024/01/01/linear-markov-chain-facts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paolo Melchiorre - My 2023 in&amp;#160;review</title>
      <link>https://www.paulox.net/2023/12/31/my-2023-in-review/</link>
      <description>The review of my 2023, trying to remember all the things done in this year, in which more than anyone I met many fantastic people and visited new&amp;#160;countries.</description>
      <author> (Paolo Melchiorre)</author>
      <guid>https://www.paulox.net/2023/12/31/my-2023-in-review/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary: Thinking in Bets by Annie Duke</title>
      <link>https://www.chestergrant.com/summary-thinking-in-bets-by-annie-duke</link>
      <description>1. Thinking in bets starts with recognizing that there are exactly two things that determine how our lives turn out: the quality of our decisions and luck. Learning to recognize the difference...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.chestergrant.com/summary-thinking-in-bets-by-annie-duke</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximizing LLM performance</title>
      <link>https://blog.ankitsanghvi.in/maximizing-llm-performace/</link>
      <description>Short excerpt on how LLMs can be pushed from prototype to performance in a scalable way</description>
      <author> (Ankit Sanghvi)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ankitsanghvi.in/maximizing-llm-performace/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The mystery of Rails’
&amp;lt;code&amp;gt;lib/&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt; folder &amp;#128218;</title>
      <link>https://simplexity.quest/posts/2023-12-23-lib-is-for-libraries.html</link>
      <description>In Ruby on Rails applications, one of the directories that
      come with the default structure is lib/. What is it
      for? How should it be used? And why should you care?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://simplexity.quest/posts/2023-12-23-lib-is-for-libraries.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why blog in an (AI) apocalypse?</title>
      <link>https://www.kibernick.com/why-blog-in-an-ai-apocalypse/</link>
      <description>On AI and how it’s been conjuring existential dread in a lot of creatives.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.kibernick.com/why-blog-in-an-ai-apocalypse/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Displaying content as a graph: An exploration</title>
      <link>https://thisisimportant.net/posts/content-as-a-graph/</link>
      <description>Most web content is displayed as a strict hierarchy, tree-based or otherwise. What if it wasn&amp;#39;t?An exploration into the advantages of graph-based content design, the numerous pitfalls, and a few case studies along the way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thisisimportant.net/posts/content-as-a-graph/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alireza Ghasemi&amp;#39;s Blog - What If Every Year Started on the First Day of the Week?</title>
      <link>https://aghasemi.js.org/blog/#P0003?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</link>
      <description>In what type of calendar would it be guaranteed that the first day of the year is the first day of the week (e.g. Monday) as well? For that to happen, we need the length of the year to be a multiple of 7, obviously. Closest multiple of 7 to 365 is 364.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aghasemi.js.org/blog/#P0003?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on a Sabbatical</title>
      <link>https://www.vipshek.com/blog/sabbatical</link>
      <description>But in the seventh year the land is to have a year of sabbath rest.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.vipshek.com/blog/sabbatical</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email is a great note-taking tool for debugging sessions</title>
      <link>https://gaurangtandon.com/blog/note-taking-email</link>
      <description>In my everyday job, I often have to reverse-engineer parts of a web app (like Google Docs) using its minified JavaScript files. These files have many levels of delegation, have timer-oriented code, and have weird data transformations. It is difficult to complete the reverse engineering in just one session. So, I must keep taking notes to remember all the tiny details and map out my progress.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gaurangtandon.com/blog/note-taking-email</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployment with JetBrains Space</title>
      <link>https://blog.rufer.be/2024/01/01/continuous-integration-and-continuous-deployment-with-jetbrains-space/</link>
      <description>The author was tasked with setting up a CI/CD process for a Blazor application using JetBrains Space. They had experience with other tools like Azure DevOps and GitHub Actions but found implementin…</description>
      <author> (Published by Marc Rufer)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.rufer.be/2024/01/01/continuous-integration-and-continuous-deployment-with-jetbrains-space/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 22:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2875/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2875/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 22:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro EP 102&amp;#160;: What is the purpose of dictionaries in C#?</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/net-tips/pro-ep-102-what-is-the-purpose-of-dictionaries-in-c-5efac01d63c0</link>
      <description>What is the purpose of dictionaries in C#?</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@mwaseemzakir)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/net-tips/pro-ep-102-what-is-the-purpose-of-dictionaries-in-c-5efac01d63c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 20:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stuff we figured out about AI in 2023</title>
      <link>https://simonwillison.net/2023/Dec/31/ai-in-2023/</link>
      <description>2023 was the breakthrough year for Large Language Models (LLMs). I think it’s OK to call these AI—they’re the latest and (currently) most interesting development in the academic field of …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://simonwillison.net/2023/Dec/31/ai-in-2023/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 20:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Apps for Windows in 2024 - Nick&amp;#39;s .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/building-apps-for-windows-in-2024/</link>
      <description>I figured I’d start the year off with a quick thought post on where things are at with building apps for Windows. As Windows rapidly approaches the 4 decade mark, you’d expect there to be a well defined model for building apps. Instead we’re still realing from the years of missteps and indecision by Microsoft. ... Read more</description>
      <author> (Nick)</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/building-apps-for-windows-in-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 19:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recording: .NET Core podcast on RavenDB, performance and .NET</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/200386-A/recording-net-core-podcast-on-ravendb-performance-and-net?Key=54b57003-234d-455e-9adf-a952849e695d</link>
      <description>Me and Jaime had a really good discussion about RavenDB, why I took the time to create his own NoSql database engine, and the fact that I built it using .NET...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/200386-A/recording-net-core-podcast-on-ravendb-performance-and-net?Key=54b57003-234d-455e-9adf-a952849e695d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 19:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock Your Code: Coding Standards for Microsoft .NET (8th Edition)</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/01/01/rock-your-code-coding-standards-for-microsoft-net-8th-edition/</link>
      <description>The 8th edition of the book, Rock Your Code: Coding Standards for Microsoft .NET, is available on Amazon. It consolidates Microsoft .NET coding standards and provides supplementary directives. Draw…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave
		

		
			I live in San Diego, Ca USA			
				View all posts by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/01/01/rock-your-code-coding-standards-for-microsoft-net-8th-edition/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 18:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After ten years, it&amp;#39;s time to stop making videos.</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=7DKv5H5Frt0</link>
      <description>Find me here: ❓ LATERAL, free weekly podcast: https://lateralcast.com/ https://youtube.com/lateralcast &amp;#128240; WEEKLY NEWSLETTER https://www.tomscott.com/newslett...</description>
      <author> (AustinMcConnell
  
  
  
    AustinMcConnell
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=7DKv5H5Frt0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 18:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meshtastic</title>
      <link>https://meshtastic.org/</link>
      <description>An open source, off-grid, decentralized, mesh network built to run on affordable, low-power devices</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://meshtastic.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 18:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Smartest Way to Onboard Developers</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pUzFZKVlPtk</link>
      <description>Save time &amp;amp; get the source code: https://www.patreon.com/CodeWithStuChange happens. People will leave your team and people join your team. But what if there ...</description>
      <author> (John McBride
  
  
  
    John McBride
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pUzFZKVlPtk</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How They’re Connected and What to Do About It – Solving Procrastination</title>
      <link>https://solvingprocrastination.com/perfectionism/</link>
      <description>Procrastination is a common issue, which occurs when people unnecessarily postpone decisions or actions, generally despite knowing that doing so is likely to cause them issues.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://solvingprocrastination.com/perfectionism/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bindings made easy with Shared Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/01/01/dotnet-maui-bindings-made-easy-with-shared-toolkit/</link>
      <description>Specify Binding as a LINQ expression without the need to specify an additional getter or setter.</description>
      <author> (By Vijay Anand E G)</author>
      <guid>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/01/01/dotnet-maui-bindings-made-easy-with-shared-toolkit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 15:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I prevent my ATL class from participating in COM aggregation? DECLARE_NOT_AGGREGATABLE didn&amp;#39;t work - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240101-00/?p=109214</link>
      <description>That marker applies only to creation via the class factory.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240101-00/?p=109214</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 15:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Compare Strings in CSharp: Tips and Tricks You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/01/01/how-to-compare-strings-in-csharp-tips-and-tricks-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <description>Wondering how to compare strings in CSharp? We&amp;#39;ll compare using string.Equals(), string.Compare(), and == operator to weigh the pros and the cons.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/01/01/how-to-compare-strings-in-csharp-tips-and-tricks-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>391: Our Predictions for Apple in 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/391</link>
      <description>Hello 2024! Let&amp;#39;s talk about what we think is coming for Apple when it comes to hardware, software, and AI!</description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/391</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - ublue-os/bazzite: Bazzite is an OCI image that serves as an alternative operating system for the Steam Deck, and a ready-to-game SteamOS-like for desktop computers, living room home theater PCs, and numerous other handheld PCs.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ublue-os/bazzite</link>
      <description>Bazzite is an OCI image that serves as an alternative operating system for the Steam Deck, and a ready-to-game SteamOS-like for desktop computers, living room home theater PCs, and numerous other h...</description>
      <author> (ublue-os)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ublue-os/bazzite</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 08:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>