<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Mathematics for Computer Science | Electrical Engineering and Computer Science | MIT OpenCourseWare</title>
      <link>https://ocw.mit.edu/courses/6-1200j-mathematics-for-computer-science-spring-2024/</link>
      <description>This course covers elementary discrete mathematics for science and engineering, with a focus on mathematical tools and proof techniques useful in computer science. Topics include logical notation, sets, relations, elementary graph theory, state machines and invariants, induction and proofs by contradiction, recurrences, asymptotic notation, elementary analysis of algorithms, elementary number theory and cryptography, permutations and combinations, counting tools, and discrete probability.</description>
      <guid>https://ocw.mit.edu/courses/6-1200j-mathematics-for-computer-science-spring-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AccuWeather APIs | Important update: new portal launch &amp; changes to free limited trial</title>
      <link>https://developer.accuweather.com/new-portal</link>
      <description>AccuWeather is excited to share important updates coming this summer to the AccuWeather API Developer Portal, which is designed to elevate your experience and ensure you get the most from our industry-leading weather data. What is Changing? To better support your development needs, AccuWeather is introducing a more powerful and streamlined platform, along with updated</description>
      <guid>https://developer.accuweather.com/new-portal</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprising no one, new research says AI Overviews cause massive drop in search clicks</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/ai/2025/07/research-shows-google-ai-overviews-reduce-website-clicks-by-almost-half/</link>
      <description>The Pew Research Center analysis shows how hard AI is hitting web traffic.</description>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/ai/2025/07/research-shows-google-ai-overviews-reduce-website-clicks-by-almost-half/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CherylUI theme for your Uno Platform Applications - Nick's .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/cherylui/</link>
      <description>I’ve talked a lot in the past about how XAML applications lend themselves to being styled using data and control templates. The Uno Platform, which defaults to the Fluent theme, also supports Material, which adjusts the control templates for the in-box controls according to the Material theme from Google. In this post we’re going to ... Read more</description>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/cherylui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Major Rule About Cooking Meat Turns out to Be Wrong</title>
      <link>https://www.seriouseats.com/meat-resting-science-11776272</link>
      <description>The traditional wisdom says resting meat keeps it juicy. But when we put that idea to the test, we found a different reason to rest—one that has nothing to do with juice.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/seriouseats)</author>
      <guid>https://www.seriouseats.com/meat-resting-science-11776272</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Promised LAN</title>
      <link>https://tpl.house/</link>
      <description>The Internet sucks, build a LAN</description>
      <guid>https://tpl.house/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aspire Roadmap (2025 → 2026) · dotnet/aspire · Discussion #10644</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/discussions/10644</link>
      <description>Hi everyone 💫 We’ve had so much fun building, learning, and Aspirifying with you over the last year. As many of you have noticed, there are lots of exciting things in the works, and we figured it w...</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/discussions/10644</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Barrel Rate with Fast Swing Rate – Running on Numbers</title>
      <link>https://runningonnumbers.com/posts/fast-swings-and-barrels/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will explore the relationship between swing speed and barrel rate in Major League Baseball (MLB) players. Barrel rate is a key metric that measures the percentage of batted balls that are classified as “barrels,” which are hits with a high probability of resulting in extra-base hits. According to MLB, batted-ball events classified as Barrels had lead to a “minium 0.500 batting average and 1.500 slugging percentage” “Standard Stats  Glossary” (2025). By understanding how swing speed impacts barrel rate, we can gain insights into player performance and potentially identify areas for improvement. We will use a linear regression model but with an added twist: we will apply a square root transformation to capture non-linear relationships between swing speed and barrel rate. I refer you to my previous article on linear regressions for a refresher on the topic.</description>
      <guid>https://runningonnumbers.com/posts/fast-swings-and-barrels/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Question Driven Development</title>
      <link>https://kinduff.com/2025/05/22/question-driven-development/</link>
      <description>A reflection on the importance of asking the right questions in software development.</description>
      <guid>https://kinduff.com/2025/05/22/question-driven-development/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:05:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You shouldn't need to write a scraper just to list the available electives</title>
      <link>https://varun.ch/posts/elective-list/</link>
      <description>An explanation of how I built a simple web tool to visualise and navigate the University of Waterloo’s confusing course listings, making elective selection easier for first-year students (like myself).</description>
      <guid>https://varun.ch/posts/elective-list/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:05:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>