<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>New Coding Short Video: Should You Be Using Vue&amp;#39;s Composition API?</title>
      <link>https://wildermuth.com/2021/06/13/New-Coding-Short-Video-Should-You-Be-Using-Vue-s-Composition-API</link>
      <description>New Coding Short Video: Should You Be Using Vue&amp;#39;s Composition API?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wildermuth.com/2021/06/13/New-Coding-Short-Video-Should-You-Be-Using-Vue-s-Composition-API</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 01:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Learn</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/?WT.mc_id=learnaka</link>
      <description>The skills required to advance your career and earn your spot at the top do not come easily. Now there’s a more rewarding approach to hands-on learning that helps you achieve your goals faster. Earn points, levels, and achieve more!</description>
      <author> (adkinn)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/?WT.mc_id=learnaka</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 01:03:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Freenode</title>
      <link>https://nedbatchelder.com/blog/202106/goodbye_freenode.html</link>
      <description>For the last month or so, the IRC world has been embroiled in drama over the new ownership of Freenode. For me, it culminated yesterday when I was banned from Freenode.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nedbatchelder.com/blog/202106/goodbye_freenode.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 01:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>kevingosse/ClrMDExports</title>
      <link>https://github.com/kevingosse/ClrMDExports/</link>
      <description>Contribute to kevingosse/ClrMDExports development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (kevingosse)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/kevingosse/ClrMDExports/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 23:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClrMDExports 2.0.0-rc1</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/ClrMDExports/2.0.0-rc1</link>
      <description>Helper library to create extensions for WinDbg/LLDB using ClrMD.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/ClrMDExports/2.0.0-rc1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 23:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image color replacement with numerical optimization</title>
      <link>https://andersource.dev/2021/06/12/image-color-replacement.html</link>
      <description>Numerical Optimization course final project</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andersource.dev/2021/06/12/image-color-replacement.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 22:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Places Lists | Robert Silvernail&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>http://robertsilvernail.com/best-places-lists/</link>
      <description>I just read through another “Best Places” list.  This one was the Top 25 Tax-Friendly States to Retire, by Yahoo News.  If you have too much time on your hands, you scroll though the article and envision yourself in one of these states.  If your currently live in a high tax state (as I do in California, which is not on the Yahoo Top 25 list), you think, “Wow!  I could drastically cut my tax bill and give myself a big raise if I moved to one of these states!”  However, before you call your real estate broker to list your house and Bekins Moving to move your stuff, there are a lot of factors to consider aside from taxes when you decide where you want to live during retirement.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://robertsilvernail.com/best-places-lists/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 22:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On surveillance through face recognition</title>
      <link>https://danuker.go.ro/on-surveillance-through-face-recognition.html</link>
      <description>A year ago, a Black man was arrested for theft. The evidence was crummy face-recognition coupled with a security guard&amp;#39;s ID who had not seen the person, only a security tape. A few months ago, some civil rights organizations filed a lawsuit against the Detroit Police Department for the wrongful …</description>
      <author> (Dan Gheorghe Haiduc)</author>
      <guid>https://danuker.go.ro/on-surveillance-through-face-recognition.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 22:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hey, so, I Think I Fucking Hate the Internet — No Octothorpe</title>
      <link>https://nooctothorpe.squarespace.com/blog/2021/6/4/hey-so-i-think-i-fucking-hate-the-internet</link>
      <description>Blaise Pascal, writing in&amp;amp;nbsp; Pens&amp;#233;es :   All of humanity&amp;#39;s problems stem from man&amp;#39;s inability to sit quietly in a room alone.   I’ve got a Safari window open behind this&amp;amp;nbsp;  Craft  &amp;amp;nbsp;draft (there&amp;#39;s no great portmanteau here, though that won&amp;#39;t prevent me from desperately searchi</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nooctothorpe.squarespace.com/blog/2021/6/4/hey-so-i-think-i-fucking-hate-the-internet</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 22:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fidenza — Tyler Hobbs</title>
      <link>https://tylerxhobbs.com/fidenza</link>
      <description>Fidenza is my most versatile generative algorithm to date. Although it is not overly complex, the core structures of the algorithm are highly flexible, allowing for enough variety to produce continuously surprising results. I consider this to be one of the most interesting ways to evaluate the quality of a generative algorithm, and certainly one that is unique to the medium. Striking the right balance of unpredictability and quality is a difficult challenge for even the best artists in this field. This is why I’m so excited that Fidenza is being showcased on Art Blocks, the only site in existence that perfectly suits generative art and raises the bar for developing these kinds of high-quality generative art algorithms.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tylerxhobbs.com/fidenza</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 22:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Starting a Business</title>
      <link>https://www.hardymariner.com/on-starting-a-business/</link>
      <description>Much has been written about starting a company or a &amp;quot;startup&amp;quot; by media and online gurus trying to sell a course.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hardymariner.com/on-starting-a-business/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are we running out of tweets?</title>
      <link>https://mco.dev/are-we-running-out-of-tweets/</link>
      <description>Twitter’s 280 character limit raises an interesting question: how many tweets are possible before nothing new can be said?</description>
      <author> (Marc Cohen)</author>
      <guid>https://mco.dev/are-we-running-out-of-tweets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 22:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pastes.glitchwrks.com/L88HFhJs</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pastes.glitchwrks.com/L88HFhJs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 21:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Handle Secrets on the Command Line</title>
      <link>https://smallstep.com/blog/command-line-secrets/</link>
      <description>How to keep secret credentials safe on the command line.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://smallstep.com/blog/command-line-secrets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 21:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every trailer and announcement from Microsoft and Bethesda’s E3 showcase</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2021/06/every-trailer-and-announcement-from-microsoft-and-bethesdas-e3-showcase/?utm_social-type=owned</link>
      <description>Halo! Forza! Psychonauts!  Age of Empires!  And dozens of other games, too!</description>
      <author> (Kyle Orland
    -  6/13/2021, 12:47 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2021/06/every-trailer-and-announcement-from-microsoft-and-bethesdas-e3-showcase/?utm_social-type=owned</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 21:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCstock2021 - The Grooviest Event for Security Operations Professionals</title>
      <link>https://www.socstock2021.com/?hss_channel=tw-887942292111228928</link>
      <description>SOCstock is a free-to-attend, one-day global virtual event from Siemplify and friends featuring speakers and attendees who are tackling the biggest challenges facing the security operations industry with the most moving ideas.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.socstock2021.com/?hss_channel=tw-887942292111228928</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 21:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Week on My Mac: The elephant at WWDC</title>
      <link>https://eclecticlight.co/2021/06/13/last-week-on-my-mac-the-elephant-at-wwdc/</link>
      <description>Every developer should watch the 5 videos about DocC from WWDC. But it’s really a plaintive cry for help. Until Apple squares up and addresses the problem, it can only grow worse.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://eclecticlight.co/2021/06/13/last-week-on-my-mac-the-elephant-at-wwdc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 19:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine Magnetic Powers #Shorts</title>
      <link>https://yewtu.be/watch?v=RRkaWQJFkBQ</link>
      <description>Why should I be exposed to so much nonsense?! They are making me old! Stop believing fake garbage!!#Shorts</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yewtu.be/watch?v=RRkaWQJFkBQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 18:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detect services based on service provider by davidfowl &amp;#183; Pull Request #32737 &amp;#183; dotnet/aspnetcore</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspnetcore/pull/32737</link>
      <description>Added an IServiceProvider argument to RequestDelegateFactory.Create
As a final fallback, try to detect services from the DI container before falling back to body behavior.

There are some gotchas:
...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspnetcore/pull/32737</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 17:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I miss the old internet</title>
      <link>https://www.sffworld.com/forum/threads/i-miss-the-old-internet.57195/</link>
      <description>Is it just me or is today&amp;#39;s internet boring and overly commercialized? I feel like today&amp;#39;s internet is like a modern mall, sterile and boring with just main-brand clothing stores, a food court, and not a lot else. Whereas I feel like the old internet was more like an exciting urban playground...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sffworld.com/forum/threads/i-miss-the-old-internet.57195/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 17:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced console.log Tips &amp;amp; Tricks</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/nmc-techblog/advanced-console-log-tips-tricks-fa3762930bca</link>
      <description>There is more than just console.log()</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@liadshiran92)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/nmc-techblog/advanced-console-log-tips-tricks-fa3762930bca</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 16:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Modern Mathematics of Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2105.04026</link>
      <description>We describe the new field of mathematical analysis of deep learning. This
field emerged around a list of research questions that were not answered within
the classical framework of learning theory. These questions concern: the
outstanding generalization power of overparametrized neural networks, the role
of depth in deep architectures, the apparent absence of the curse of
dimensionality, the surprisingly successful optimization performance despite
the non-convexity of the problem, understanding what features are learned, why
deep architectures perform exceptionally well in physical problems, and which
fine aspects of an architecture affect the behavior of a learning task in which
way. We present an overview of modern approaches that yield partial answers to
these questions. For selected approaches, we describe the main ideas in more
detail.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 9 May 2021])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2105.04026</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 15:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QNAP removes backdoor account in NAS backup, disaster recovery app</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qnap-removes-backdoor-account-in-nas-backup-disaster-recovery-app/</link>
      <description>QNAP has addressed a critical vulnerability allowing attackers to log into QNAP&amp;#160;NAS (network-attached storage) devices using hardcoded credentials.</description>
      <author> (Sergiu Gatlan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qnap-removes-backdoor-account-in-nas-backup-disaster-recovery-app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 14:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is software development really a dead-end job after age 35-40?</title>
      <link>https://www.quora.com/Is-software-development-really-a-dead-end-job-after-age-35-40</link>
      <description>Last year, my 45th, having just left Facebook and then taking a break, I wound up running a number of interviews and doing really horribly, until I found the right discipline for the eclectic set of skills I’ve developed over these years. The cutoff varies, depending on your time in the industry. Since I skipped college and went straight into the business, it really started around 40 for me. The work is there, the opportunities are there, but the interviews and expectations on you change. People are going to want more expertise and knowledge out of you than key-pressing. They’re going to expect an architect, an engineer, a solutions designer, an instructor, a risk analyzer, a mentor.. “I like to get my hands dirty” stops implying team player and starts suggesting “micro-manager” or under-development of your engineering skills (this candidate won’t build our new micro-service architecture, instead manually write html files at 10 words per minute while telling us all about the new hotness in apache from 6 years ago). The angle of many of your interviews is going to change. Your adaptability, enthusiasm for learning, those are obstacles as you shift from talking to junior managers to hiring managers and executives and CTOs. You’re also going to be increasingly likely to be interviewed as a team-match by people who are (perhaps not aware they’re going to be) junior to you. I had several Google all-day Google interviews last year which were some of the best/worst I’ve ever experienced. Acing thru the big-picture interviews, I struggled bitterly in the key-word-matching-disguised-as-coding-interview tests: The interviewer presents a fairly trivial problem with no context. ([edit] And when they say ‘imagine you’re working with a co-worker’ in these: Would you tolerate that from a co-worker? What am I, stack overflow incarnate?) Or they present a fairly specific yet abstract problem and propose a skeleton approach: “Oh, I wouldn’t take this approach because REALLY GOOD REASONS”. The interviewer feels the top of their head: was that static or a really low flying aircraft? “We could come back to that, but lets start with this”. Great: I wrote a multi-tasking operating system in assembler at the age of 14 and you want me to slog thru this 101 problem and say “linked list” at the right moment so you can ask me “when would a linked list be bad”, I can try not to quip “when it has you using it” and then you can say “what if we had billions of entries”. In these interviews I try to remember the consultants I&amp;#39;ve had to work with. Knew all the high-level jargon but couldn&amp;#39;t tell you how a pointer works. That doesn&amp;#39;t make it any less uncomfortable knowing we&amp;#39;re going to waste 45 minutes obtaining phone-screen level stuff by someone who engages you as though Linked Lists are special magic. As an interviewee, this is incredibly difficult because I&amp;#39;m applying for a senior role, and now 45 minutes of my window is spent discussing linked lists 101. What makes this grate so badly is that sense of being on a rail. I asked one interviewer: Would you have used a linked list to solve the first problem? Oh no, it obviously wouldn&amp;#39;t scale. Do you know I&amp;#39;m interviewing for a senior position? I&amp;#39;m filling in for another interviewer, I&amp;#39;m not exactly sure what position we&amp;#39;re interviewing you for, I wouldn&amp;#39;t have expected a senior to struggle so much with the initial linked-list problem. He wouldn&amp;#39;t have used a linked list to solve his own linked-list problem... If this was a co-worker, I&amp;#39;d sit them down and walk them through applications and concerns with doubly vs single, circular, intrusive vs non-intrusive, figure out what facet of their requirement I’ve missed or they haven’t expressed, or what the gap in their knowledge is. In some of these 101 questions, I&amp;#39;ve actually been able to do this - come off the rail, so to speak - and that&amp;#39;s actually been great. But, again: It all comes back down to the fear that you&amp;#39;re losing 45 minutes of your window to someone&amp;#39;s script. Again: it’s the rail. It’s like being asked to do finger painting while you wait for a real interviewer. I would certainly have reservations about hiring someone who did well in one of those interviews. Seriously? You chose an algorithmX to solve that problem? And you had to have a back-and-forth with the interviewer to finally decide to use an algorithmY to solve it for stage 2 and algorithmZ to solve it for stage 3? Yeesh. A bigger challenge, the bigger the company, is the interviewers recognizing that you&amp;#39;re being interviewed because you stand out in some field; that you might be a peer. During my last round with Google, I didn’t do so well. One engineer asked me to write a very specific application, continually declined requests to clarify what part of the app he might want me to focus on, bemoaned my outlining the scope of what he’d just presented me, and then let me fall into a “well, this part is the most complex, so I’m going there” trap. Ultimately, he explicitly wanted to discuss a single function of a mundane part of the app. After the interview was officially over, he indicated that he had worked on the reference implementation of this part and had recently rewritten it with the “X Y Z algorithm” - wait: I mentioned that during the first 5 minutes of the interview! “No, you said X Z Y”. A second facet of this manifests in the sort of cloak-and-daggery aspect of people using storied examples. It can be challenging to get them to recognize &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m interviewing here precisely because I know about this kind of thing&amp;quot;. In two other cases, the engineers were put-off by my recognition of the problem and assumed I had “had this one before”. Seriously? You’ve read my resume, and you chose a question based on my experience, and then you are *surprised* that I say “oh this?” The first came in and sketched a distributed multi-process debugging problem, and I jokingly said “like, hunt the ooming java process?” He looked offended. But went ahead and gave me a 5 minute explanation of the system. I summarized “So it’s an ad-market with a web-based front end?” I spent a few seconds double-checking I had not just said something awful about his mother. I took a minute to make him aware we were on the same page because experience, and he responded really well to that. Asked me to walk him thru my thinking. But, tbh, I was frustrated at this point, so I gambled on instead showing him a totally different approach that I would build or work with producers/managers to get the engineers to build-in themselves. I wanted to get away from the “you read this on stack overflow” suspicion. Instead of treating this as a one-time issue, I identified it as a recurring issue, he argued but I pointed out: we’ve *both* done this multiple times. We know what the cause is, it’s the where and restoration-of-service that we care about. Ok, he bought that. At the end he confided that this was completely not what they were looking for in this particular question, but that he’d never had a candidate present the approach I had and that he’d actually be rethinking the question entirely. It was a difficult interview session, largely because the interviewer seemed so reluctant to consider that someone who hadn&amp;#39;t worked at Google yet could have experienced a scenario like this. The second case … Presented me with a nice solid practical problem. A variation of something I’ve had to deal with in several scenarios, but he again seemed unaware of that. This bewilders me, because translating solutions into metaphors so that they can be reapplied is a basic aspect of engineering. In retrospect, he became increasingly annoyed as I moved towards a subtly different path than the one he seemed to be pushing for, with me - at the time - misreading the pushes as discussion bait. Ultimately I arrived close to his solution with a few improvements that he credited to his guidance. His final good humor fell away during the post-interview, when I pointed out that those improvements were specifically this point I’d made and that point I’d made, and that I’d been aiming towards this particular set of approaches from the offset (pointing to one of them still on the board). He specifically intimated that, because that wasn’t the system he’d implemented 10 years ago, we couldn’t know if it would have been better. [edit] I describe the above poorly, he&amp;#39;d specifically asked for feedback, and I was describing like he&amp;#39;d been trying to push me to a particular goal. Ultimately, this was a solved problem to both of us, but this interviewer just wasn’t ready to actually be challenged on it. His solution was elegant and simple; mine was similar with with a twist rather than an increment in complexity. It also involved an informed gamble that gave it more longevity than his. -Edit: This interviewer opened saying that he wanted us to treat this as an active problem we were trying to solve, working together with myself as lead to evaluate the level of seniority I was suited for. At each step he acknowledged the directions. The problem is either an unwillingness by an engineer to see someone else has already solved their problem (a common conceit among the big tech companies) or they didn’t believe my resume and were expecting a vastly less experienced engineer that they would prove to be a fraud through not knowing the word “linked list”. In either case, it’s agonizingly painful, [edit] and something worth finding a way to practice and prepare for. Attending conventions is a good way to find peers to challenge yourself with. I told one interviewer: How much do you know about modern CPU architecture? Because if what matters to you is whether I have a linked list implementation in L1 cache rather than RAM full of years of practical experience, knowledge of the various different implementations, plus intrusive vs non-intrusive caveats, cache coherence implications, etc, etc… We can stop here. I’ve discovered that in many of these scenarios, the interviewer is possibly overwhelmed or uncomfortable with your level of experience to the degree they struggle to find a common ground, and the interview is largely an attempt to try and figure out some way that they can disprove your claims or map your experience onto theirs. Have a couple of interesting problems up your sleeve. If you sit down and work on a meaningful project, you would do far better together than trying to randomly figure out an algorithm or data-structure you can sit around and discuss like a water-cooler conversation. The key to success, for me, came in finding companies that were capable of being interview*ed*. When I interviewed at Facebook in 2014, that was still very much the case, and Facebook’s interviews, although nail biting, were also utterly engaging. Google, LinkedIn, and some of the other big-tech companies, the entire process seems to presume you are a bug under a microscope. The slightest indication you might be looking back and you scare or anger them off. You can probably expect more churn, you’ll need more persistence and patience, but it’s not because the work is no-longer there.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.quora.com/Is-software-development-really-a-dead-end-job-after-age-35-40</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 14:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s Encrypt</title>
      <link>https://letsencrypt.org/</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s Encrypt is a free, automated, and open certificate authority brought to you by the nonprofit Internet Security Research Group (ISRG).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://letsencrypt.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 14:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&amp;#39;s next generation of Windows — What we know so far</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsofts-next-generation-of-windows-what-we-know-so-far/</link>
      <description>Microsoft will soon reveal their next generation of Windows at an upcoming press event later this month. Here is what we know so far about Microsoft&amp;#39;s new version of Windows.</description>
      <author> (Mayank Parmar)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsofts-next-generation-of-windows-what-we-know-so-far/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 14:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taildrop was kind of easy, actually</title>
      <link>https://tailscale.com/blog/2021-06-taildrop-was-easy/</link>
      <description>Taildrop was the first test of an experimental p2p app discovery layer in Tailscale. Let us talk about why it was so easy to build, and where we go from here.</description>
      <author> (Tailscale)</author>
      <guid>https://tailscale.com/blog/2021-06-taildrop-was-easy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elevator Saga - the elevator programming game</title>
      <link>https://play.elevatorsaga.com/</link>
      <description>Wiki &amp;amp; Solutions
            Documentation
            Help</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://play.elevatorsaga.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 12:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Print-in-place ATAT Print on Twotrees Bluer plus</title>
      <link>https://yewtu.be/watch?v=hv90qwgkzS8</link>
      <description>STL- https://fab365.net/items/229Requests from FAB365.net have received numerous requests from customers. Among them, there are the most requests for Star Wa...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yewtu.be/watch?v=hv90qwgkzS8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 11:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.1.0 &amp;#183; natemcmaster/LettuceEncrypt</title>
      <link>https://github.com/natemcmaster/LettuceEncrypt/releases/tag/v1.1.0</link>
      <description>Notes
New features:

Add API for controlling whether HTTP-01, TLS-ALPN-01, or both challenge types are used (#197)
create abstraction for SNI certificates in Kestrel (#108)
add API to configure Let...</description>
      <author> (natemcmaster)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/natemcmaster/LettuceEncrypt/releases/tag/v1.1.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 09:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source and Mental Health - Redox</title>
      <link>https://www.redox-os.org/news/open-source-mental-health/</link>
      <description>The Redox official website</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.redox-os.org/news/open-source-mental-health/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 07:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC FixMan – Earn BTC for fixing python exceptions</title>
      <link>https://fixexception.com/tournaments/</link>
      <description>Participate Bitcon Tournament for fixing exceptions. Free in!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fixexception.com/tournaments/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 06:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Answering Community Questions and What’s Ahead for Mina</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/minaprotocol/answering-community-questions-and-whats-ahead-for-mina-d771fa94489b</link>
      <description>By Evan Shapiro, O(1) Labs CEO &amp;amp; Mina Foundation Board Member</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@minaprotocol)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/minaprotocol/answering-community-questions-and-whats-ahead-for-mina-d771fa94489b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 03:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>