<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Team Fortress 2 source code has leaked, and you can apparently get malware by playing</title>
      <link>https://www.techradar.com/uk/news/team-fortress-2-source-code-has-leaked-and-you-can-apparently-get-malware-by-playing</link>
      <description>Remote Code Execution is being reported</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/TechRadar)</author>
      <guid>https://www.techradar.com/uk/news/team-fortress-2-source-code-has-leaked-and-you-can-apparently-get-malware-by-playing</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 03:12:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVP Program</title>
      <link>https://www.digicert.com/friends/msmvp/</link>
      <description>When you visit our website, we store cookies on your browser to collect information. The information collected might relate to you, your preferences or your device, and is mostly used to make the site work as you expect it to and to provide a more personalized web experience. However, you can choose not to allow certain types of cookies, which may impact your experience of the site and the services we are able to offer. Click on the different category headings to find out more and change our default settings according to your preference. You cannot opt-out of our First Party Strictly Necessary Cookies as they are deployed in order to ensure the proper functioning of our website (such as prompting the cookie banner and remembering your settings, to log into your account, to redirect you when you log out, etc.). For more information about the First and Third Party Cookies used please follow this link.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.digicert.com/friends/msmvp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 01:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‎The Numberphile Podcast: The Accidental Streamer - with 3blue1brown on Apple Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/the-numberphile-podcast/id1441474794?i=1000471941740</link>
      <description>‎Show The Numberphile Podcast, Ep The Accidental Streamer - with 3blue1brown - 19 Apr 2020</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/the-numberphile-podcast/id1441474794?i=1000471941740</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 23:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosting Blazor Applications on GitHub Pages - MikaBerglund.com</title>
      <link>https://mikaberglund.com/2019/12/29/hosting-blazor-applications-on-github-pages/</link>
      <description>GitHub Pages provides free storage for static websites. With a little tweeking, a Blazor WebAssembly application can be published to GitHub Pages too.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/mikaberglund)</author>
      <guid>https://mikaberglund.com/2019/12/29/hosting-blazor-applications-on-github-pages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 22:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telerik UI for Blazor 2.11.0: New Grid Features &amp; Much More!</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-for-blazor-2-11-0-grid-features-scheduler-improvements-wasm-3-2-0-preview-4-more#disqus_thread</link>
      <description>Telerik UI for Blazor 2.11.0 now includes Grid Nested Models, Automatic Column Generation, Column Virtualization, Support for WebAssembly 3.2.0 Preview 4!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-for-blazor-2-11-0-grid-features-scheduler-improvements-wasm-3-2-0-preview-4-more#disqus_thread</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MikaBerglund.com - Developing for Microsoft Azure and Office 365</title>
      <link>https://mikaberglund.com/</link>
      <description>Developing for Microsoft Azure and Office 365</description>
      <author> (Mika Berglund)</author>
      <guid>https://mikaberglund.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 22:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call MS Graph APIs from ASP.NET Core 3.1</title>
      <link>https://cmatskas.com/call-ms-graph-apis-from-asp-net-core-3-1/</link>
      <description>As I spend more time in my role as a PM for Microsoft Identity, the more I realize there is a whole world I don't know about. And as many of the developers out there, I make sure I spend as much time as I can learning new things. Today's</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cmatskas.com/call-ms-graph-apis-from-asp-net-core-3-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 22:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our data centers now work harder when the sun shines and wind blows</title>
      <link>https://blog.google/inside-google/infrastructure/data-centers-work-harder-sun-shines-wind-blows</link>
      <description>Today we’re announcing a carbon-intelligent computing platform, which can shift tasks to hours of the day when energy from cleaner power sources is plentiful.</description>
      <author> (Ana Radovanovic

    
      
        Technical Lead for Carbon-Intelligent Computing)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.google/inside-google/infrastructure/data-centers-work-harder-sun-shines-wind-blows</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 21:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Home &amp; End keys behave like Windows on Mac OS X</title>
      <link>https://damieng.com/blog/2015/04/24/make-home-end-keys-behave-like-windows-on-mac-os-x</link>
      <description>I’ve been using Mac OS X daily since 2001 when I purchased my Titanium PowerBook and I still can’t get used the home and end key behavior.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://damieng.com/blog/2015/04/24/make-home-end-keys-behave-like-windows-on-mac-os-x</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Leap reportedly slashes 1,000 jobs and steps away from consumer plans – TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2020/04/22/magic-leap-announces-layoffs-amid-covid-19-slowdown/</link>
      <description>Magic Leap laid off a “number of employees” this morning and announced they were backing away from their consumer ambitions to focus more heavily on selling to enterprise customers. Bloomberg reports that half of Magic Leap’s employees were laid off, roughly 1,000 in total. Magic …</description>
      <author> (Brian Heater, Lucas Matney / 8:49 am PDT • April 22, 2020comment Comment)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2020/04/22/magic-leap-announces-layoffs-amid-covid-19-slowdown/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Framework</title>
      <link>https://www.phoenixframework.org/blog/build-a-real-time-twitter-clone-in-15-minutes-with-live-view-and-phoenix-1-5</link>
      <description>Posted on April 22nd, 2020 by Chris McCord</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.phoenixframework.org/blog/build-a-real-time-twitter-clone-in-15-minutes-with-live-view-and-phoenix-1-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's New in Skype for Windows, Mac, Linux and Web? | Skype Support</title>
      <link>https://support.skype.com/en/faq/FA34778/what-s-new-in-skype-for-windows-mac-linux-and-web</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://support.skype.com/en/faq/FA34778/what-s-new-in-skype-for-windows-mac-linux-and-web</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating and Packaging a .NET Standard library | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/creating-and-packaging-net-standard-library/</link>
      <description>In this post we will cover how you can create a .NET Standard library and then share that with other developers via NuGet. We will be demonstrating this with Visual Studio for Mac, but you can also follow along with Visual Studio,</description>
      <author> (Sayed HashimiSenior Program Manager, Visual Studio for MacFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/creating-and-packaging-net-standard-library/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLab</title>
      <link>https://sharplab.io/#v2:EYLgZgpghgLgrgJwgZwLRIMaOQSwG4SoAOsMECAdsgDQwgJwUA+AAgEwCMAsAFC/sACFhwDsAgN68B0oRwBsQgCwCAslBwUAFAEoJUmQYCSHATgEBeARQgB3AQCEdAbn0HpOAHQrnAgPS+BACJ7QNcBAF9eSL4eDTIEMCgMCAFjXkkeAxZlb20XHmj+NgEAQQEQVO4eDOlsyq8dCwA+WQBOTUCSwLyo3iKHctLqSvT9OuMG3XMW4Xbg7vzCniA==</link>
      <description>C#/VB/F# compiler playground.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sharplab.io/#v2:EYLgZgpghgLgrgJwgZwLRIMaOQSwG4SoAOsMECAdsgDQwgJwUA+AAgEwCMAsAFC/sACFhwDsAgN68B0oRwBsQgCwCAslBwUAFAEoJUmQYCSHATgEBeARQgB3AQCEdAbn0HpOAHQrnAgPS+BACJ7QNcBAF9eSL4eDTIEMCgMCAFjXkkeAxZlb20XHmj+NgEAQQEQVO4eDOlsyq8dCwA+WQBOTUCSwLyo3iKHctLqSvT9OuMG3XMW4Xbg7vzCniA==</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 19:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home | The Permanent Legacy Foundation - The Permanent Legacy Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.permanent.org/</link>
      <description>Become a Founding Supporter</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.permanent.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 19:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things I Wished More Developers Knew About Databases</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@rakyll/things-i-wished-more-developers-knew-about-databases-2d0178464f78</link>
      <description>A large majority of computer systems have some state and are likely to depend on a storage system. My knowledge on databases accumulated…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@rakyll)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@rakyll/things-i-wished-more-developers-knew-about-databases-2d0178464f78</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 18:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EF Core Power Tools - Visual Studio Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=ErikEJ.EFCorePowerTools</link>
      <description>Getting Started | Feedback</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=ErikEJ.EFCorePowerTools</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 18:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Terminal Preview v0.11 Release | Windows Command Line</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/windows-terminal-preview-v0-11-release/</link>
      <description>We are back with one last major update before the 1.0 release of Windows Terminal! Releases between now and then will be revisions of this version. This is the v0.11 release and you can download the Terminal from the Microsoft Store or from the GitHub releases page.</description>
      <author> (Kayla CinnamonProgram Manager, Windows Terminal, Console, Command Line, &amp; Cascadia CodeFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/windows-terminal-preview-v0-11-release/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 18:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>wizard zines</title>
      <link>https://wizardzines.com/zines/networking/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wizardzines.com/zines/networking/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 17:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to find cause of high kernel_task cpu usage?</title>
      <link>https://apple.stackexchange.com/questions/363337/how-to-find-cause-of-high-kernel-task-cpu-usage/363933</link>
      <description>Occasionally my machine will have a kernel_task instance max out the CPU:
This can last from minutes to sometimes hours. The machine is effectively unusable in this state. Restarting doesn't help;...</description>
      <author> (Adam)</author>
      <guid>https://apple.stackexchange.com/questions/363337/how-to-find-cause-of-high-kernel-task-cpu-usage/363933</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 17:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telerik UI for Blazor - UI for Blazor 2.11.0</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/support/whats-new/blazor-ui/release-history/ui-for-blazor-2-11-0</link>
      <description>UI for Blazor 2.11.0 - Review Telerik UI for Blazor release in detail. Check out full release history for more info about new controls and functionalities.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/support/whats-new/blazor-ui/release-history/ui-for-blazor-2-11-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 14:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conversations with a six-year-old on functional programming</title>
      <link>https://byorgey.wordpress.com/2018/05/06/conversations-with-a-six-year-old-on-functional-programming/</link>
      <description>My six-year-old son walked up to me yesterday. “What are you reading?” At the time, I was reading part of Janis Voigtländer’s habilitation thesis. Unsure where to even start, I decided to just ans…</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://byorgey.wordpress.com/2018/05/06/conversations-with-a-six-year-old-on-functional-programming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 14:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patreon lays off 13% of workforce – TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2020/04/21/patreon-lays-off-13-of-workforce/</link>
      <description>Creative platform Patreon has laid off 30 employees, which is 13% of its workforce, TechCrunch has learned. “It is unclear how long this economic uncertainty will last and therefore, to prepare accordingly, we have made the difficult decision to part ways with 13% of Patreon’s workforce,&amp;#822…</description>
      <author> (Megan Rose Dickey@meganrosedickey / 2:13 pm PDT • April 21, 2020comment Comment)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2020/04/21/patreon-lays-off-13-of-workforce/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering code quality in the Firefox browser: A look at our tools and challenges – Mozilla Hacks - the Web developer blog</title>
      <link>https://hacks.mozilla.org/2020/04/code-quality-tools-at-mozilla/</link>
      <description>Here's an insider's look at Firefox's code quality toolchain that's been designed to manage the ongoing development and monthly releases of our desktop browser. This post explores the architecture, challenges, ...</description>
      <author> (https://nextcairn.com@La0)</author>
      <guid>https://hacks.mozilla.org/2020/04/code-quality-tools-at-mozilla/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Miller's answer to Why are Soviet mathematics/physics textbooks so insanely hardcore in comparison to US textbooks?</title>
      <link>https://www.quora.com/Why-are-Soviet-mathematics-physics-textbooks-so-insanely-hardcore-in-comparison-to-US-textbooks/answer/Scott-Miller-307?share=1</link>
      <description>There are a lot of good points being made in this thread. I have had a theory that it is in part related to the funding available for lab equipment and computers. During the latter half of the 20th century, in Russia you were very lucky to get access to a “real” computer. I spent some time in 1992 in Protvino, RU, a science city of (at the time) some 20,000 scientists and engineers. The city hadn’t been listed on any official map from the USSR, even though it had existed since 1958; it was devoted to a large synchrotron. I was really struck by the contrast between the super-abundance of material resources to get the job done in the US and EU, vs. the creativity and thought by the Russians. At the risk of oversimplifying, I noticed that because of the traditional scarcity of equipment, Russian students and scientists had to think rather than experiment, whether with computers or accelerators; it was often all that was available to them. For instance, there was much more of an effort in Protvino to repurpose equipment than to have new equipment machined as I had seen at FermiLab or CERN. The rank and file Russian engineers that I saw in the ’90s were using a home-grown knockoff of the Intel 8088 series. The managers got imported IBM XTs. At the same time in the US working on the SSC, on my desk I had a SuperSPARC minicomputer, a Mac, and an HP 80486 Windows machine, as well as access to a twin Hypercube. As a result, “computer experiments” like Monte Carlo simulation were not used very often in Protvino except by those for whom it was essential (and often not even then - such experiments were usually pushed down so far in the queue that they never got executed). Rather, there was much more emphasis on closed-form or approximate analytical solutions. Coding up a simulation and having a computer torture it until it confessed the results you wanted certainly takes talent, but it is arguably a different kind of talent than thinking deeply about the problem itself. Thinking about the simulation often leads to thinking that improves the computing methods and hardware used. Thinking about the problem itself gives insight into the nature of the problem itself and its connections with other areas of study. Understanding the problem deeply leads to radically different approaches to the problem - “I noted that there was an SU(n) symmetry in the problem, so I could reduce the computational time by O(nn).” A group theoretical approach might not normally occur to someone that thinks in terms of GPU clusters. Chess was played at multiple tables in every park, not just in the “Science City.” And like others have mentioned in this thread, Mir publishers are great. They were cheap and very well-written. The only disadvantage were they were printed on a paper so thin that you could see the printing from the other side through it. This made the books less expensive and got more pages per meter on the bookshelf. The local Protvino bookshops had all kinds of math and science tracts. I filled my luggage with as many of these as I could carry.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.quora.com/Why-are-Soviet-mathematics-physics-textbooks-so-insanely-hardcore-in-comparison-to-US-textbooks/answer/Scott-Miller-307?share=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running ML.NET + Notebooks in Azure Machine Learning Studio</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-ai/running-ml-net-notebooks-in-azure-machine-learning-studio/ba-p/1323238</link>
      <description>Time Series Forecasting in ML.NET and Notebooks in Azure ML Studio In this sample, learn how to run time series forecasting in a Jupyter notebook. We will read in data from a csv file, do some exploratory plots, fit a regression model, and fit a more sophisticated Singular Spectrum Analysis (SSA) fo...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/625570)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-ai/running-ml-net-notebooks-in-azure-machine-learning-studio/ba-p/1323238</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo 64 Architecture | A Practical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://copetti.org/projects/consoles/nintendo-64/</link>
      <description>An in-depth analysis that explains how this console works internally</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://copetti.org/projects/consoles/nintendo-64/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity Framework Core Part 3</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Entity-Framework-Core-Part-3</link>
      <description>In this episode, Robert is joined by Phil Japikse for part 3 of a 5 part series on Entity Framework Core. Aimed at folks new to EF Core, Phil shows how to start with an existing SQL Server database, c</description>
      <author> (by Robert Green)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Entity-Framework-Core-Part-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from .NET Framework to .NET Core</title>
      <link>https://codeopinion.com/migrating-from-net-framework-to-net-core/</link>
      <description>This is a blog series covering the topic of migrating from .NET Framework to .NET Core. Topics such as Dependencies (NuGet), BCL, Entity Framework, and more!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://codeopinion.com/migrating-from-net-framework-to-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab — CS-3210, Spring 2020 1 documentation</title>
      <link>https://tc.gts3.org/cs3210/2020/spring/lab.html</link>
      <description>In this course, we are going to build an operating system in
Rust programming language.
The operating system that we will build targets AArch64 (ARM) architecture,
and it will run on Raspberry Pi 3.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tc.gts3.org/cs3210/2020/spring/lab.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tempdb – Here’s a Problem You Didn’t Know You Have - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/sql/performance/tempdb-heres-a-problem-you-didnt-know-you-have/</link>
      <description>Because of its many roles, tempdb is the source of performance issues in SQL Server, and there are recommended configuration changes to mitigate this. In this article, Fabiano Amorim demonstrates another issue with tempdb performance that you probably didn’t know about.</description>
      <author> (Fabiano Amorim)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/sql/performance/tempdb-heres-a-problem-you-didnt-know-you-have/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patterns for Managing Source Code Branches</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/articles/branching-patterns.html#mainline</link>
      <description>Mainline, Feature Branching, Continuous Integration, Release Branch and a clutch of other handy patterns.</description>
      <author> (Martin Fowler)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/articles/branching-patterns.html#mainline</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help us shape the future of deep learning in .NET | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/help-us-shape-the-future-of-deep-learning-in-net/</link>
      <description>Whether you're actively implementing deep learning now or just starting to learn about it, we would love to hear your feedback to shape upcoming support.</description>
      <author> (Brigit MurtaughProgram Manager, .NETFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/help-us-shape-the-future-of-deep-learning-in-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Uno Platform 2.2 - Windows Community Toolkit support, Performance Improvements and more - Uno Platform</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/announcing-uno-platform-2-2-windows-community-toolkit-support-performance-improvements-and-more/</link>
      <description>The Uno 2.2 release is packed with new features, performance improvements and bug fixes, even if it’s closely following the 2.1 release! In addition to expanding our support for Windows Community Toolkit (WCT)  today we are also shipping additional 70 smaller features and performance improvements. If you are following our GitHub repo (hint – you should star it – many more features coming), you may have noticed we are also hard at work on adding support for macOS apps (Thanks @MartinZikmund), and while we still do not have anything to announce, it’s taking shape! The #WinUIEverywhere vision is closer by the day!   About Uno Platform For those new to Uno Platform – it enables for creation of single-source C# and XAML apps which run natively on iOS and Android, and Web via WebAssembly. Uno Platform is Open Source (Apache 2.0) and available on GitHub. To learn more about Uno Platform, see how it works, or create a small sample app. Among the implemented features in this release, you’ll find: Support for MenuFlyout, UIElement.ContextFlyout Support for MenuBar from WinUI 2 Support for ScrollBar Add support for dotnet new unoapp, Visual Studio Code for WebAssembly and macOS templates Support for Electron hosted apps ImageSource.SetSourceAsync support for WebAssembly (Thanks @SuperJMN) Support for ColorAnimation Support …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/announcing-uno-platform-2-2-windows-community-toolkit-support-performance-improvements-and-more/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS CodeBuild Test Reporting with .NET Core | Amazon Web Services</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/aws-codebuild-test-reporting-with-net-core/</link>
      <description>At AWS re:Invent 2019, AWS CodeBuild announced a new test reporting feature which can help make diagnosing test failures in CodeBuild much easier. You can read more about it here. I wanted to use this feature for .NET and after a little research I was able to quickly add support for .NET tests to my […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/aws-codebuild-test-reporting-with-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On WD Red NAS Drives - Western Digital Corporate Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.westerndigital.com/wd-red-nas-drives/</link>
      <description>On WD Red NAS Drives - Tech &amp; Products - Western Digital Corporate Blog</description>
      <author> (Western Digital)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.westerndigital.com/wd-red-nas-drives/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cognitive Services + Xamarin Combo Challenge! | Xamarin Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xamarin/cognitive-services-xamarin-challenge/</link>
      <description>The Cognitive Services + Xamarin Challenge: Combine some Azure Cognitive Services and Xamarin by April 30 and get some amazing Xamarin swag!</description>
      <author> (Matt SoucoupSenior Cloud Developer Advocate, Developer RelationsFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xamarin/cognitive-services-xamarin-challenge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TypeScript Assertion Signatures</title>
      <link>https://www.carlrippon.com/typescript-assertion-signatures/</link>
      <description>How to write a type guard using an assertion signature in TypeScript</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.carlrippon.com/typescript-assertion-signatures/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 06:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four new Google Duo features to help you stay connected</title>
      <link>https://www.blog.google/products/duo/4-new-google-duo-features-help-you-stay-connected/</link>
      <description>A few new features to help you feel close to friends and family even when you’re apart.</description>
      <author> (Dave Citron

    
      
        Group Product Manager, Google Duo)</author>
      <guid>https://www.blog.google/products/duo/4-new-google-duo-features-help-you-stay-connected/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 05:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>98.css</title>
      <link>https://jdan.github.io/98.css/</link>
      <description>A design system for building faithful recreations of old UIs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jdan.github.io/98.css/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 04:51:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>