<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>4 Things I Would Do DIFFERENTLY In My Software Engineering Journey</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=jC0fJ2PCaeA</link>
      <description>Wouldn&amp;#39;t it be cool if you had a time machine?!

Well -- unfortunately that&amp;#39;s not an option.

But what IS an option is sharing lessons that can help others! You might not be able to help yourself directly, but you can help others from your experiences.

In this video, I share 4 things that I would do differently in my software engineering journey if I were to do it again.

----
&amp;#128273; Membership &amp;amp; Subscriptions:
- &amp;#128232; Weekly Newsletter: https://subscribe.devleader.ca
- &amp;#127960;️ Private Discord Community: https://discord.com/invite/TVY79BZ3Wy
- &amp;#128253;️ YouTube Membership: https://www.youtube.com/@DevLeader/join

&amp;#129504; Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?affcode=1115529_nl-teyzg
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?affcode=1115529_nl-teyzg
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?affcode=1115529_nl-teyzg
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?affcode=1115529_nl-teyzg
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?affcode=1115529_nl-teyzg
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?affcode=1115529_nl-teyzg
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

&amp;#128483;️ Social Media &amp;amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs:  @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp;amp; Products/Services That I Love:
- @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper Opus Clip: https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----

#softwareengineering #softwaredeveloper #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=jC0fJ2PCaeA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quartz.NET with ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://malshikay.medium.com/quartz-net-with-asp-net-core-531ad7771245</link>
      <description>How to implement scheduling tasks with Quartz.NET in ASP.NET Core</description>
      <author> (https://malshikay.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://malshikay.medium.com/quartz-net-with-asp-net-core-531ad7771245</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several Russian developers lose kernel maintainership status [LWN.net]</title>
      <link>https://lwn.net/Articles/995186/</link>
      <description>Perhaps one of the more surprising changes in the 6.12-rc4 development
kernel was the removal
of several entries from the kernel&amp;#39;s</description>
      <author> ([Posted October 22, 2024 by corbet])</author>
      <guid>https://lwn.net/Articles/995186/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandwich Helix</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3003/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3003/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 8  .&amp;#128640;&amp;#128293;: Open Telemetry and .NET with Aspire Dashboard &amp;#128293;&amp;#128293;</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wPGsyVQhe2s</link>
      <description>In this video we will discussing Open Telemetry integration 

Support me on Patreon to access the source code:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand

Let us connect:
&amp;#127757;  My website  - https://www.mohamadlawand.com
&amp;#128248;  Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/mohamadlawand087/
&amp;#128038;  Twitter - https://twitter.com/moe23
♯     Github - https://github.com/mohamadlawand087
&amp;#127915; LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/mlawand
&amp;#128165; LinkTree - https://linktr.ee/mohamadlawand
Discord - https://discord.gg/KEepAhxTeu

Gear I use  (affiliate link): https://amzn.to/3EbT8Jw

Support my work:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand
https://www.buymeacoffee.com/mohamadlawand

Hire Me:
https://transactions.sendowl.com/products/78999951/625477F1/view

WHO AM I:
I&amp;#39;m Mohamad, a Enterprise Architect working in Manchester, UK. I make videos about web, cloud, desktop and mobile development. 

GET IN TOUCH:
If you’d like to talk, I’d love to hear from you. Tweeting @moe23 directly will be the quickest way to get a response, but if your question is very long, feel free to email me at hello@mohamadlawand.com.

#dotnet   #api   #opentelemetry</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wPGsyVQhe2s</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Rider is Now Free! Rider vs Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=V17kOlK_F1I</link>
      <description>Check out JetBrains Rider: https://bit.ly/chapsasfreerider
Check out my courses: https://dometrain.com
Subscribe to my weekly newsletter: https://nickchapsas.com

Become a Patreon and get special perks: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsas

Hello, everybody. I&amp;#39;m Nick, and in this video, I will talk about JetBrains Rider becoming free for non-commercial use. This has been something I&amp;#39;ve been waiting for for a long time and it&amp;#39;s finally here!

Workshops: https://bit.ly/nickworkshops

Don&amp;#39;t forget to comment, like and subscribe :)

Social Media:
Follow me on GitHub: https://github.com/Elfocrash
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/nickchapsas
Connect on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick-chapsas

Keep coding merch: https://keepcoding.shop

#csharp #dotnet</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=V17kOlK_F1I</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Introduction to the .NET Muxer (aka dotnet.exe) - Steve Gordon - Code with Steve</title>
      <link>https://www.stevejgordon.co.uk/a-brief-introduction-to-the-dotnet-muxer</link>
      <description>This post introduces the dotnet.exe muxer responsible for loading the runtime and the CLI commands, exploring some of its internal code.</description>
      <author> (Steve Gordon)</author>
      <guid>https://www.stevejgordon.co.uk/a-brief-introduction-to-the-dotnet-muxer</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering Up with Erik Jensen: An Introduction to EF Core Power Tools</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HBgVkellxE4</link>
      <description>Metalama This episode of The Modern .NET Show is supported, in part, by Metalama, reduce your boilerplate code by up to 15% with Metalama&amp;#39;s C#-to-C# template engine and reduce your code complexity today!

 Show Notes Hi everyone,

 Just a quick thing before we start: this episode was recorded in the middle of summer, which meant that Erik needed to have his office window open. It&amp;#39;s possible to hear the outside traffic throughout, but rest assured that our editing team have done what they can to reduce it&amp;#39;s presence.

 It&amp;#39;s not that noticable and shouldn&amp;#39;t affect your enjoyment of the show, but I wanted to give you a heads-up. Also, do remember that there&amp;#39;s a full transcription available at the show&amp;#39;s website; so check that out, too.

 Anyway, let&amp;#39;s get to it.

 &amp;quot;So, I think my mantra for creating things like these tools is, &amp;quot;should be easy to get started and there should be a like an easy happy path but then if you want to deep dive and do a lot of options or even a t4 templates you can also do that,&amp;quot; but there should be a simple happy path with good error reporting if something fails.&amp;quot;— Erik Jensen

 Welcome friends to The Modern .NET Show; the premier .NET podcast, focussing entirely on the knowledge, tools, and frameworks that all .NET developers should have in their toolbox. We are the go-to podcast for .NET developers worldwide, and I am your host: Jamie &amp;quot;GaProgMan&amp;quot; Taylor.

 In this episode, Erik Jensen joined us to talk about EF Core Power Tools, and how you can use his project to increase your productivity with EF Core-based databases, regardless of the database technology used; if it&amp;#39;s supported by EF Core, then the Power Tools extension supports it to.

 &amp;quot;The one that&amp;#39;s definitely used the most is what in a tool is referred to as reverse engineering. Where you point to an existing database, which can be some of the database types I mentioned previously. Like SQL Server, as a SQL database, Postgres, Oracle, MySQL, and Firebird. And then the tool asks you for a number of options, like you can specify what namespaces you&amp;#39;re using, and where the files are laid in your project, and many, many other options. And then when you press OK at that point, as you said, Jamie, the tool generates a DB context and some classes that represent your tables with navigations between the tables based on discovery of foreign key relationships.&amp;quot;— Erik Jensen

 We also briefly touched on the MSBuild.Sdk.SqlProj project and its goal of giving cross-platform .NET developers a way to both describe and build their ideal database schema in code. We also covered Erik&amp;#39;s personal process for dealing with feature requests, and how developers can ensure that that are providing valueable feedback to open-source projects; a subject that will come up again soon with future guest Scott Harden.

 Anyway, without further ado, let&amp;#39;s sit back, open up a terminal, type in `dotnet new podcast` and we&amp;#39;ll dive into the core of Modern .NET.

 Supporting the Show If you find this episode useful in any way, please consider supporting the show by either leaving a review (check our review page for ways to do that), sharing the episode with a friend or colleague, buying the host a coffee, or considering becoming a Patron of the show.

 Full Show Notes The full show notes, including links to some of the things we discussed and a full transcription of this episode, can be found at:  https://dotnetcore.show/season-7/powering-up-with-erik-jensen-an-introduction-to-ef-core-power-tools/

 EF Core Power Tools Contributors The following list is correct as of Oct 4th, 2024, and aims to show that it takes a village to create a tool as ubiquitous as EF Core Power Tools. It contains the top 10 (arranged by number of contributions) devs who have worked on EF Core Power Tools.

  Erik Ejlskov Jensen Stephan Over Varorbc Will 保哥 Pedro Rocha P. Le&amp;#243;n Pratik Pote Emanuele Curati Jonathon Wyza  Useful Links  EF Core Power Tools wiki EF Core Power Tools on GitHub  Install EF Core Power Tools as a .NET global tool XKCD: Dependency DacFx MSBuild.Sdk.SqlProj  Episode 19 - The .NET Foundation with Jon Galloway Connect with Erik on GitHub Connect with Erik on X Erik&amp;#39;s blog Music created by Mono Memory Music, licensed to RJJ Software for use in The Modern .NET Show  Supporting the show:  Leave a rating or review Buy the show a coffee Become a patron  Getting in Touch:  Via the contact page Joining the Discord  Remember to rate and review the show on  Apple Podcasts, Podchaser, or wherever you find your podcasts, this will help the show&amp;#39;s audience grow. Or you can just share the show with a friend.

 And don&amp;#39;t forget to reach out via our Contact page. We&amp;#39;re very interested in your opinion of the show, so please get in touch.

 You can support the show by making a monthly donation on the show&amp;#39;s Patreon page at: https://www.patreon.com/TheDotNetCorePodcast.</description>
      <author> (Jamie Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HBgVkellxE4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 09:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On React Codebases and NextJs</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=iSSAvlrvK6Y</link>
      <description>React codebases are always awful. And NextJs is the most opinionated framework out there right now.</description>
      <author> (Codewrinkles)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=iSSAvlrvK6Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve licensing language (#10) &amp;#183; bitwarden/sdk-internal@db648d7</title>
      <link>https://github.com/bitwarden/sdk-internal/commit/db648d7ea85878e9cce03283694d01d878481f6b</link>
      <description>Improve language around licensing for most crates to be GPL or Bitwarden
SDK License.</description>
      <author> (Hinton)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/bitwarden/sdk-internal/commit/db648d7ea85878e9cce03283694d01d878481f6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 05:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Skyvern-AI/skyvern: Automate browser-based workflows with LLMs and Computer Vision</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Skyvern-AI/Skyvern</link>
      <description>Automate browser-based workflows with LLMs and Computer Vision - Skyvern-AI/skyvern</description>
      <author> (Skyvern-AI)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Skyvern-AI/Skyvern</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 04:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing quantized Llama models with increased speed and a reduced memory footprint</title>
      <link>https://ai.meta.com/blog/meta-llama-quantized-lightweight-models/?_fb_noscript=1</link>
      <description>As our first quantized models in this Llama category, these instruction-tuned models retain the quality and safety of the original 1B and 3B models, while achieving 2-4x speedup.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ai.meta.com/blog/meta-llama-quantized-lightweight-models/?_fb_noscript=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 02:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List-Taking and Note-Taking</title>
      <link>https://blog.nestful.app/p/on-list-taking-and-note-taking</link>
      <description>Why you should do both</description>
      <author> (Nestful)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.nestful.app/p/on-list-taking-and-note-taking</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Django Admin: Implementing Reverse ManyToMany Filters with Horizontal</title>
      <link>https://kenan7.com/achieving-symmetrical-manytomany-filtering-in-django-admin</link>
      <description>Enhance Django admin with a symmetrical ManyToMany filter widget for a consistent and user-friendly experience. Improve UI and UX with this guide</description>
      <author> (https://hashnode.com/@kenan7)</author>
      <guid>https://kenan7.com/achieving-symmetrical-manytomany-filtering-in-django-admin</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object API – `Object.groupBy()`</title>
      <link>https://jskatas.org/katas/es15/language/object-api/groupBy/</link>
      <description>A kata to (re-)learn about Object API | `Object.groupBy()` |  | 8 tests to solve | Difficulty Level: BEGINNER</description>
      <author> (Wolfram Kriesing)</author>
      <guid>https://jskatas.org/katas/es15/language/object-api/groupBy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A decade of WiFi</title>
      <link>https://jasmcole.com/2024/10/18/a-decade-of-wifi/</link>
      <description>It was just over 10 years ago when I wrote my original blog post on WiFi. Looking back on it, it’s incredibly nerdy – did I really include a sparsity plot for a matrix? Nevertheless, it…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jasmcole.com/2024/10/18/a-decade-of-wifi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compressed Apache Arrow Tables Over HTTP</title>
      <link>https://felipe.rs/2024/10/23/arrow-over-http/</link>
      <description>Returning Arrow tables over HTTP is relatively straightforward. TheArrow IPC streaming formatis repurposed to the HTTP use case and you can return each seria...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://felipe.rs/2024/10/23/arrow-over-http/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why that one coworker got fired for no reason</title>
      <link>https://gieseanw.wordpress.com/2024/10/24/why-that-one-coworker-got-fired-for-no-reason/</link>
      <description>(Featured image by Camille Couvez on Unsplash) Your manager calls you into a virtual meeting and, after wading through the requisite bullshit small talk, asks what you’ve been working on for the la…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gieseanw.wordpress.com/2024/10/24/why-that-one-coworker-got-fired-for-no-reason/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Framework overload: when convenience dulls innovation in software development</title>
      <link>https://prahladyeri.github.io/blog/2024/10/framework-overload.html</link>
      <description>Web and software developers are more empowered today than ever. But there’s a growing problem: the increasing reliance on frameworks, libraries, and pre-packaged solutions. Frameworks like Laravel, React, Angular, and Django have become household names, not just for their ability to streamline development but also for their role in reshaping...</description>
      <author> (Prahlad Yeri)</author>
      <guid>https://prahladyeri.github.io/blog/2024/10/framework-overload.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wayland: i3 to Sway migration</title>
      <link>https://anarc.at/software/desktop/wayland/</link>
      <description>I started migrating my graphical workstations to Wayland, specifically
migrating from i3 to Sway. This is mostly to address serious graphics
bugs in the latest Framwork
laptop, but also something I
felt was inevitable.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anarc.at/software/desktop/wayland/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruby on (Guard)Rails</title>
      <link>https://mikemcquaid.com/ruby-on-guard-rails/</link>
      <description>I’ve worked on a few Ruby apps in my career at varying scales (Homebrew, AllTrails, GitHub, Workbrew) and there’s been a consistent theme: Ruby is great for moving fast (and breaking things).</description>
      <author> (Mike McQuaid)</author>
      <guid>https://mikemcquaid.com/ruby-on-guard-rails/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Retrieval using Postgres Recursive CTEs</title>
      <link>https://www.sheshbabu.com/posts/graph-retrieval-using-postgres-recursive-ctes/</link>
      <description>Using Postgres as an alternative to graph databases for storing and retrieving graphs</description>
      <author> (Sheshbabu Chinnakonda)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sheshbabu.com/posts/graph-retrieval-using-postgres-recursive-ctes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a better and scalable system for data migrations</title>
      <link>https://yorickpeterse.com/articles/building-a-better-and-scalable-system-for-data-migrations/</link>
      <description>Recently I read about a new Rust web framework called
rwf. I was especially curious about its approach
to handling database migrations, as many frameworks released in recent years
tend to either overlook this or provide a mechanism that won&amp;#39;t scale to larger
projects. Reading through the documentation I learned that rwf falls in the
second category: it generates two SQL files, one for migrating forward and one
for migrating backwards, and evaluates the appropriate files based on the
migration direction.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yorickpeterse.com/articles/building-a-better-and-scalable-system-for-data-migrations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Freelance</title>
      <link>https://blog.diegoreis.me/first-freelance/</link>
      <description> This’s my first blog post, so if you’re reading this, thank you! The idea is to write regularly, documenting a bit about my experience as a Computer Science student getting into the job market.
Let’s get straight to the point: how my first freelance went and what lessons I learned.
Freelance Definition “Freelance is all, closed-scope, paid work where there’s no employment relationship between the payer and the one getting the job done.” – Me</description>
      <author> (Diego Reis)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.diegoreis.me/first-freelance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s Coming with .NET 9?</title>
      <link>https://www.claudiobernasconi.ch/2024/10/24/what-is-coming-with-dotnet9/</link>
      <description>An in-depth overview of .NET 9&amp;#39;s new features and updates! Learn whether upgrading now or waiting for .NET 10 is the right choice for your applications.</description>
      <author> (Claudio Bernasconi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.claudiobernasconi.ch/2024/10/24/what-is-coming-with-dotnet9/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 23:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2048 by Gabriele Cirulli</title>
      <link>https://play2048.co/</link>
      <description>Join the tiles and reach 2048! Play the free online game loved by millions.</description>
      <author> (Gabriele Cirulli)</author>
      <guid>https://play2048.co/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smarter than &amp;#39;Ctrl+F&amp;#39;: Linking Directly to Web Page Content</title>
      <link>https://alfy.blog/2024/10/19/linking-directly-to-web-page-content.html</link>
      <description>Discover how text fragments revolutionize web navigation. Learn to link directly to specific text on any web page, surpassing traditional &amp;#39;Ctrl+F&amp;#39; searches. Explore this powerful, user-friendly feature for precise content sharing and improved web experiences.</description>
      <author> (Ahmad Elalfy)</author>
      <guid>https://alfy.blog/2024/10/19/linking-directly-to-web-page-content.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 19:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>