<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - drawdb-io/drawdb: Free, simple, and intuitive online database design tool and SQL generator.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/drawdb-io/drawdb</link>
      <description>Free, simple, and intuitive online database design tool and SQL generator. - drawdb-io/drawdb</description>
      <author> (drawdb-io)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/drawdb-io/drawdb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - maharmstone/btrfs: WinBtrfs - an open-source btrfs driver for Windows</title>
      <link>https://github.com/maharmstone/btrfs</link>
      <description>WinBtrfs - an open-source btrfs driver for Windows - maharmstone/btrfs</description>
      <author> (maharmstone)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/maharmstone/btrfs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform Test and AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/aws-builders/terraform-test-and-aws-lambda-5158</link>
      <description>You may find my base repository here.                                  bervProject        /         ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/aws-builders/terraform-test-and-aws-lambda-5158</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Agents Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2402.05120</link>
      <description>We find that, simply via a sampling-and-voting method, the performance of large language models (LLMs) scales with the number of agents instantiated. Also, this method is orthogonal to existing complicated methods to further enhance LLMs, while the degree of enhancement is correlated to the task difficulty. We conduct comprehensive experiments on a wide range of LLM benchmarks to verify the presence of our finding, and to study the properties that can facilitate its occurrence. Our code is publicly available at: \url{https://anonymous.4open.science/r/more_agent_is_all_you_need}.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 3 Feb 2024])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2402.05120</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 15:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT’s Tarot Shuffle: Random Musings on Love, Family, and Financial Fortunes</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/04/07/chatgpts-tarot-shuffle-random-musings-on-love-family-and-financial-fortunes/</link>
      <description>The funny article explores the practice of Tarot card readings, emphasizing their subjective interpretation and potential for personal reflection rather than supernatural insight. Through a randomi…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/04/07/chatgpts-tarot-shuffle-random-musings-on-love-family-and-financial-fortunes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A JavaScript library for generating vector-based cartoon faces</title>
      <link>https://zengm.com/facesjs/</link>
      <description>To load new random faces, click here or press &amp;quot;r&amp;quot; on your keyboard.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zengm.com/facesjs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 04:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>503 days working full-time on FOSS: lessons learned</title>
      <link>https://mathspp.com/blog/503-days-working-full-time-on-foss-lessons-learned</link>
      <description>This article shares some of the lessons I learned from working full-time on a FOSS project for 503 days.</description>
      <author> (Rodrigo Gir&amp;#227;o Serr&amp;#227;o)</author>
      <guid>https://mathspp.com/blog/503-days-working-full-time-on-foss-lessons-learned</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for Alice</title>
      <link>https://www.henrikkarlsson.xyz/p/looking-for-alice</link>
      <description>Not dating</description>
      <author> (Henrik Karlsson)</author>
      <guid>https://www.henrikkarlsson.xyz/p/looking-for-alice</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cows and Carbon for Dummies - Ben Hunt</title>
      <link>https://benhunt.com/cows-and-carbon-for-dummies/</link>
      <description>It is popular to claim that cattle are bad for the environment, and the best thing we can do for the planet is to eat a plant-based diet. So let’s look at the carbon cycle, specifically as it applies to grazing cattle, and try to see how cows can be a net GHG emitter. I’m […]</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/webdesignfromscratch)</author>
      <guid>https://benhunt.com/cows-and-carbon-for-dummies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can’t spell “Gell-Mann amnesia” without LLM</title>
      <link>https://esham.io/2024/03/gell-mann-amnesia</link>
      <description>For a while I assumed we were all on the same page about this AI thing. I thought we all understood that—aside from the considerable ethical concerns with the unauthorized scraping of everybody’s creative work, and the dismal treatment of the people who annotate that work, and the electricity it takes to compile those annotations into models, and the likelihood that companies will see this new technology as a cheaper alternative to their human employees—those things aside, I thought we agreed that all of these “AI” systems are fundamentally just making shit up, and that if they happen to construct coherent sentences more often than your phone’s predictive-text keyboard then the difference is one of degree rather than kind. It’s amazing that the technology works as well as it does, but it’s been clear for a while now that these tools are unreliable, and that that unreliability is inherent.</description>
      <author> (Benjamin Esham)</author>
      <guid>https://esham.io/2024/03/gell-mann-amnesia</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the Clicks Keyboard</title>
      <link>https://g7o.today/posts/thoughts_on_the_clicks_keyboard/</link>
      <description>A brief review of the Clicks iPhone keyboard</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://g7o.today/posts/thoughts_on_the_clicks_keyboard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sustainable Path Forward for Modrinth</title>
      <link>https://blog.modrinth.com/p/capital-return</link>
      <description>Our capital return and what’s next.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.modrinth.com/p/capital-return</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Open Source Contribution</title>
      <link>https://www.preethamrn.com/posts/my-first-open-source-contribution</link>
      <description>One of the things that I love about programming is that you can see a problem in the world and solve it. So when I found out that one of the apps I used on a daily basis was open source, I was pleasantly surprised</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.preethamrn.com/posts/my-first-open-source-contribution</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pkgsrc on macOS: still works</title>
      <link>https://schmonz.com/2024/04/02/pkgsrc-on-macos-still-works/</link>
      <description>A few weeks ago, Apple released new versions of
Xcode
and
Command Line Tools.
Not thinking too hard about how
my pkgsrc developer environment
often gets broken by OS or tool updates, I updated promptly.
For one thing, I’m
kinda used to it.
For another, it doesn’t usually break.
For a third thing, managing dependencies — anything not my code that can break my code — means responsibility for dealing with the inevitable trouble, and therefore the sooner I find it the better.
(More on my approach to life with dependencies.)</description>
      <author> (Amitai Schleier)</author>
      <guid>https://schmonz.com/2024/04/02/pkgsrc-on-macos-still-works/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimized Model Auditing with PaperTrail</title>
      <link>https://danielabaron.me/blog/model-audit-paper-trail/</link>
      <description>Learn how to optimize model auditing in your Rails application using the PaperTrail gem by setting up separate audit tables for each model, enhancing performance and organization in the auditing process</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://danielabaron.me/blog/model-audit-paper-trail/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Blessing of the Strings</title>
      <link>https://bkardell.com/blog/blessing-strings.html</link>
      <description>Trusted Types have been a proposal by Google for quite some time at this point, but it&amp;#39;s currently getting a lot of attention and work in all browsers (Igalia is working on impleme</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bkardell.com/blog/blessing-strings.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to do when an airline website doesn&amp;#39;t accept your legal name</title>
      <link>https://www.preethamrn.com/posts/southwest-flight-bug</link>
      <description>Southwest usually has good customer service... but in this case it&amp;#39;s completely broken, I can&amp;#39;t fix it myself, and the company has no plans of fixing it</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.preethamrn.com/posts/southwest-flight-bug</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to correctly link to UCRT (and why it works that way) — mingwpy 0.1 documentation</title>
      <link>https://mingwpy.github.io/ucrt.html</link>
      <description>The license that Microsoft imposes on the Windows runtime SDK makes it
impossible for the gcc/mingw-w64 developers to use the official CRT
.lib files. They have to recreate everything from scratch, and in
particular, they need to jerry-rig their own mechanism for linking to
ucrtbase.dll.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mingwpy.github.io/ucrt.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My favorite button on the Internet</title>
      <link>https://breadchris.com/blog/my-favorite-button-on-the-internet/</link>
      <description>A button is a deceptively hard web component to get right. A good button makes a lot of things simple to do. You only need to press one thing, and a lot of things happen.
&amp;gt; “Design is not just what it looks like and feels like. Design is how it works.” ~ Steve Jobs
Beyond what the button does, it also captures intent. The user desires to interact with this button because they want what it offers.</description>
      <author> (breadchris)</author>
      <guid>https://breadchris.com/blog/my-favorite-button-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A few servers and a load balancer.</title>
      <link>https://shayy.org/posts/a-few-servers/</link>
      <description>Deploying products with a few servers and a load balancer.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shayy.org/posts/a-few-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit sync</title>
      <link>https://zamundaaa.github.io/wayland/2024/04/05/explicit-sync.html</link>
      <description>Recently news went around about explicit sync being merged into Wayland protocols, and in the wake of that I saw a lot of people having questions about it, and why it was such a big deal… So here’s a short-ish explanation of what it is, why it’s needed and what the benefits are over the old model.</description>
      <author> (Xaver Hugl)</author>
      <guid>https://zamundaaa.github.io/wayland/2024/04/05/explicit-sync.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I think about when I edit — Eva Parish</title>
      <link>https://evaparish.com/blog/how-i-edit</link>
      <description>I’m often asked to edit friends’ or coworkers’ writing, anything from emails to short stories to documentation. Recently, someone asked me  how  I edit. What am I looking for? How do I know what changes to make? That made me stop and think about what I’ve been doing semi-instinctually.</description>
      <author> (Jun 21
            
            Written By Eva Parish)</author>
      <guid>https://evaparish.com/blog/how-i-edit</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 22:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>