<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Music AI Sandbox, now with new features and broader access</title>
      <link>https://deepmind.google/discover/blog/music-ai-sandbox-now-with-new-features-and-broader-access/</link>
      <description>Google has long collaborated with musicians, producers, and artists in the research and development of music AI tools. Ever since launching the Magenta project, in 2016, we’ve been exploring how...</description>
      <guid>https://deepmind.google/discover/blog/music-ai-sandbox-now-with-new-features-and-broader-access/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB Atlas Vector Search in .NET (full tutorial)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=LQJJjIjUW6U</link>
      <description>Learn more about MongoDB Atlas Vector Search: https://fnf.dev/4iLtBck
Get the source code for this video for FREE → https://the-dotnet-weekly.kit.com/mongodb-atlas

Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt

In this comprehensive tutorial, I demonstrate how to implement semantic search using MongoDB Atlas Vector Search in a .NET application. Unlike traditional keyword-based search which looks for specific terms, semantic search understands the meaning behind your queries, providing more intuitive and powerful search capabilities.

I'll walk you through:
- Understanding vector embeddings and how they work
- Setting up MongoDB Atlas Vector Search
- Generating embeddings from your content using local LLMs
- Implementing vector search queries in .NET
- Pre-filtering search results for better performance

Learn how MongoDB can function as both your primary document database and vector database, eliminating the need for separate specialized systems. This tutorial includes complete code examples for generating embeddings, creating vector search indexes, and implementing semantic search in a movie database application.

Whether you're building AI-powered search, recommendation systems, or just want to improve your application's search experience, this tutorial will show you how to leverage MongoDB Atlas Vector Search for powerful semantic understanding.

More docs: Adding MongoDB Atlas Vector Search to a .NET Blazor C# Application
https://www.mongodb.com/developer/languages/csharp/vector-search-with-csharp-driver/

Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters
0:00 Why MongoDB Atlas
1:16 Vector Search and MongoDB
5:29 Exploring the sample application
8:59 Creating a MongoDB Atlas DB
11:27 Creating a Vector Search Index
16:17 Generating embeddings with MEAI
24:39 Implementing Vector Search with MongoDB</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=LQJJjIjUW6U</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 12:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Discord Indexes Trillions of Messages</title>
      <link>https://discord.com/blog/how-discord-indexes-trillions-of-messages</link>
      <description>Learn how Discord scaled its search infrastructure to index trillions of messages and unlock new features.</description>
      <guid>https://discord.com/blog/how-discord-indexes-trillions-of-messages</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Hello World to Hello Customers: Why Programs Aren’t Products</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/from-hello-world-to-hello-customers-why-programs-arent-products-imp</link>
      <description>We’ve all been there. You knock out a script in an hour, it runs, it works, and you feel like a...</description>
      <guid>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/from-hello-world-to-hello-customers-why-programs-arent-products-imp</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Loop the Wrong Way in .NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=uoFRGkMPaRc</link>
      <description>Get 40% off everything on Dometrain: https://dometrain.com/courses/?ref=nick-chapsas&amp;promo=youtube&amp;coupon_code=BIRTHDAY2
Subscribe to my weekly newsletter: https://nickchapsas.com

Become a Patreon and get special perks: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsas

Hello, everybody. I'm Nick, and in this video, I will talk about IEnumerable and IEnumerator and whether one makes more sense to use over the other when you're iterating collections.

Workshops: https://bit.ly/nickworkshops

Don't forget to comment, like and subscribe :)

Social Media:
Follow me on GitHub: https://github.com/Elfocrash
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/nickchapsas
Connect on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick-chapsas

#csharp #dotnet</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=uoFRGkMPaRc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Data Community Standup - Azure SQL vector search with Davide Mauri</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=RksCLw2OU_M</link>
      <description>Join us for a special edition of the .NET Data Community Standup as we welcome Davide Mauri, Principal Product Manager at Microsoft, to explore the exciting new vector search capabilities in Azure SQL. With the rise of AI-powered applications and semantic search, vector databases are more relevant than ever. In this session, Davide will demonstrate how Azure SQL is evolving to meet these modern needs with integrated vector search features.

Featuring: Jiri Cincura, Shay Rojansky, Davide Mauri

#ai #vector #databases</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=RksCLw2OU_M</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘trickonometry’ of math olympiad inequalities (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://www.andreinc.net/2025/03/17/the-trickonometry-of-math-olympiad-inequalities</link>
      <description>Getting started with competitive math inequalities</description>
      <author> (Andrei Ciobanu)</author>
      <guid>https://www.andreinc.net/2025/03/17/the-trickonometry-of-math-olympiad-inequalities</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instant SQL is here: Speedrun ad-hoc queries as you type - MotherDuck Blog</title>
      <link>https://motherduck.com/blog/introducing-instant-sql/</link>
      <description>Type, see, tweak, repeat! Instant SQL is now in Preview in MotherDuck and the DuckDB Local UI. Bend reality with SQL superpowers to get real-time query results as you type. | Reading time: 8 min read</description>
      <guid>https://motherduck.com/blog/introducing-instant-sql/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going Out With A Bang</title>
      <link>https://blog.dshr.org/2025/04/going-out-with-bang.html</link>
      <description>In 1.5C Here We Come  I criticized people like Eric Schmidt  who said that:   the artificial intelligence boom was too powerful, and had too...</description>
      <guid>https://blog.dshr.org/2025/04/going-out-with-bang.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can Be a Great Designer and Be Completely Unknown - Christopher Butler</title>
      <link>https://www.chrbutler.com/you-can-be-a-great-designer-and-be-completely-unknown</link>
      <description>I often find myself contemplating the greatest creators in history — those rare artists, designers, and thinkers whose work transformed how we see</description>
      <guid>https://www.chrbutler.com/you-can-be-a-great-designer-and-be-completely-unknown</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If We Could Rebuild Kafka From Scratch?</title>
      <link>https://www.morling.dev/blog/what-if-we-could-rebuild-kafka-from-scratch/</link>
      <description>
The last few days I spent some time digging into the recently announced KIP-1150 ("Diskless Kafka"), as well AutoMQ’s Kafka fork, tightly integrating Apache Kafka and object storage, such as S3. Following the example set by WarpStream, these projects aim to substantially improve the experience of using Kafka in cloud environments, providing better elasticity, drastically reducing cost, and paving the way towards native lakehouse integration.


This got me thinking, if we were to start all over and develop a durable cloud-native event log from scratch—​Kafka.next if you will—​which traits and characteristics would be desirable for this to have? Separating storage and compute and object store support would be table stakes, but what else should be there? Having used Kafka for many years for building event-driven applications as well as for running realtime ETL and change data capture pipelines, here’s my personal wishlist:
</description>
      <guid>https://www.morling.dev/blog/what-if-we-could-rebuild-kafka-from-scratch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More about Figma's "Dev Mode" trademark</title>
      <link>https://jonatron.github.io/randomstuff/trademark/fig.html</link>
      <description>Disclaimer: I am not a lawyer or journalist, might be wrong about things</description>
      <guid>https://jonatron.github.io/randomstuff/trademark/fig.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't make it "like Google"</title>
      <link>https://rakhim.exotext.com/dont-make-it-like-google</link>
      <description>Don't make it "like Google" | exotext</description>
      <guid>https://rakhim.exotext.com/dont-make-it-like-google</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Billion Dollar Idea (Seedless Torrents) is dead</title>
      <link>https://dustinmontgomery.com/seedless-torrents.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://dustinmontgomery.com/seedless-torrents.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for Seeds - Smol Nero </title>
      <link>https://smolnero.com/posts/looking-for-seeds</link>
      <description>Merchant Cash Advances (MCAs) are gaining popularity in the loan market. These short-term loans were introduced under the guise of supporting small businesses—providing short-term capital to help cover expenses in...</description>
      <guid>https://smolnero.com/posts/looking-for-seeds</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTokification and Enshitification</title>
      <link>https://niteshpant.com/essays/tiktokification-and-enshitification</link>
      <description>TikTokification is the denouement of Enshitification, where engagement metrics-driven growth models and an unregulated dopamine market force companies and platforms to offer algorithmically driven endless doom-scrolling as their core product over socially beneficial and innovative products.</description>
      <guid>https://niteshpant.com/essays/tiktokification-and-enshitification</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Really Happens When You Drop a Column in Postgres</title>
      <link>https://www.thenile.dev/blog/drop-column</link>
      <description>When you drop a column in Postgres, the data doesn't actually go away - here's why, and what that means for you</description>
      <guid>https://www.thenile.dev/blog/drop-column</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's ok to not be a machine</title>
      <link>https://fourohfour.net/its-ok-to-not-be-a-machine/</link>
      <description>How routines and toxic productivity ignores what makes us human</description>
      <guid>https://fourohfour.net/its-ok-to-not-be-a-machine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Got Hacked: A Warning about Malicious PoCs | Chocapikk's Cybersecurity Blog 🛡️💻</title>
      <link>https://chocapikk.com/posts/2025/s1nk/</link>
      <description>An in-depth forensic analysis of how a seemingly legitimate Proof-of-Concept (PoC) for CVE-2020-35489 turned out to be a cleverly disguised malware. This blog post details the attack vector, payload deobfuscation, Indicators of Compromise (IoCs), and the steps taken to analyze and neutralize the threat.</description>
      <author> (Valentin Lobstein (Chocapikk) 🛡️)</author>
      <guid>https://chocapikk.com/posts/2025/s1nk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufactured consensus on x.com</title>
      <link>https://rook2root.co/articles/20250424-manufacturing-consensus-on-x</link>
      <description>How algorithm-driven influence quietly replaces genuine discourse with engineered popularity—no fake users, no overt propaganda.</description>
      <guid>https://rook2root.co/articles/20250424-manufacturing-consensus-on-x</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 22:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Inside Story of the Windows Start Menu</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=INLSnd2p8uQ</link>
      <description>Retired Windows developer Dave Plummer takes you a visual journey through the history of the Windows Start Menu, from its origins in Cairo, to Windows 95, Windows 98, Windows XP, Vista, Windows 7, 8, 10, and 11.</description>
      <author> (Dave's Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=INLSnd2p8uQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 20:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On loyalty to your employer — Talent Stuff</title>
      <link>https://www.talentstuff.com/blog/on-loyalty-to-your-employer</link>
      <description>Your employer pays you to spend more time with them than you spend with your family and/or loved ones. Your employer is one of the biggest influencers on your mental well-being. Your employer can and will replace you in a heartbeat if absolutely necessary.  Let me be explicitly clear, your employer </description>
      <guid>https://www.talentstuff.com/blog/on-loyalty-to-your-employer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I wrote to the address in the GPLv2 license notice and received the GPLv3 license</title>
      <link>https://code.mendhak.com/gpl-v2-address-letter/</link>
      <description>I was curious about the 51 Franklin Street address in the GPLv2 license notice so I wrote to them as they said</description>
      <guid>https://code.mendhak.com/gpl-v2-address-letter/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Access Evolution &amp; AI with Michael Pizzo - Microsoft Data Expert</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=yzjzLzBGsbU</link>
      <description>Register for Build - https://build.microsoft.com

My interview with Microsoft's Michael Pizzo—a true trailblazer with over 30 years at Microsoft. Michael began his journey integrating Excel with relational data, and went on to play a pivotal role in the design of ODBC, OLE DB, and ADO.NET, driving standards and innovation every step of the way. Now a Principal Architect in our Identity Division, his influence is felt in modern tools like Microsoft Graph. Let's dive into his incredible story!

Chapters: 
00:00 - Intro
01:00 - Developer Conferences &amp; Speaking
04:00 - Data Access Evolution
06:00 - Standardization of Data Access
08:40 - AI's Impact on Data
11:30 - Future Excitement
12:37 - Wrap-up

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCENTmbKaTphpWV2R2evVz2A/join

👕 Buy some swag! - https://jamesmontemagno.myspreadshop.com/
☕️ Buy me a coffee - https://www.buymeacoffee.com/jamesmontemagno

Follow:
👨‍💻 GitHub: https://github.com/jamesmontemagno
🦜 X: https://x.com/jamesmontemagno
📄 Website: https://www.montemagno.com
📰 Newsletter: https://newsletter.montemagno.com/

Disclaimer: This channel, videos, and streams are created in my spare time and are a product of me... James Montemagno! They are NOT officially affiliated or endorsed by Microsoft (my employer) in any way. Opinions and views are my own.

What is on my hat? It is the CLE clothing logo because I am from Cleveland! Checkout their awesome CLE merch: https://cleclothingco.myshopify.com/

What is that art on my wall? It is an original piece from the French street artist Gregos of La Butte Montmartre: https://www.instagram.com/p/BceZ1oNHiQx/

My Setup:
📷 Canon M50 Mark II - https://amzn.to/3P8R7lp
💡 Nanoleaf Elements Lights - https://amzn.to/3umwJVW
🎙 Blue Spark Microphone - https://amzn.to/3qgtYkq
🎙 Blue Pop Filter - https://amzn.to/3jEWM3r
🤳 Rode Microphone Arm - https://amzn.to/2Z68AlE
🎧 Sony MDR7306 Headphones - https://amzn.to/372jxta
📲 Stream Deck - https://amzn.to/373Uk1n
🖱 MX Master 2S Mouse - https://amzn.to/3d7J2gj
⌨️ Tecware Phantom Keyboard - https://amzn.to/3aUP4y9

Using links I provide I may receive a commission if you buy something which helps support the channel.

#microsoftemployee #microsoft50 #dataaccess #data #engineer #interview</description>
      <author> (James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=yzjzLzBGsbU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing .NET APIs &amp; Web Apps with Microsoft Entra | Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SZTsdOpEb8M</link>
      <description>💻Get the full source code (free): https://go.dotnetacademy.io/aspnet-core-entra
🔥Become a .NET Cloud Developer: https://dotnetacademy.io/bootcamp

Learn how to secure your ASP.NET Core APIs and Web Apps with Microsoft Entra (formerly Azure AD), step by step.

⭐️ Topics ⭐️
00:00 Welcome!
01:45 The app we will protect
05:45 Registering the ASP.NET Core API in Entra
11:46 Securing the ASP.NET Core API
19:03 Registering Postman in Entra
24:09 Getting access tokens from Entra
32:07 Registering the Web App in Entra
36:11 Configuring the Web App for Entra
49:04 Enabling login and logout
01:03:39 Show/hide UI based on user identity
01:07:38 Calling protected APIs from the Web App
01:16:59 Next steps

🌐Build the ASP.NET Core API: https://youtu.be/AhAxLiGC7Pc
🌐Build the Blazor Web App: https://youtu.be/RBVIclt4sOo

🆓How to get Free Azure Credits: https://juliocasal.com/blog/4-ways-to-get-free-azure-credits

🗺️Free .NET Developer Roadmap: https://juliocasal.com/roadmap

My website: https://juliocasal.com
Follow me on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/juliocasal
Follow me on X: https://twitter.com/julioc

#aspnetcore #dotnet #azuread</description>
      <author> (Julio Casal)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SZTsdOpEb8M</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 15:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How can I learn more about .NET Aspire?</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=yUBiUOfJtX0</link>
      <description>Ready to jump into the world of .NET Aspire but not sure where to start? In this One Dev Question Jayme Singleton introduces about the brand-new Beginner-Friendly Video Series — your ultimate guide to understanding and using .NET Aspire like a pro! 

Access the series here: https://msft.it/6055SJuSl</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=yUBiUOfJtX0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 15:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# and Database Configuration</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=1qj_KgrJTAU</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Fritz is working on SharpSite - an open source CMS that has been built on these live streams.  Learn more at https://sharpsite.org</description>
      <author> (Fritz's Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=1qj_KgrJTAU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 15:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>