<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Friction</title>
      <link>https://5x9s.svix.com/p/adding-friction</link>
      <description>Today, we&amp;#39;re diving into an interesting topic: friction in development processes. I recently had a conversation with Tom about this, and it brought some new perspectives to light. An Initial Confusion During a call with our engineering team, our CEO Tom suggested adding a bit of friction to our processes. This was strange because I always want to remove friction to make things smoother and faster. Velocity is crucial for us— Tom harps on how we want to move quickly and efficiently. So, why would we want to add friction?</description>
      <author> (The Five 9&amp;#39;s Newsletter)</author>
      <guid>https://5x9s.svix.com/p/adding-friction</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fun with Positron | Andrew Heiss</title>
      <link>https://www.andrewheiss.com/blog/2024/07/08/fun-with-positron/</link>
      <description>Combine the best of RStudio and Visual Studio Code in Posit’s new Positron IDE</description>
      <author> (Andrew Heiss)</author>
      <guid>https://www.andrewheiss.com/blog/2024/07/08/fun-with-positron/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healing Broken Bone at Anatomy and Art</title>
      <link>http://anatomyandart.com/blog/?p=3358</link>
      <description>a blog by Sara Egner</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://anatomyandart.com/blog/?p=3358</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading my electric meter with RTLSDR • pdx.su</title>
      <link>https://pdx.su/blog/2024-03-17-reading-my-electric-meter-with-rtlsdr/</link>
      <description>The personal blog of software engineer Jeff Sandberg</description>
      <author> (Jeff Sandberg)</author>
      <guid>https://pdx.su/blog/2024-03-17-reading-my-electric-meter-with-rtlsdr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fat Tony’s Under Water: My Dream Startup Incubator</title>
      <link>https://sebs.website/blog/fat-tonys-under-water-my-dream-startup-incubator</link>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 1946 George Orwell wrote his short essay ‘The Moon Under Water’, describing what his dream pub would look like. Heavily influenced by this (in fact, some paragraphs are nearly identical), I have decided to write a modern version of Orwell’s essay, describing my dream startup incubator.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>
      <author> (Sebastian David Lees)</author>
      <guid>https://sebs.website/blog/fat-tonys-under-water-my-dream-startup-incubator</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG Trick: Embeddings are Spheres</title>
      <link>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2024/07/10/spheres</link>
      <description>Wed July 10, 2024</description>
      <author> (Tim Kellogg)</author>
      <guid>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2024/07/10/spheres</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I manage my KDE email</title>
      <link>https://pointieststick.com/2024/07/09/how-i-manage-my-kde-email/</link>
      <description>Every once in a while people ask me about my email routine, so I thought I’d write about it here. Everything I do starts with the philosophy that work and project email is a task queue. There…</description>
      <author> (Nate)</author>
      <guid>https://pointieststick.com/2024/07/09/how-i-manage-my-kde-email/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRL HTML Is the Place For Your Most Hand-Written Websites</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickweaver.net/blog/irl-html-is-the-place-for-your-most-hand-written-websites/</link>
      <description>Patrick Weaver’s Website</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.patrickweaver.net/blog/irl-html-is-the-place-for-your-most-hand-written-websites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Markets Act, Google, Chrome extensions - case study</title>
      <link>https://blog.lukaszolejnik.com/digital-markets-act-google-chrome-extensions-case-study/</link>
      <description>The Digital Markets Act is one of the least understood EU technology laws, yet it has tangible impacts—both positive and negative—on the technology landscape. We’ll use the opportunity to study an interesting and real-world case. It concerns the practice of Chrome preloading its web browser extension so</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.lukaszolejnik.com/digital-markets-act-google-chrome-extensions-case-study/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Programmable Web</title>
      <link>https://www.mattwensing.com/the-programmable-web/</link>
      <description>Today’s app development ecosystems resemble the creative contexts for writers and photographers pre-web and pre-iPhone.</description>
      <author> (Matthew Wensing)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mattwensing.com/the-programmable-web/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 5 Stages of Posthuman Grief - “Acceptance” Makes Progress Possible - Dan Faggella</title>
      <link>https://danfaggella.com/acceptance/</link>
      <description>The 5 Stages of Grief Model isn’t perfect - but it also seems to overlap well with the experiences of grieving people. The psychological model itself needn’t</description>
      <author> (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://danfaggella.com/acceptance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evict Your Darlings: Banish dotfiles from your home directory</title>
      <link>https://r.je/evict-your-darlings</link>
      <description>Erase Your Darlings is a great approach but what if we could banish dotfiles from our home directory entirely?</description>
      <author> (Dr. Tom Butler)</author>
      <guid>https://r.je/evict-your-darlings</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HCI Is the Bottleneck</title>
      <link>https://joshmpollock.com/blog/hci-bottleneck/</link>
      <description>HCI Is the Bottleneck in a World with Strong AI  As model capabilities advance, we are rapidly gaining the ability to generate images, videos, and audio from simple text prompts that are indistinguishable from human-generated content.  Yet, even if we discount existing flaws with models, there’s still a huge gap between model capabilities and systems that are effective in practice. I argue this gap is caused primarily by HCI problems and not model capabilities, and the gap will only continue to increase as model capabilities improve.  Is this gap due to failings of HCI? Not entirely. I think it’s also due to the mental model of AI that persists despite growing problems with integrating AI solutions.  AI is typically thought of in the following way:  input -&amp;gt; model -&amp;gt; output  The goal of core machine learning is to create the model that optimizes the output given the input, e.g., producing an output image that most faithfully represents an input text prompt. The central limitation of this model is that it ignores where inputs come from and where outputs go to. The picture looks a little more like this:  human -input-&amp;gt; model -output-&amp;gt; human  Even if we assume a perfect model that optimizes the input-output correlation, the model is still fundamentally limited by the information contained in the input, and the usefulness of the output is still fundamentally limited by a human’s ability to interpret and use it.  Improving input and output interfaces is the bottleneck as models get more capable. It can be viewed as an information-theoretic problem. How do you get more bits of information into the input stream? How do you allow humans to interpret more bits of information from the output stream? Now, solutions to these problems aren’t simply algorithmic, but also require existing context to understand. That is, it’s not as simple as cramming in more information, but also in doing so in a way that allows humans to create and understand that information.  What’s the role of HCI with imperfect models?  HCI still has a profound role, possibly a more important role, even with imperfect models. We can think of an imperfect model as a perfect model with some additional (possibly/probably biased) noise. The HCI problems with imperfect models are thus the same as with perfect models but with the added difficultly of allowing humans to understand and handle “noise” in the model output.  Won’t strong AI solve the HCI problem?  Even as models get better at producing interfaces, their capabilities are still limited to the human&amp;lt;-&amp;gt;model feedback loop. This loop can probably be used to design these interfaces (and this is already starting to happen with things like Copilot and Figma AI, for example), but it doesn’t let us sidestep this problem completely.  Aren’t’ UIs just going to be ephemerally generated all the time?  Complex interfaces like the Blenders and Photoshops of the world are still likely to be semi-stable interfaces rather than ones that are generated on the fly, because of how difficult it is to learn such interfaces and the benefits humans have when using tools they have deep knowledge/skill/practice/craft around. So these interfaces are still subject to the feedback loop problem.  How do we improve input and output fidelity?  I think I’ll save this for another time.</description>
      <author> (Josh Pollock)</author>
      <guid>https://joshmpollock.com/blog/hci-bottleneck/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Code Reviews: Align your team and ship better code</title>
      <link>https://faingezicht.com/articles/2024/07/10/pull-requests/?src=hn</link>
      <description>The pull request review process introduces a lot of friction in the development cycle but serves multiple purposes, including knowledge sharing, code quality, and team alignment. It is a worthwhile investment. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://faingezicht.com/articles/2024/07/10/pull-requests/?src=hn</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Commitment to Art and Dogs</title>
      <link>https://samwho.dev/dogs/</link>
      <description>Introducing a new design for the samwho.dev dogs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://samwho.dev/dogs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updating Prism Template to .NET 8</title>
      <link>https://checox.com/updating-prism-template-to-net-8/</link>
      <description>Have you notice that now when create a MAUI project using the new Prism Template Pack for MAUI, you are not able to select the .NET version of your project? well, in this post I will show you how to update it.</description>
      <author> (steven.checo.19)</author>
      <guid>https://checox.com/updating-prism-template-to-net-8/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Crossword Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2957/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2957/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zed on Linux is here!</title>
      <link>https://zed.dev/linux</link>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ve stabilized our Linux build, download it today!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zed.dev/linux</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD to buy Finnish start-up Silo AI for $665mn in drive to compete with Nvidia</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/7b8d2057-2687-45b3-bae4-1488a75ac5b2</link>
      <description>All-cash acquisition by California-based chipmaker is the largest of its kind in Europe in a decade</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ft.com/content/7b8d2057-2687-45b3-bae4-1488a75ac5b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe&amp;#39;s new Ariane 6 rocket powers into space</title>
      <link>https://www.esa.int/Enabling_Support/Space_Transportation/Ariane/Europe_s_new_Ariane_6_rocket_powers_into_space</link>
      <description>09/07/2024
				26710 views
										165 likes</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.esa.int/Enabling_Support/Space_Transportation/Ariane/Europe_s_new_Ariane_6_rocket_powers_into_space</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating an already-completed asynchronous activity in C++/WinRT, part 2 - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240710-00/?p=109963</link>
      <description>Making our function a coroutine.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240710-00/?p=109963</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses DMCA copyright claim in GitHub Copilot suit</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2024/07/08/github_copilot_dmca/</link>
      <description>A few devs versus the powerful forces of Redmond – who did you think was going to win?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2024/07/08/github_copilot_dmca/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 11:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deactivating an API, One Step at a Time</title>
      <link>https://apichangelog.substack.com/p/deactivating-an-api-one-step-at-a</link>
      <description>How do you make sure all consumers stop using an API so you can safely deactivate it?</description>
      <author> (Bruno Pedro)</author>
      <guid>https://apichangelog.substack.com/p/deactivating-an-api-one-step-at-a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Antivirus to .NET Aspire Systems</title>
      <link>https://jeffreyfritz.com/2024/07/adding-antivirus-to-net-aspire-systems/</link>
      <description>I was working on a web application over the weekend and I needed to add a feature that would allow images to be uploaded by end-users.  As we all know, we should never trust content uploaded by anonymous ‘friends’ on the internet.  I wanted to add malware scanning to my project, but how?  In this article, I introduce a proof-of-concept project that adds the open source ClamAV antivirus scanner to a .NET Aspire system and shares connection information so that other resources can request malware scans.</description>
      <author> (by Jeff)</author>
      <guid>https://jeffreyfritz.com/2024/07/adding-antivirus-to-net-aspire-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a .NET TWAIN Document Scanner Application for Windows and macOS using MAUI</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/yushulx/building-a-net-twain-document-scanner-application-for-windows-and-macos-using-maui-34gl</link>
      <description>Dynamsoft used to offer both the .NET TWAIN SDK and the Dynamic Web TWAIN SDK. However, the .NET...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/yushulx/building-a-net-twain-document-scanner-application-for-windows-and-macos-using-maui-34gl</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET and .NET Framework July 2024 servicing releases updates - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-and-dotnet-framework-july-2024-servicing-updates/</link>
      <description>A recap of the latest servicing updates for .NET and .NET Framework for July 2024.</description>
      <author> (Tara Overfield)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-and-dotnet-framework-july-2024-servicing-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity Framework Core– Avoid losing precision</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/07/entity-framework-core-avoid-losing.html</link>
      <description>When mapping a decimal type to a database through an ORM like EF Core, it is important to consider the precision. You don&amp;#39;t want to lose dat...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/07/entity-framework-core-avoid-losing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTML Datalist for ASP.NET Core Inputs</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/html-datalist-for-aspnet-core-inputs</link>
      <description>In my last blog post, I discussed range inputs. This time, we’ll examine a tag helper that adds support for the HTML element of datalist.</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/html-datalist-for-aspnet-core-inputs</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The React useId Hook</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/react-useid-hook</link>
      <description>The React useId Hook offers a robust solution for managing unique identifiers within components. Explore its functionality, use cases and benefits, particularly how it enhances accessibility and simplifies the creation of consistent, maintainable applications.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/react-useid-hook</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from election night</title>
      <link>https://codeblog.jonskeet.uk/2024/07/09/lessons-from-election-night/</link>
      <description>Introduction On Thursday (July 4th, 2024) the UK held a general election. There are many, many blog posts, newspaper articles, podcast episodes etc covering the politics of it, and the lessons that…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://codeblog.jonskeet.uk/2024/07/09/lessons-from-election-night/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Renovate as Azure DevOps Pipeline for Automatic .NET NuGet Package Updates</title>
      <link>https://nietras.com/2024/07/09/renovate-azure-devops/</link>
      <description>Renovate is a tool/bot that can automatically
update dependencies in a repository similar to GitHub
dependabot. Renovate is open
source and written in TypeScript. It
supports a wide range of platforms and package managers. Here I will show how to
set up Renovate as a single central Azure DevOps pipeline to automatically
update NuGet packages (and .NET SDK) in multiple git repositories across
different projects in Azure DevOps.

</description>
      <author> (nietras)</author>
      <guid>https://nietras.com/2024/07/09/renovate-azure-devops/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure cross-platform and file-based token cache for MSAL.NET</title>
      <link>https://anthonysimmon.com/secure-cross-platform-file-based-token-cache-for-msal-net/</link>
      <description>When dealing with client applications, use the official Microsoft file-based token cache for MSAL.NET rather than implementing your own.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anthonysimmon.com/secure-cross-platform-file-based-token-cache-for-msal-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using use in Gleam</title>
      <link>https://erikarow.land/notes/using-use-gleam</link>
      <description>Recently, a colleague checked out Gleam’s language tour. They liked what they saw, but they were confused by Gleam’s use syntax. I like Gleam’s syntax a lotI even wrote an article about Gleam’s syntax., but I was also confused by use when I first encountered it. Here’s how I use use:The use expression was introduced in Gleam v0.25, as a more general replacement for the try keyword that preceded it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://erikarow.land/notes/using-use-gleam</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Liner Notes for Spore</title>
      <link>https://www.chrishecker.com/My_Liner_Notes_for_Spore</link>
      <description>This page is intended to be a sort of liner notes for my contributions to Spore.  It&amp;#39;s a place for me to write up miscellaneous development comments about the parts of the game I worked on, while they&amp;#39;re still fresh in my mind.  I think the game had over 80 people working on it towards the end, and it was in development for more than 5 years, so basically everything in the game was touched by more than one person and was a team effort.  Given that, I will strive for inclusion and accuracy, and I will only talk about systems to which I made substantial contributions.  If I&amp;#39;ve left somebody out or made a mistake, I apologize; please email me and I&amp;#39;ll correct it immediately.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.chrishecker.com/My_Liner_Notes_for_Spore</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some thoughts on real open source Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://ainali.com/2024/some-thoughts-on-real-open-source-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <description>We are in the midst of a hype around Artificial Intelligence (AI) and the market is trying to get ahead of each other in all sorts of ways. One way is to claim that their AI is open source. So far, there has been a lot of open washing, meaning that they claim they are open but failing to apply commo</description>
      <author> (Jan Ainali)</author>
      <guid>https://ainali.com/2024/some-thoughts-on-real-open-source-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMCA as a vector for pornographic spam?</title>
      <link>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2024/07/dmca-as-a-vector-for-pornographic-spam/</link>
      <description>There’s a law in the USA called the DMCA – Digital Millennium Copyright Act. Amongst its myriad provisions is the ability for copyright holders to send takedown notices to service provi…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2024/07/dmca-as-a-vector-for-pornographic-spam/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan-Piet Mens</title>
      <link>https://jpmens.net/2024/07/09/when-my-systems-send-me-instructions/</link>
      <description>It’s close on a quarter century that I worked for a company which had deployed a humongous issue-and-everything tracking system employees detested using. I can’t remember the name of the product, b...</description>
      <author> (Jan-Piet Mens)</author>
      <guid>https://jpmens.net/2024/07/09/when-my-systems-send-me-instructions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timeseries Indexing at Scale - Artem Krylysov</title>
      <link>https://artem.krylysov.com/blog/2024/06/28/timeseries-indexing-at-scale/</link>
      <description>Note</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://artem.krylysov.com/blog/2024/06/28/timeseries-indexing-at-scale/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Borderless Is Inevitable</title>
      <link>https://www.jerry.wtf/posts/borderless-is-inevitable/</link>
      <description>
The world is shrinking, and some people are upset. Today I read on article on Hacker News “What does a world without Airbnb look like?” which talks about the negative sentiment against long-term tourists in Barcelona, and it corroborated the discussion I saw on the Digital Nomad subreddit yesterday “Cancel Barcelona Trip?”.
Mobility
When I was a kid, my family moved from China to Canada. The ease of it all seemed normal to me. Make a life in a new country? No big deal. As I grew up, I realized this wasn’t far from the truth for most of the developed world. If you’re in a Western country and dead set on becoming a citizen of another, is it really that hard? Not really.
This is the world we created after World War II. We asked for peace and open borders. Now we’re surprised when people use them?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jerry.wtf/posts/borderless-is-inevitable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awareness, power, and morality</title>
      <link>https://www.alexahn.com/2024/07/awareness-power-and-morality.html</link>
      <description>There are few things as intoxicating as knowing something that other people do not know. Exclusive information is perhaps the oldest and mos...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://www.alexahn.com/2024/07/awareness-power-and-morality.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Dedupe Then Sort or Sort Then Dedupe?</title>
      <link>https://tomeraberba.ch/to-dedupe-then-sort-or-sort-then-dedupe</link>
      <description>I recently came across a deceptively simple problem. I wanted to dedupe and sort
a list of integers in-place.

My initial instinct was to first remove duplicates and then sort using the
programming…</description>
      <author> (Tomer Aberbach)</author>
      <guid>https://tomeraberba.ch/to-dedupe-then-sort-or-sort-then-dedupe</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving the Almgren Chris Model</title>
      <link>https://dm13450.github.io/2024/06/06/Solving-the-Almgren-Chris-Model.html</link>
      <description>The Almgren Chris model from Optimal Execution of Portfolio Transactions is the most well known optimal execution model and provides the foundational math about how to think about trading some quantity of an asset. This blog post goes through the math and how we set the problem up and arrived at the various solutions.</description>
      <author> (Dean Markwick)</author>
      <guid>https://dm13450.github.io/2024/06/06/Solving-the-Almgren-Chris-Model.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self Documenting Code Is Bullshit – Klaus Breyer</title>
      <link>https://www.v01.io/posts/2024-self-documenting-code-is-bullshit/</link>
      <description>Hopefully, every development team reaches a point where they discuss their guidelines and policies. Part of this discussion, hopefully, includes expectations around documentation.
So far, so good. Unfortunately, many teams (and I have made this mistake in the past as well) take the easy route and claim they don’t need extensive documentation if they write self-documenting code. Besides the fact that this is just an easy way to avoid a discussion (because everyone interprets this differently), it is just plain wrong.</description>
      <author> (Klaus Breyer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.v01.io/posts/2024-self-documenting-code-is-bullshit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did I leave IT services? and why I do not regret it.</title>
      <link>https://www.asanverse.com/why-i-left-it-services-why-you-should-also-think-about-this/</link>
      <description>A lot of people talk about business people being data-driven and AI literate. However, I believe the more important issue is that data professionals need to become business-savvy.</description>
      <author> (UB)</author>
      <guid>https://www.asanverse.com/why-i-left-it-services-why-you-should-also-think-about-this/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do you test the quality of search results?</title>
      <link>https://tomhazledine.com/assessing-search-quality/</link>
      <description>Improving or comparing search algorithms requires being able to objectively test their performance. How on earth do you actually do that?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tomhazledine.com/assessing-search-quality/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rails 7.2 Adds app:update Task to be a Rails Command.</title>
      <link>https://blog.saeloun.com/2024/07/09/rails-app-update-command/</link>
      <description>The app:update task to be a Rails command, and adds the --force flag to it, to allow running bin/rails app:update while accepting all the changes it makes.</description>
      <author> (Saeloun Blog)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.saeloun.com/2024/07/09/rails-app-update-command/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binary Kelly Trainer: Ship Investor Game</title>
      <link>https://two-wrongs.com/binary-kelly-criterion-training-ship-investor-game</link>
      <description>A few years ago I made a simple web game to practise applying the Kelly
criterion to binary bets. Play Ship Investor here if you want.</description>
      <author> (kqr)</author>
      <guid>https://two-wrongs.com/binary-kelly-criterion-training-ship-investor-game</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerk</title>
      <link>https://ivanish.ca/jerk/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ivanish.ca/jerk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life without the front page</title>
      <link>https://jesseduffield.com/Life-Without-The-Front-Page/</link>
      <description>I consider myself low on the spectrum of addict-ability: I don’t smoke, I rarely drink, I don’t gamble, I don’t have a video game addiction, and I don’t snack on sweets. But every man has his kryptonite, and a couple years ago I found myself compulsively checking the front page of Hacker News and various programming subreddits for the tech world’s latest goss.

</description>
      <author> (Pursuit Of Laziness)</author>
      <guid>https://jesseduffield.com/Life-Without-The-Front-Page/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My High School banned Phones... in 2011!</title>
      <link>https://www.neelc.org/posts/school-phone-ban/</link>
      <description>Today I read that many schools from NYC to LA want to ban smartphones in school. Well, let me tell you that my high school, Somers High School of Somers, NY (an rural-ish but rich NYC exurb) did actually ban phones back in 2011, and when I graduated in 2015 they still did.
When it comes to mobile tech, the early-to-mid-2010s were almost like the stone age. Whereas most of my peers had an iPhone on Verizon, my family chose to go with Samsung phones on Sprint.</description>
      <author> (Neel Chauhan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.neelc.org/posts/school-phone-ban/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for a better search box - koaning.io</title>
      <link>https://koaning.io/posts/search-boxes/</link>
      <description>Sessions, not searches. Prompts, not queries.</description>
      <author> (Vincent D. Warmerdam)</author>
      <guid>https://koaning.io/posts/search-boxes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 + 1 &amp;gt; 2 - ganji.blog</title>
      <link>https://ganji.blog/one-plus-one</link>
      <description>I had a shoulder injury a few years ago. After that, I struggled to go back to working out consistently. I signed up for an expensive gym. They had an incentive where I had to pay a penalty if ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ganji.blog/one-plus-one</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Remember for iOS — defn.io</title>
      <link>https://defn.io/2024/04/09/ann-remember-for-ios/</link>
      <description>A little over four years ago, I released Remember
for macOS, a small reminders app written using a combination of Swift
and Racket. Today, I&amp;#39;ve released a version of Remember on the iOS App
Store!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://defn.io/2024/04/09/ann-remember-for-ios/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gRPC Over HTTP/3</title>
      <link>https://kmcd.dev/posts/grpc-over-http3/</link>
      <description>Turbocharging gRPC with HTTP/3</description>
      <author> (Kevin McDonald Kevin)</author>
      <guid>https://kmcd.dev/posts/grpc-over-http3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating enterprise apps stuck on legacy technologies</title>
      <link>https://agostonbarna.github.io/posts/migrating-enterprise-apps-stuck-on-legacy-technologies/</link>
      <description>Enterprise applications often have a hefty and complex code base, mission-critical functionality, and a constant influx of feature demands that can result in a slower pace of dependency updates and a tendency to lag behind. This situation can worsen over time, as certain high-profile dependencies become outdated or discontinued, preventing the update of interlocked dependencies and leading to a cascade of technological stagnation. Eventually, this can reach a critical point, requiring big bang migrations to break free from the constraints of problematic legacy technologies.</description>
      <author> (Barnab&amp;#225;s &amp;#193;goston)</author>
      <guid>https://agostonbarna.github.io/posts/migrating-enterprise-apps-stuck-on-legacy-technologies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magic of Clip Path</title>
      <link>https://emilkowal.ski/ui/the-magic-of-clip-path</link>
      <description>One of the most underrated CSS properties.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://emilkowal.ski/ui/the-magic-of-clip-path</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The dual nature of seniority in software development</title>
      <link>https://www.jenchan.biz/blog/the-dual-nature-of-seniority</link>
      <description>On expectations vs. reality of senior software developer roles, and the unspoken requirement of professional mindreading for navigating politics in senior+ roles.</description>
      <author> (jen chan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jenchan.biz/blog/the-dual-nature-of-seniority</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonas Hietala: Microfeatures in my blog</title>
      <link>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2024/07/09/microfeatures_in_my_blog/</link>
      <description>A while I ago I encountered a blog post called Microfeatures I Love in Blogs and Personal Websites, and together with the related Hacker News discussion I got nerd sniped.
(I spent more time than I care to admit implementing new and exciting microfeatures for the blog.)</description>
      <author> (Jonas Hietala)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2024/07/09/microfeatures_in_my_blog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>