<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>The Seniority Roller Coaster and Down-Leveling in Tech</title>
      <link>https://blog.pragmaticengineer.com/the-seniority-roller-coaster/amp/</link>
      <description>In tech, switching jobs almost always comes with either a financial or a title upside. However, it doesn’t always come with both. Switching for higher compensation can result in a “lower” title, like going from Senior Software Engineer to SWE 2 or VP Engineering to Senior Engineering Manager. This</description>
      <author> (by Gergely Orosz)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.pragmaticengineer.com/the-seniority-roller-coaster/amp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 19:06:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - JonPSmith/AuthPermissions.AspNetCore: This library provides extra authorization features to an ASP.NET Core application.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/JonPSmith/AuthPermissions.AspNetCore</link>
      <description>This library provides extra authorization features to an ASP.NET Core application. - GitHub - JonPSmith/AuthPermissions.AspNetCore: This library provides extra authorization features to an ASP.NET ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/JonPSmith/AuthPermissions.AspNetCore</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 18:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShlinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://www.shlinkedin.com/join</link>
      <description>Tomorrow&amp;#39;s Thought Leadership, Today</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.shlinkedin.com/join</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 13:06:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 392 - SQL Managed Instances</title>
      <link>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-392-SQL-Managed-Instances</link>
      <description>Episode 190 - MSSQL ScripterThe guys talk to Tara Raj, a PM in the SQL for Linux team about an open source tool called MSSQL Scr...Episode 173 - SQL Data WarehouseThe guys have a great chat with Ellis Butterfield, a PM in the Azure team, on the nuts and bolts beh...Episode 369 - Learn Azure SQLThe team meets with recurring guest Bob Ward and meet a new one, Anna Hoffman, to talk about their L...</description>
      <author> (Sujit D&amp;#39;Mello)</author>
      <guid>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-392-SQL-Managed-Instances</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 13:06:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did American “wokeness” jump from elite schools to everyday life?</title>
      <link>https://www.economist.com/briefing/2021/09/04/how-did-american-wokeness-jump-from-elite-schools-to-everyday-life</link>
      <description>And how deep will its influence be? | Briefing</description>
      <author> (Sep 4th 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://www.economist.com/briefing/2021/09/04/how-did-american-wokeness-jump-from-elite-schools-to-everyday-life</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 12:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Programming Languages 2021</title>
      <link>https://spectrum.ieee.org/top-programming-languages-2021</link>
      <description>Python dominates as the de facto platform for new technologies</description>
      <author> (Stephen Cass)</author>
      <guid>https://spectrum.ieee.org/top-programming-languages-2021</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 10:05:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DATAWING LIMITED - Filing history (free information from Companies House)</title>
      <link>https://find-and-update.company-information.service.gov.uk/company/07650812/filing-history</link>
      <description>DATAWING LIMITED - Free company information from Companies House including registered office address, filing history, accounts, annual return, officers, charges, business activity</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://find-and-update.company-information.service.gov.uk/company/07650812/filing-history</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 08:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delays Aren&amp;#39;t Good Enough—Apple Must Abandon Its Surveillance Plans</title>
      <link>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/09/delays-arent-good-enough-apple-must-abandon-its-surveillance-plans</link>
      <description>Apple announced today that it would “take additional time over the coming months to collect input and make improvements” to a program that will weaken privacy and security on iPhones and other products. EFF is pleased Apple is now listening to the concerns of customers, researchers, civil liberties...</description>
      <author> (Cindy Cohn)</author>
      <guid>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/09/delays-arent-good-enough-apple-must-abandon-its-surveillance-plans</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release v3.5.0 &amp;#183; dotnet/orleans</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/orleans/releases/tag/v3.5.0</link>
      <description>Improvements and bug fixes since 3.4.3


Non-breaking improvements

Add C# 9.0 record support to serializer (#7119)
Fallback to ILBasedSerializer when BinaryFormatter is disabled (#7198)
AAD TokenC...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/orleans/releases/tag/v3.5.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 07:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 259</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-259/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m &amp;#160;back from the most epic of holidays! How epic? Just have a scroll through the thread: I’m back! Went offline for most of the last week, pics and stories to follow &amp;#128010; pic.twitter.com/hRUcKMwgGU &amp;amp;mdash; Troy Hunt (@troyhunt) September 2, 2021 Which the Twitter client on my</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-259/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 07:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mathlets : MIT Mathlets</title>
      <link>https://mathlets.org/mathlets/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mathlets.org/mathlets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 07:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A nasty bit of undefined timezone behavior in Golang</title>
      <link>https://www.dolthub.com/blog/2021-09-03-golang-time-bugs/</link>
      <description>Go is a great language. Really, it is! We complain about the rough
edges, but on the whole it&amp;#39;s been a great choice for us, and we&amp;#39;re not…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dolthub.com/blog/2021-09-03-golang-time-bugs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 06:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running (Mostly) Minimal .NET 6 APIs in Azure Functions</title>
      <link>https://www.cazzulino.com/net6functions.html</link>
      <description>Ok, I have to admit that the provided instructions aren’t bad at all. They actually state (most) of the required steps to do this, with a couple key missing pieces that caused me some trouble and resulted in quite a few trial-and-error attempts. I’m writing this down for my own future reference and hopefully it will save you some time too. Why First, why is any of this needed at all? Well, basically, at the time of this writing, neither .NET 5 nor .NET 6 are officially supported in Azure Functions. This means there isn’t a simple dropdown to just...</description>
      <author> (Daniel Cazzulino)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cazzulino.com/net6functions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 05:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>uBlock Origin—everything you need to know about the ad blocker - Firefox Add-on Reviews</title>
      <link>https://addons.mozilla.org/blog/ublock-origin-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-ad-blocker/</link>
      <description>Rare is the browser extension that can satisfy both passive and power users. But that’s an essential part of uBlock Origin’s brilliance—it is an ad blocker you could recommend to your most tech forward friend as easily as you could to someone who’s just emerged from the jungle lost for the past 20 years.&amp;#160; If […]</description>
      <author> (by Raymond Hill)</author>
      <guid>https://addons.mozilla.org/blog/ublock-origin-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-ad-blocker/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 05:04:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Made $80,000 On Side Projects In 2020 — Compiled;</title>
      <link>https://www.compiled.blog/blog/how-i-made-80000-in-2020</link>
      <description>Money is a taboo topic in many cultures, however I think it’s important to discuss how I was able to publish side projects that allowed me to pay off my overwhelming medical debt, buy a house, and build my savings.</description>
      <author> (Aug 26
            
            Written By Emma Bostian)</author>
      <guid>https://www.compiled.blog/blog/how-i-made-80000-in-2020</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 02:57:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core Blazor routing</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/aspnet/core/blazor/fundamentals/routing?view=aspnetcore-6.0#query-strings</link>
      <description>Learn how to manage request routing in apps and how to use the NavLink component in Blazor apps for navigation.</description>
      <author> (guardrex)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/aspnet/core/blazor/fundamentals/routing?view=aspnetcore-6.0#query-strings</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 01:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New evidence supports idea that America&amp;#39;s first civilization was made up of &amp;#39;sophisticated&amp;#39; engineers</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-09-evidence-idea-america-civilization-sophisticated.html</link>
      <description>The Native Americans who occupied the area known as Poverty Point in northern Louisiana more than 3,000 years ago long have been believed to be simple hunters and gatherers. But new Washington University in St. Louis archaeological findings paint a drastically different picture of America&amp;#39;s first civilization.</description>
      <author> (Washington University in St. Louis)</author>
      <guid>https://phys.org/news/2021-09-evidence-idea-america-civilization-sophisticated.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 00:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Practical tips to improve your users&amp;#39; experience</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=elktRChdHJw</link>
      <description>As humans we have limitations like perception, focus, concentration, distractions, you name it. With a simple mindset shift to start recognizing that there i...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=elktRChdHJw</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 00:06:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I declared my Windows Runtime method as accepting an array by reference, but it always arrives empty</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210903-00/?p=105644</link>
      <description>A customer was writing a Windows Runtime component that took as one of its parameters an array of strings. namespace Contoso {   runtimeclass Widget   {     Widget();     void SetMessages(ref String[] messages);   } }  They tried to pass an array of strings from C#:   Widget widget = new Widget();</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210903-00/?p=105644</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should Zcash switch from Proof of Work to Proof of Stake? - Electric Coin Company</title>
      <link>https://electriccoin.co/blog/should-zcash-switch-from-proof-of-work-to-proof-of-stake/</link>
      <description>ZEC is the engine driving the sustainable growth necessary to provide economic and social freedom for everyone.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://electriccoin.co/blog/should-zcash-switch-from-proof-of-work-to-proof-of-stake/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimal Viable Developer: acing your first month in software</title>
      <link>https://deberker.com/archy/minimal-viable-developer-acing-your-first-month-in-software/</link>
      <description>Get fast at contributing code and flourish in your first software role</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://deberker.com/archy/minimal-viable-developer-acing-your-first-month-in-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:05:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Design of Disasters and the Disaster of Design</title>
      <link>https://pre.hn/the-disaster-of-design</link>
      <description>In the days after Hurricane Ida, I&amp;#39;ve been thinking about how completely design and technology have failed us as disciplines.</description>
      <author> (Robert Prehn)</author>
      <guid>https://pre.hn/the-disaster-of-design</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow boring advice</title>
      <link>http://nywkap.com/other/follow-boring-advice.html</link>
      <description>Most of the advice leading to great results in life is boring. Also, it’s free and has forever been so. In my twenties, I believed that successful people hold secret knowledge leading to their success. I obsessed over “self-help porn”: books, videos, and blogs promising to reveal little secrets that would make me successful one day, too. But when I started observing and talking to people I consider successful, I noticed they don’t do anything extraordinary. In fact, they do quite the opposite. They follow “boring” advice I already heard a million times in proverbs, religious and old philosophy stories, and even from my grandma. And it makes sense!. It has already been figured out for thousands of years! There is nothing new a Brian can write in his next New York Times bestseller while sipping a $9 latte that I didn’t hear before. All I ever had to do is to act on that well-known advice. You know it in one form or another, too! Here are a couple of examples:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://nywkap.com/other/follow-boring-advice.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:05:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New UT/Texas Politics Project Poll finds Texans dour and deeply divided</title>
      <link>https://texaspolitics.utexas.edu/blog/new-uttexas-politics-project-poll-finds-texans-dour-and-deeply-divided</link>
      <description>The latest University of Texas/Texas Politics Project poll finds Texans in a dour mood colored by a resurgent COVID-19 virus, an economy recovering yet roiled by its impact, and state politics driven by increasingly entrenched and in many instances extreme partisanship, which is being accentuated by the Republican monopoly on state government. Texans expressed more worry about the surging pandemic and its effects than in June, and gave Governor Abbott the lowest job approval rating of his tenure in office. A majority – 52% –&amp;#160; said the state is headed in the wrong direction, the worst assessment of the direction of the state since the inception of this polling project in 2008.</description>
      <author> (By:&amp;#160;Jim HensonJoshua Blank)</author>
      <guid>https://texaspolitics.utexas.edu/blog/new-uttexas-politics-project-poll-finds-texans-dour-and-deeply-divided</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:05:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Illusion of Output - Keith Brown</title>
      <link>https://keithbrown.com/illusion-of-output/</link>
      <description>The 40-hour workweek has stood in as a poor replacement for well-written strategy and great middle management. That illusion is now gone.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://keithbrown.com/illusion-of-output/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:05:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Audio Augmentation with PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://jonathanbgn.com/2021/08/30/audio-augmentation.html</link>
      <description>No matter if you are training a model for automatic speech recognition or something more esoteric like recognizing birds from sound, you could benefit a lot from audio data augmentation. The idea is simple: by applying random transformations to your training examples, you can generate new examples for free and make your training dataset bigger.</description>
      <author> (Jonathan Boigne)</author>
      <guid>https://jonathanbgn.com/2021/08/30/audio-augmentation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosing memory leaks in .NET apps</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SHGeE_PFA4s</link>
      <description>In this episode, Software Engineer, Mike Rousos, joins Rich to show can we can use tools like dotnet-dump and Visual Studio to diagnose memory leaks in our ....</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •
  
  
    
      4.6K views
    
      2 weeks ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SHGeE_PFA4s</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quitting Your Dream Job (Twice)</title>
      <link>https://t3.gg/blog/posts/quitting</link>
      <description>Quitting is never easy. Building things can be. I&amp;#39;m leaving TTFM Labs to start a company.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://t3.gg/blog/posts/quitting</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenMoji</title>
      <link>https://openmoji.org/</link>
      <description>Open source emojis for designers, developers and everyone else!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://openmoji.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 21:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome to remove detailed cookie and site data controls</title>
      <link>https://lapcatsoftware.com/articles/chrome-cookie.html</link>
      <description>A month ago I ran into an obscure Google Chrome bug on macOS that caused the &amp;quot;All cookies and site data&amp;quot; page in Chrome settings (chrome://settings/siteData) to load very slowly. You can see this page if you open Preferences, select &amp;quot;Privacy and security&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Cookies and other site data&amp;quot;, and then &amp;quot;See all cookies and site data&amp;quot;. I filed a bug report with Chromium&amp;#39;s issue tracker. Since then, some members of the Chromium team have been trying to track down the cause of the bug, a normal and boring process. However, this week I got an update on the issue that was shocking to me:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lapcatsoftware.com/articles/chrome-cookie.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 21:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rejected internal applicants twice as likely to quit | Cornell Chronicle</title>
      <link>https://news.cornell.edu/stories/2021/08/rejected-internal-applicants-twice-likely-quit</link>
      <description>Internal job applicants who face rejection are nearly twice as likely to leave their organizations than those who were either hired for an internal job or had not applied for a new job at all, ILR School research finds.</description>
      <author> (By      
        
  

            Julie Greco

    




                        
    
       |)</author>
      <guid>https://news.cornell.edu/stories/2021/08/rejected-internal-applicants-twice-likely-quit</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 20:06:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>