<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>AI App Builders – Re-take –&amp;#160;TempoLabs - Nick&amp;#39;s .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/ai-app-builders-re-take-tempolabs/</link>
      <description>In my previous attempt with TempoLabs I was able to successfully build the ABN lookup scenario that I’d been testing with other app builders. I was prompted to take another look and I was even more impressed this time around. In order to do a comparison with my experience from my last attempt I started ... Read more</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/ai-app-builders-re-take-tempolabs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup-CTO-Handbook/StartupCTOHandbook.md at main &amp;#183; ZachGoldberg/Startup-CTO-Handbook</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ZachGoldberg/Startup-CTO-Handbook/blob/main/StartupCTOHandbook.md</link>
      <description>The Startup CTO&amp;#39;s Handbook, a book covering leadership, management and technical topics for leaders of software engineering teams - ZachGoldberg/Startup-CTO-Handbook</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ZachGoldberg/Startup-CTO-Handbook/blob/main/StartupCTOHandbook.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certificate Apocalypse: Bringing Your Chromecast Back from the Dead</title>
      <link>https://mensfeld.pl/2025/03/bringing-your-chromecast-back/</link>
      <description>Learn how to fix your Chromecast 2 that stopped working on March 9, 2025 due to an expired certificate. Simple workarounds for both regular and factory-reset devices until Google releases an official solution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mensfeld.pl/2025/03/bringing-your-chromecast-back/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why do LLMs fail to count letters in a word?</title>
      <link>https://anands.me/blog/why-do-llms-fail-to-count-letters</link>
      <description>Why do LLMs fail to count letters in a word? Here&amp;#39;s an easy way to understand. But let&amp;#39;s NOT do the famous </description>
      <author> (https://anands.me/about/)</author>
      <guid>https://anands.me/blog/why-do-llms-fail-to-count-letters</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5% in EU Innovation Funding Yields a 4,300% ROI</title>
      <link>https://www.karlsnotes.com/5-in-eu-innovation-funding-yields-a-4-300-roi/</link>
      <description>Some observations from a report on &amp;#39;Startups backed by the EU’s Framework Programmes&amp;#39;, recently released by dealroom.co, dealflow.eu, and EU Startups:

While only 5% of the EU innovation funding (about €12B) goes directly to startups, these same startups have raised an additional €70B in private capital and</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.karlsnotes.com/5-in-eu-innovation-funding-yields-a-4-300-roi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extrinsic termination proofs for well-founded recursion in Lean – Blog – Joachim Breitner&amp;#39;s Homepage</title>
      <link>https://www.joachim-breitner.de/blog/816-Extrinsic_termination_proofs_for_well-founded_recursion_in_Lean</link>
      <description>A few months ago I explained that one reason why this blog has become more quiet is that all my work on Lean is covered elsewhere.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.joachim-breitner.de/blog/816-Extrinsic_termination_proofs_for_well-founded_recursion_in_Lean</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Every Programming Language Sucks at Error Handling - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://blog.aiono.dev/posts/why-every-programming-language-sucks-at-error-handling---part-1.html</link>
      <description>Proper error handling is hard. It&amp;#39;s a concept since the inception of programming, yet solutions we have are hardly satisfying. When one tries to add proper error handling into their code it gets much more complicated than just implementing the happy path. Part of it is inescapable because it&amp;#39;s essential complexity, but part of the complication is not necessary hence accidental complexity. A lot of production code either ignores errors or simply accumulate them to the top level with a generic error message. It&amp;#39;s very rare that all possible error cases are even considered before implementation, let alone reflected in the code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.aiono.dev/posts/why-every-programming-language-sucks-at-error-handling---part-1.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering reasoning LLMs: Notes and Observations</title>
      <link>https://www.thelis.org/blog/reasoning-model-notes</link>
      <description>Engineering reasoning LLMs: Notes and Observations</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.thelis.org/blog/reasoning-model-notes</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Staff+ Performance Cliff</title>
      <link>https://sylormiller.com/posts/2025/staff-plus-cliff/</link>
      <description>When Staff+ engineers transition from a team lead to an org-level lead, the increased ambiguity often leads to feeling lost and overwhelmed. This article explores the &amp;quot;Performance Cliff&amp;quot; phenomenon and offers practical strategies to adapt, stay organized, and redefine success in a leadership role.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sylormiller.com/posts/2025/staff-plus-cliff/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Research Topics for the Rest of Us | Engin Arslan</title>
      <link>https://www.enginarslan.com/posts/deep-research-topics-for-the-rest-of-us</link>
      <description>Engin Arslan - Software developer, teacher, entrepreneur</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.enginarslan.com/posts/deep-research-topics-for-the-rest-of-us</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dangers of an IDE</title>
      <link>https://jensrantil.github.io/posts/integrated-development-environments-harmful/</link>
      <description>A modern IDE constantly nudges you to couple your code in a bad way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jensrantil.github.io/posts/integrated-development-environments-harmful/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe, the Digital Colony</title>
      <link>https://molnett.com/blog/posts/25-03-11-eu-digital-colony</link>
      <description>Digital colonisation is happening before our eyes. We&amp;#39;re sleepwalking into a digital dependency that puts our hospitals, schools, and government services at risk.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://molnett.com/blog/posts/25-03-11-eu-digital-colony</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital sufficiency: The right amount of technology</title>
      <link>https://the-way-of-emacs.com/posts/digital-sufficiency.html</link>
      <description>March 11, 2025</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://the-way-of-emacs.com/posts/digital-sufficiency.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth Functional Logic for Hackers - Part One</title>
      <link>https://lagomor.ph/2025/02/truth-functional-logic-for-hackers-part-one/</link>
      <description>Bob and Alice are two hackers working on an embedded system with a severe computational constraint - there is a bug in their low-cost microcontroller making OR operations significantly slower than any other operation on the chipset.
When they profiled their micropython code, they found that OR operations were up to 5x slower than any other operation.
Alice This is a big problem! We could replace the faulty chips with better ones, if they arrive before the deadline. Bob I don’t think we can afford to wait - the deadline is in 3 days. A better option is to rewrite the code to avoid the OR operation. Alice How could we do that? We’re using the OR operation in a lot of critical places. Look: def authorize_access(request): # A user is denied if they are on a blacklist OR # their account is expired if (user_is_blacklisted(request.user_id) or account_is_expired(request.account) return &amp;quot;Access denied&amp;quot; return &amp;quot;Access granted&amp;quot; Let’s take a moment to understand the problem. The authorize_access function is used to check if a user is authorized to access a resource. The or operation is used to combine the conditions. How could we rewrite this function to avoid the OR operation?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lagomor.ph/2025/02/truth-functional-logic-for-hackers-part-one/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&amp;#39;s not cheating if you write the video game solver yourself | Robert Heaton</title>
      <link>https://robertheaton.com/cocoon/</link>
      <description>My wife and two little boys sometimes go on trips to see friends or family for whom my presence isn’t strictly required. While my wife books the flights I make a show of weighing up my options and asking if it’s really OK if I don’t come. Eventually I’m persuaded that it truly would be the best thing for all of us for me to have five to seven days to myself with no nappies and all Nintendo.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robertheaton.com/cocoon/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Components Are Just Sparkling Hooks</title>
      <link>https://www.bbss.dev/posts/sparkling-hooks/</link>
      <description>Here’s a question you might encounter while interviewing for React developer roles:
“What is the difference between a component and a hook?”
The answer that the interviewer is likely looking for is along the lines of “A component is a building block for the UI, and hooks are utility functions provided by React to manage state and side-effects &amp;#128564;”.
It’s a satisfactory answer if your goal is to find employment. But if you want to make an impression, the more daring answer is: “There is no difference &amp;#128293;”.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bbss.dev/posts/sparkling-hooks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 50% of Android Apps use Mobile Trackers – James O&amp;#39;Claire</title>
      <link>https://jamesoclaire.com/2025/03/11/nearly-50-of-android-apps-use-mobile-trackers/</link>
      <description>There are 5 large mobile app trackers, also called MMPs. Those are AppsFlyer, Adjust (owned by AppLovin), Branch and Yandex AppMetrica.  These mobile attribution companies track users data across many apps. For Android nearly 50% of all apps contain a mobile app tracker and for iOS a bit less at 1 in 4 apps. This number of course skews much higher for apps and games that spend money on advertising to gain users and thus rely on mobile app attribution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jamesoclaire.com/2025/03/11/nearly-50-of-android-apps-use-mobile-trackers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Web Development Guide For Clients | My Blog | Enindu Alahapperuma</title>
      <link>https://enindu.com/blog/ultimate-web-development-guide-for-clients</link>
      <description>I come across numerous web development groups on Facebook every day. These groups are filled with people—some searching for web developers at low prices, whi...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://enindu.com/blog/ultimate-web-development-guide-for-clients</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe coding is not coding</title>
      <link>https://www.toolongautomated.com/posts/2025/vibe-coding-is-not-coding.html</link>
      <description>LLMs make it possible to directly translate human language into code, making them valuable proxies that can express what we mean in a source code.</description>
      <author> (Bartosz Miselis)</author>
      <guid>https://www.toolongautomated.com/posts/2025/vibe-coding-is-not-coding.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flipping the switch on far-UVC</title>
      <link>https://www.worksinprogress.news/p/flipping-the-switch-on-far-uvc</link>
      <description>We’ve known about far-UVC’s promise for a decade. Why isn&amp;#39;t it everywhere?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.worksinprogress.news/p/flipping-the-switch-on-far-uvc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Rotately Works | Browser-Based Video Rotation</title>
      <link>https://rotately.live/blog/how-it-works.html</link>
      <description>Learn how Rotately works to rotate your videos quickly and securely, directly in your browser without uploading them anywhere.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rotately.live/blog/how-it-works.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kratix for Database Management: A Step-by-Step Guide to Amazon RDS Deployment</title>
      <link>https://www.syntasso.io/post/kratix-for-database-management-a-step-by-step-guide-to-amazon-rds-deployment</link>
      <description>As a platform engineer, your team launched a new application, and demand is growing rapidly. Thousands of users are signing up, so you must create multiple RDS instances with varying RDS instance types: one for testing, another for staging, and another for production.However, setting up these databases takes too much time. You must go through the console&amp;#160;or use IaC, apply the correct configurations, apply security policies, and ensure everything is correct. This process requires significant time</description>
      <author> (Obusor Ezekiel Umesi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.syntasso.io/post/kratix-for-database-management-a-step-by-step-guide-to-amazon-rds-deployment</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Language Models Understand Nullability</title>
      <link>https://dmodel.ai/nullability/</link>
      <description>The last five years have shown us that large language models, like
ChatGPT, Claude, and DeepSeek, can effectively write programs in many
domains. This is an impressive capability, given that writing programs
involves having a formal understanding of program semantics. But though
we know that these large models understand programs to an extent, we
still don’t know many things about these models’ understanding. We don’t
know where they have deep understanding and where they use heuristic
reasoning, how they represents program knowledge, and what kinds of
situations will challenge their capabilities.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dmodel.ai/nullability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An early look at Nix Dynamic Derivations</title>
      <link>https://fzakaria.com/2025/03/10/an-early-look-at-nix-dynamic-derivations</link>
      <description>I normally like to write about concepts from first principles and wait for much of the dust to have settled on the implementation details, but let me take you on a small tour of an upcoming feature instead.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fzakaria.com/2025/03/10/an-early-look-at-nix-dynamic-derivations</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Write more blog articles, not fewer (Don’t leave the scraps on the cutting floor)</title>
      <link>https://rmoff.net/2025/03/11/write-more-blog-articles-not-fewer-dont-leave-the-scraps-on-the-cutting-floor/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rmoff.net/2025/03/11/write-more-blog-articles-not-fewer-dont-leave-the-scraps-on-the-cutting-floor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The prevalance of productivity porn | Jannes on the web</title>
      <link>https://jannestimm.com/posts/productivity-porn/</link>
      <description>Productivity porn is becoming ever more prevalent in our lifes.</description>
      <author> (Jannes Timm)</author>
      <guid>https://jannestimm.com/posts/productivity-porn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switching to BunnyCDN in Less Than 2 Hours | Jonathan&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://jonathan-frere.com/posts/switching-to-bunny-cdn</link>
      <description>Given some recent, uh, instability in US politics, and given that everyone likes an underdog, I’ve been looking at European alternatives to my current hosting situation, which is Cloudflare.
After looking through european-alternatives.eu, and reading some opinions on Bluesky, I figured I’d try out BunnyCDN, which is a CDN service based in Slovenia. The process of completely switching over to BunnyCDN was remarkably easy, and took a little under two hours to set up.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jonathan-frere.com/posts/switching-to-bunny-cdn</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET and .NET Framework March 2025 servicing releases updates - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-and-dotnet-framework-march-2025-servicing-updates/</link>
      <description>A recap of the latest servicing updates for .NET and .NET Framework for March 2025.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-and-dotnet-framework-march-2025-servicing-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 23:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform Live Coding: Looking at Wasm binding and ContentControl loading issues</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=8KHM9Mxd87k</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io</description>
      <author> (Uno Platform)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=8KHM9Mxd87k</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6   Intro to Semantic Kernel</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=0pXmrWmYJmI</link>
      <description>Get a subscription and improve your career: https://courses.devs.school

In this course, you will learn what Semantic Kernel is and how you can use it for generating text, images, audio, transcriptions, and more.

Content:

00:00:00 - What is Semantic Kernel?
00:05:21 - Components in Semantic Kernel
00:06:37 - Benefits and use cases
00:09:28 - Setting up a project in VS 2022 with Semantic Kernel
00:14:04 - Understanding the Kernel as an orchestrator
00:16:09 - The Builder pattern
00:19:17 - Demonstration of the Builder pattern
00:23:32 - Creating an API Key to connect with OpenAI
00:26:31 - Creating an API Key to connect with Azure OpenAI
00:30:00 - Creating the project, environment variables, and Kernels
00:40:07 - Chat completion using Semantic Kernel
00:46:02 - Chat completion streaming using Semantic Kernel
00:49:37 - Generating images using Semantic Kernel
01:03:36 - Generating audio files using Semantic Kernel
01:14:51 - Extracting text from audio using Semantic Kernel</description>
      <author> (Devs School)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=0pXmrWmYJmI</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factorio Learning Environment</title>
      <link>https://jackhopkins.github.io/factorio-learning-environment/</link>
      <description>Mine 16 Iron Oreper minute</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jackhopkins.github.io/factorio-learning-environment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 10x Faster TypeScript - TypeScript</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/typescript-native-port/</link>
      <description>Embarking on a native port of the existing TypeScript compiler and toolset to achieve a 10x performance speed-up.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/typescript-native-port/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cronjob vs systemd timers - how to create a systemd timer</title>
      <link>https://ryansouthgate.com/systemd-timer/</link>
      <description>cronjobs have a new contender. In this post I create a new simple systemd timer and compare with cronjobs</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ryansouthgate.com/systemd-timer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTTP Methods: The Verbs That Make the Web Go Round - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/http-methods-the-verbs-that-make-the-web-go-round/</link>
      <description>If HTTP were a language, its methods—also known as verbs—would be the action words that keep the internet running. Every time you load a webpage, submit a form, or delete a post, you&amp;#39;re using one of these methods. Understanding them is key to working with web APIs, debugging issues, and just generally feeling like a web wizard. Let’s break them down.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/http-methods-the-verbs-that-make-the-web-go-round/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why AI Adoption is Critical Now?</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=19fgD3kVQuw</link>
      <description>In this video, we explore why AI adoption is essential for businesses today and how companies that don&amp;#39;t adapt risk falling behind.

#ai   #techtransformation   #businessgrowth   #futureofwork</description>
      <author> (Volosoft)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=19fgD3kVQuw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap Themes and .NET Aspire</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=esB89aYCrBw</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Fritz is working on SharpSite, an open-source CMS we&amp;#39;re building live on stream.  https://sharpsite.org</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=esB89aYCrBw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Deploy Your .NET Application To Azure Using GitHub Actions (2025)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=6qPzeB0dN9o</link>
      <description>Master REST APIs: https://dub.sh/rest-cicd
Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Get the source code here: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic

Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=6qPzeB0dN9o</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer convicted for “kill switch” code activated upon his termination</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2025/03/fired-coder-faces-10-years-for-revenge-kill-switch-he-named-after-himself/</link>
      <description>Software developer plans to appeal after admitting to planting malicious code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2025/03/fired-coder-faces-10-years-for-revenge-kill-switch-he-named-after-himself/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>