<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>From Anemic Models to Behavior-Driven Models: A Practical DDD Refactor in C#</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/from-anemic-models-to-behavior-driven-models-a-practical-ddd-refactor-in-csharp</link>
      <description>A practical guide to transforming anemic domain models into behavior-rich aggregates in C# through incremental refactoring, enhancing code maintainability and business rule clarity.</description>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/from-anemic-models-to-behavior-driven-models-a-practical-ddd-refactor-in-csharp</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 01:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending my edit web page bookmarklet | James' Coffee Blog</title>
      <link>https://jamesg.blog/2025/05/09/extending-my-edit-web-page-bookmarklet</link>
      <description>I have a bookmarklet called “Edit” which, when clicked, takes me to the editing page of GitHub that corresponds to the page on my website that I am viewing.</description>
      <guid>https://jamesg.blog/2025/05/09/extending-my-edit-web-page-bookmarklet</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fix That Let Us Run the Biggest Open Models Overnight</title>
      <link>https://www.basisset.com/the-fix-that-let-us-run-the-biggest-open-models-overnight</link>
      <description>We hit GPU limits with every new model until we found a better way. Here's how we cut costs and seamlessly swapped in open-source LLMs like Qwen3 and Llama 4 using Parasail.</description>
      <guid>https://www.basisset.com/the-fix-that-let-us-run-the-biggest-open-models-overnight</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreground segmentation with JBIG2 for improved PDF compression: pdf-segmented</title>
      <link>https://yingtongli.me/blog/2025/05/09/pdf-segmented.html</link>
      <description>JBIG2 is an efficient image compression format for bi-level (bi-tonal) images, which is supported by the PDF file format and common PDF viewers. To date, tooling for producing documents using JBIG2 (particularly open source tooling) has been limited; I have previously presented file-jbig2pdf, a GIMP plugin for generating PDF files using JBIG2. This suffices for simple black-and-white documents, but does not assist when documents contain both black-and-white text and colour graphics.</description>
      <guid>https://yingtongli.me/blog/2025/05/09/pdf-segmented.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Performance Investigation Challenge — Matthew Gaudet</title>
      <link>https://www.mgaudet.ca/technical/2025/5/9/a-performance-investigation-challenge</link>
      <description>I really liked matklad’s Performance Visualization challenge (partially because it didn’t take me long to find the line with samply, which made me feel good).</description>
      <guid>https://www.mgaudet.ca/technical/2025/5/9/a-performance-investigation-challenge</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too much magic</title>
      <link>https://willmcgugan.github.io/too-much-magic/</link>
      <description>A common criticisms of frameworks like Textual is that they have “too much magic”.</description>
      <guid>https://willmcgugan.github.io/too-much-magic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reason 1,000,001 why OpenAI sucks - blog.thms.uk</title>
      <link>https://blog.thms.uk/2025/05/openai-sucks</link>
      <description>After days of debugging unexplained span usage in Sentry - despite an ultra-low sampling rate - I discovered `traceparent` headers in requests traced back to OpenAI. Turns out, it's always AI.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.thms.uk/2025/05/openai-sucks</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shut up, Siri - Christopher Butler</title>
      <link>https://www.chrbutler.com/shut-up-siri-post-screen-future</link>
      <description>Every day I see a new thinkpiece on “the post-screen future” or “UI-less design” or “the end of the click.” I even used to write things like that.</description>
      <guid>https://www.chrbutler.com/shut-up-siri-post-screen-future</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A decade of employment - blakewatson.com</title>
      <link>https://blakewatson.com/journal/a-decade-of-employment/</link>
      <description>I celebrate ten years of being employed by looking back at the difficult journey it took to get there.</description>
      <guid>https://blakewatson.com/journal/a-decade-of-employment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live Topic: Build and Run AI-powered .NET Apps Anywhere with ONNX Runtime</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=587fR17jvVc</link>
      <description>Do you need a cross-platform AI engine that optimizes and accelerates machine learning models, including large language models? In this week's episode, Microsoft MVP Hayden Barnes shows us how to build cross-platform AI-powered applications using .NET, Windows Subsystem for Linux, and the ONNX Runtime.

🎙️ Featuring: Hayden Barnes

#ai #llm #onnx</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=587fR17jvVc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Zero by Rocicorp</title>
      <link>https://www.solberg.is/zero</link>
      <description>I’ve been diving into Zero, the new query-powered sync engine, and I'm genuinely impressed. It’s still in alpha, so things are evolving, but the core ideas are incredibly compelling for building fast, reactive web apps.</description>
      <guid>https://www.solberg.is/zero</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titles Don’t Matter (To You), But They Sure Matter to Your Client - David Raistrick</title>
      <link>https://davidraistrick.com/blog/2025-05-09-titles-matter/</link>
      <description>Why the title you use as a fractional leader can significantly impact your client's success</description>
      <guid>https://davidraistrick.com/blog/2025-05-09-titles-matter/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You should have private evals</title>
      <link>https://thundergolfer.com/blog/private-evals</link>
      <description>Everybody should have a personal set of test prompts to try on LLMs.</description>
      <guid>https://thundergolfer.com/blog/private-evals</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transactions as Transformers</title>
      <link>https://will62794.github.io/databases/transactions/isolation/2025/05/04/transformers-not-transactions.html</link>
      <description>Database transactions are traditionally modeled as a sequence of read/write operations on a set of keys, where each read operation returns some value and each write sets a key to some value. This is reflected in most of the formalisms that define various transactional isolation semantics (Adya, Crooks, etc.).</description>
      <guid>https://will62794.github.io/databases/transactions/isolation/2025/05/04/transformers-not-transactions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've been here the whole time</title>
      <link>https://brianredbeard.com/blog/ive_been_here_the_whole_time/</link>
      <description>A key inspiration for this post is Sam Reich, who lives in my general neighborhood.
Reich has spent seven seasons of the show "Game Changer" (Wikipedia) reminding everyone of a single crucial detail:
Sam: thanks for the reminder that there's always some troll hanging out. 😅 The current tech climate often focuses on uncovering vulnerabilities. So, in that spirit, let's dive in.
And so this tale will surely end well, won't it?</description>
      <guid>https://brianredbeard.com/blog/ive_been_here_the_whole_time/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheating my social anxiety with T-Shirts | Nayan Gautam</title>
      <link>https://gtmnayan.com/blog/000-tshirts-social-anxiety/</link>
      <description>How funny t-shirts helped me overcome my fear of talking to strangers and make friends</description>
      <guid>https://gtmnayan.com/blog/000-tshirts-social-anxiety/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pascal's Law</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3087/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3087/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and Programming: The Beginning of a New Era</title>
      <link>https://www.oreilly.com/radar/ai-and-programming-the-beginning-of-a-new-era/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://www.oreilly.com/radar/ai-and-programming-the-beginning-of-a-new-era/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 20:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALICE detects the conversion of lead into gold at the LHC</title>
      <link>https://www.home.cern/news/news/physics/alice-detects-conversion-lead-gold-lhc</link>
      <description>In a paper published in Physical Review Journals, the ALICE collaboration reports measurements that quantify the transmutation of lead into gold in CERN’s Large Hadron Collider (LHC). Transforming the base metal lead into the precious metal gold was a dream of medieval alchemists. This long-standing quest, known as chrysopoeia, may have been motivated by the observation that dull grey, relatively abundant lead is of a similar density to gold, which has long been coveted for its beautiful colour and rarity. It was only much later that it became clear that lead and gold are distinct chemical elements and that chemical methods are powerless to transmute one into the other. With the dawn of nuclear physics in the 20th century, it was discovered that heavy elements could transform into others, either naturally, by radioactive decay, or in the laboratory, under a bombardment of neutrons or protons. Though gold has been artificially produced in this way before, the ALICE collaboration has now measured the transmutation of lead into gold by a new mechanism involving near-miss collisions between lead nuclei at the LHC. Extremely high-energy collisions between lead nuclei at the LHC can create quark–gluon plasma, a hot and dense state of matter that is thought to have filled the universe around a millionth of a second after the Big Bang, giving rise to the matter we now know. However, in the far more frequent interactions where the nuclei just miss each other without “touching”, the intense electromagnetic fields surrounding them can induce photon–photon and photon–nucleus interactions that open further avenues of exploration. The electromagnetic field emanating from a lead nucleus is particularly strong because the nucleus contains 82 protons, each carrying one elementary charge. Moreover, the very high speed at which lead nuclei travel in the LHC (corresponding to 99.999993% of the speed of light) causes the electromagnetic field lines to be squashed into a thin pancake, transverse to the direction of motion, producing a short-lived pulse of photons. Often, this triggers a process called electromagnetic dissociation, whereby a photon interacting with a nucleus can excite oscillations of its internal structure, resulting in the ejection of small numbers of neutrons and protons. To create gold (a nucleus containing 79 protons), three protons must be removed from a lead nucleus in the LHC beams. “It is impressive to see that our detectors can handle head-on collisions producing thousands of particles, while also being sensitive to collisions where only a few particles are produced at a time, enabling the study of electromagnetic ‘nuclear transmutation’ processes,” says Marco Van Leeuwen, ALICE spokesperson. The ALICE team used the detector’s zero degree calorimeters (ZDC) to count the number of photon–nucleus interactions that resulted in the emission of zero, one, two and three protons accompanied by at least one neutron, which are associated with the production of lead, thallium, mercury and gold, respectively. While less frequent than the creation of thallium or mercury, the results show that the LHC currently produces gold at a maximum rate of about 89 000 nuclei per second from lead–lead collisions at the ALICE collision point. Gold nuclei emerge from the collision with very high energy and hit the LHC beam pipe or collimators at various points downstream, where they immediately fragment into single protons, neutrons and other particles. The gold exists for just a tiny fraction of a second. The ALICE analysis shows that, during Run 2 of the LHC (2015–2018), about 86 billion gold nuclei were created at the four major experiments. In terms of mass, this corresponds to just 29 picograms (2.9 ×10-11 g). Since the luminosity in the LHC is continually increasing thanks to regular upgrades to the machines, Run 3 has produced almost double the amount of gold that Run 2 did, but the total still amounts to trillions of times less than would be required to make a piece of jewellery. While the dream of medieval alchemists has technically come true, their hopes of riches have once again been dashed. “Thanks to the unique capabilities of the ALICE ZDCs, the present analysis is the first to systematically detect and analyse the signature of gold production at the LHC experimentally,” says Uliana Dmitrieva of the ALICE collaboration. “The results also test and improve theoretical models of electromagnetic dissociation which, beyond their intrinsic physics interest, are used to understand and predict beam losses that are a major limit on the performance of the LHC and future colliders,” adds John Jowett, also of the ALICE collaboration. Additional image:  Illustration of an ultra-peripheral collision where the two lead (208Pb) ion beams at the LHC pass by close to each other without colliding. In the electromagnetic dissociation process, a photon interacting with a nucleus can excite oscillations of its internal structure and result in the ejection of small numbers of neutrons (two) and protons (three), leaving the gold (203Au) nucleus behind (Image: CERN)  </description>
      <guid>https://www.home.cern/news/news/physics/alice-detects-conversion-lead-gold-lhc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 19:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 9 🔥🚀 : ASP.NET Core Webhooks</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=eBrElmGDai0</link>
      <description>In this video we will discussed how we can implement .NET webooks

Support me on Patreon to access the source code:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand

Base App: https://youtu.be/NNiupSwiVfg

Let us connect:
🌍  My website  - https://mohamadlawand.com
📸  Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/mohamadlawand087/
🐦  Twitter - https://twitter.com/moe23
♯     Github - https://github.com/mohamadlawand087
🎫 LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/mlawand
💥 LinkTree - https://linktr.ee/mohamadlawand
Discord - https://discord.gg/KEepAhxTeu

Gear I use  (affiliate link): https://amzn.to/3EbT8Jw

Support my work:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand
https://www.buymeacoffee.com/mohamadlawand

Hire Me:
https://transactions.sendowl.com/products/78999951/625477F1/view

WHO AM I:
I'm Mohamad, a Enterprise Architect working in Manchester, UK. I make videos about web, cloud, desktop and mobile development. 

GET IN TOUCH:
If you’d like to talk, I’d love to hear from you. Tweeting @moe23 directly will be the quickest way to get a response, but if your question is very long, feel free to email me at hello@mohamadlawand.com.

#dotnet   #api   #webhooks</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=eBrElmGDai0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 19:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design Patterns Unveiled  It's All About Separation! #coding #aws #serverless #softwareengineering</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=-sbwYCOW29I</link>
      <description>Avoid the pitfalls of monolithic code by separating business logic from infrastructure concerns.

Learn why a clean separation of concerns is vital for maintainable and adaptable code, regardless of whether you're using .NET, Node.js, Python, or Rust. By the end, you'll understand how to make your code more testable, scalable, and adaptable to changes in deployment environments.


@serverlessjames</description>
      <author> (James Eastham)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=-sbwYCOW29I</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 18:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Figma threatens companies using "Dev Mode"</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=P73EGVfKNr0</link>
      <description>Figma just did one of the most absurd things I've ever seen. They've done some sketchy stuff behind the scenes before, but nothing like this...

Want to sponsor a video? Learn more here: https://soydev.link/sponsor-me

SOURCES
https://x.com/theo/status/1912205144885997580?s=46
https://uspto.report/TM/98045640
https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/figma-confidentially-files-us-ipo-2025-04-15/

Check out my Twitch, Twitter, Discord more at https://t3.gg

S/O Ph4se0n3 for the awesome edit 🙏</description>
      <author> (Theo - t3․gg)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=P73EGVfKNr0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Powerhouse PC for under $600?! MINISFORUM UM880 Plus Mini PC Review - Ryzen 7, 1TB SSD, 32GB RAM!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=WRF_rOh4vLE</link>
      <description>Buy UM880 Plus AMD Ryzen 7 - https://amzn.to/3ZayBzJ
Buy NAB9 Plus Intel Core i9 - https://amzn.to/4m7s5Uq

Let's take a look at a super cute, super affordable mini PC from MINISFORUM, the UM880 Plus that is packed with features including a Ryzen 7 8845HS, 32GB DDR5 RAM, 1TB SSD, an OCuLink Port for external GPUs, a bunch of ports and a 2.5GB Enternet port!??! All for around $600! Is it any good? Is it a good dev device? Let's take a quick look.

Buy UM880 Plus AMD Ryzen 7 - https://amzn.to/3ZayBzJ
Buy NAB9 Plus Intel Core i9 - https://amzn.to/4m7s5Uq

Chatpers:
00:00 - Intro
00:45 - Unboxing &amp; Overview
03:38 - Specs &amp; Benchmarks
05:00 - Compiling Code
06:15 - Thoughts, Review, &amp; Wrap-up

MINISFORUM provided me this machine completely free of charge, but had no influence over this review and did not see it before I posted. Thanks to MINISFORUM for sending me this unit.

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCENTmbKaTphpWV2R2evVz2A/join

👕 Buy some swag! - https://jamesmontemagno.myspreadshop.com/
☕️ Buy me a coffee - https://www.buymeacoffee.com/jamesmontemagno

Follow:
👨‍💻 GitHub: https://github.com/jamesmontemagno
🦜 X: https://x.com/jamesmontemagno
📄 Website: https://www.montemagno.com
📰 Newsletter: https://newsletter.montemagno.com/

Disclaimer: This channel, videos, and streams are created in my spare time and are a product of me... James Montemagno! They are NOT officially affiliated or endorsed by Microsoft (my employer) in any way. Opinions and views are my own.

What is on my hat? It is the CLE clothing logo because I am from Cleveland! Checkout their awesome CLE merch: https://cleclothingco.myshopify.com/

What is that art on my wall? It is an original piece from the French street artist Gregos of La Butte Montmartre: https://www.instagram.com/p/BceZ1oNHiQx/

My Setup:
📷 Canon M50 Mark II - https://amzn.to/3P8R7lp
💡 Nanoleaf Elements Lights - https://amzn.to/3umwJVW
🎙 Blue Spark Microphone - https://amzn.to/3qgtYkq
🎙 Blue Pop Filter - https://amzn.to/3jEWM3r
🤳 Rode Microphone Arm - https://amzn.to/2Z68AlE
🎧 Sony MDR7306 Headphones - https://amzn.to/372jxta
📲 Stream Deck - https://amzn.to/373Uk1n
🖱 MX Master 2S Mouse - https://amzn.to/3d7J2gj
⌨️ Tecware Phantom Keyboard - https://amzn.to/3aUP4y9

Using links I provide I may receive a commission if you buy something which helps support the channel.

#miniforum #macmini #review #um880plus</description>
      <author> (James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=WRF_rOh4vLE</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Changing LINQ Updates in .NET 9</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=v2KQ0oEaU4c</link>
      <description>.NET 9 takes LINQ to the next level! Say goodbye to GroupBy performance issues. In this video, we explore the new CountBy and AggregateBy methods, delivering faster and cleaner code.

Full video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ejhytCyOMhk&amp;t=1784s
Our website: https://abp.io 

#linq  #dotnet9  #codingtips  #csharp  #abp #abpframework</description>
      <author> (Volosoft)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=v2KQ0oEaU4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Docker with Redis and C# in 10 Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=rb8PijbwHXE</link>
      <description>I've put out a bunch of videos now on data access patterns in C#, and one of the exciting things we have to work with in ASP NET Core is of course... caching!

The most popular key-value store that developers work with is Redis -- an excellent choice for your distributed cache. I figured we'd get up and running with Docker and Redis in just a few minutes!

----
Timestamps:

0:00 - Intro
0:55 - Docker Desktop Download
1:37 - Getting Redis
3:14 - Running BUT There's an Issue
4:03 - C# Project Setup
5:11 - Exploring The Code
6:22 - Dometrain Courses!
6:47 - Run The Example
7:53 - Identify and Fix the Error
10:08 - Proving State is Maintained
10:48 - Summary
----
🔑 Membership &amp; Subscriptions:
- 📨 Weekly Newsletter: https://weekly.devleader.ca
- 🏘️ Private Discord Community: https://sidestack.io/devleader

🧠 Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Get Promoted As A Software Engineer: https://dometrain.com/course/career-getting-promoted-as-a-software-engineer/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?ref=nick-cosentino
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

🗣️ Social Media &amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs:  @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp; Products/Services That I Love:
- @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper Opus Clip: https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----

#softwareengineering #softwaredeveloper #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=rb8PijbwHXE</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-Driven .NET: Building a Publish/Subscribe System with RabbitMQ</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=daaiAjZnOm4</link>
      <description>Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Get the source code here: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic

Want to use RabbitMQ in your .NET apps but not sure how to route messages correctly?

In this video, I’ll walk you through key messaging patterns using RabbitMQ + .NET, including:

✅ Competing consumers pattern
✅ Broadcasting messages to multiple consumers
✅ Using queues vs. exchanges
✅ Setting up fan-out, direct, and topic exchanges
✅ Practical RabbitMQ code with the official .NET client
✅ A complete example with a producer, multiple consumers, and a real RabbitMQ instance in Docker
✅ Visual insights using the RabbitMQ Management UI

If you're building distributed systems or microservices with .NET, understanding RabbitMQ exchanges is critical for scalable messaging.

Bonus: I’ll also show you how to structure a robust broker topology using exchanges and queue bindings to scale message delivery cleanly.

Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters
0:00 Competing consumers pattern
3:12 Solving competing consumers? Kinda...
5:54 RabbitMQ Exchanges
8:23 Implementing Fanout Exchanges</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=daaiAjZnOm4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LegoGPT: Generating Physically Stable and Buildable LEGO Designs from Text</title>
      <link>https://avalovelace1.github.io/LegoGPT/</link>
      <description>LegoGPT generates a LEGO structure from a user-provided text prompt in an end-to-end manner. Notably, our generated LEGO structure is physically stable and buildable.</description>
      <guid>https://avalovelace1.github.io/LegoGPT/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>