<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>I'm Done With Social Media</title>
      <link>https://www.carolinecrampton.com/im-done-with-social-media/</link>
      <description>Or: why I have a blog now.</description>
      <guid>https://www.carolinecrampton.com/im-done-with-social-media/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Error Handling in ASP.NET Core: From Middleware to Modern Handlers</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/global-error-handling-in-aspnetcore-from-middleware-to-modern-handlers</link>
      <description>Learn How to handle errors globally in ASP.NET Core using middleware, IProblemDetailsService, and the new IExceptionHandler in .NET 8. This week's issue walks you through pragmatic approaches to error handling, with real-world tips for validation, chaining, and observability.</description>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/global-error-handling-in-aspnetcore-from-middleware-to-modern-handlers</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 01:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win, lose, or draw: trends in English football match results</title>
      <link>https://blog.engora.com/2025/06/english-football-data.html</link>
      <description>Win, lose, or draw: trends in English football match results</description>
      <guid>https://blog.engora.com/2025/06/english-football-data.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Rite/Pantone Spectrophotometer Unlock</title>
      <link>https://adam.zeloof.xyz/2025/07/10/x-rite-pantone-spectrophotometer-unlock/</link>
      <description>I recently came across a couple of X-Rite/Pantone RM200 spectrophotometers on eBay for cheap. No power-on test, no cable, and no packaging, but for $20 each I had to buy them. The devices — t…</description>
      <guid>https://adam.zeloof.xyz/2025/07/10/x-rite-pantone-spectrophotometer-unlock/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Postgres Replication Slots: Preventing WAL Bloat and Other Production Issues</title>
      <link>https://www.morling.dev/blog/mastering-postgres-replication-slots/</link>
      <description>
Over the last couple of years, I’ve helped dozens of users and organizations to build Change Data Capture (CDC) pipelines for their Postgres databases. A key concern in that process is setting up and managing replication slots, which are Postgres' mechanism for making sure that any segments of the write-ahead log (WAL) of the database are kept around until they have been processed by registered replication consumers.


When not being careful, a replication slot may cause unduly large amounts of WAL segments to be retained by the database. This post describes best practices helping to prevent this and other issues, discussing aspects like heartbeats, replication slot failover, monitoring, the management of Postgres publications, and more. While this is primarily based on my experience of using replication slots via Debezium’s Postgres connector, the principles are generally applicable and are worth considering also when using other CDC tools for Postgres based on logical replication.
</description>
      <guid>https://www.morling.dev/blog/mastering-postgres-replication-slots/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ULTIMATE AI Coding Guide for Developers (Claude Code)</title>
      <link>https://www.sabrina.dev/p/ultimate-ai-coding-guide-claude-code</link>
      <description>How I use Claude Code to implement new features in an existing complex codebase.</description>
      <guid>https://www.sabrina.dev/p/ultimate-ai-coding-guide-claude-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fabio Manganiello (@fabio@manganiello.social)</title>
      <link>https://manganiello.social/notice/Aw0O4ueJ0ilKz9ZDhA</link>
      <description>This is why I got frustrated with #IoT after many years of enthusiasm.  In an ideal world, all devices should seamlessly talk to each other, with no need for too many bridges, apps and intermediari...</description>
      <guid>https://manganiello.social/notice/Aw0O4ueJ0ilKz9ZDhA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Neural Nets better, post 5 of N -- Code Assistant shootout</title>
      <link>http://addxorrol.blogspot.com/2025/07/understand-neural-nets-better-post-5-of.html</link>
      <description>In a series of previous blogposts [ 1 , 2 ,  3 , 4 ] I ran some experiments drawing the boundaries of the polytopes generated by a fully-con...</description>
      <guid>http://addxorrol.blogspot.com/2025/07/understand-neural-nets-better-post-5-of.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Converting Your REST APIs to MCP</title>
      <link>https://www.jlowin.dev/blog/stop-converting-rest-apis-to-mcp</link>
      <description>Your auto-generated MCP is bad, and you should feel bad.</description>
      <guid>https://www.jlowin.dev/blog/stop-converting-rest-apis-to-mcp</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Take Notes for Research</title>
      <link>https://lambdaland.org/posts/2025-07-11_research_notes/</link>
      <description>The key principle I follow is this: how I take my notes will evolve over time. I do not stick to any system too dogmatically.
That said, I’ve settled on a system that’s been fairly robust and stable for the past few years. I have tweaked it here and there to make it easier for me to find what I need.</description>
      <guid>https://lambdaland.org/posts/2025-07-11_research_notes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasm the Hard Way: Porting the Chicory Compiler to Android</title>
      <link>https://blog.evacchi.dev/posts/2025/07/11/wasm-the-hard-way-porting-the-chicory-compiler-to-android/</link>
      <description>I am resurrecting my old “Wasm the Hard Way” series with a some fresh new content about a recent project I have been working on: porting the Chicory Wasm compiler to Android.
If you are interested in Wasm and Java, you might have heard about Chicory, a pure-Java Wasm runtime. Ever since I started working at Dylibso, I have been contributing to the project.
Extism is Dylibso’s family of open-source projects to develop and host WebAssembly (Wasm) plugins. Going forward, we believe the Chicory SDK is a solid foundation for running Wasm modules in Java applications, making it our default Wasm runtime for Extism on the Java platform. We’re putting our money where our mouth is: the mcpx4j library for running mcp.run servlets is built on top of the Chicory SDK.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.evacchi.dev/posts/2025/07/11/wasm-the-hard-way-porting-the-chicory-compiler-to-android/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So why don't we pick the optimal query plan?</title>
      <link>https://vondra.me/posts/so-why-dont-we-pick-the-optimal-query-plan/</link>
      <description>A follow up to my blog post exploring how often we pick the optimal query plan. Instructions how to reproduce it, why it happens and how to address it.</description>
      <guid>https://vondra.me/posts/so-why-dont-we-pick-the-optimal-query-plan/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire math</title>
      <link>https://apenwarr.ca/log/20250711</link>
      <description>I have a friend who exited his startup a few years ago and is now rich. How
rich is unclear. One day, we were discussing ways to expedite th...</description>
      <guid>https://apenwarr.ca/log/20250711</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my digital minimalism journey</title>
      <link>https://sym.bearblog.dev/digital-minimalism/</link>
      <description>The main question of this big picture is one: Is it possible to live without a smartphone in the modern era? The short answer doesn't exist, because the righ...</description>
      <guid>https://sym.bearblog.dev/digital-minimalism/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Give Imperfect People Perfect Systems</title>
      <link>https://loganmarek.com/do-not-give-imperfect-people-perfect-systems/</link>
      <description>As engineers and optimists, we build perfect systems. These systems make sense when we think about machines that, in general, are good at doing things perfec...</description>
      <guid>https://loganmarek.com/do-not-give-imperfect-people-perfect-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stages of adoption</title>
      <link>https://www.robertotonino.com/adoption</link>
      <description>One day, you stumble on a new methodology/tool.</description>
      <guid>https://www.robertotonino.com/adoption</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I outline everything</title>
      <link>https://literallythevoid.com/why-i-outline-everything/</link>
      <description>When I changed my major to English, I had a lot of catching up to do. That meant that one of my semesters was all upper-level English classes and one upper-l...</description>
      <guid>https://literallythevoid.com/why-i-outline-everything/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading an M4 Pro Mac mini's storage for half the price</title>
      <link>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2025/upgrading-m4-pro-mac-minis-storage-half-price</link>
      <description>A few months ago, I upgraded my M4 Mac mini from 1 to 2 TB of internal storage, using a then-$269 DIY upgrade kit from ExpandMacMini.</description>
      <guid>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2025/upgrading-m4-pro-mac-minis-storage-half-price</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 22:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not So Fast: AI Coding Tools Can Actually Reduce Productivity</title>
      <link>https://secondthoughts.ai/p/ai-coding-slowdown</link>
      <description>Study Shows That Even Experienced Developers Dramatically Overestimate Gains</description>
      <guid>https://secondthoughts.ai/p/ai-coding-slowdown</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Fire</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3114/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3114/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Vs The Law</title>
      <link>https://formularsumo.co.uk/blog/2025/apple-vs-the-law/</link>
      <description>Apple &amp; Google at the DMA compliance workshops, June 2025</description>
      <author> (James Heppell)</author>
      <guid>https://formularsumo.co.uk/blog/2025/apple-vs-the-law/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>