<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How to Show and Hide the Keyboard in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://askxammy.com/how-to-show-and-hide-the-keyboard-in-net-maui/</link>
      <description>As I always say, the more control we have over how elements behave in our apps, the better experience we can provide to users.
In this article, we’ll explore an interesting feature of the virtual keyboard: how to show or hide it strategically to improve usability. With .NET MAUI, you can achieve this easily in just a few steps. Let’s dive in! &amp;#128640;




Let&amp;#39;s get started! &amp;#128640;
The first thing you should know when you hear or read about the term soft input keyboard is that it refers to the virtual keyboard that appears on the screen when entering text.

What are SoftInputExtensions?
In .NET MAUI, several UI elements, such as Entry and Editor, accept text input and automatically interact with the soft input keyboard. With SoftInputExtensions, we can take full control of its visibility using extension methods, allowing us to easily show or hide the keyboard as needed.

SoftInputExtensions Methods
The SoftInputExtensions class provides the following methods:
&amp;#128313; HideSoftInputAsync – Hides the soft input keyboard if it is currently visible.
&amp;#128313; ShowSoftInputAsync – Displays the soft input keyboard if it is currently hidden.
&amp;#128313; IsSoftInputShowing – Returns a boolean value indicating whether the soft input keyboard is currently displayed on the screen. - ✍️ I recommend using this method before deciding whether to show or hide the soft input keyboard.

How to implement it




Spanish article

 	https://es.askxammy.com/como-mostrar-y-ocultar-el-teclado-en-net-maui/

References
This article was based on the official documentation.

 	https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/maui/user-interface/controls/entry?view=net-maui-8.0&amp;amp;viewFallbackFrom=net-maui-7.0
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://askxammy.com/how-to-show-and-hide-the-keyboard-in-net-maui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 03:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Succinct data structures</title>
      <link>https://blog.startifact.com/posts/succinct/</link>
      <description>An overview of a class of data structures I didn&amp;#39;t know about!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.startifact.com/posts/succinct/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 03:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SalvaSC</title>
      <link>https://salvasc.dev/blog/My-Weekend-at-JSCONF-es-2025soLUiTnK_R_0FHAAGIu97</link>
      <description>This past weekend, I had the incredible opportunity to attend JSCONF.es. It was an inspiring and enriching experience, filled with insightful talks, engaging workshops, and—most importantly—meaningful connections with fellow developers. Conferences like these remind me why I love working in the JavaScript ecosystem.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://salvasc.dev/blog/My-Weekend-at-JSCONF-es-2025soLUiTnK_R_0FHAAGIu97</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design tips for startups</title>
      <link>https://www.vigilant.run/blog/design-tips-for-startups</link>
      <description>Practical design advice for startups from two years of experience. Learn how to iterate quickly, set clear goals, and avoid common design pitfalls.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.vigilant.run/blog/design-tips-for-startups</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Don’t Know What They Don’t Know—And That’s a Problem</title>
      <link>https://blog.scottlogic.com/2025/03/06/llms-dont-know-what-they-dont-know-and-thats-a-problem.html</link>
      <description>LLMs are not just limited by hallucinations—they fundamentally lack awareness of their own capabilities, making them overconfident in executing tasks they don’t fully understand. While “vibe coding” embraces AI’s ability to generate quick solutions, true progress lies in models that can acknowledge ambiguity, seek clarification, and recognise when they are out of their depth.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.scottlogic.com/2025/03/06/llms-dont-know-what-they-dont-know-and-thats-a-problem.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trying to Justify SNMP</title>
      <link>https://www.robopenguins.com/snmp/</link>
      <description>Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) is a protocol for collecting info from devices like resource usage or configuration. It’s come up a few times when ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.robopenguins.com/snmp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If your content is only on social media, I&amp;#39;m not going to see it</title>
      <link>https://www.coryd.dev/posts/2025/if-your-content-is-only-on-social-media-im-not-going-to-see-it/</link>
      <description>If you only post on social media, I won&amp;#39;t see it. If you don&amp;#39;t have an RSS feed, I won&amp;#39;t follow it, I won&amp;#39;t subscribe to it. I don&amp;#39;t want want your app because I don&amp;#39;t want a homescreen full of apps for publications and platforms. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.coryd.dev/posts/2025/if-your-content-is-only-on-social-media-im-not-going-to-see-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Twitter Threads; Write A Blog Post Instead! | Kev Quirk</title>
      <link>https://kevquirk.com/blog/forget-twitter-threads-write-a-blog-post-instead</link>
      <description>All of the kool kids in Twitter land seem to be jumping on the bandwagon of a very annoying craze. Twitter threads. Please stop; write a blog post instead</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kevquirk.com/blog/forget-twitter-threads-write-a-blog-post-instead</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The More Important Half of Great API Boundaries</title>
      <link>https://www.kylegill.com/essays/api-boundaries</link>
      <description>Designing good tools depends on much more than the features you include. Like the best margherita pizzas in Italy, or the best ambient music…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.kylegill.com/essays/api-boundaries</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude, the librarian</title>
      <link>https://martinklepsch.org/posts/claude-the-librarian/</link>
      <description>Personal Website and Blog of Martin Klepsch</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martinklepsch.org/posts/claude-the-librarian/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The “Every” thing Blueprint</title>
      <link>https://www.hunter.vc/p/the-every-thing-blueprint</link>
      <description>How AI is Enabling a New Type of Media Company</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hunter.vc/p/the-every-thing-blueprint</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s Take a Look at... KIP-932: Queues for Kafka!</title>
      <link>https://www.morling.dev/blog/kip-932-queues-for-kafka/</link>
      <description>
In the &amp;quot;Let’s Take a Look at…!&amp;quot; blog series I am going to explore interesting projects, developments and technologies in the data and streaming space. This can be KIPs and FLIPs, open-source projects, services, and more. The idea is to get some hands-on experience, learn about potential use cases and applications, and understand the trade-offs involved. If you think there’s a specific subject I should take a look at, let me know in the comments below!





That guy above? Yep, that’s me, whenever someone says &amp;quot;Kafka queue&amp;quot;. Because, that’s not what Apache Kafka is. At its core, Kafka is a distributed durable event log. Producers write events to a topic, organized in partitions which are distributed amongst the brokers of a Kafka cluster. Consumers, organized in groups, divide the partitions they process amongst themselves, so that each partition of a topic is read by exactly one consumer in the group.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.morling.dev/blog/kip-932-queues-for-kafka/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTML, but not too HTML</title>
      <link>https://lars.ingebrigtsen.no/2025/02/17/html-but-not-too-html/</link>
      <description>When writing blog posts, I use ewp, an Emacs package to administrate Wordpress. It offers an editing mode based on the revolutionary idea of just writing HTML. Everything is cyclical in computing, …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lars.ingebrigtsen.no/2025/02/17/html-but-not-too-html/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In defense of Gemini</title>
      <link>https://www.strangeloopcanon.com/p/in-defense-of-gemini</link>
      <description>a kvetch</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.strangeloopcanon.com/p/in-defense-of-gemini</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firecracker vs QEMU — E2B Blog</title>
      <link>https://e2b.dev/blog/firecracker-vs-qemu</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://e2b.dev/blog/firecracker-vs-qemu</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sum Types and Subtypes and Unions
</title>
      <link>https://blog.jle.im/entry/sum-types-and-subtypes-and-unions.html</link>
      <description>There’s yet again been a bit of functional programming-adjacent twitter drama recently, but it’s actually sort of touched into some subtleties about sum types that I am asked about (and think about) a lot nowadays. So, I’d like to take this opportunity to talk a bit about the “why” and nature of sum types and how to use them effectively, and how they contrast with other related concepts in programming and software development and when even cases where sum types aren’t the best option.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jle.im/entry/sum-types-and-subtypes-and-unions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaming in the desert</title>
      <link>https://blog.etra0.lat/posts/2025-03-05-remote-gaming/</link>
      <description>If you ever ask yourself, where can you see the most pristine dark skies in the world? Well, I’m lucky enough to work in one of those places; in the middle of the desert, where humidity levels on average are less than 20%, and no civilization is in sight.
I work as a Software Engineer over there, since the workplace is literally in the middle of the desert, we usually work in shifts, I arrive on a Tuesday, and stay until the next Tuesday, over +1.000km away from my home.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.etra0.lat/posts/2025-03-05-remote-gaming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbage collection theory - Basic Algorithms - Michał &amp;#39;Chlebik&amp;#39; Piotrowski</title>
      <link>https://michalpiotrowski.dev/2025/03/05/gc-theory-basic-algorithms/</link>
      <description>Reading Time:  5 minutesIn the world of garbage collection, there are three algorithms, that are the founding stone for all the other. In this article I will try to briefly introduce all of them – reference counting algorithm, mark-sweep and copying algorithm. More detailed articles about them will follow in the weeks to come. The reference counting algorithm</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://michalpiotrowski.dev/2025/03/05/gc-theory-basic-algorithms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawn of Personal AIs</title>
      <link>https://maraoz.com/personal-ai/</link>
      <description>maraoz&amp;#39;s personal website.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://maraoz.com/personal-ai/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk Migrations by Passing validate(_check)_constraint through change_table</title>
      <link>https://blog.saeloun.com/2025/03/06/bulk-migrations-validate-check-constraint/</link>
      <description>Rails 7.1 now delegates validate(_check)_constraint through change_table for bulk migrations by letting us define and validate check constraints within a single change_table block.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.saeloun.com/2025/03/06/bulk-migrations-validate-check-constraint/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say Yes To Interesting Things - Don&amp;#39;t Break Prod</title>
      <link>https://dontbreakprod.com/posts/say-yes-to-interesting-things</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t Break Prod provides bite-sized pieces of career advice for software engineers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dontbreakprod.com/posts/say-yes-to-interesting-things</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobody Watches Computers Play Chess - Billy Gardner McIntyre</title>
      <link>https://gardnermcintyre.com/post/nobody-watches-computers-play-chess</link>
      <description>March 6th 2025</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gardnermcintyre.com/post/nobody-watches-computers-play-chess</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion models are interesting</title>
      <link>https://rnikhil.com/2025/03/06/diffusion-models-eval</link>
      <description>I stumbled across this tweet a week or so back where this company called Inception Labs released a Diffusion LLM (dLLM). Instead of being autoregressive and predicting tokens left to right, here you start all at once and then gradually come up with sensible words simultaneously (start/finish/middle etc. all at once). Something which worked historically for image and video models is now outperforming similar-sized LLMs in code generation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rnikhil.com/2025/03/06/diffusion-models-eval</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Aspire and Dev Container</title>
      <link>https://laurentkempe.com/2025/03/06/dotnet-aspire-and-dev-container/</link>
      <description>.NET Aspire 9.1 was just released on February 25th, 2025. It comes with great new dashboard features, and there is more! One feature I am particularly interested in is the ability to use Dev Container</description>
      <author> (Laurent Kemp&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://laurentkempe.com/2025/03/06/dotnet-aspire-and-dev-container/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 01:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Hot Design Public Beta - A Visual Designer for Cross-Platform Desktop, Mobile and Web Apps</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/hot-design-public-beta/</link>
      <description>Pixel-Perfect Multi-Platform Applications with C# and WinUI for Windows, WebAssembly, iOS, macOS, Android and Linux</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/hot-design-public-beta/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 20:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET AI Template Now Available in Preview - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-ai-template-preview1/</link>
      <description>Announcing the first preview of the .NET AI Template, for Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, and the .NET CLI. Get started building amazing AI apps with .NET.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-ai-template-preview1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 20:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistral OCR | Mistral AI</title>
      <link>https://mistral.ai/fr/news/mistral-ocr</link>
      <description>Introducing the world’s best document understanding API.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mistral.ai/fr/news/mistral-ocr</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 19:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMG 20250306 014717 — Postimages</title>
      <link>https://postimg.cc/phdVNwPz</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://postimg.cc/phdVNwPz</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 17:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>zig/lib/std/heap/SmpAllocator.zig at 0.14.0 &amp;#183; ziglang/zig</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ziglang/zig/blob/0.14.0/lib/std/heap/SmpAllocator.zig</link>
      <description>General-purpose programming language and toolchain for maintaining robust, optimal, and reusable software. - ziglang/zig</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ziglang/zig/blob/0.14.0/lib/std/heap/SmpAllocator.zig</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age and cognitive skills: Use it or lose it</title>
      <link>https://www.science.org/doi/full/10.1126/sciadv.ads1560?af=R</link>
      <description>Cognitive skills do not decline with age for those who use math and reading throughout their life.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.science.org/doi/full/10.1126/sciadv.ads1560?af=R</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Code with GitHub Copilot in Visual Studio 2022 to Boost Productivity Everyday</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Z6BYhJl9hV8</link>
      <description>Want to see how I code every day inside of Visual Studio with GitHub Copilot? Follow along as I show you how I get up to speed on new code bases, refactor code, add documentation, create diagrams, debug exceptions, implement new features, commit code, and even write some code on occasion. Using the latest features of Visual Studio 2022 and GitHub Copilot are a complete productivity boost once you know where to look and how to use them.

GitHub Copilot Free: https://aka.ms/copilot-free-vs
GitHub Copilot: https://github.com/features/copilot
GitHub Copilot Blogs for Visual Studio: https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/category/github-copilot/
GitHub Copilot Videos for Visual Studio: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLReL099Y5nRckZDdcQ21UigO9pKa14yxC

Chapters
00:00 - Intro &amp;amp; App Overview
02:00 - GitHub Copilot Chat - Understanding Code
04:15 - In-line Chat, Documentation, Refactoring, and more
06:50 - Analyzing and improving code while debugging
08:40 - Analyzing Exceptions with GitHub Copilot
10:00 - Adding new functionality with GitHub Copilot Edits
15:55 - Code suggestions with GitHub Copilot
17:20 - Commit &amp;amp; PR Message Generation &amp;amp; Customization
20:35 - Using Extensions to generate Mermaid Charts
22:30 - Wrap-up

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCENTmbKaTphpWV2R2evVz2A/join

&amp;#128085; Buy some swag! - https://jamesmontemagno.myspreadshop.com/
☕️ Buy me a coffee - https://www.buymeacoffee.com/jamesmontemagno

Follow:
&amp;#128104;‍&amp;#128187; GitHub: https://github.com/jamesmontemagno
&amp;#129436; X: https://x.com/jamesmontemagno
&amp;#128196; Website: https://www.montemagno.com
&amp;#128240; Newsletter: https://newsletter.montemagno.com/

Disclaimer: This channel, videos, and streams are created in my spare time and are a product of me... James Montemagno! They are NOT officially affiliated or endorsed by Microsoft (my employer) in any way. Opinions and views are my own.

What is on my hat? It is the CLE clothing logo because I am from Cleveland! Checkout their awesome CLE merch: https://cleclothingco.myshopify.com/

What is that art on my wall? It is an original piece from the French street artist Gregos of La Butte Montmartre: https://www.instagram.com/p/BceZ1oNHiQx/

My Setup:
&amp;#128247; Canon M50 Mark II - https://amzn.to/3P8R7lp
&amp;#128161; Nanoleaf Elements Lights - https://amzn.to/3umwJVW
&amp;#127897; Blue Spark Microphone - https://amzn.to/3qgtYkq
&amp;#127897; Blue Pop Filter - https://amzn.to/3jEWM3r
&amp;#129331; Rode Microphone Arm - https://amzn.to/2Z68AlE
&amp;#127911; Sony MDR7306 Headphones - https://amzn.to/372jxta
&amp;#128242; Stream Deck - https://amzn.to/373Uk1n
&amp;#128433; MX Master 2S Mouse - https://amzn.to/3d7J2gj
⌨️ Tecware Phantom Keyboard - https://amzn.to/3aUP4y9

Using links I provide I may receive a commission if you buy something which helps support the channel.

#visualstudio #githubcopilot #dotnet #dotnetmaui</description>
      <author> (James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Z6BYhJl9hV8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C#, Aspire, and Awesomesauce</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=h6bjaB4dEQo</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Fritz is working on SharpSite, an open-source CMS we&amp;#39;re building live on stream.  https://sharpsite.org</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=h6bjaB4dEQo</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform Power-Ups: The Best Tools to Supercharge Your IaC Workflow - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/terraform-power-ups-the-best-tools-to-supercharge-your-iac-workflow/</link>
      <description>Terraform is already an amazing tool for automating infrastructure, but what if I told you it could get even better? […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/terraform-power-ups-the-best-tools-to-supercharge-your-iac-workflow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 15:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET &amp;#128165; - Event Driven Architecture with Azure Service Bus (step by step)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=9w4XQx2CGaI</link>
      <description>In this video we will be discussing in .NET &amp;amp;  Event Driven Architecture with Service bus

Support me on Patreon to access the source code:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand

Let us connect:
&amp;#127757;  My website  - https://mohamadlawand.com
&amp;#128248;  Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/mohamadlawand087/
&amp;#128038;  Twitter - https://twitter.com/moe23
♯ Github - https://github.com/mohamadlawand087
&amp;#127915; LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/mlawand
&amp;#128165; LinkTree - https://linktr.ee/mohamadlawand

Gear I use  (affiliate link): https://amzn.to/3EbT8Jw

Support my work:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand
https://www.buymeacoffee.com/mohamadlawand

Hire Me:
https://transactions.sendowl.com/products/78999951/625477F1/view

WHO AM I:
I&amp;#39;m Mohamad, a Enterprise Architect working in Manchester, UK. I make videos about web, cloud, desktop and mobile development. 

GET IN TOUCH:
If you’d like to talk, I’d love to hear from you. Tweeting @moe23 directly will be the quickest way to get a response, but if your question is very long, feel free to email me at hello@mohamadlawand.com.

#dotnet  #eventdrivenarchitecture    #servicebus</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=9w4XQx2CGaI</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy European Made</title>
      <link>https://www.buy-european-made.eu/</link>
      <description>A directory of EU-made alternatives. From software and electronics to everyday products - all made in Europe</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.buy-european-made.eu/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 12:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdentiyServer4 is BACK!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=-Cn_vAd4KxY</link>
      <description>Check out my courses on Dometrain: https://dometrain.com/
Subscribe to my weekly newsletter: https://nickchapsas.com

Become a Patreon and get special perks: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsas

Hello, everybody. I&amp;#39;m Nick, and in this video, I will talk about IdentityServer4 coming back!

Workshops: https://bit.ly/nickworkshops

Don&amp;#39;t forget to comment, like and subscribe :)

Social Media:
Follow me on GitHub: https://github.com/Elfocrash
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/nickchapsas
Connect on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick-chapsas

#csharp #dotnet</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=-Cn_vAd4KxY</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 12:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ipex-llm/docs/mddocs/Quickstart/llamacpp_portable_zip_gpu_quickstart.md at main &amp;#183; intel/ipex-llm</title>
      <link>https://github.com/intel/ipex-llm/blob/main/docs/mddocs/Quickstart/llamacpp_portable_zip_gpu_quickstart.md</link>
      <description>Accelerate local LLM inference and finetuning (LLaMA, Mistral, ChatGLM, Qwen, DeepSeek, Mixtral, Gemma, Phi, MiniCPM, Qwen-VL, MiniCPM-V, etc.) on Intel XPU (e.g., local PC with iGPU and NPU, discr...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/intel/ipex-llm/blob/main/docs/mddocs/Quickstart/llamacpp_portable_zip_gpu_quickstart.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 11:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git without a forge</title>
      <link>https://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/quasiblog/git-no-forge/</link>
      <description>[Simon Tatham, 2025-03-05]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/quasiblog/git-no-forge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET MAUI Community Standup - Agent Maui: Copilot Pro-tips for devs</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sCgvmPNIzbM</link>
      <description>Are you already a power user of GitHub Copilot? Let&amp;#39;s find out. Copilot is rapidly adding features that we can take advantage of to build .NET MAUI apps better and faster than ever before. 

Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/maui-standup-mar2025

Featuring: David Ortinau (@davidortinau) and Rachel Kang (@therachelkang)

#dotnet #dotnetmaui #githubcopilot</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sCgvmPNIzbM</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 07:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>