<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous C# and F# IDE for iPads and iPhones</title>
      <link>https://continuous.codes/</link>
      <description>Continuous is always running your code so you can
                see changes to objects as you type. This makes writing
                interactive applications easier than
                with the old Code-Build-Run cycle. You are now
                free to make lots of small changes and see their
                effects immediately.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://continuous.codes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2010 Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://www.packtpub.com/application-development/visual-studio-2010-best-practices</link>
      <description>Learn and implement recommended practices for the complete software development lifecycle with Visual Studio 2010 with this book and ebook.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.packtpub.com/application-development/visual-studio-2010-best-practices</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appstat - App Store Sales &amp; Analytics on your Mac</title>
      <link>https://gumroad.com/l/appstat</link>
      <description>With Appstat, your apps' status, proceeds, and analytics are just one click away. It lives in your Mac's status bar and, when clicked, displays all the apps you have for sale and how much you are making with each one. Once you try Appstat you'll wonder how you ever monitored app sales without it! For App Developers This app only fully functions if you are a developer with an active subscription with Apple. With just a click, Appstat displays all of the following information about your apps: Name and platform, Average proceeds per day (including in-app purchases), Average unit sales per day (including free apps), Bundle identifier and SKU, Your app's website, Original release date and time on the store, Latest version number and time on the store, Rate at which people rate your app (ratings/month), Latest version rating, Overall app rating, Device distribution based on purchases, Country distribution based on purchases, Chart of proceeds over time, Average proceeds per day, Projected proceeds per month and year, Chart of unit sales over time, Latest builds uploaded to TestFlight. All stats are linked to the appropriate section of Apple's developer site, making Appstat a great launchpad. Total store proceeds are also displayed: Average total proceeds per day (and standard deviation), Projected total proceeds per month (estimated using a configurable amount of history), Projected total proceeds per year. Now you can see how you're doing month by month or year by year. They're just projections so take them with a grain of salt! Security and privacy were taken seriously and baked into every step: No usernames or passwords needed! Appstat will never collect these and instead uses API keys generated securely on App Store Connect. All account settings are encrypted locally on your machine for your privacy. Absolutely no data is stored on the machine except those encrypted account settings. Everything is done in-memory and all data is lost when the app is closed. Only uses encrypted communication with Apple servers and never transmits any data to anyone else (especially not me, I don't want it). Doesn't waste battery or network time and fetches data only when you need it. I hope you love it!</description>
      <author> (By




Frank A. Krueger)</author>
      <guid>https://gumroad.com/l/appstat</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lychee — Self-hosted photo-management done right</title>
      <link>https://lycheeorg.github.io/</link>
      <description>Lychee is a free photo-management tool, which runs on your server or web-space. Upload, manage and share photos like from a native application. Lychee comes with everything you need and all your photos are stored securely.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lycheeorg.github.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 01:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xamarin/Essentials</title>
      <link>https://github.com/xamarin/Essentials/releases/tag/1.5.0-pre1</link>
      <description>Essential cross platform APIs for your mobile apps. - xamarin/Essentials</description>
      <author> (xamarin)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/xamarin/Essentials/releases/tag/1.5.0-pre1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 01:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://www.vrtx.com/twitterguidelines</link>
      <description>Thank you for visiting the Vertex Pharmaceuticals Incorporated official Corporate Twitter page. This is our corporate page and not a page for our approved or investigational medicines. As a biotechnology company, at times our engagement may seem limited or delayed, but that is because we must adhere to certain ethical, legal, and regulatory standards unique to this industry. To ensure our communications are consistent with our mission and public obligations, below are our Community Guidelines. They are subject to change at any time, so we encourage you to check back often. Please note that we reserve the right to block users from this page who violate or misuse these Community Guidelines.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.vrtx.com/twitterguidelines</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 01:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cldubya - Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/cldubya</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> (cldubya)</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/cldubya</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connection Abstractions · Issue #1793 · dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/issues/1793</link>
      <description>System.Net.Connections Connections is an abstraction for composable connection establishment. It aims to improve layering separation and provide a standard extensibility model for making network co...</description>
      <author> (scalablecory)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/issues/1793</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>system.net - Domain Name For Sale | DAN.COM</title>
      <link>https://system.net/</link>
      <description>I found a great domain name for sale. Check it out!</description>
      <author> (DAN.COM)</author>
      <guid>https://system.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMMEBIT</title>
      <link>https://femmebit.art/</link>
      <description>FEMMEBIT is a biennial festival uniting an all-female roster of Los Angeles based artists working in video and new media. A 3-day celebration spanning a curated program of symposiums, screenings and exhibitions, FEMMEBIT examines today’s society at large as an ever-changing medium; how women working</description>
      <author> (Screening: Heterotopias)</author>
      <guid>https://femmebit.art/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 23:08:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Troughton-Smith is creating Tech, Development &amp; Games Commentary | Patreon</title>
      <link>https://www.patreon.com/steventroughtonsmith</link>
      <description>Become a patron of Steven Troughton-Smith today:
            Read 5 posts by Steven Troughton-Smith and get access to exclusive
            content and experiences on the world’s largest membership
            platform for artists and creators.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.patreon.com/steventroughtonsmith</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 23:08:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Habitica - Gamify Your Life</title>
      <link>https://habitica.com/static/home</link>
      <description>Habitica is a free habit and productivity app that treats your real life like a game. Habitica can help you achieve your goals to become healthy and happy.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://habitica.com/static/home</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 22:08:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paperwork</title>
      <link>https://paperwork.cloud/</link>
      <description>Paperwork is an open-source, self-hosted alternative to services like Evernote ®, Microsoft OneNote ® or Google Keep ®</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://paperwork.cloud/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 22:07:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlurHash</title>
      <link>https://blurha.sh/</link>
      <description>Does your designer cry every time you load their beautifully designed screen, and it is
          full of empty boxes because all the images have not loaded yet? Does your database
          engineer cry when you want to solve this by trying to cram little thumbnail images into
          your data to show as placeholders?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blurha.sh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 22:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bitcrazed (Rich Turner) | Keybase</title>
      <link>https://keybase.io/bitcrazed</link>
      <description>bitcrazed (Rich Turner) is now on Keybase, an open source app for encryption and cryptography.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://keybase.io/bitcrazed</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 22:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strings and Loops within Pi - Numberphile</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W20aT14t8Pw</link>
      <description>Tom Crawford from Oxford University looks at self-locating strings and interesting loops.
Get a Piece of Pi: https://www.patreon.com/posts/piece-of-pi-for-33529079

More links &amp; stuff in full description below ↓↓↓ 

More of Tom on Numberphile: http://bit.ly/TomPlaylist

See our Pi Playlist: http://bit.ly/PiPlaylist

Tom's website: https://tomrocksmaths.com

The Pi Search Page: https://www.angio.net/pi/

OEIS sequences and pages of interest:
https://oeis.org/A057680
https://oeis.org/A064810

 Numberphile is supported by the Mathematical Sciences Research Institute (MSRI): http://bit.ly/MSRINumberphile

We are also supported by Science Sandbox, a Simons Foundation initiative dedicated to engaging everyone with the process of science. https://www.simonsfoundation.org/outreach/science-sandbox/

And support from Math For America - https://www.mathforamerica.org/

NUMBERPHILE
Website: http://www.numberphile.com/
Numberphile on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/numberphile
Numberphile tweets: https://twitter.com/numberphile
Subscribe: http://bit.ly/Numberphile_Sub

Videos by Brady Haran

Patreon: http://www.patreon.com/numberphile

Numberphile T-Shirts and Merch: https://teespring.com/stores/numberphile

Brady's videos subreddit: http://www.reddit.com/r/BradyHaran/

Brady's latest videos across all channels: http://www.bradyharanblog.com/

Sign up for (occasional) emails: http://eepurl.com/YdjL9</description>
      <author> (Numberphile)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W20aT14t8Pw</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 21:05:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB.local SF 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.eventbrite.com/e/mongodblocal-sf-2018-tickets-50361477535</link>
      <description>MongoDB is coming to SF! Join us for a full-day educational conference covering the fundamentals to advanced techniques of app design and performance management. You’ll hear from the team that builds the database and power users running MongoDB deployments.
At MongoDB.local SF, we'll also host our first annual Women in Tech luncheon. Luncheon attendees will be able to participate in additional networking opportunities and will receive special swag. 
This day of learning will close with a happy hour. Register now to claim your seat.
WHAT YOU'LL LEARN
Insight into building applications with MongoDB Stitch, the serverless platform from MongoDB
How to deploy, operate, and scale your database on all major cloud platforms with MongoDB Atlas
What’s new in MongoDB 4.0, including multi-document ACID transactions, and how the latest version of MongoDB can help your business succeed
Best practices from the experts on topics including schema design, analytics, microservices, performance, and more
Register for hands-on, deep-dive technical sessions, equipping you with the tools you need to build and deploy your giant ideas
Register for a day of hands-on, deep-dive technical sessions, equipping you with the tools you need to build and deploy your giant ideas. 
Admission includes breakfast, lunch, and access to all sessions and sponsor area. Space is limited. Reserve your spot today.
For more information including agenda and speakers, visit https://www.mongodb.com/local.
Cancellation Policy:
To cancel your order, send your request to events@mongodb.com. Full refunds will be granted through October 31, 2018 via the original payment method. 50% refunds will be granted through November 31, 2018. After November 31, 2018, refunds will no longer be granted. Event registration may be transferred to another participant.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.eventbrite.com/e/mongodblocal-sf-2018-tickets-50361477535</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 21:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streisand effect - Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Streisand_effect</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Streisand_effect</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 21:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plain Text Offenders</title>
      <link>https://plaintextoffenders.com/</link>
      <description>Did you just email me back my own password?!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://plaintextoffenders.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 21:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temperature Blanket - A Rare Opportunity for My Coding to Assist Jocelyn's Crafting</title>
      <link>https://blog.iannelson.uk/temperature-blanket/</link>
      <description>In which, after almost 17 years, Mrs Nelson finally has cause to call upon my programming skills.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.iannelson.uk/temperature-blanket/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:14:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing an event-driven business process at scale: A health management example, Part 1 - Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2020/02/19/designing-an-event-driven-business-process-at-scale-a-health-management-example-part-1/</link>
      <description>Follow along with this series to define a health management event-driven business process and then implement it in jBPM (an open source business automation suite).</description>
      <author> (By Maurizio Carioli February 19, 2020February 18, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2020/02/19/designing-an-event-driven-business-process-at-scale-a-health-management-example-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:14:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February 2020 SDK Release</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-sdk/february-2020-sdk-release/ba-p/1174661</link>
      <description>Welcome to the February release of the Azure SDK. We have updated the following libraries:  Cosmos (JavaScript only). Event Hubs (Java and JavaScript). Key Vault (Python only). Storage (Blobs, Files, and Queues across all languages). These are ready to use in your production applications. You can fi...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/311932)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-sdk/february-2020-sdk-release/ba-p/1174661</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:14:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code review red flag: Where is the missing code?</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/189986-B/code-review-red-flag-where-is-the-missing-code</link>
      <description>I recently had what amounted to a drive by code review. I was looking into code that wasn’t committed or PR. Code that might not have been even saved to disk...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/189986-B/code-review-red-flag-where-is-the-missing-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:14:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Jobs in Azure SQL Database – What and Why</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-sql-database/elastic-jobs-in-azure-sql-database-what-and-why/ba-p/1177902</link>
      <description>Elastic Jobs are currently in public preview.  The feature is ready and we are preparing to make it officially generally available.  No whitelisting or extra steps are required to get started.   Elastic Jobs is a feature of Azure SQL Database that lets you run a set of T-SQL scripts against a collec...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/553780)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-sql-database/elastic-jobs-in-azure-sql-database-what-and-why/ba-p/1177902</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:14:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing .NET Conf: Focus on Xamarin | Xamarin Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xamarin/net-conf-focus-on-xamarin/</link>
      <description>Announcing .NET Conf: Focus on Xamarin. A one-day, live-streamed event featuring speakers from the Xamarin product team and Xamarin community.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/motzcodes)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xamarin/net-conf-focus-on-xamarin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React Context with TypeScript: Part 1 - Simple context with function components</title>
      <link>https://www.carlrippon.com/react-context-with-typescript-p1/</link>
      <description>How to use TypeScript to create a strongly-typed React context for function components where the context isn't changed by the consumer</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.carlrippon.com/react-context-with-typescript-p1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSIX Packaging Tool Insider Program</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/msix-blog/msix-packaging-tool-insider-program/ba-p/1182647</link>
      <description>Early access, preview, beta, whatever you want to call it, joining the MSIX Packaging Tool Insider Program allows you to have access to new features in development that aren’t available to anyone else.   Its incredibly easy to join, all you have to do is sign up here. Once you’ve joined the program,...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/145112)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/msix-blog/msix-packaging-tool-insider-program/ba-p/1182647</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Anti-Forgery Tokens in ASP.NET Core Razor Pages</title>
      <link>https://exceptionnotfound.net/using-anti-forgery-tokens-in-asp-net-core-razor-pages/</link>
      <description>Let's see how to use anti-forgery tokens and validation to prevent CSRF attacks in our Razor Pages apps!</description>
      <author> (exceptionnotfound)</author>
      <guid>https://exceptionnotfound.net/using-anti-forgery-tokens-in-asp-net-core-razor-pages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Builder as a monoid</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2020/02/17/builder-as-a-monoid/</link>
      <description>Builder, particularly Fluent Builder, is one of the more useful design patterns. Here's why.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2020/02/17/builder-as-a-monoid/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating your applications to Azure using Virtual Machine Scale Sets, Packer and Virtual Machine extensions – Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.domstamand.com/migrating-your-applications-to-azure-using-virtual-machine-scale-sets-and-packer-and-vm-extensions-part-1/</link>
      <description>I'm a Canadian Software Developer that is programming his life away while still maintaining a healthy lifestyle with a passion for fitness. The world of 0's and 1's got injected into my DNA at an early age, which made me turn a passion into a job.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.domstamand.com/migrating-your-applications-to-azure-using-virtual-machine-scale-sets-and-packer-and-vm-extensions-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catch up with Visual Studio Tools for Unity on Mac | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/catch-up-with-visual-studio-tools-for-unity-on-mac/</link>
      <description>Since the launch of Visual Studio for Mac, we have been continuously working on improving Visual Studio Tools for Unity (VSTU). Visual Studio for Mac has been the default IDE for Unity on Mac and it provides free world class support for Unity projects through VSTU.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/catch-up-with-visual-studio-tools-for-unity-on-mac/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Confirmation with ASP.NET Core Identity - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/email-confirmation-aspnet-core-identity/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to learn how to enable email confirmation during the registration process with ASP.NET Core Identity</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/email-confirmation-aspnet-core-identity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Blazor For Everyone? — App vNext</title>
      <link>http://www.appvnext.com/blog/2020/2/18/is-blazor-for-everyone</link>
      <description>Someone recently asked me why I was so enthusiastic about Blazor. This person didn’t like the programming experience as much as their JavaScript framework.   So, here’s the deal. If you are happy with your stack, your tribe, rock on. Blazor obviously isn’t for you. So, who is it for?  Blazor is for </description>
      <author> (Carl Franklin)</author>
      <guid>http://www.appvnext.com/blog/2020/2/18/is-blazor-for-everyone</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline Templates: Complete Azure Pipelines Example for a Uno Project for iOS, Android and Windows - Nick's .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/uno-complete-pipeline/</link>
      <description>My last post was a bit of a long one as it covered a bunch of steps for setting up the bits and pieces required for signing an application for different platforms. In this post I just wanted to provide a complete example that shows a single multi-stage (6 in total) Azure Pipelines pipeline for … Continue reading "Pipeline Templates: Complete Azure Pipelines Example for a Uno Project for iOS, Android and Windows"</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/uno-complete-pipeline/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor by Example - A dismissable banner</title>
      <link>https://jonhilton.net/blazor-banner/</link>
      <description>How do you store simple state in a Blazor app, such as whether a user has dismissed a banner or not?</description>
      <author> (Jon Hilton)</author>
      <guid>https://jonhilton.net/blazor-banner/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQL Bits 2020 is happening in London: join us March 31 to April 4 - SQL Server Blog</title>
      <link>https://cloudblogs.microsoft.com/sqlserver/2020/02/19/sql-bits-2020-is-happening-in-london-join-us-march-31-to-april-4/</link>
      <description>It’s that time of the year when the Microsoft Azure Data engineering team is getting ready to participate at SQL Bits 2020. Excitement for this year’s show is everywhere, as SQL Bits provides us with a unique opportunity to learn, connect, and share with you, our SQL Server community. SQL Bits is the largest gatheringRead more</description>
      <author> (SQL Server Team)</author>
      <guid>https://cloudblogs.microsoft.com/sqlserver/2020/02/19/sql-bits-2020-is-happening-in-london-join-us-march-31-to-april-4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:13:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Coding Standards | Jesse Liberty</title>
      <link>http://jesseliberty.com/2020/02/18/xamarin-coding-standards/</link>
      <description>There are many best practices in writing Xamarin.  Here are some that we’ve canonized where I work…</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>http://jesseliberty.com/2020/02/18/xamarin-coding-standards/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:12:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters Weekly 152 -  GitHub Actions and .NET Core</title>
      <link>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/02/monsters-weekly/ep152/</link>
      <description>GitHub Actions makes it really easy to setup a continuous integration build for your .NET Core projects. In this episode, Dave shows us how to configure a workflow to build and test your .NET Core pro</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/02/monsters-weekly/ep152/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:12:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hash functions and security | Manning</title>
      <link>https://freecontent.manning.com/hash-functions-and-security/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (From Real-World Cryptography by David Wong)</author>
      <guid>https://freecontent.manning.com/hash-functions-and-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:12:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSLA .NET Version 5.1.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://blog.lhotka.net/2020/02/17/CSLA-Version-5.1.0-Release</link>
      <description>I am pleased to announce the release of CSLA .NET version 5.1.0.</description>
      <author> (Rockford Lhotka)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.lhotka.net/2020/02/17/CSLA-Version-5.1.0-Release</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:12:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rider 2020.1 Roadmap - .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/02/19/rider-2020-1-roadmap/</link>
      <description>We’d like to share our plans for Rider 2020.1 with you and find out what we can do next to improve your development experience. Your feedback is always welcome! For the 2020 release, we’ve been burning through the Great Ticket … Continue reading →</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/02/19/rider-2020-1-roadmap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:12:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Pseudo Localization - Protecting developers from themselves</title>
      <link>https://www.mrlacey.com/2020/02/resource-pseudo-localization-protecting.html</link>
      <description>I have a tool to help test the localization of strings in an app . It does this by making changes to the resource files (.resx &amp; .resw) to h...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mrlacey.com/2020/02/resource-pseudo-localization-protecting.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:12:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIFs and SwipeView in Xamarin Forms 4.4</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/gifs-swipeview-xamarin-forms-4-4</link>
      <description>Xamarin Forms 4.4 includes GIFs and swiping for options on a content item like an entry in a list view. Let’s take a look!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/gifs-swipeview-xamarin-forms-4-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:12:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Types for classes in TypeScript</title>
      <link>https://2ality.com/2020/02/types-for-classes-typescript.html</link>
      <description>In this blog post about TypeScript, we examine how to use types for classes and their instances.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2ality.com/2020/02/types-for-classes-typescript.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:11:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core MVC 3.x – AddMvc(), AddMvcCore(), AddControllers() and other bootstrapping approaches</title>
      <link>https://www.strathweb.com/2020/02/asp-net-core-mvc-3-x-addmvc-addmvccore-addcontrollers-and-other-bootstrapping-approaches/</link>
      <description>There are several ways of bootstrapping your MVC applications on top of ASP.NET Core 3.x. One thing that you need to do, in order to use the framework, is to initialize it into the state where it can actually discover your controllers, views, pages and expose them as HTTP endpoints.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.strathweb.com/2020/02/asp-net-core-mvc-3-x-addmvc-addmvccore-addcontrollers-and-other-bootstrapping-approaches/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 20:11:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Careers at Microsoft | Microsoft jobs</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/</link>
      <description>Are you looking for a new career or maybe just out for an upgrade? Explore all of the career options and job opportunities that Microsoft has to offer?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 19:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure This Week: Azure This Week - Ignite The Tour: Sydney</title>
      <link>https://acloud.guru/series/azure-this-week/view/307a</link>
      <description>In this special episode of Azure This Week, Lars is in Sydney at Microsoft Ignite The Tour. He speaks to Azure experts including Troy Hunt, Christina Warren and Sonia Cuff. He also gives a flavour of what the conference is like for the 6,000 attendees over the two-day event.</description>
      <author> (Published on 17 Feb 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://acloud.guru/series/azure-this-week/view/307a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 19:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OS hacking: Let's port git to SerenityOS!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1-7VQwWo2Tg</link>
      <description>SerenityOS is open source on GitHub: https://github.com/SerenityOS/serenity
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/awesomekling
Support me on Patreon: https://patreon.com/serenityos
Sponsor me on GitHub: https://github.com/sponsors/awesomekling
Donate via Paypal: http://paypal.me/awesomekling

SerenityOS is a Unix-like operating system that I'm implementing from scratch. http://www.serenityos.org/</description>
      <author> (Andreas Kling)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1-7VQwWo2Tg</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 19:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Program Manager 2 in Redmond, Washington, United States | Engineering at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/777599/Program-Manager-2</link>
      <description>Apply for Program Manager 2 job with Microsoft in Redmond, Washington, United States. Engineering at Microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/777599/Program-Manager-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 18:30:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Careers at Microsoft | Microsoft jobs</title>
      <link>http://careers.microsoft.com/</link>
      <description>Are you looking for a new career or maybe just out for an upgrade? Explore all of the career options and job opportunities that Microsoft has to offer?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://careers.microsoft.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 18:29:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bvckup 2 | Introducing a small spinoff project - byenow - a faster folder deleter</title>
      <link>https://bvckup2.com/wip/18022020</link>
      <description>Bvckup 2 | Development blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bvckup2.com/wip/18022020</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 17:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Fonts</title>
      <link>https://fonts.google.com/analytics</link>
      <description>Making the web more beautiful, fast, and open through great typography</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fonts.google.com/analytics</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 15:24:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>syscolabs/kasaya</title>
      <link>https://github.com/syscolabs/kasaya</link>
      <description>A "WYSIWYG" scripting language and runtime for browser automation - syscolabs/kasaya</description>
      <author> (hliyan)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/syscolabs/kasaya</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 14:26:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>data stories</title>
      <link>http://t.me/datastudies</link>
      <description>канал о том, как (цифровые) технологии и данные меняют общество / PM @Katerfas</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://t.me/datastudies</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 14:08:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC Micro bot</title>
      <link>http://www.8bitkick.cc/bbc-micro-bot.html</link>
      <description>If you've never tried BASIC playing with the examples on the @bbcmicrobot Twitter account is a good place to start.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.8bitkick.cc/bbc-micro-bot.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 07:39:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screaming in the Cloud Archives - Last Week in AWS</title>
      <link>http://screaminginthecloud.com/</link>
      <description>The Staying Power of Kubernetes with Kelsey Hightower</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://screaminginthecloud.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 07:06:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Week in AWS - AWS News Sprinkled With a Side of Snark</title>
      <link>http://lastweekinaws.com/</link>
      <description>Posts about AWS come out over sixty times a day. We filter through it to find the hidden gems and stuff worth reading--right to your inbox each Monday.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://lastweekinaws.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 07:06:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ralfholly/git-autocommit</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ralfholly/git-autocommit</link>
      <description>Automatically commit Git working copy changes. Contribute to ralfholly/git-autocommit development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (ralfholly)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ralfholly/git-autocommit</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 06:28:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copyrighting all the melodies to avoid accidental infringement | Damien Riehl | TEDxMinneapolis</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/sJtm0MoOgiU</link>
      <description>In the litany of copyright infringement lawsuits, technology lawyer and musician Damien Riehl demonstrates that music is merely math, and has a finite number of possible melodies. If you’ve ever thought a song you like sounded similar to another, the culprit may not be an unethical forger, but rather the limited mathematical musical equations that our favorite artists have to work with.  Current copyright law is at risk of severely limiting future music creation and future human creativity. This talk suggests a new way to handle these legal cases.  Damien Riehl is a technology lawyer with a B.S. in music. After beginning to code in 1985, and for the web in 1995, he has worked for the chief judges of state and federal courts; litigated for a decade; taught law-school copyright classes; and led teams in software development, digital forensics, proactive cybersecurity, reactive cybersecurity incidents, and world-scale investigations. Damien’s combined experience in the law, technology, and music has inspired his most recent project—copyrighting billions of unique melodies. This talk was given at a TEDx event using the TED conference format but independently organized by a local community. Learn more at https://www.ted.com/tedx</description>
      <author> (TEDx Talks)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/sJtm0MoOgiU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 06:06:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zaid-Ajaj/Npgsql.FSharp.Analyzer</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Zaid-Ajaj/Npgsql.FSharp.Analyzer</link>
      <description>Analyzer that provides embedded SQL syntax analysis when writing queries using Npgsql.FSharp. It verifies query syntax, checks the parameters in the query match with the provided parameters and per...</description>
      <author> (Zaid-Ajaj)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Zaid-Ajaj/Npgsql.FSharp.Analyzer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 05:05:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marten</title>
      <link>https://martendb.io/</link>
      <description>The Marten library provides .NET developers with the ability to easily use the proven PostgreSQL database engine
                    and its fantastic JSON support as a fully fledged document database. The Marten team believes that a document database has far reaching benefits for developer productivity
                    over relational databases with or without an ORM tool.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martendb.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 01:05:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straffic</title>
      <link>http://straffic.io/</link>
      <description>Why Choose Straffic</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://straffic.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 01:05:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Szkoła Event Sourcing - Fakty i Mity o Event Sourcing</title>
      <link>https://www.szkola-event-sourcing.pl/</link>
      <description>Darmowy ebook - 'Fakty i Mity o Event Sourcing'</description>
      <author> (zytheme)</author>
      <guid>https://www.szkola-event-sourcing.pl/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 01:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Standard</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRAdsfhKI4OWx321A_pr-7HhRNk7wOLLY</link>
      <description>In this series of short videos I'm showing you what .NET Standard is, how it works, and how you can use it.</description>
      <author> (Immo Landwerth
      
      

    
      
    

    
    
    
  
        •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRAdsfhKI4OWx321A_pr-7HhRNk7wOLLY</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://netcorehttp3.westus2.cloudapp.azure.com/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://netcorehttp3.westus2.cloudapp.azure.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lupusa87 - Overview</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Lupusa87</link>
      <description>I am from Georgia, came in USA June 2017.
I try to be productive programmer. - Lupusa87</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Lupusa87</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 23:16:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>joshfree - Overview</title>
      <link>https://github.com/joshfree</link>
      <description>Dev Lead on the Azure SDK team at Microsoft. Previously on .NET Core Base Class Libraries. - joshfree</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/joshfree</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 23:16:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Crossing: New Horizons Direct (Nintendo Switch)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/woE240wJxnA</link>
      <description>Pre-order Animal Crossing: New Horizons now: https://www.nintendo.co.uk/Games/Nintendo-Switch/Animal-Crossing-New-Horizons-1438623.html?c=purchase&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=youtube&amp;utm_campaign=AnimalCrossingNewHorizons%7CDirectAnnouncement%7Co1%7Cm_id_AtmznWEq7m%7C1438623%7Cw8

Tune in on February 20th at 2pm UK time for a roughly 25-minute livestreamed Animal Crossing: New Horizons Direct, featuring an in-depth look at Nook Inc.’s Deserted Island Getaway Package!

Facebook Nintendo Switch: https://facebook.com/NintendoSwitchUK
Facebook Animal Crossing: https://facebook.com/AnimalCrossingUK
Twitter Nintendo UK: https://twitter.com/NintendoUK
Twitter Animal Crossing: https://twitter.com/AC_Isabelle
Twitch Nintendo UK: https://twitch.tv/NintendoUK
Instagram Nintendo UK: https://www.instagram.com/nintendouk/
YouTube Nintendo UK: https://bit.ly/2cREWfu

#AnimalCrossing #ACNH #NintendoDirect #NintendoSwitch</description>
      <author> (Nintendo UK)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/woE240wJxnA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 22:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Computer Scientist Responsible For Cut, Copy, and Paste, Has Passed Away</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/larry-tessler-modeless-computing-advocate-has-passed-1841787408</link>
      <description>The advent of the personal computer wasn’t just about making these powerful machines available to everyone, it was also about making them accessible and usable, even for those lacking a computer science degree. Larry Tesler, who passed away on Monday, might not be a household name like Steve Jobs or Bill Gates, but his contributions to making computers and mobile devices easier to use are the highlight of a long career influencing modern computing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gizmodo.com/larry-tessler-modeless-computing-advocate-has-passed-1841787408</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 22:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seba's Photography - A blog about photography and (if happens) travels. Photographer based in Portsmouth, UK. Mainly portraits, street and few landscape photography</title>
      <link>http://sebasphotography.com/</link>
      <description>A blog about photography and (if happens) travels. Photographer based in Portsmouth, UK. Mainly portraits, street and few landscape photography</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://sebasphotography.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 21:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sebas77 - Overview</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sebas77</link>
      <description>CTO at Freejam, Developer of Robocraft and Cardlife. 
 - sebas77</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sebas77</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 21:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Perspective Validation Improves Domain Validation Security - Let's Encrypt - Free SSL/TLS Certificates</title>
      <link>https://letsencrypt.org/2020/02/19/multi-perspective-validation.html</link>
      <description>At Let’s Encrypt we’re always looking for ways to improve the security and integrity of the Web PKI. We’re proud to launch multi-perspective domain validation today because we believe it’s an important step forward for the domain validation process. To our knowledge we are the first CA to deploy multi-perspective validation at scale.
Domain validation is a process that all CAs use to ensure that a certificate applicant actually controls the domain they want a certificate for.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://letsencrypt.org/2020/02/19/multi-perspective-validation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 21:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is there a good way to communicate choose at least one?</title>
      <link>https://ux.stackexchange.com/questions/131633/is-there-a-good-way-to-communicate-choose-at-least-one</link>
      <description>I am wondering if there are any known good ways to concisely convey to users that they must must choose at least one option.
  
  Check boxes convey that the user can select 0 or more items.
  Radio</description>
      <author> (allenretzallenretz
        
            37922 silver badges44 bronze badges)</author>
      <guid>https://ux.stackexchange.com/questions/131633/is-there-a-good-way-to-communicate-choose-at-least-one</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 21:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepL Translator</title>
      <link>https://www.deepl.com/translator</link>
      <description>Use the free DeepL Translator to translate your texts with the best machine translation available, powered by DeepL’s world-leading neural network technology. Currently supported languages are English, German, French, Spanish, Portuguese, Italian, Dutch, Polish, and Russian.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.deepl.com/translator</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 20:51:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latacora - Stop Using Encrypted Email</title>
      <link>https://latacora.singles/2020/02/19/stop-using-encrypted.html</link>
      <description>Email is unsafe and cannot be made safe. The tools we have today to encrypt email are badly flawed. Even if those flaws were fixed, email would remain unsafe. Its problems cannot plausibly be mitigated. Avoid encrypted email.
Technologists hate this argument. Few of them specialize in cryptography or privacy, but all of them are interested in it, and many of them tinker with encrypted email tools.
Most email encryption on the Internet is performative, done as a status signal or show of solidarity.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://latacora.singles/2020/02/19/stop-using-encrypted.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 20:23:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password Managers with guest Troy Hunt | Weekly Dev Tips</title>
      <link>https://www.weeklydevtips.com/episodes/password-managers-with-guest-troy-hunt</link>
      <description>This is episode 63 on password managers with guest Troy Hunt.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.weeklydevtips.com/episodes/password-managers-with-guest-troy-hunt</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 20:22:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 1500 bytes became the MTU of the internet</title>
      <link>https://blog.benjojo.co.uk/post/why-is-ethernet-mtu-1500</link>
      <description>CC BY-SA 4.0 - Dmitry Nosachev</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.benjojo.co.uk/post/why-is-ethernet-mtu-1500</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 20:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does register selection matter to performance on x86 CPUs?</title>
      <link>https://fiigii.com/2020/02/16/Does-register-selection-matter-to-performance-on-x86-CPUs/</link>
      <description>Instruction selection is a critical portion in compilers, which different instructions could cause significantly performance difference even though the semantics not changed. Does register selection a</description>
      <author> (fiigii.com)</author>
      <guid>https://fiigii.com/2020/02/16/Does-register-selection-matter-to-performance-on-x86-CPUs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 20:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core Middleware Registration</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/aspnet-core-middleware-registration</link>
      <description>One of my favorite features of modern web development is Middleware. Middleware is a powerful abstraction that can encapsulate your intent, enrich an incoming request, enhance an outgoing response, or do all the above. Once you embrace Middleware as a potential approach to solving problems, it becomes second nature to think in that paradigm.</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/aspnet-core-middleware-registration</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 19:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hexa</title>
      <link>https://hexa.run/</link>
      <description>The ultimate companion for the Azure CLI. Setup and deploy in seconds.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hexa.run/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 18:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xLayers: Design – Code – Repeat</title>
      <link>https://xlayers.dev/</link>
      <description>Preview and Convert UI designs into ANY code, for ANY platform.</description>
      <author> (Wassim Chegham)</author>
      <guid>https://xlayers.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 18:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ngx.tools: Angular Packages Discovery</title>
      <link>https://ngx.tools/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ngx.tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 18:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor, a new framework for browser-based .NET apps - Steve Sanderson</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Khn7sDUSEJM</link>
      <description>Blazor is a new web UI framework that has become one of the headline features of .NET Core 3 and beyond. It lets you build rich interactive user experiences in C# and Razor, offering the benefits of a single-page app (SPA) framework while keeping all your code and data in .NET. It gives you a modern component-based architecture for powerful code reuse, first-class development tools, and all the productivity of .NET.

This talk will focus mostly on Blazor WebAssembly, which lets you create true client-side applications. We'll go right from </description>
      <author> (NDC Conferences)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Khn7sDUSEJM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 17:46:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Lawrence Montgomery, 1947-2020</title>
      <link>https://iacr.org/people/PeterMontgomery.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iacr.org/people/PeterMontgomery.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 17:46:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>galaxus.de – mehr als ein Onlineshop</title>
      <link>https://www.galaxus.de/</link>
      <description>Galaxus ist die deutsche Tochter des größten Schweizer Onlinehändlers und bietet Onlineshoppern in Deutschland ein hochwertiges Produktsortiment rund um IT, Elektronik und Telekommunikation an.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.galaxus.de/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 17:46:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Game Engine Exchange</title>
      <link>http://opengex.org/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://opengex.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 17:45:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSW Consulting - .NET, Web, Mobile, CRM, SharePoint, Azure, Power BI, Angular, React, Office 365 and Dynamics</title>
      <link>http://ssw.com.au/</link>
      <description>SSW Consulting has over 25 years of Microsoft software and web development experience. We build on top of Angular, React, .NET Core, Azure, Azure DevOps, SharePoint, Office 365, Dynamics 365 CRM and SQL Server. We have software consultants located in Sydney, Brisbane, Melbourne, Newcastle, and China.</description>
      <author> (SSW)</author>
      <guid>http://ssw.com.au/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 17:45:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why we left AWS</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/simplelogin/why-we-left-aws-2g8c</link>
      <description>I've always been using AWS for hosting from simple prototypes to critical B2B systems. Thanks to its...</description>
      <author> (Nguyen Kim Son)</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/simplelogin/why-we-left-aws-2g8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 17:15:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Worldwide Center of Mathematics on YouTube!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/centerofmath</link>
      <description>Welcome to the Worldwide Center of Mathematics!

Learn more about the Worldwide Center of Mathematics: http://centerofmath.org

About - http://centerofmath.org/about
Textbooks - http://centerofmath.org/store

Faculty may request free review copies anytime, anywhere: http://centerofmath.org

Request a video topic and contact us: info@centerofmath.org

Find @centerofmath on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Google+ and more!

#centerofmath</description>
      <author> (Worldwide Center of Mathematics)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/centerofmath</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 13:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Traveler</title>
      <link>https://codetraveler.io/</link>
      <description>Stories from a traveling developer</description>
      <author> (Brandon Minnick)</author>
      <guid>https://codetraveler.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 13:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core News - Your weekly update of everything ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://aspnetcore.news/</link>
      <description>ASP.NET Core News is the only weekly newsletter dedicated to ASP.NET Core. Whether you build Razor Pages, MVC applications, Web APIs, SignalR awesomeness, or anything else available on the ASP.NET Core platform, we've got you covered. Every Friday you will receive a weekly digest of the most interesting posts and articles from the last seven days.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aspnetcore.news/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 13:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-Truc Creation</title>
      <link>https://github.com/g-truc</link>
      <description>G-Truc Creation has 21 repositories available. Follow their code on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/g-truc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 13:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jkotas - Overview</title>
      <link>https://github.com/jkotas</link>
      <description>jkotas has 24 repositories available. Follow their code on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/jkotas</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 12:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIT/EE interface cleanup by jkotas · Pull Request #32521 · dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/32521/files</link>
      <description>Delete methods on JIT/EE interface that are no longer used in CoreCLR</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/32521/files</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 12:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeachPie | PHP compiler to .NET</title>
      <link>https://peachpie.io/</link>
      <description>PeachPie allows you to run PHP applications on .NET Core - faster, stabler and more secure.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://peachpie.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 10:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Southall</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.co.uk/Ed-Southall/e/B06XT254RD/ref=sr_ntt_srch_lnk_1?qid=1528537432&amp;sr=8-1</link>
      <description>Follow Ed Southall and explore their bibliography from Amazon.com's Ed Southall Author Page.</description>
      <author> (Ed Southall)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.co.uk/Ed-Southall/e/B06XT254RD/ref=sr_ntt_srch_lnk_1?qid=1528537432&amp;sr=8-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 10:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure This Week: Watch the latest videos</title>
      <link>https://acloud.guru/series/azure-this-week/view/latest</link>
      <description>Join our ACG technical instructors as they recap the past week's developments in the world of Azure.</description>
      <author> (Published on 17 Feb 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://acloud.guru/series/azure-this-week/view/latest</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 08:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initial Memcached protocol by MonsieurTib · Pull Request #84 · davidfowl/BedrockFramework</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidfowl/BedrockFramework/pull/84</link>
      <description>This is a first version of Memcached protocol (and my first PR to an open source projet :-) ).
Currently, only binary protocol and GET/SET commands are supported.
Next steps :

cluster support
more...</description>
      <author> (MonsieurTib)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/davidfowl/BedrockFramework/pull/84</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 07:24:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StackShare Weekly Digest.</title>
      <link>https://stackshare.io/weekly</link>
      <description>Free newsletter featuring the best hand-curated new dev tools and infrastructure services.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stackshare.io/weekly</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 07:24:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There Are Whales Alive Today Who Were Born Before Moby Dick Was Written</title>
      <link>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/there-are-whales-alive-today-who-were-born-before-moby-dick-was-written-660944/</link>
      <description>Some of the bowhead whales in the icy waters off of Alaska today are over 200 years old</description>
      <author> (Rose Eveleth)</author>
      <guid>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/there-are-whales-alive-today-who-were-born-before-moby-dick-was-written-660944/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 07:24:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debuggers &amp; Domains | My Notes: Using Azure AD and MSAL for Application Authentication</title>
      <link>https://debuggers.domains/post/msal-app-auth/</link>
      <description>When building an internal application you probably have authentication and authorization needs. If you already have a Single Sign On (SSO) provider like Auth0 or Okta then you are in pretty good hands as they both have great documentation and features to support these kinds of scenarios. For the rest of us, we need to get creative and use the tools we already have available. For some of us Azure AD may be that tool. If your business is already using Office 365 or Azure you may be able to use Azure AD to meet your internal authentication needs. To add convenience, you may even already have your desired users entered in Azure AD and organized into groups.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://debuggers.domains/post/msal-app-auth/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 07:00:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/mbcrump</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/mbcrump</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 04:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome | Azure Tips and Tricks</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/</link>
      <description>Welcome to Azure Tips and Tricks, this site is a special collection of over 230+ tips, videos, conference talks that span the entire universe of the Azure platform. The tips you'll find here are based on real-world scenarios that I've encountered (along with the community) while using Azure. Feel free to jump in and come back weekly for new tips! - Michael Crump (@mbcrump)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 04:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating an OpenID Connect server proxy with OpenIddict 3.0's degraded mode</title>
      <link>https://kevinchalet.com/2020/02/18/creating-an-openid-connect-server-proxy-with-openiddict-3-0-s-degraded-mode/</link>
      <description>In this post, discover how to create a minimalist OIDC server proxy between Steam and your own APIs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kevinchalet.com/2020/02/18/creating-an-openid-connect-server-proxy-with-openiddict-3-0-s-degraded-mode/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 03:06:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdentityServer4: Building a Simple Token Server and Protecting Your ASP.NET Core APIs with JWT</title>
      <link>http://vmsdurano.com/apiboilerplate-and-identityserver4-access-control-for-apis/</link>
      <description>Introduction I got many questions how the ASP.NET Core ApiBoilerplate protects the API endpoints and which URL validates the token. If you are new to ASP.NET Core and are using the template to get started, chances are you...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://vmsdurano.com/apiboilerplate-and-identityserver4-access-control-for-apis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 03:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Feb 25, 2020 - Intro to Kubernetes with Ryan Nowak</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U_Jv3YoPcSI</link>
      <description>Join members from the ASP.NET teams for our community standup covering great community contributions for ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, and more. 

Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/aspnet-community-standup-2020-02-25</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U_Jv3YoPcSI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 03:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>