<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Portable Air Conditioners</title>
      <link>https://pmarks.net/ac/</link>
      <description>I bought a couple EdgeStar AP14001HS portable air conditioners in April 2020, since I expect to spend most of the Summer at home.  I'm not able to use window A/Cs here, though that would be the obvious choice for efficiency because all the hot parts remain outside.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pmarks.net/ac/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The mysterious case of man who can read letters—but not numbers—exposes roots of consciousness</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/07/mysterious-case-man-who-can-read-letters-not-numbers-exposes-complex-roots</link>
      <description>With a condition that’s “too strange for words,” patient can do mental math but cannot recognize numerals</description>
      <author> (By Sam KeanJul. 29, 2020 , 12:35 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/07/mysterious-case-man-who-can-read-letters-not-numbers-exposes-complex-roots</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>andrewlock/blazor-with-source-generators-poc</title>
      <link>https://github.com/andrewlock/blazor-with-source-generators-poc</link>
      <description>Contribute to andrewlock/blazor-with-source-generators-poc development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (andrewlock)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/andrewlock/blazor-with-source-generators-poc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Astronauts Return Home in SpaceX's Crew Dragon Spacecraft</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=13OkD0C_TWU</link>
      <description>They’re coming home! 🌎

On Aug. 1, NASA astronauts Robert Behnken and Douglas Hurley will depart from the International Space Station aboard SpaceX’s Dragon “Endeavour” spacecraft after their mission aboard our orbiting laboratory. Starting at 5:15 p.m. EDT, tune in for our live coverage to see the duo undock from the station and make their return back to planet Earth.</description>
      <author> (NASA)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=13OkD0C_TWU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 09:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Wong Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://www.davidwong.fr/</link>
      <description>Check the menu on the left to see what I've been up to!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.davidwong.fr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 08:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pimp up your Blazor EditForms with Tailwind CSS!</title>
      <link>https://jonhilton.net/pimp-up-blazor-edit-forms-with-tailwind-css</link>
      <description>EditForms are a unstyled by default, so it falls to you to make your forms pop!</description>
      <author> (Jon Hilton)</author>
      <guid>https://jonhilton.net/pimp-up-blazor-edit-forms-with-tailwind-css</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 08:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2km From Home</title>
      <link>https://2kmfromhome.com/5km</link>
      <description>How far can you exercise from home during the Government restrictions?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2kmfromhome.com/5km</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 06:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber attack downs Telstra network, affecting thousands of internet users</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/national/nsw/thousands-affected-by-telstra-internet-outage-20200802-p55hq9.html</link>
      <description>A cyber attack has brought down the critical internet address books that help run Telstra's network, resulting in thousands of people across Australia reporting outages on Sunday morning.</description>
      <author> (Angus Thompson, Ben Grubb)</author>
      <guid>https://www.smh.com.au/national/nsw/thousands-affected-by-telstra-internet-outage-20200802-p55hq9.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 05:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NES Background Parallax Explained - Audiovisual Effects Pt. 03</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wt73KPS_23w</link>
      <description>How can NES games create parallax background effects if the console only supports one background layer? It's all explained right here.

LINKS
Twitter (updates): https://twitter.com/RetroGameMechEx
Patreon (support): https://www.patreon.com/rgmechex
SubscribeStar (support): https://www.subscribestar.com/rgmechex
Discord (discussion): http://discord.rgmechex.com

SUPPORTERS
Thank you to everyone who supports the channel!
Anthony Losego, Dan Salvato, F. Murmel, Jonathan Aldrich, Ange Albertini, hyperforce, Avi Drissman, Mike Gerow, Larry Koubiak, Tina Wuest, Owen Christensen, Gynvael, Buddy, Chris Margroff, Brandan Lennox, Nik, Jason Hughes, Diamond Ice, Chris Post, Cypher Signal, Rupix, Gabe S, krivx, Walter Huf, Pixy011, David Spalding, Acceleration Shark, Rory Kelly, Carl Cassler, Joe Mecca, Michael Greb, Kefen, Heptonion, leftler, Scott Beca, 19day, Michael Dragone, John Losego, Travis, Arthur Kunkle, Jordan Wright, Christopher Tramel, Alexander Paz, Stephan J Hennion, coon, Node1729, Andrea, Michael Cafarelli, Red Sona, Kodi_x86, tripper, Nebelwerfer Granitara, Sten, 333Rich333, Glenn hEADcRASH Sugden NPC, Alex Yancey, David Mazarro, Steven, null, Ryan, Corey Ogburn, Martin Trozell, Garret Kelly, Jake Hickman, Joel Kuhn, Dan Shedd, Sembiance, Xander479, 4F Panda, Max Roncace, David, A Sentient JDAM, Alec Johnson, Brian Henriquez, Travis Nellor, Zach Hugethanks, dishsoap42, Yakov, Oxygen Chen, RetroReversing.com, yuriks, Ceres, Jeremiah, Chris Roy, Chris Connett, Mark, Matthew, sapslaj, Jonathan Scott, Xkeeper, Bjoern Hansen, ers35, Daniel Bernard (ReckedCat), Lukas Kalbertodt, Vier Ladair, Bwangry, iPaq, zephyrin, Jeremy Wright, David Johnson, Brandon, Matt Shepard, Felix Freiberger, Sypwn, Niles Rogoff, Reflet, Yann Le Brech, Evan, Eugene Bulkin, Walter Weaver, Gethiox, Articate, Julien Oster, buzzert, Steve Losh, Samuel Stoddard, HattyJetty, Paige ? Hex, Yeero, Cruz Godar, Linh Pham, Noah Greenberg, Nick Rogers, Sean Nelson (audiohacked), Bryce, Andrew Yukhymchak, Sean Bryant, John Gabriel, BazBadger, Kyle, Master Knight DH, Tim Romero, Michael B., Eric Loewenthal, Adrian Haslinger, Proxy, Nolan Varani, Thoscellen, Wii2, Daniel Robinson, Hans Jorgensen, waielal, Daniel A.A. Pelsmaeker, Aaron, Max Gartung, Nicolas Dohrendorf, Eric Hoppe, Chaz Serir, derHinek, Gyiyg, Niels Peyronnel, samfu, Dominic Wehrmann, André Greubel, Anon42, Urda, Ted Berkowitz, araknofennisti, AA, Joseph Torres, serhef, Daniel, Patrick Johnston, Rodrigo Monteiro, Punchmaster, Stephen Bank, Thomas Berg, Crazed Geek, Dasterin, Matthew Yu, Alice Hartley, KieferSkunk, Tasman, &amp; Marcus N!</description>
      <author> (Retro Game Mechanics Explained)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wt73KPS_23w</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 03:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing Passwords</title>
      <link>https://textslashplain.com/2020/07/29/revealing-passwords/</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Edge browser, Edge Legacy, and Internet Explorer all offer a convenient mechanism for users to unmask their typing as they edit a password field: Clicking the little eye icon disables…</description>
      <author> (Published by ericlaw)</author>
      <guid>https://textslashplain.com/2020/07/29/revealing-passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 02:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Wong Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://davidwong.fr/index2.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidwong.fr/index2.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 02:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Wong</title>
      <link>https://davidwong.fr/</link>
      <description>site vitrine de david wong</description>
      <author> (david wong)</author>
      <guid>https://davidwong.fr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 02:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happened When I Peeked Into My Node_Modules Directory</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/s/silicon-satire/i-peeked-into-my-node-modules-directory-and-you-wont-believe-what-happened-next-b89f63d21558</link>
      <description>Just absolute madness</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@jdan)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/s/silicon-satire/i-peeked-into-my-node-modules-directory-and-you-wont-believe-what-happened-next-b89f63d21558</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 01:44:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ineffective Altruism</title>
      <link>https://www.zainrizvi.io/blog/the-most-effective-altruism/</link>
      <description>What a homeless cametaught me about caring for others</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.zainrizvi.io/blog/the-most-effective-altruism/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 23:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did Neobanks become so boring? - This Too Shall Pass by Rhys Wallace</title>
      <link>https://thistooshallpass.blog/why-did-neobanks-become-so-boring/</link>
      <description>In the first half of 2020, overhyped neobanks went from a contrarian opinion to a major industry talking point. What happened?</description>
      <author> (This Too Shall Pass by Rhys Wallace					

					Exploring the business of tech and media strategy)</author>
      <guid>https://thistooshallpass.blog/why-did-neobanks-become-so-boring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 23:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chartfleau | Kodak Insider Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.chartfleau.com/kodak/</link>
      <description>A look at the impact of inside information on Kodak's stock price.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.chartfleau.com/kodak/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 23:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing knowledge in a remote team, across timezones</title>
      <link>https://erickhun.com/posts/sharing-knowledge-in-a-remote-team/</link>
      <description>“True innovation comes an intersection of a cross-pollination of roles and ideas” - Sunil, ex-CTO@Buffer
 I’ve been working remotely at Buffer for 6 years now. As a software engineer, one of the critical skill I believe we should must have is being able to learn continuously. However, working in a fully distributed team, split accross 10+ timezones. I live in Asia (UTC +8) while most of my teammates live in the US or Europe.</description>
      <author> (Eric Khun)</author>
      <guid>https://erickhun.com/posts/sharing-knowledge-in-a-remote-team/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 23:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>English to SQL: progess updates</title>
      <link>https://paulfitz.github.io/2020/08/01/translate-english-to-sql-progress-updates.html</link>
      <description>English to SQL translation is getting better!  Can you guess which of
these queries to find the actor appearing in the most movies (in a fictional dataset)
was written by a human, and which by machine?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://paulfitz.github.io/2020/08/01/translate-english-to-sql-progress-updates.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 23:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techniques for Difficult Team Members - dcaulfield</title>
      <link>http://www.dcaulfield.com/techniques-for-difficult-team-members/</link>
      <description>Leading a team is difficult – it’s why people love or hate the job. Where a team member incorporates themselves into the people and culture around them, the team lead drives that assimilation and culture. They must understand that each person has a different personality, and therefore each team culture is different. If this wasn’t …</description>
      <author> (David Caulfield)</author>
      <guid>http://www.dcaulfield.com/techniques-for-difficult-team-members/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When you find out you’re the copycat</title>
      <link>https://bbirnbaum.com/when-you-find-out-youre-the-copycat/</link>
      <description>It was a rollercoaster of a week. It began when my side project, which I’d been quietly building for seven months, unexpectedly made it to the number two spot on Hacker News. It ended with me considering whether I should give up on the project completely.</description>
      <author> (About Ben Birnbaum)</author>
      <guid>https://bbirnbaum.com/when-you-find-out-youre-the-copycat/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 23:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python is now the second most popular language for programming  - newserector</title>
      <link>https://www.newserector.com/python-is-now-the-second-most-popular-language-for-programming</link>
      <description>Java is not one of the top two locations on RedMonk 's popularity list for the first time since 2012.</description>
      <author> (Article Edited by | Jhon N  |)</author>
      <guid>https://www.newserector.com/python-is-now-the-second-most-popular-language-for-programming</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 22:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dodyg/practical-aspnetcore</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dodyg/practical-aspnetcore/tree/3.1-LTS/projects/5-0/orleans/hello-world-3</link>
      <description>Practical samples of aspnet core 2.1, 2.2, 3.1 and 5.0 Preview 7 projects you can use. Readme contains explanations on all projects. - dodyg/practical-aspnetcore</description>
      <author> (dodyg)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dodyg/practical-aspnetcore/tree/3.1-LTS/projects/5-0/orleans/hello-world-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 21:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbricking a $2,000 Bike With a $10 Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://ptx2.net/posts/unbricking-a-bike-with-a-raspberry-pi/</link>
      <description>The Flywheel Home Bike. Image: Flywheel Sports.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ptx2.net/posts/unbricking-a-bike-with-a-raspberry-pi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 20:34:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordSafety.com</title>
      <link>http://wordsafety.com/</link>
      <description>Trying to decide a name for a website, app or other project?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://wordsafety.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 20:12:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I Learned from Doing 60+ Technical Interviews in 30 Days</title>
      <link>https://meekg33k.dev/what-i-learned-from-doing-60-technical-interviews-in-30-days-ckda9sn7s00iftss13b0wd0ky?guid=none&amp;deviceId=d42a5b4b-1ad8-4bd6-833b-a63fe2520944</link>
      <description>In this article, I’ll share my motivation for doing 60+ technical interviews in 30 days. More importantly, I’ll share 13 lessons I learned from my failures and my successes.
I’ve grouped the lessons into three categories to match the phases of a typi...</description>
      <author> (Uduak Obong-ErenJul 3113 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://meekg33k.dev/what-i-learned-from-doing-60-technical-interviews-in-30-days-ckda9sn7s00iftss13b0wd0ky?guid=none&amp;deviceId=d42a5b4b-1ad8-4bd6-833b-a63fe2520944</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 14:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OctoPrint.org</title>
      <link>https://octoprint.org/</link>
      <description>OctoPrint is the snappy web interface for your 3D printer that allows you to control and monitor all aspects of your printer and print jobs, right from your browser.</description>
      <author> (Gina Häußge)</author>
      <guid>https://octoprint.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 12:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OctoPrint/OctoPrint</title>
      <link>https://github.com/OctoPrint/OctoPrint</link>
      <description>OctoPrint is the snappy web interface for your 3D printer! - OctoPrint/OctoPrint</description>
      <author> (OctoPrint)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/OctoPrint/OctoPrint</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 12:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>