<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Moon – Bartosz Ciechanowski</title>
      <link>https://ciechanow.ski/moon/</link>
      <description>Interactive article about the Moon</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ciechanow.ski/moon/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 19:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf 2024 Recap - Celebrating .NET 9, AI, Community, &amp;amp; More - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-conf-2024-recap/</link>
      <description>.NET Conf 2024 is over, but you can catch up with all the announcement and fun with video recordings, slides, demos, and more.</description>
      <author> (facebook.com/dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-conf-2024-recap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 19:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting to Two Million Users as a One Woman Dev Team</title>
      <link>https://brightonruby.com/2024/getting-to-2-million-users-as-a-one-woman-dev-team/</link>
      <description>The story of the The StoryGraph with graphs</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://brightonruby.com/2024/getting-to-2-million-users-as-a-one-woman-dev-team/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 17:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA&amp;#39;s $249 Secret Weapon for Edge AI - Jetson Orin Nano Super: Driveway Monitor</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=QHBr8hekCzg</link>
      <description>FREE GIVEAWAY OF JENSEN-HUANG-SIGNED ORIN NANO SUPER!  See Below!
Join Dave as he explores NVIDIA&amp;#39;s Jetson Orin Nano, a compact AI powerhouse with 1024 CUDA cores and 6 ARM cores for just $249. Learn why this could be the best AI board for your projects in robotics, IoT, or AI development.  Free Sample of my Book on the Spectrum: https://amzn.to/3zBinWM

Orin Nano Super: https://nvda.ws/41DSukS

We&amp;#39;re giving away a free Jetson Orin Nano to a lucky winner randomly selected from the comments.  Better yet, it&amp;#39;s personally signed by Jensen Huang!

Leave a useful comment to be automatically entered to win!  Winner will be announced by their ebay username in a FUTURE VIDEO.  I will not contact you on YouTube, and I do not use Telegram. 

Highlights:
Unboxing and First Impressions
Performance Comparison: Against Raspberry Pi and high-end desktops
Real-World Use: Smart driveway with AI vehicle detection
Software Setup: Ubuntu, CUDA, and AI models like YOLOv8
AI Experiments: Running Llama 3.2 on this tiny board

Why Watch:
Dive into edge computing and AI on a budget
See practical applications of AI hardware
Understand NVIDIA&amp;#39;s CUDA cores for machine learning

Python Code:
https://github.com/davepl/ObjectDetect</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=QHBr8hekCzg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C#, Web Dev, Accessibility, GitHub Actions, and YOUR contributions!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=44zZYwF5fwo</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Fritz is working on adding a plugin system to SharpSite https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/SharpSite</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=44zZYwF5fwo</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybridCache - The New Caching Library in .NET 9</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=MQ96krIOjs4</link>
      <description>Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Join a community of 1000+ .NET developers: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic

Learn about HybridCache, an exciting new caching library in .NET 9! This tutorial covers how to implement hybrid caching by combining local in-memory caching with Redis distributed caching using just a few lines of code. We&amp;#39;ll explore the new HybridCacheEntryOptions, set up expiration times, and show you how to efficiently manage your application&amp;#39;s cache across different storage layers. HybridCache solves many of the drawbacks of the existing caching implementations we have today.

HybridCache in ASP.NET Core - New Caching Library
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/hybrid-cache-in-aspnetcore-new-caching-library

Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters
0:00 IMemoryCache and its drawbacks
3:46 IDistributedCache and its drawbacks
4:58 Installing and using HybridCache
10:42 Using Redis as a distributed cache
14:24 Cache stampede protection</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=MQ96krIOjs4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 13:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Surprising Lessons Software Developers Can Learn From &amp;#39;Factfulness’</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_Q5kDt3lR2s</link>
      <description>Here are 10 lessons from the book &amp;quot;Factfulness&amp;quot; that made me a better developer.
 
&amp;#128217; Factfulness: https://www.amazon.es/dp/147363749X?ref_=as_li_ss_tl&amp;amp;language=en_US&amp;amp;linkCode=gg2&amp;amp;linkId=89e43c4da086b74ba218d0df26a59e71&amp;amp;tag=guiferreira07-20

⏲️ CHAPTERS
00:00 Intro
02:17 Lesson 1
03:56 Lesson 2
05:55 Lesson 3
07:53 Lesson 4
09:33 Lesson 5
11:46 Lesson 6
14:10 Lesson 7
15:51 Lesson 8
17:33 Lesson 9
19:12 Lesson 10</description>
      <author> (Gui Ferreira)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_Q5kDt3lR2s</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 13:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Way to Run Database Migrations</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=StBf3-M5WdM</link>
      <description>Subscribe to Gui: https://www.youtube.com/@gui.ferreira
Get the source code: https://mailchi.mp/dometrain/stbf3-m5wdm

Become a Patreon and get special perks: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsas

Hello, everybody. I&amp;#39;m Nick and in this video, @gui.ferreira will show you how to properly run your database migrations.

Workshops: https://bit.ly/nickworkshops

Don&amp;#39;t forget to comment, like and subscribe :)

Social Media:
Follow me on GitHub: https://github.com/Elfocrash
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/nickchapsas
Connect on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick-chapsas

Keep coding merch: https://keepcoding.shop

#csharp #dotnet</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=StBf3-M5WdM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 12:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - markmoxon/elite-source-code-commodore-64: Fully documented and annotated source code for Elite on the Commodore 64</title>
      <link>https://github.com/markmoxon/elite-source-code-commodore-64</link>
      <description>Fully documented and annotated source code for Elite on the Commodore 64 - markmoxon/elite-source-code-commodore-64</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/markmoxon/elite-source-code-commodore-64</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 11:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Protobuf: The new Opaque API - The Go Programming Language</title>
      <link>https://go.dev/blog/protobuf-opaque</link>
      <description>We are adding a new generated code API to Go Protobuf.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://go.dev/blog/protobuf-opaque</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 11:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluesky and Decentralization -- Dustycloud Brainstorms</title>
      <link>https://dustycloud.org/blog/re-re-bluesky-decentralization/</link>
      <description>A few weeks ago I wrote
How decentralized is Bluesky really?,
a blogpost which received far more attention than I expected on the
fediverse and Bluesky both.  Thankfully, the blogpost was received
well generally, including by Bluesky&amp;#39;s team.  Bryan Newbold, core
Bluesky engineer, wrote a thoughtful response article:
Reply on Bluesky and Decentralization,
which I consider worth reading.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dustycloud.org/blog/re-re-bluesky-decentralization/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 01:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Hands-on Resilient Programming</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ID-bz6PUWF8</link>
      <description>How do you ensure your .NET apps survive crashes and service restarts with minimal impact to the user? In this week&amp;#39;s episode, community member Thomas Stidsborg Sylvest joins the panel to show us how to implement ensure our apps stay running when external calls fail.

Repo: https://github.com/stidsborg/Cleipnir.Flows/tree/main/Samples/Cleipnir.Flows.Sample.MicrosoftOpen/Flows

Featuring: Thomas Stidsborg Sylvest, Cam Soper (@CamSoper), Scott Addie (@Scott_Addie), David Pine (@davidpine7)

#resiliency</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ID-bz6PUWF8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 01:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loog Piano: My review</title>
      <link>https://joeblu.com/blog/2024_12_loog/</link>
      <description>I bought two of the original Loog guitars, little 3-string acoustic guitars intended for new learners and especially children. There’s a lot to like about them: they’re inexpensive, cute, and have surprisingly good sound and volume. The larger one gives a tenor guitar sort of sound that’s pleasant, and the smaller one is ukulele-ish. The kids are getting old enough to be into them, and I love having them around.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joeblu.com/blog/2024_12_loog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreasonable Effectiveness of SKIP LOCKED in PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://www.inferable.ai/blog/posts/postgres-skip-locked</link>
      <description>Using SKIP LOCKED to distribute work across machines in a distributed system is a popular pattern. We explore why, the alternatives, and a real world example from our own codebase.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.inferable.ai/blog/posts/postgres-skip-locked</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I over-engineered this blog?</title>
      <link>https://mbeaudru.com/posts/why-i-overengineered-this-blog</link>
      <description>Exploring the benefits of doing your own blog from scratch</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mbeaudru.com/posts/why-i-overengineered-this-blog</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crashing rockets and recovering data from damaged flash chips</title>
      <link>https://dontvacuum.me/rocketflashrecovery/index.html</link>
      <description>In Spring 2020, during IAP, the MIT Rocket team launched multiple rockets at the FAR site in the Mojave desert in California.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dontvacuum.me/rocketflashrecovery/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why we need seven bins</title>
      <link>https://takes.jamesomalley.co.uk/p/why-we-need-seven-bins</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s time for some #binchat</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://takes.jamesomalley.co.uk/p/why-we-need-seven-bins</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An invitation into Droste&amp;#39;s Lair</title>
      <link>https://vezwork.github.io/drostes-lair-post/</link>
      <description>A swords-and-sorcery programming environment for building and counting mathematical structures</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vezwork.github.io/drostes-lair-post/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Dictate a Note’ is my new favorite shortcut (and that’s saying something)</title>
      <link>https://heydingus.net/blog/2024/12/dictate-a-note-is-my-new-favorite-shortcut-and-thats-saying-something</link>
      <description>Imagine this: You’re driving down the road when a Very Good Idea springs to mind. You need to capture it quickly without fumbling through screens or</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://heydingus.net/blog/2024/12/dictate-a-note-is-my-new-favorite-shortcut-and-thats-saying-something</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LFGSS and Microcosm shutting down 16th March 2025 (the day before the Online Safety Act is enforced)</title>
      <link>https://www.lfgss.com/conversations/401475/</link>
      <description>Why

Reading https://www.ofcom.org.uk/online-safety/illegal-and-harmful-content/time-for-tech-firms-to-act-uk-online-safety-regulation-comes-into-force/ and we&amp;amp;#39;re done... we fall firmly into scope, and I have no way to dodge it. The act is too broad, and it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t matter that there&amp;amp;#39;s never been an instance of any of the proclaimed things that this act protects adults, children and vulnerable people from... the very broad language and the fact that I&amp;amp;#39;m based in the UK means we&amp;amp;#39;re covered.

The act simply does not care that this site and platform is run by an individual, and that I do so philanthropically without any profit motive (typically losing money), nor that the site exists to reduce social loneliness, reduce suicide rates, help build meaningful communities that enrich life.

The act only cares that is it &amp;amp;#34;linked to the UK&amp;amp;#34; (by me being involved as a UK native and resident, by you being a UK based user), and that users can talk to other users... that&amp;amp;#39;s it, that&amp;amp;#39;s the scope.

I can&amp;amp;#39;t afford what is likely tens of thousand to go through all the legal hoops here over a prolonged period of time, the site itself barely gets a few hundred in donations each month and costs a little more to run... this is not a venture that can afford compliance costs... and if we did, what remains is a disproportionately high personal liability for me, and one that could easily be weaponised by disgruntled people who are banned for their egregious behaviour (in the years running fora I&amp;amp;#39;ve been signed up to porn sites, stalked IRL and online, subject to death threats, had fake copyright takedown notices, an attempt to delete the domain name with ICANN... all from those whom I&amp;amp;#39;ve moderated to protect community members)... I do not see an alternative to shuttering it.

The conclusion I have to make is that we&amp;amp;#39;re done... Microcosm, LFGSS, the many other communities running on this platform... the risk to me personally is too high, and so I will need to shutter them all.

What and When

So here&amp;amp;#39;s the statement...

On Sunday 16th March 2025 (the last day prior to the Act taking effect) I will delete the virtual servers hosting LFGSS and other communities, and effectively immediately end the approximately 300 small communities that I run, and the few large communities such as LFGSS.

It&amp;amp;#39;s been a good run, I&amp;amp;#39;ve administered internet forums since 1996 having first written my own in Perl to help fans of music bands to connect with each other, and I then contributed to PHP forum software like vBulletin, Vanilla, and phpBB, before finally writing a platform in Go that made it cost efficient enough to bring interest based communities to so many others, and expand the social good that comes from people being connected to people.

Approximately 28 years and 9 months of providing almost 500 forums in total to what is likely a half a million people in that time frame... the impact that these forums have had on the lives of so many cannot be understated.

The peak of the forums has been the last 5 years, we&amp;amp;#39;ve plateaued around 275k monthly users across the almost 300 websites on multiple instances of the platform that is Microcosm, though LFGSS as a single community probably peaked in the 2013-2018 time period when it alone was hitting numbers in excess of 50k monthly users.

The forums have delivered marriages, births, support for those who have passed (cancer being the biggest reason), people reunited with stolen bikes, travel support, work support, so much joy and happiness and memorable experiences... but it&amp;amp;#39;s also been directly cited by many as being the reason that they are here today, the reason they didn&amp;amp;#39;t commit suicide or self-harm. It&amp;amp;#39;s help people get through awful relationship breakups, and helped people overcome incredible challenges with their health.

It&amp;amp;#39;s devastating to just... turn it off... but this is what the Act forces a sole individual running so many social websites for a public good to do.

I don&amp;amp;#39;t know where to recommend... I know lots of people have moved small groups to places like Signal and WhatsApp, and that some people are on the fediverse, and some are in other websites and groups.

There is no central place that could take us all and preserve the very special thing we had... so it&amp;amp;#39;s done.

This is a really special place... the people are special... I guess the next 3 months will be a time of sharing what it meant, and of groups figuring out where they want to go next.

Love you all forever, it&amp;amp;#39;s been amazing to be a part of it all, I never thought I&amp;amp;#39;d touch the lives of so many people by running websites, and in turn to give so much reason to my own life. In the end, the person I save most was likely myself.

Dee</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lfgss.com/conversations/401475/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A color for every day</title>
      <link>https://notes.npilk.com/daily-colors</link>
      <description>To make daily updates feel different from one day to the next, I generated a unique color combination for every day of the year.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.npilk.com/daily-colors</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The problem with User-Agent strings – Hello my name is Niels Leenheer</title>
      <link>https://nielsleenheer.com/articles/2024/the-problem-with-user-agent-strings/</link>
      <description>If you regularly check your website’s analytics, you may have noticed something weird in the past year or two. None of your visitors use Windows 11, and nobody upgraded their computer past macOS 10.15 Catalina. That can’t be right. So what is going on?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nielsleenheer.com/articles/2024/the-problem-with-user-agent-strings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform Rules of Thumb</title>
      <link>https://meadon.net/blog/terraform-rules-of-thumb/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://meadon.net/blog/terraform-rules-of-thumb/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;m a FIRST Mentor Again</title>
      <link>https://hardfault.life/p/frc</link>
      <description>It was only a matter of time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hardfault.life/p/frc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Essay</title>
      <link>https://what.yuri.is/advanced-essay/</link>
      <description>What might essays look like in the age of AI? (&amp;#127793; First draft.)
In the 1970s, decades before computers began to compete at the highest levels of chess, a new variant of the game was invented, called Advanced Chess. The idea was that instead of a human player competing against a computer, the human and machine would play together on the same side.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://what.yuri.is/advanced-essay/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The power of prototyping</title>
      <link>https://dzidas.com/datascience/2024/12/16/the-power-of-prototyping/</link>
      <description>Learn practical strategies for innovation, prototyping, and creating data-driven products from AWS experience. Explore the Working Backwards framework and real-world examples of successful prototyping.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dzidas.com/datascience/2024/12/16/the-power-of-prototyping/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On OpenTelemetry and the value of Standards | Jeremy Morrell</title>
      <link>https://jeremymorrell.dev/blog/opentelemetry-and-the-value-of-standards/</link>
      <description>OpenTelemetry is not perfect, but the value of having one shared standard for instrumentation and telemetry is huge</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jeremymorrell.dev/blog/opentelemetry-and-the-value-of-standards/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complexity Dynamics of Grokking</title>
      <link>https://brantondemoss.com/research/grokking/</link>
      <description>In grokking experiments, the
unregularized network’s complexity rises and remains high as it
memorizes the training data, never generalizing. The regularized
network’s complexity similarly rises, but as it groks and generalization
occurs, the complexity falls.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://brantondemoss.com/research/grokking/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Right Way to Split a Bill – betterchurn.com</title>
      <link>https://betterchurn.com/?p=18</link>
      <description>You’re at dinner with your friends. The bill arrives. You’ve been there. Everyone got something different, and the restaurant cant split by seat. What do you do? Its simple. Use this app I made.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://betterchurn.com/?p=18</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Care about the domain, not about implementing all the patterns and principles under the sun</title>
      <link>https://blog.codingmilitia.com/2024/12/16/care-about-the-domain-not-about-implementing-all-the-patterns-and-principles-under-the-sun/</link>
      <description>Time again for a rant adjacent post, on this occasion, about building applications following some domain-driven design ideas.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.codingmilitia.com/2024/12/16/care-about-the-domain-not-about-implementing-all-the-patterns-and-principles-under-the-sun/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 21:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData with Qdrant and Azure AI Search - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/vector-data-qdrant-ai-search-dotnet/</link>
      <description>Discover how to use Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData to implement semantic search using Qdrant and Azure AI Search</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/vector-data-qdrant-ai-search-dotnet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 20:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 years of Dillo</title>
      <link>https://dillo-browser.github.io/25-years/</link>
      <description>Back in 1999, a group of developers lead by Jorge Arellano Cid forked the
Gzilla/Armadillo code originally
developed by Raph Levien, and began working on what is now known as the Dillo
web browser.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dillo-browser.github.io/25-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 20:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>