<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>LPCAMM2 Is Finally Here, and It’s a Big Deal | iFixit News</title>
      <link>https://www.ifixit.com/News/95078/lpcamm2-memory-is-finally-here</link>
      <description>LPCAMM2 promises to be the thin, fast, efficient, and REPAIRABLE laptop memory standard of the future. Today, we take apart the first laptop to actually use it.</description>
      <author> (Article by:
      Carsten Frauenheim
      @carsten)</author>
      <guid>https://www.ifixit.com/News/95078/lpcamm2-memory-is-finally-here</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Big Guide to Hydrogen</title>
      <link>https://climate.benjames.io/hydrogen/</link>
      <description>Hydrogen is a critical ingredient and dominant cost in most green fuels. You can&amp;#39;t produce cheap green ammonia or Sustainable Aviation Fuel without cheap hydrogen.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://climate.benjames.io/hydrogen/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing and smelling the Critical Zone</title>
      <link>https://rybakov.com/blog/smelling_cz/</link>
      <description>










As part of the Critical Zones exhibition in ZKM Karlsruhe, Hanna Jurisch and I offered workshops to experience the Critical Zone in a more direct way. We called it “Kritische Zone riechen und sehen”, or, translated, “Seeing and smelling the Critical Zone”.
The Critical Zone is all about the processes of living, about living organisms and their entanglements.
The difficult thing about dealing with the Critical Zone is that our usual mental models that describe the space we live in seem inadequate and insufficient: top-down maps may show geographical features but are frozen in time. Worse yet, they don’t show any chemical, biological, mechanical processes of living, or any living organisms at all for that matter. They capture a specific point of view, not a point of life (point de vue vs. point de vie as Bruno Latour would say). Sure, maps might sometimes show a single tree, but not the other things that make the tree alive – the water level, the rain, the chemical exchange between tree roots and bacterial colonies, the parasites and the birds that hunt them and so on. There is no future nor past in a map, there is no illness, no movement, no birth or death in a map.
It’s not a problem of scale, as it does not change even if we become very local, if we zoom in closely on one specific point.
Here an example:

  
      
  
  
  


On the left you see the changes to Dubai over a time period of 1984-2016, taken by satellite, looking down on earth from the outside. This is as an extreme example of terraforming and land development, fueled by vanity and the political will to build funny looking shapes into the ocean. And even with this being the extreme example, the timeframe of thirty years is a large one. A casual observer drinking tea in the orbit and looking down on earth would not notice the change brought by our processes of life.
On the right, a flock of common wood pigeons landed in front of my house in Karlsruhe, February 2021. The polar vortex broke in February, covering large parts of US and Europe in ice and snow. The wood pigeons moved from the woods to cities to find a bit more warmth and food. They move as individuals, until they get spooked by an arriving bike driver, and fly away as a flock, as a superorganism.
This slice of life may be human scale, but it still shows just a point of view. The text description above is needed to turn it into a (very limited, admittedly) point of life.
So Hanna and I decided to cast aside the hyper-global medium of maps and hyper-local medium of video, and searched for a new way to get attuned to the processes of living, of all the tiny interwoven actions happening within the Critical Zone.
We arrived at similar but distinct approaches.









	Hanna talking about the similarities in shape and texture between human-made and non-human made found objects




Hanna would take the workshop participants for a walk and let them gather material, human-made and non-human-made alike. Gather everything that grew around the museum or was discarded by people. All the unseen, unintentional objects in the surroundings. Like a dog that sheds hair, processes of life shed bottle caps, pieces of glass, feathers, drinking straws, leaves, bark, empty vodka bottles, screws, scrunchies, moss and concrete.
All the gathered material would later be arranged into sculptures and new taxonomies by the participants.









	Some of the sculptures and taxonomic reorderings that happened in the first workshop





My own approach was to try and capture the scent of the world around us.
I let participants gather fragrance materials from within their homes – basically everything that has a smell – and use these to create perfumes. Old coffee grounds, earth from a flower pot, fresh leaves, stale bread, or a mushroom found in the garden – all that was welcome, all that we would mix together into a perfume. A perfume of our own – very local – part of the Critical Zone.
I see these perfumes as true ‘scent maps’ of one specific point of life. Not only were the materials gathered by a person who (most of the time) somehow decided to have them in their lives, scents are also seemingly immaterial witnesses of material processes of life. Most smells that surround us are organic in origin, are witnesses of transformation of matter through living organisms, often unseen by us humans. Smell is a process.
One other thing I particularly like about smells is the sensory parallelism. Sure, some particularly smelly molecule might be overpowering others, but most of the times what we perceive as a scent is a combination of many different scents, many different organic molecules stemming from many different processes of life. And we perceive it all at once – something that is impossible to achieve by mapping the Critical Zone in the usual, top-down way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rybakov.com/blog/smelling_cz/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A comprehensive introduction to CDNs</title>
      <link>https://00f.net/2024/05/07/what-is-a-cdn/</link>
      <description>For many people, CDNs are an obvious requirement for any public API or web service. However, I’ve come to realize that for the vast majority, they remain somewhat mysterious - or something they’re unaware of, even though they unknowingly use them daily.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://00f.net/2024/05/07/what-is-a-cdn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation – Please Disregard</title>
      <link>https://shermanonsoftware.com/2024/05/06/explanation-please-disregard/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (jeffpsherman)</author>
      <guid>https://shermanonsoftware.com/2024/05/06/explanation-please-disregard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>immibis.com</title>
      <link>https://immibis.com/blog/5</link>
      <description>Date: 2024-05-07 04:20Tags: politics, wtf, platforms</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://immibis.com/blog/5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi is getting into the services game</title>
      <link>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2024/raspberry-pi-getting-services-game</link>
      <description>...and it&amp;#39;s all free—so far.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2024/raspberry-pi-getting-services-game</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should I run npm run build/prod on dev or prod?</title>
      <link>https://www.vincentschmalbach.com/should-i-run-npm-run-build-prod-on-dev-or-prod/</link>
      <description>Should you run on your development machine and commit everything to Git or should you commit your app without those files and run on your production server? Here are the pros and cons of those two…</description>
      <author> (by Vincent Schmalbach)</author>
      <guid>https://www.vincentschmalbach.com/should-i-run-npm-run-build-prod-on-dev-or-prod/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Tilde - The Tilde Text Editor</title>
      <link>https://os.ghalkes.nl/tilde/index.html</link>
      <description>Tilde is a text editor for the console/terminal, which provides an intuitive
interface for people accustomed to GUI environments such as Gnome, KDE
and Windows. For example, the short-cut to copy the current selection is
Control-C, and to paste the previously copied text the short-cut Control-V can
be used. As another example, the File menu can be accessed by pressing Meta-F.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://os.ghalkes.nl/tilde/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(yet another) Broken Adversarial Example Defense at IEEE S&amp;amp;P 2024</title>
      <link>https://nicholas.carlini.com/writing/2024/yet-another-broken-defense.html</link>
      <description>IEEE S&amp;amp;P 2024 (one of the top computer security conferences)
        has, again, accepted an adversarial example defense paper
        that is broken with simple attacks.
        It contains claims that are mathematically impossible,
        does not follow recommended guidance on evaluating adversarial
        robustness,
        and its own figures present all the necessary evidence that the
        evaluation was conducted incorrectly.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicholas.carlini.com/writing/2024/yet-another-broken-defense.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Server in 2024</title>
      <link>https://martinbaun.com/blog/posts/securing-your-server-in-2024/</link>
      <description>Using knockd to secure your ubuntu or other linux server</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martinbaun.com/blog/posts/securing-your-server-in-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The illusion of having it all figured out - Scott Taylor</title>
      <link>https://st.im/posts/the-illusion-of-having-it-all-figured-out</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://st.im/posts/the-illusion-of-having-it-all-figured-out</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The birth of Parquet</title>
      <link>https://sympathetic.ink/2024/01/24/Chapter-1-The-birth-of-Parquet.html</link>
      <description>By Julien Le Dem</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sympathetic.ink/2024/01/24/Chapter-1-The-birth-of-Parquet.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double-Entry Bookkeeping for Hackers</title>
      <link>http://markan.net/double-entry.html</link>
      <description>Sean Markan</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://markan.net/double-entry.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Operating System for the Web</title>
      <link>https://jasongullickson.com/an-operating-system-for-the-web.html</link>
      <description>This was before things like local storage, etc. were available in browsers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jasongullickson.com/an-operating-system-for-the-web.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How &amp;amp; Why I use IBM&amp;#39;s Quantum Computer to Make Decisions</title>
      <link>https://parel.es/blog/quantum-dice?hn2=</link>
      <description>Not sure if you should choose A or B? Do a unix fork on the universe to guarantee you made both choices. Maybe a more appropriate name is &amp;#39;quantum coin flip&amp;#39;. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://parel.es/blog/quantum-dice?hn2=</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Casual Dired - an opinionated porcelain for the Emacs file manager</title>
      <link>http://yummymelon.com/devnull/announcing-casual-dired---an-opinionated-porcelain-for-the-emacs-file-manager.html</link>
      <description>Truth be told, my thoughts about the Emacs file manager Dired are complicated. On the one hand, I do buy the argument that Dired is unparalleled as a file manager. It enables workflows that...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://yummymelon.com/devnull/announcing-casual-dired---an-opinionated-porcelain-for-the-emacs-file-manager.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knuth • Sameer Ismail</title>
      <link>https://sameerismail.org/knuth</link>
      <description>Flipping through the mail one day the familiar maroon-tinged Stanford
        letterhead stuck out. Below it, clearly typeset,
        Donald E. Knuth Professor Emeritus of The Art of Computer
          Programming.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sameerismail.org/knuth</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Careful with That Lock, Eugene: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://kaveland.no/careful-with-that-lock-eugene-part-2.html</link>
      <description>A while back, I wrote Careful with That Lock,Eugene about an idea for how to check if a database migration is likely to disturb production. That post came about after having an inspiring chat with a colleague about the advantages of transactional migration scripts and the ability to check …</description>
      <author> (https://kaveland.no/author/robin-kaveland.html)</author>
      <guid>https://kaveland.no/careful-with-that-lock-eugene-part-2.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micro-dosing Caffeine</title>
      <link>https://ajkprojects.com/microdosingcaffeine</link>
      <description>Home</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ajkprojects.com/microdosingcaffeine</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managers have no human rights</title>
      <link>https://yosefk.com/blog/managers-have-no-human-rights.html</link>
      <description>Here are some thoughts which are often basically correct:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yosefk.com/blog/managers-have-no-human-rights.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Package Management &amp;amp; improved .NET Aspire support come to C# Dev Kit - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/may-release-of-csharp-dev-kit/</link>
      <description>Explore the new features and enhancements in the latest version of C# Dev Kit including NuGet package management, .NET Aspire project support, and much more.</description>
      <author> (Wendy Breiding (SHE/HER))</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/may-release-of-csharp-dev-kit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big O Notation</title>
      <link>https://henriquesd.medium.com/big-o-notation-7138a3e52786</link>
      <description>Big O Notation is a mathematical notation that describes the efficiency of an algorithm. This is useful to evaluate the efficiency of an…</description>
      <author> (https://henriquesd.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquesd.medium.com/big-o-notation-7138a3e52786</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotNetDave Rocks The Austin .NET User Group (2024)</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/05/07/dotnetdave-rocks-the-austin-net-user-group-2024/</link>
      <description>The dotNetDave No Rest for the Wicked World Tour is coming to the Austin .NET User Group in Texas on May 9th. This session will focus on code and app performance for Microsoft .NET, covering effici…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/05/07/dotnetdave-rocks-the-austin-net-user-group-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awaiting a set of handles with a timeout, part 6: Capturing the handles efficiently - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240507-00/?p=109729</link>
      <description>SFINAE&amp;#39;ing the case of a random-access(ish) iterator.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240507-00/?p=109729</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple introduces M4 chip</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apple-introduces-m4-chip/</link>
      <description>Apple today announced M4, the latest Apple-designed silicon chip delivering phenomenal performance to the all-new iPad Pro.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apple-introduces-m4-chip/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair Your Compilers At The ABI Caf&amp;#233; - Faultlore</title>
      <link>https://faultlore.com/blah/abi-puns/</link>
      <description>May 5th, 2024</description>
      <author> (Aria Beingessner)</author>
      <guid>https://faultlore.com/blah/abi-puns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proton Mail Discloses User Data Leading to Arrest in Spain</title>
      <link>https://restoreprivacy.com/protonmail-discloses-user-data-leading-to-arrest-in-spain/</link>
      <description>Proton Mail came under scrutiny for its role in a legal request by the Spanish authorities leading to the identification and arrest of a user.</description>
      <author> (Alex Lekander)</author>
      <guid>https://restoreprivacy.com/protonmail-discloses-user-data-leading-to-arrest-in-spain/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code It Any Way You Want: Constants vs. Read-only Fields</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/05/07/code-it-any-way-you-want-constants-vs-read-only-fields/</link>
      <description>The article discusses best practices for checking strings for null in coding. It outlines three common methods: using == null, is null, or string.IsNullOrEmpty().</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/05/07/code-it-any-way-you-want-constants-vs-read-only-fields/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 10:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middleware-Based Exception Handling in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/middleware-exception-handling-aspnet-core-guide/</link>
      <description>Unlock the full potential of your ASP.NET Core applications with our definitive guide to middleware-based exception handling. Learn how to gracefully manage errors, boost your application&amp;#39;s resilience, and protect against downtime with practical, easy-to-follow strategies</description>
      <author> (Pierre Belin)</author>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/middleware-exception-handling-aspnet-core-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;Secret&amp;quot; elmah.io features #4 - Get help from AI and ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://blog.elmah.io/secret-elmah-io-features-4-get-help-from-ai-and-chatgpt/</link>
      <description>This post highlights one of several AI/machine learning features available on elmah.io: AI-assisted error resolution using ChatGPT from OpenAI.</description>
      <author> (Written by Thomas Ardal, May 07, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.elmah.io/secret-elmah-io-features-4-get-help-from-ai-and-chatgpt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3661: TunnelVision - How Attackers Can Decloak Routing-Based VPNs For a Total VPN Leak — Leviathan Security Group - Penetration Testing, Security Assessment, Risk Advisory</title>
      <link>https://www.leviathansecurity.com/blog/tunnelvision</link>
      <description>We discovered a fundamental design problem in VPNs and we&amp;#39;re calling it TunnelVision. This problem lets someone see what you&amp;#39;re doing online, even if you think you&amp;#39;re safely using a VPN.</description>
      <author> (May 6
            
            Written By Cody Martin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.leviathansecurity.com/blog/tunnelvision</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring State Management Solutions Beyond Redux and MobX</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/exploring-state-management-solutions-beyond-redux-mobx</link>
      <description>State management is a crucial in React, and choosing a suitable state management tool is paramount. Explore state management solutions beyond Redux and MobX.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/exploring-state-management-solutions-beyond-redux-mobx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent Marten &amp;amp; Wolverine Improvements and Roadmap Update</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/05/03/recent-marten-wolverine-improvements-and-roadmap-update/</link>
      <description>I’d love any feedback on any of this of course. And from something I wrote in a survey of sorts about the commercial product ideas down below yesterday (which is partially a response to a rec…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/05/03/recent-marten-wolverine-improvements-and-roadmap-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactive Architecture Guarding</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@bnayae/proactive-architecture-guarding-b71c4a77a0ec</link>
      <description>Architecture Guarding with Static Code Analyzer and Code Fix</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@bnayae)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@bnayae/proactive-architecture-guarding-b71c4a77a0ec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is platform engineering and why do we need it? | Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/06/what-platform-engineering-and-why-do-we-need-it</link>
      <description>Discover the power of platform engineering and developer portals, which provide infrastructure, tools, and processes to boost productivity and reduce friction.</description>
      <author> (Markus Eisele)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/06/what-platform-engineering-and-why-do-we-need-it</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deniable Encryption</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/200993-C/deniable-encryption?Key=425d04e4-6c67-4830-ad02-6f6ab305848c</link>
      <description>I ran into an interesting Reddit comment&amp;amp;nbsp;about deniable encryption and decided to spend an evening playing with it. The concept is that we have a way to...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/200993-C/deniable-encryption?Key=425d04e4-6c67-4830-ad02-6f6ab305848c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Core - View outdated packages</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/05/net-core-view-outdated-packages.html</link>
      <description>When creating and maintaining (.NET Core) applications, it is always a good idea to keep the dependencies up-to-date. This helps to fix iden...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/05/net-core-view-outdated-packages.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#128273; Keyed Services in .NET Core 8: The Death of the Factory Pattern? &amp;#128273;</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/ahmedshahjr/keyed-services-in-net-core-8-the-death-of-the-factory-pattern-41ff</link>
      <description>In the world of .NET Core 8, we&amp;#39;re always looking for ways to write cleaner, more maintainable code....</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/ahmedshahjr/keyed-services-in-net-core-8-the-death-of-the-factory-pattern-41ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest effect on code quality</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/05/the-biggest-effect-on-code-quality.html</link>
      <description>You carefully assembled a team of great developers, a top architect, UX designers, product owners, etc… You are confident that with this tea...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/05/the-biggest-effect-on-code-quality.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C#: How to Enumerate over Enum values and names</title>
      <link>https://pietschsoft.com/post/2024/05/03/csharp-iterate-over-enum</link>
      <description>I have more than 20 years of experience in the Software Development industry that includes working as a Consultant and Trainer in a wide array of different industries. Welcome to my resume and work history portfolio website!</description>
      <author> (Chris Pietschmann)</author>
      <guid>https://pietschsoft.com/post/2024/05/03/csharp-iterate-over-enum</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative codomain conjecture</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/05/06/conservative-codomain-conjecture/</link>
      <description>An API design heuristic.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/05/06/conservative-codomain-conjecture/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disabling .NET Aspire authentication to skip the login page</title>
      <link>https://anthonysimmon.com/disabling-dotnet-aspire-authentication-skip-login-page/</link>
      <description>Do you find the login page of the .NET Aspire dashboard unnecessary for local development? Use of of these two methods to disable it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anthonysimmon.com/disabling-dotnet-aspire-authentication-skip-login-page/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to check if a DLL  and an exe is a .NET assembly - G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/how-to-check-if-a-dll-and-an-exe-is-a-dotnet-assembly.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to check if a DLL and an exe is a .NET assembly.</description>
      <author> (G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/how-to-check-if-a-dll-and-an-exe-is-a-dotnet-assembly.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sep 0.4.0-0.5.2 - Insanely Fast Single- &amp;amp; Multi-threaded .NET CSV Parsing (up to 35x faster than CsvHelper)</title>
      <link>https://nietras.com/2024/05/05/sep-0-4-0-0-5-2/</link>
      <description>As mentioned at the end of Sep 0.3.0 - Unescape Support (still the Most
Efficient .NET CSV Parser) there was
one big “issue” remaining with regards to Sep being the world’s fastest .NET CSV
parser and that was parallelization. Below is a sneak peek of how insanely fast
Sep is now, read on for more.

</description>
      <author> (nietras)</author>
      <guid>https://nietras.com/2024/05/05/sep-0-4-0-0-5-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good and Bad Ideas</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2929/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2929/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 05:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>