<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptography for Beginners With Christof Paar</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6r6nEVF3o8V13tzvyNm1rb?si=i6uHH80WQtqq6rZ89izHZQ&amp;dl_branch=1</link>
      <description>Listen to this episode from Madison Kanna Podcast on Spotify. In this epiosde, Christof gives an overview of cryptography for beginners.Christof Paar is Founding Director of the Max Planck Institute for Security and Privacy and Research Professor at the Univ. of Massachusetts Amherst. He has taught crypto and security courses for 25 years to thousands of students in the US &amp;amp; Europe. He also taught extensively in industry, including courses at NASA, Motorola &amp;amp; Philips. Christof has given invited talks at MIT, Yale, Stanford, IBM and Intel. He co-founded, with Cetin Koc, the Workshop on Cryptographic Hardware and Embedded Systems (CHES) and has 200+ scientific publications on applied cryptography.Christof&amp;#39;s crypto video series: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC1usFRN4LCMcfIV7UjHNuQgChristof&amp;#39;s book, Understanding Cryptography: https://www.amazon.com/Understanding-Cryptography-Textbook-Students-Practitioners/dp/3642446493Book site: https://www.crypto-textbook.com/</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6r6nEVF3o8V13tzvyNm1rb?si=i6uHH80WQtqq6rZ89izHZQ&amp;dl_branch=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 22:07:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s simple protocol, people,&amp;quot; the father said. &amp;quot;We follow certain rules for a very good reason.&amp;quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.tiktok.com/@usatoday/video/7000834914681769222?_d=secCgYIASAHKAESPgo8c0nQ8kyneQJlCNBhR%2Bqa2%2F%2F%2B1eI7H4BEDey00B7l%2FWlc%2FFyg%2BGOfIPh4VW7d22w1SUxAG5yoKpSwpZ9vGgA%3D&amp;checksum=b803ab03eb21746b47da8a79e5e29c0349b7bb9d553bcccf4d47870bca5dbf68&amp;language=en&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;sec_user_id=MS4wLjABAAAAWAzP1FOcrBhIELx12zOOtjBHXBKClkebOjMeU3ZHxjY&amp;share_app_id=1233&amp;share_item_id=7000834914681769222&amp;share_link_id=7237A75B-5854-445B-A799-6A9AB931FA21&amp;timestamp=1630098663&amp;u_code=42l9gl&amp;user_id=26565711&amp;_r=1</link>
      <description>USA TODAY (@usatoday) has created a short video on TikTok with music original sound. | &amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s simple protocol, people,&amp;quot; the father said. &amp;quot;We follow certain rules for a very good reason.&amp;quot; | Dripping Springs Independent School District</description>
      <author> (usatodayUSA TODAY &amp;#183; 1d ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiktok.com/@usatoday/video/7000834914681769222?_d=secCgYIASAHKAESPgo8c0nQ8kyneQJlCNBhR%2Bqa2%2F%2F%2B1eI7H4BEDey00B7l%2FWlc%2FFyg%2BGOfIPh4VW7d22w1SUxAG5yoKpSwpZ9vGgA%3D&amp;checksum=b803ab03eb21746b47da8a79e5e29c0349b7bb9d553bcccf4d47870bca5dbf68&amp;language=en&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;sec_user_id=MS4wLjABAAAAWAzP1FOcrBhIELx12zOOtjBHXBKClkebOjMeU3ZHxjY&amp;share_app_id=1233&amp;share_item_id=7000834914681769222&amp;share_link_id=7237A75B-5854-445B-A799-6A9AB931FA21&amp;timestamp=1630098663&amp;u_code=42l9gl&amp;user_id=26565711&amp;_r=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 22:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Store Payments Will Have Increased Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.kalzumeus.com/2021/08/27/app-store-payment-competition/</link>
      <description>Late on Thursday, Apple announced some refinements to their App Store policies. The most important one is about so-called “steering”, which is the practice of letting customers know about out-of-app options for transacting with them. I couldn’t not write about the trifecta of payments, platform strategy, and video games. (Disclaimer: while I work at Stripe, these are my own opinions.)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.kalzumeus.com/2021/08/27/app-store-payment-competition/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 22:07:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>r/kaiju - Is Clifford the Big red dog a kaiju?</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/kaiju/comments/by0klw/is_clifford_the_big_red_dog_a_kaiju/</link>
      <description>45 votes and 16 comments so far on Reddit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/kaiju/comments/by0klw/is_clifford_the_big_red_dog_a_kaiju/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:06:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is &amp;#39;Clifford the Big Red Dog&amp;#39; a kaiju?</title>
      <link>https://www.timeout.com/news/is-clifford-the-big-red-dog-a-kaiju-063021</link>
      <description>The live-action trailer suggests the mutt is of a kind with Godzilla</description>
      <author> (Andy Kryza)</author>
      <guid>https://www.timeout.com/news/is-clifford-the-big-red-dog-a-kaiju-063021</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:06:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Clifford the Big Red Dog a kaiju?</title>
      <link>https://www.quora.com/Is-Clifford-the-Big-Red-Dog-a-kaiju</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ll choose some of my favourite ones, The Endbringers from the web serial Worm. These are a group of semi-kaiju, but I think they count. They fullfill a similar role in any case. Every few months one of them attacks a target. The target is typically a city, though other targets have been shown, but they always want to cause damage and instability to society. For example, Behemoth, the first one, attacked and destroyed a large oil field in Iran, and another attacked and destroyed a plane containing the prince of China, causing a war. All of these should be able to easily beat most versions of Godzilla, though I don’t know about the high-end versions included in the composite. General Capabilities: Each Endbringer has absolutely insane durability. They consist of about 200 layers, each twice as tough as the last, with a core at the middle. They only die if you manage to destroy the core. The outer layer is quite vulnerable, but their durability quickly starts getting insane just a few layers in. By the time you reach the middle, you pretty much have to break the laws of physics to break through. A guy had a halberd that breaks molecular bonds, effectively disintigrating any matter it touches with no resistance. It got halfway through one Endbringer’s hand before getting stuck. The limbs are far more fragile than the torso, only consisting of 33 layers. The characters once dropped a bomb that would have destroyed India on Behemoth, concentrated on him using forcefields. The damage was entirely superficial. Nukes hardly even scratch them. They also have insane regeneration, only getting quicker the further towards to core you get. Most of them could easily destroy humanity through various ways. The only reason everyone in the books isn’t dead is because the Endbringers don’t want them dead, and run away if they take enough superficial damage during fights, which only superhumans can do. It takes hundreds of them, and many die in the fights. If the Endbringers stopped jobbing, they could kill almost every single one of the people fighting them. Now, for the specific Endbringers Behemoth45 feet tall, Behemoth is the second largest and most durable of the Endbringers. He’s a dynakinetic, so he controls energy. Radiation, kinetic energy, you name it. He shoots lightning that he controls completely, powerful enough to incinerate buildings, and if anyone gets within 32 feet of him they are instantly incinerated from the inside and out. He can emit a shockwave that levels buildings and extends for over half a mile, or a scream that turns people into figurative jelly. He can also redirect kinetic energy, whether it be into the ground or back at the one who inflicted the damage. He can also use this to run pretty quickly. While not attacking, he constantly burrows through the Earths mantle. It’s stated that he could manipulate energy underground to cause richter 10 earthquakes across the planet, but he doesn’t. Behemoth could probably just pull the radiation right out of Godzilla and turn it into enough energy to incinerate him from the inside. LeviathanLeviathan is the one that most resembles classic kaiju, though smaller. 30 feet tall, he’s a hydrokinetic powerful enough that he in a previous attack sunk Newfoundland. Yes, that Newfoundland. Kyushu as well. It took him a few hours, probably a lot less if he had actually been trying. At least supersonic underwater (He’s stated as moving so fast it looks like he’s teleporting), he’s extremely fast on land and when he moves creates water where he’s been. He can also create large amounts of water at will. He floods entire cities in minutes. Fast enough to run on water even though he weighs nine tons, though that might be an effect of his hydrokinesis. Additionally extremely agile. He at one point overpowered and held down a hero who held up over a million tons of steel by herself. Easily capable of breaking steel with physical strength. Also very intelligent, capable of exploiting weaknesses and using basic strategy, such as feigning injury to launch a surprise attack. After an upgrade he gained fins that severed molecular bonds, ignoring conventional durability. I’m pretty sure he could cut Godzilla to pieces after pinning him under a literal oceans worth of water. Could also use the water in Godzilla (if there is any) to rip him apart. SimurghSecond smallest of the Endbringers, at around 15 feet, the Simurgh is also the least conventionally dangerous, though by far the most dangerous in the long term. She’s an extremely powerful telekinetic, easily capable of lifting large buildings and flinging them several miles away and ripping people to shreds, though she typically doesn’t do the last one. She’s also the only telepath in the setting, as she uses her telekinesis to affect the brains of people around her. This includes people hearing constant screaming, hallucinations, or just reprogramming them to do her bidding. When she first appeared she reprogrammed an entire city into terrorists. Many people who fight her go insane. She also has near perfect precognition, seeing 80 years into the future and the past. It makes her literally perfect at manipulating events around her. During one attack she built a portal to another dimension and a few people came through. They tried to survive in this new, strange world, but two years later one of them turned into a giant monster and exposed a worldwide conspiracy. Just as planned. Another brilliant scientist turned into one of the world’s worst supervillains after an attack from Simurgh killed his family. If you’re fighting her, she’s been preparing for years. She knows everything you’re going to do before you were even born. She also coordinates the other Endbringers to deal the most damage in a single attack. It’s largely because of her that things are going to shit in the book. Also capable of space travel at at least orbital speed. Can assimilate technology and build enhanced versions of that tech using things around her. While fighting. If she’s fighting Godzilla, she has something prepared. Or she could just rip apart any vulnerable parts on him, including brains and internal organs, without breaching the skin. KhonsuKhonsu is one of the most dangerous Endbringers, as he doesn’t pick one target. He just keeps picking targets until he’s beaten. His main thing is teleporting on a global scale. Around 35 feet tall. Also the most durable of the Endbringers due to having powerful forcefields between all of his layers. Main offense is three city block-sized pillars of accelerated time that randomly appear, move, and disappear around him. He controls what gets in and out of the pillars, and if he doesn’t want it, it’s literally impossible to get in or out. People who get stuck in there starve to death in seconds. He hit a nuclear weapon stockpile in Russia, trapping them in the pillars, waiting for the casings to erode, and then lifting the effect the second they detonated. He can also use the pillars on himself to speed up his regeneration. If Godzilla gets trpped in one of the pillars, he stays there for as long as Khonsu wants him to stay there. If he doesn’t fit in them it would get very unpleasant, as Godzilla would likely, again, be ripped apart. The Twins, Tohu and Bohu Smallest and largest of the Endbringers respectively, Tohu is around 10 feet tall while Bohu ranges in size from 10 feet to 5 miles after absorbing material from the ground, though she’s still as durable even in small form. Bohu appears from the ground in the middle of her target city. She’s a small-scale reality warper, turning the entire city against the defenders, creating traps from the buildings and the streets. It’s unclear as to whether or not she can affect living things. She can also cover the streets in giant spikes. While she might not be able to kill Godzilla, she can definitely help Tohu against him. Tohu is the dangerous one of the two. While Bohu destroys the city, Tohu defends her. Tohu has three heads, and each head is that of a superhuman, granting her the powers of that super. She can do this with any super featured in the book. For example, she uses the head of one who is literally invincible, and one who shoots lasers. Used creatively, Godzilla doesn’t have a ghost of a chance against her. There are literally hundreds of ways she could do it, including trapping his head in a small time loop. All in all, any of the endbringers have this in the bag. While not all of them have the firepower to hurt Godzilla, Godzilla in turn has not a chance in hell of permanently hurting them. The only way any of them were killed was by a guy who blatantly ignores the laws of physics (Yes, I know Godzilla does this too, but that’s not the point). Edit: It has come to my attention that composite Godzilla is fucking insane, so several of these wouldn’t be able to beat him. Khonsu or Tohu with some OP combo of powers should still be able to do it though.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.quora.com/Is-Clifford-the-Big-Red-Dog-a-kaiju</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:06:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Expert: Build a Web App with Blazor</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Ask-the-Expert/Ask-the-Expert-Build-a-Web-App-with-Blazor</link>
      <description>Join Brian Clark and Cecil Phillip as they walkthrough building an app with Blazor and take your questions live.</description>
      <author> (by Melanie McKenna)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Ask-the-Expert/Ask-the-Expert-Build-a-Web-App-with-Blazor</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:06:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBAC like it was meant to be</title>
      <link>https://tailscale.com/blog/rbac-like-it-was-meant-to-be/</link>
      <description>Role-based access control was great. Let’s talk about what happened since then.</description>
      <author> (Tailscale)</author>
      <guid>https://tailscale.com/blog/rbac-like-it-was-meant-to-be/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Surface Studio 2 – The Ultimate Creative Studio – Microsoft Surface</title>
      <link>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/d/surface-studio-2/8sbjxm0m58t4?activetab=pivot%3Atechspecstab</link>
      <description>Create, paint and edit at light speed on the New Surface Studio 2. Unlock immersive experiences on the fully adjustable and versatile 28” touchscreen, now with Intel&amp;#174; Core™ i7 processors.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/d/surface-studio-2/8sbjxm0m58t4?activetab=pivot%3Atechspecstab</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 20:05:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://sponsor.ajay.app/</link>
      <description>SponsorBlock is a crowdsourced browser extension to skip sponsor segments in YouTube videos.</description>
      <author> (Created by Ajay Ramachandran)</author>
      <guid>https://sponsor.ajay.app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 19:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Semiconductor Heist Of The Century | Arm China Has Gone Completely Rogue, Operating As An Independent Company With Inhouse IP/R&amp;amp;D</title>
      <link>https://semianalysis.substack.com/p/the-semiconductor-heist-of-the-century</link>
      <description>Arm China has gone completely rogue, operating as an independent company with their own IP and R&amp;amp;D. This is the semiconductor heist of the century. There are many questions swirling about what this means for a potential Nvidia takeover or IPO, but it is clear that SoftBank’s short sighted profit driven behavior has caused a massive conundrum.</description>
      <author> (Dylan Patel)</author>
      <guid>https://semianalysis.substack.com/p/the-semiconductor-heist-of-the-century</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 19:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - hecrj/iced: A cross-platform GUI library for Rust, inspired by Elm</title>
      <link>https://github.com/hecrj/iced/</link>
      <description>A cross-platform GUI library for Rust, inspired by Elm - GitHub - hecrj/iced: A cross-platform GUI library for Rust, inspired by Elm</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/hecrj/iced/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 17:06:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core 6: Minimal APIs, two reasons why I can’t do without it so far</title>
      <link>https://anthonygiretti.com/2021/08/27/asp-net-core-6-minimal-apis-two-reasons-why-i-cant-do-without-it-so-far/</link>
      <description>Introduction A few days ago I introduced you to the minimal APIs, in this blog...</description>
      <author> (by anthonygiretti)</author>
      <guid>https://anthonygiretti.com/2021/08/27/asp-net-core-6-minimal-apis-two-reasons-why-i-cant-do-without-it-so-far/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 17:06:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falco - Vienna Calling (Official Video)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MTlSjRMx5Ic</link>
      <description>Check out the official music video for &amp;quot;Vienna Calling&amp;quot; by FalcoGet Falco&amp;#180;s biggest hits in one new Product:https://lnk.to/Falco60 Falco&amp;#180;s biggest hits in on...</description>
      <author> (FALCO
  
  
  
    FALCO
  




  
    
    
  
  Official Artist Channel





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MTlSjRMx5Ic</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 16:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How can I break down a shell item in the same way as the breadcrumb bar?</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210827-00/?p=105612</link>
      <description>Suppose you have a shell item in the form of an IShell&amp;#173;Item. How can you produce the folders that lead up to the shell item? One idea is to start from the item you have in your hand and keep trying to get its parent item,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210827-00/?p=105612</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 15:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Claims Responsibility for T-Mobile Attack - Says: </title>
      <link>https://www.vpnranks.com/blog/hacker-claims-responsibility-for-t-mobile-attack-says-their-security-is-awful/</link>
      <description>A hacker has claimed partial responsibility for T-Mobile data breach and he describes their security as </description>
      <author> (Minnie J. Hamilton Posts by Minnie J. Hamilton)</author>
      <guid>https://www.vpnranks.com/blog/hacker-claims-responsibility-for-t-mobile-attack-says-their-security-is-awful/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 14:06:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascading retires and the sulky applications</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/194626-C/cascading-retires-and-the-sulky-applications?Key=86fa9d75-d68c-4783-b7b9-5863657a4a4b</link>
      <description>I recently run into a bit of code that made me go: Stop! Don’t you dare going this way!The reason that I had such a reaction for the code in question is that...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/194626-C/cascading-retires-and-the-sulky-applications?Key=86fa9d75-d68c-4783-b7b9-5863657a4a4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 13:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to collect the code coverage of your tests in .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xwMWGYD8rgk</link>
      <description>Subscribe: http://bit.ly/ChapsasSubBecome a Patreon and get source code access: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsasHello everybody I&amp;#39;m Nick and in this video...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xwMWGYD8rgk</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 13:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 258</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DE0P6M8VkyA</link>
      <description>MyOnly Fans Account; Cookie Tracking, GDPR and Brexit; Thread Hijacking &amp;amp; Targeted Spam; Pwned Passwords &amp;amp; 1B Requests; Sponsored by 1Passwordhttps://www.tro...</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt
  
  
  
    Troy Hunt
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DE0P6M8VkyA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 11:06:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Tungsten Cube - Tristan Hume</title>
      <link>https://thume.ca/2019/03/03/my-tungsten-cube/</link>
      <description>A few months ago I bought a featureless cube of tungsten. It’s 1.5 inches across and cost $130, but I argue it was one of the best purchases I’ve made recently.</description>
      <author> (Tristan Hume)</author>
      <guid>https://thume.ca/2019/03/03/my-tungsten-cube/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 08:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 258</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-258/</link>
      <description>A really brief intro as this is my last key strokes before going properly off the grid for the next week (like really off the grid, middle of nowhere style). Lots of little things this week, hoping next week will be the big &amp;quot;hey, Pwned Passwords just passed 1 billion&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-258/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 08:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-08-27</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/08/app-developer-links-2021-08-27/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/08/app-developer-links-2021-08-27/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 07:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding support for $count segment in $filter collections in OData WebAPI</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/odata/adding-support-for-count-segment-in-filter-collections-in-odata-webapi/</link>
      <description>Introduction In OData core&amp;#160; v7.9.0 we added improved support for $count segment in $filter collection properties. $filter=navProp/$count($filter=prop gt 1) gt 2 $filter=collectionProp/$count($filter=prop gt 1) gt 2 Previously, versions of OData core had support for: $filter=navProp/$count gt 2 $filter=collectionProp/$count gt 2 We are constantly improving filtering capabilities in OData WebAPI.</description>
      <author> (Kennedy Kangethe Munga)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/odata/adding-support-for-count-segment-in-filter-collections-in-odata-webapi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 06:06:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support for fetching nested paths in OData Web API</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/odata/support-for-fetching-nested-paths-in-odata-web-api/</link>
      <description>Background OData services use nested paths to access properties or entities related to a resource. For example, if you want to access orders of a given customer, you would use a request path like: http://localhost:8080/Customers/1/Orders Microsoft.AspNetCore.OData 7.x provides two main approaches for handling such requests: convention and attribute routing.</description>
      <author> (Cl&amp;#233;ment Habinshuti)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/odata/support-for-fetching-nested-paths-in-odata-web-api/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 06:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Three Pillars of WebAssembly - The New Stack</title>
      <link>https://thenewstack.io/the-three-pillars-of-webassembly/</link>
      <description>Contributor Connor Hicks describes three benefits of WebAssembly — security, portability and performance — and why they make WASM powerful.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thenewstack.io/the-three-pillars-of-webassembly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 06:05:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: Building an Online Ticket Store with Blazor WebAssembly | The .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2021/08/26/webinar-building-an-online-ticket-store-with-blazor-webassembly/</link>
      <description>Join us Tuesday, September 28, 2021, 16:00 - 17:00 CEST (10:00 AM - 11:00 AM EDT or check other timezones) for our free live webinar, Building an Online Ticket Store with Blazor WebAssembly, with Stev</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2021/08/26/webinar-building-an-online-ticket-store-with-blazor-webassembly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 06:05:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s Learn .NET: Razor Pages - Events</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learntv/lets-learn-dotnet-razor-pages-aug-2021/?WT.mc_id=dotnet-36709-jasingl</link>
      <description>August 27th, 2021 | 8:30 AM – 10:30 AM PDT</description>
      <author> (t-claricedu)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learntv/lets-learn-dotnet-razor-pages-aug-2021/?WT.mc_id=dotnet-36709-jasingl</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 06:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to the Node.js reference architecture, Part 5: Building good containers | Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2021/08/26/introduction-nodejs-reference-architecture-part-5-building-good-containers</link>
      <description>Explore the Node.js reference architecture&amp;#39;s best practices for building good containers and ensuring faster development cycles and better deployments.</description>
      <author> (Michael Dawson)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2021/08/26/introduction-nodejs-reference-architecture-part-5-building-good-containers</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 06:05:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosing memory leaks in .NET apps</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Diagnosing-memory-leaks-in-NET-apps</link>
      <description>In this episode, Software Engineer, Mike Rousos, joins Rich to show can we can use tools like dotnet-dump and Visual Studio to diagnose memory leaks in our .NET applications, even if they&amp;#39;re running o</description>
      <author> (by Cecil Phillip, Matthew Leib)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Diagnosing-memory-leaks-in-NET-apps</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 06:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s New in .NET 6 for Blazor?</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-dotnet-6-blazor</link>
      <description>.NET 6 is coming with some notable Blazor improvements. Dynamic components, hot reload, Blazor MAUI apps—the list goes on and on. Here are the main highlights.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-dotnet-6-blazor</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 06:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing TypeScript 4.4</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-4-4/</link>
      <description>Today we’re excited to announce the availability of TypeScript 4.4! If you haven’t heard of TypeScript yet, it’s a language that builds on JavaScript by adding syntax for&amp;#160;static types. Tools like the TypeScript compiler just erase those types, leaving you with clean readable JavaScript that you can run anywhere;</description>
      <author> (Daniel Rosenwasser)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-4-4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 06:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - faissaloo/SponSkrub: Strip advertisements from downloaded YouTube videos</title>
      <link>https://github.com/faissaloo/SponSkrub</link>
      <description>Strip advertisements from downloaded YouTube videos - GitHub - faissaloo/SponSkrub: Strip advertisements from downloaded YouTube videos</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/faissaloo/SponSkrub</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 04:55:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny detail in Queensland premier’s selfie tweet sparks stinging rebuke</title>
      <link>https://7news.com.au/news/qld/twitter-user-highlights-small-detail-in-queensland-premiers-selfie-post-c-3787493</link>
      <description>Annastacia Palaszczuk’s critics are taking aim as she comes under pressure over her increasingly tough border stance.</description>
      <author> (Digital StaffPublished: 25/08/2021Updated: Thursday, 26 August 2021 4:20 PM AEST)</author>
      <guid>https://7news.com.au/news/qld/twitter-user-highlights-small-detail-in-queensland-premiers-selfie-post-c-3787493</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 03:06:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work hard</title>
      <link>https://terrytao.wordpress.com/career-advice/work-hard/</link>
      <description>Every mathematician worthy of the name has experienced … the state of lucid exaltation in which one thought succeeds another as if miraculously… this feeling may last for hours at a tim…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://terrytao.wordpress.com/career-advice/work-hard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 01:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailwind in 100 Seconds</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mr15Xzb1Ook</link>
      <description>Tailwind is a utility-first CSS framework for building websites. It takes a functional approach to web design by providing thousands of tiny classes to use d...</description>
      <author> (Fireship
  
  
  
    Fireship
  




  
    
    
  
  Verified





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mr15Xzb1Ook</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:36:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - yt-dlp/yt-dlp: A youtube-dl fork with additional features and fixes</title>
      <link>https://github.com/yt-dlp/yt-dlp</link>
      <description>A youtube-dl fork with additional features and fixes - GitHub - yt-dlp/yt-dlp: A youtube-dl fork with additional features and fixes</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/yt-dlp/yt-dlp</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:07:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three major networks devoted a full five minutes to Afghanistan in 2020 – Responsible Statecraft</title>
      <link>https://responsiblestatecraft.org/2021/08/20/three-major-networks-devoted-a-full-five-minutes-to-afghanistan-in-2020/</link>
      <description>It should be no surprise then, that Americans are shocked at the images of violence and the grim political situation on the ground today.</description>
      <author> (Written by 
Jim Lobe 







 Share	


 Copy	

 Print)</author>
      <guid>https://responsiblestatecraft.org/2021/08/20/three-major-networks-devoted-a-full-five-minutes-to-afghanistan-in-2020/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 23:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I switched from macOS to Linux after 15 years of Apple</title>
      <link>https://markosaric.com/linux/</link>
      <description>After using Macs for fifteen years, I switched to Linux as my main operating system and I’m enjoying it. Here’s an introduction to Linux that may help you too.</description>
      <author> (By Marko Saric)</author>
      <guid>https://markosaric.com/linux/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 23:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>