<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>AutoRegex</title>
      <link>https://autoregex.xyz/</link>
      <description>Converting plain english to RegEx with Natural Language Processing</description>
      <author> (Aarya Gadekar)</author>
      <guid>https://autoregex.xyz/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 05:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Incident at Our Email Vendor</title>
      <link>https://unstoppabledomains.com/blog/security-incident-at-our-email-vendor</link>
      <description>Recently, an employee of our email vendor, Customer.io, used their access to Customer.io systems to download and share a set of email addresses with an unauthorized third party. Late last night, Customer.io informed us that the data extracted included email addresses that our users and subscribers provided to Unstoppable Domains. Our own systems weren’t impacted as part of this incident, which we understand affected six companies.&amp;#160;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://unstoppabledomains.com/blog/security-incident-at-our-email-vendor</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 02:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a REST API | Developer Roadmap .NET 6 Rest API | Pt. 7</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/_wO-rH-Y9ck</link>
      <description>In this series of .NET Book Study, we will be discussing and building a REST API using .NET 6.Join us in this conversation and live-coding session! Let&amp;#39;s hav...</description>
      <author> (IBM Technology
  
  
  
    IBM Technology
  




  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/_wO-rH-Y9ck</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 01:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUI Developer Day in GCR, Sat, Jul 9, 2022, 9:00 AM   | Meetup</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/microsoft-reactor-shanghai/events/286865797/</link>
      <description>Sat, Jul 9, 9:00 AM  CST: 作為一個支援在單一函式庫中開發能夠運行在 Android、iOS、macOS 和 Windows 等跨平台應用程式的跨平台框架，.NET MAUI （跨平台應用程式用戶端介面）還在預覽版時就已備受關注。

千呼萬喚始出來。終於，在今年的 Microsoft Build 2022 上，.NET MAUI 正式發布。

對於 .NET MAUI，</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/microsoft-reactor-shanghai/events/286865797/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 01:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - DamianEdwards/TrimmedTodo: An app to try out trimming stuff in .NET 7</title>
      <link>https://github.com/DamianEdwards/TrimmedTodo</link>
      <description>An app to try out trimming stuff in .NET 7. Contribute to DamianEdwards/TrimmedTodo development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (DamianEdwards)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/DamianEdwards/TrimmedTodo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 01:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdSec - The open-source &amp;amp; collaborative security IPS</title>
      <link>https://www.crowdsec.net/</link>
      <description>CrowdSec is an open-source and collaborative security stack leveraging the crowd power. Analyze behaviors, respond to attacks &amp;amp; share signals across the community. Join the community and le&amp;#39;s make the Internet safer, together.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.crowdsec.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker News Status</title>
      <link>https://hacker-news.statuspal.io/</link>
      <description>Hacker News&amp;#39;s status page provides information on the current status and incident history of Hacker News.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hacker-news.statuspal.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmologist Gift</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2643/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2643/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As VS Code Hits v1.69, Microsoft Announces VS Code Server -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/07/08/vs-code-updates.aspx</link>
      <description>This week, along with announcing the regular monthly update to Visual Studio Code (now at v1.69), Microsoft added a surprise: a private preview of VS Code Server, serving up the backend functionality that allows the editor to be run remotely or in a browser.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel07/08/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/07/08/vs-code-updates.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 23:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roundup of .NET MAUI Videos - Week of June 20, 2022</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/davidortinau/roundup-of-net-maui-videos-week-of-june-20-2022-4okj</link>
      <description>Another week, and round of new content for .NET MAUI learners! This week I also found content in...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/davidortinau/roundup-of-net-maui-videos-week-of-june-20-2022-4okj</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 22:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad UI is causing people to get scammed | Ashlan&amp;#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://ashlan.com/blog/bad-ui-is-causing-people-to-get-scammed/</link>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;#39;ve asked anybody who&amp;#39;s tried to sell anything on Facebook Marketplace, Offerup or Craigslist, I can guarantee you that every one of them have encountered somebody trying to scam them. I&amp;#39;ve encountered quite a few but I&amp;#39;ll explain how this particular scam works and how bad UI contributes to scammers being successful.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I recently posted a laptop for sale on Facebook Marketplace and immediately got a somebody interested. I know it&amp;#39;s a scam right away because of the language they use. They never say they&amp;#39;re interested in the Macbook or laptop or computer. They always say things like what&amp;#39;s the present condition of the item, what&amp;#39;s the final asking price, and i will pay you to ship it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer1.png style=width: 50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer2.png style=width: 50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer3.png style=width: 50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer4.png style=width: 50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer5.png style=width: 50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer6.png style=width: 50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer7.png style=width: 50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Usually I will blow them off but when I&amp;#39;m bored I&amp;#39;ll continue the conversation. The usual scam I&amp;#39;ve encountered involves Zelle (I&amp;#39;ll blog about this in another article) but this one in particular involves Venmo. After a few back and forwards, he agrees to send the full amount with a shipping fee via Venmo if I send it next day USPS. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer-email1.png width=50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer-email2.png width=50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He sends the payment and asks me to check my email. I receive as an email from Venmo. This is where bad UI design is causing people to get scammed. The email appears to be legit with the Venmo colors and wording. If you aren&amp;#39;t tech savvy, you will only see it coming from Venmo. You have to click and expand it to show the email address is onlinevenmoforwarderserver@gmail.com. Gmail by default hides the sender email address (but conveniently shows the recipient email address??). I&amp;#39;m sure many people mostly use their phones to email and don&amp;#39;t know how to expand to display the full email address. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=/blog/images/scammer-email3.png width=50% border=1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If I was an unsuspecting victim and followed through with the email, I may have sent my laptop to this person thinking Venmo will fund my account once I produced a tracking number. Once I realized my account isn&amp;#39;t funded, I would probably contact Venmo who will tell me that they never sent any email to me. Then I would become another statistic.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This Gmail feature is one example of what I consider bad UI (either via discovery problems or plain bad UI). When the iPhone first came out, it was very user friendly and non-techies in my friend had no problem using it. As iOS added more and more features, all these came more hidden or had to find. Try explaining to your grandma how to unlock the orientation lock on their iPhone over the phone. Was it swipe down on upper right corner of the screen or upper left corner? Maybe swipe up from the bottom? Wait, which version of the iPhone is it?.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ashlan.com/blog/bad-ui-is-causing-people-to-get-scammed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 22:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i trained StyleGAN3 with 10000 Bored Apes</title>
      <link>https://johnnys.news/2022/07/I-trained-StyleGAN3-on-10000-Bored-Apes/</link>
      <description>I started “collecting” NFTs (not the real token but the JPGs) a while ago when i released OpenSee. One fun project i thought about was to play around with the pictures and see if i could train GAN (Ge</description>
      <author> (johnnys.news)</author>
      <guid>https://johnnys.news/2022/07/I-trained-StyleGAN3-on-10000-Bored-Apes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 22:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIST-PQC Choices Out</title>
      <link>https://mark-schultz.github.io/nist-standard-out/</link>
      <description>Today, NIST put out its preliminary choice of PQC algorithms to standardize.
I wrote an introduction to lattice-based KEMs (for non-cryptographers) this last weekend in preparation for the report, where one implements an (aggressively unoptimized) variant of FrodoKEM.
FrodoKEM ended up not being standardized, but the “broad picture” of the construction should still be useful to understand Kyber.

</description>
      <author> (Mark Schultz)</author>
      <guid>https://mark-schultz.github.io/nist-standard-out/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 22:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is auth WAY too hard in .NET? : r/dotnet</title>
      <link>https://teddit.pussthecat.org/r/dotnet/comments/vttrib/is_auth_way_too_hard_in_net/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m either going to get one or two upvotes here or I&amp;#39;m going to be downvoted into oblivion but I have to know if it&amp;#39;s a </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://teddit.pussthecat.org/r/dotnet/comments/vttrib/is_auth_way_too_hard_in_net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 20:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - facundoolano/software-papers: &amp;#128218; A curated list of papers for Software Engineers</title>
      <link>https://github.com/facundoolano/software-papers/</link>
      <description>&amp;#128218; A curated list of papers for Software Engineers. Contribute to facundoolano/software-papers development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (facundoolano)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/facundoolano/software-papers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 20:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low Code Ceremony Sagas with Jasper &amp;amp; Marten</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2022/07/08/low-code-ceremony-sagas-with-jasper-marten/</link>
      <description>You’ll need at least Jasper v2.0.0-alpha-4 if you want to recreate the saga support in this post. All the sample code for this post is in an executable sample on GitHub. Jasper does support s…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2022/07/08/low-code-ceremony-sagas-with-jasper-marten/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIST’s pleasant post-quantum surprise</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/nist-post-quantum-surprise/</link>
      <description>On Tuesday, the US National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) announced which post-quantum cryptography they will standardize. We were already drafting this post with an educated guess on the choice NIST would make.</description>
      <author> (Bas Westerbaan)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/nist-post-quantum-surprise/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 18:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>