<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>TL;DR Rust</title>
      <link>https://christine.website/blog/TLDR-rust-2020-09-19</link>
      <description>TL;DR Rust - Christine Dodrill's Blog</description>
      <author> (Christine Dodrill)</author>
      <guid>https://christine.website/blog/TLDR-rust-2020-09-19</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 08:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuckDB - An embeddable SQL OLAP database management system</title>
      <link>https://duckdb.org/</link>
      <description>DuckDB is an embeddable SQL OLAP database management system. Simple, feature-rich, fast &amp; open source.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://duckdb.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 07:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mozilla/rr</title>
      <link>https://github.com/mozilla/rr/wiki/Zen</link>
      <description>Record and Replay Framework. Contribute to mozilla/rr development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (mozilla)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/mozilla/rr/wiki/Zen</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 01:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Server Vulnerability Requires Immediate Attention</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/blog/2020/09/18/windows-server-vulnerability-requires-immediate-attention</link>
      <description>This afternoon, CISA issued Emergency Directive 20-04 (https://cyber.dhs.gov/ed/20-04/), which instructs the Federal Civilian Executive Branch agencies to apply August 2020 security update (CVE-2020-1472) for Microsoft’s Windows Servers to all domain controllers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cisa.gov/blog/2020/09/18/windows-server-vulnerability-requires-immediate-attention</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 01:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pin_ptr (C++/CLI)</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/cpp/extensions/pin-ptr-cpp-cli?view=vs-2019</link>
      <description>Declares a pinning pointer, which is used only with the common language runtime.</description>
      <author> (corob-msft)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/cpp/extensions/pin-ptr-cpp-cli?view=vs-2019</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 01:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most people are happy to share their work! #learnontiktok #tiktokpartner #research #edutok</title>
      <link>https://www.tiktok.com/@dr.noc/video/6874291013205249285?_d=secCgsIARCbDRgBIAIoARI%2BCjwUGi71%2By7GC0MAZWDg18OulmkaJtQMsmWVt2LuaMVRUjlYKUDj25w7eGfFCf6%2FWjI%2BpVTYe7Fary8JF5YaAA%3D%3D&amp;language=en&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;sec_user_id=MS4wLjABAAAAlPRSgspKevK7loTWLF-0PWIRbFTEZ82tI9MTZBP-OsHRGCegTYx-nUioRJQ81GZ4&amp;share_app_name=musically&amp;share_item_id=6874291013205249285&amp;share_link_id=3e8a6c08-f530-4239-949d-a85af63b2ba5&amp;timestamp=1600561034&amp;u_code=d8iiablcjf9582&amp;user_id=6745704899826353157</link>
      <description>Dr Noc, PhD 🧪 (@dr.noc) has created a short video on TikTok with music original sound. | Most people are happy to share their work! #learnontiktok #tiktokpartner #research #edutok | Tip: How to access a research article if it’s behind a paywall...  | Just send an email to the corresponding author saying that you are interested! | When you pay a subscription fee or article access fee for a Journal, zero of that money goes to the authors.</description>
      <author> (dr.nocDr Noc, PhD 🧪 · 5h ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiktok.com/@dr.noc/video/6874291013205249285?_d=secCgsIARCbDRgBIAIoARI%2BCjwUGi71%2By7GC0MAZWDg18OulmkaJtQMsmWVt2LuaMVRUjlYKUDj25w7eGfFCf6%2FWjI%2BpVTYe7Fary8JF5YaAA%3D%3D&amp;language=en&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;sec_user_id=MS4wLjABAAAAlPRSgspKevK7loTWLF-0PWIRbFTEZ82tI9MTZBP-OsHRGCegTYx-nUioRJQ81GZ4&amp;share_app_name=musically&amp;share_item_id=6874291013205249285&amp;share_link_id=3e8a6c08-f530-4239-949d-a85af63b2ba5&amp;timestamp=1600561034&amp;u_code=d8iiablcjf9582&amp;user_id=6745704899826353157</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 01:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1472: 'Zerologon' Vulnerability in Netlogon Could Allow Attackers to Hijack Windows Domain Controller</title>
      <link>https://www.tenable.com/blog/cve-2020-1472-zerologon-vulnerability-in-netlogon-could-allow-attackers-to-hijack-windows</link>
      <description>Security researchers reveal how the cryptographic authentication scheme in Netlogon can be exploited to take control of a Windows domain controller (DC).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tenable.com/blog/cve-2020-1472-zerologon-vulnerability-in-netlogon-could-allow-attackers-to-hijack-windows</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 23:12:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max Hodak - What is relativity, anyway?</title>
      <link>https://maxhodak.com/nonfiction/2020/09/18/relativity.html</link>
      <description>Relativity is one of my favorite topics in physics. Its origins were almost pure logic puzzle science, which in my opinion is one of the most fun and satisfying types of science. Most people have a vague sense of what relativity is – the speed of light is finite, and something about time travel? – but they don’t really know what it is, which is too bad because the principles are very simple, and the results are pretty awesome.</description>
      <author> (September 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://maxhodak.com/nonfiction/2020/09/18/relativity.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 23:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring my home network</title>
      <link>https://mrkaran.dev/posts/isp-monitoring/</link>
      <description>Setting up a home network monitoring stack built with Telegraf, Grafana and Raspberry Pi</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mrkaran.dev/posts/isp-monitoring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 23:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>👨‍🔧 Maker tech on the land</title>
      <link>https://tatham.blog/2020/08/22/maker-tech-on-the-land/</link>
      <description>I live in an inner-city apartment. There’s a concrete slab, brick walls, and no ceiling cavity access. Oh, and we rent, so drilling into things is frowned upon. The home automation potential in a s…</description>
      <author> (Tatham Oddie)</author>
      <guid>https://tatham.blog/2020/08/22/maker-tech-on-the-land/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 23:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Be Talent</title>
      <link>https://leo.fm/2020/09/talent/</link>
      <description>One of our hosts asked me for some talent coaching. This is how I responded.</description>
      <author> (Leo Laporte)</author>
      <guid>https://leo.fm/2020/09/talent/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 23:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Think About Your Marketing Career</title>
      <link>https://kracov.co/writing/how-to-think-about-your-marketing-career</link>
      <description>Framework for how to think about navigating your marketing career</description>
      <author> (By Alex Kracov)</author>
      <guid>https://kracov.co/writing/how-to-think-about-your-marketing-career</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 23:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My first 15,000 curl commits</title>
      <link>https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2020/09/18/my-first-15000-curl-commits/</link>
      <description>I’ve long maintained that persistence is one of the main qualities you need in order to succeed with your (software) project. In order to manage to ship a product that truly conquers the world. By continuously and never-ending keeping at it: polishing away flaws and adding good features. On and on and on.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2020/09/18/my-first-15000-curl-commits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 23:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brittney Braxton - Journaling as a Dev [w/ASL Interpreting]</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AzrEDnIye14</link>
      <description>Note: There are initial captions directly in the video until the interpreter begins.

Are you working with impact and purpose? Are you solidly attuned on what you're doing month-to-month with your role? How difficult is it for you to track your accomplishments at work? If any of these questions lead to uncertain answers, then you should learn what it means to journal professionally as a dev. This talk will cover my exploration into journaling and its application to tracking my goals and progress as a software engineer. I will discuss how to set up your journal for any goals and how to score on your performance review!
-----
Brittney is a software engineer who loves a good cup of tea. In her spare time, she draws illustrations for teaNotes.dev on Instagram. Brittney strives to connect with folks who geek out over code with hopes to contribute to a friendly and inviting tech community.


Brittney Braxton:
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/teanotes.dev/
Twitter:  https://twitter.com/mintiib</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AzrEDnIye14</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Precursor « bunnie's blog</title>
      <link>https://www.bunniestudios.com/blog/?p=5921</link>
      <description>Precursor (pre·​cur·​sor |  pri-ˈkər-sər):
1. one that precedes or gives rise to; a predecessor; harbinger
2. a pocketable open development board</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bunniestudios.com/blog/?p=5921</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RxUI Conf</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FjqZbkZYOzw</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (ReactiveUI)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FjqZbkZYOzw</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 21:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARS-CoV-2 positivity rates associated with circulating 25-hydroxyvitamin D levels</title>
      <link>https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0239252</link>
      <description>Until treatment and vaccine for coronavirus disease-2019 (COVID-19) becomes widely available, other methods of reducing infection rates should be explored. This study used a retrospective, observational analysis of deidentified tests performed at a national clinical laboratory to determine if circulating 25-hydroxyvitamin D (25(OH)D) levels are associated with severe acute respiratory disease coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) positivity rates. Over 190,000 patients from all 50 states with SARS-CoV-2 results performed mid-March through mid-June, 2020 and matching 25(OH)D results from the preceding 12 months were included. Residential zip code data was required to match with US Census data and perform analyses of race/ethnicity proportions and latitude. A total of 191,779 patients were included (median age, 54 years [interquartile range 40.4–64.7]; 68% female. The SARS-CoV-2 positivity rate was 9.3% (95% C.I. 9.2–9.5%) and the mean seasonally adjusted 25(OH)D was 31.7 (SD 11.7). The SARS-CoV-2 positivity rate was higher in the 39,190 patients with “deficient” 25(OH)D values (&lt;20 ng/mL) (12.5%, 95% C.I. 12.2–12.8%) than in the 27,870 patients with “adequate” values (30–34 ng/mL) (8.1%, 95% C.I. 7.8–8.4%) and the 12,321 patients with values ≥55 ng/mL (5.9%, 95% C.I. 5.5–6.4%). The association between 25(OH)D levels and SARS-CoV-2 positivity was best fitted by the weighted second-order polynomial regression, which indicated strong correlation in the total population (R2 = 0.96) and in analyses stratified by all studied demographic factors. The association between lower SARS-CoV-2 positivity rates and higher circulating 25(OH)D levels remained significant in a multivariable logistic model adjusting for all included demographic factors (adjusted odds ratio 0.984 per ng/mL increment, 95% C.I. 0.983–0.986; p&lt;0.001). SARS-CoV-2 positivity is strongly and inversely associated with circulating 25(OH)D levels, a relationship that persists across latitudes, races/ethnicities, both sexes, and age ranges. Our findings provide impetus to explore the role of vitamin D supplementation in reducing the risk for SARS-CoV-2 infection and COVID-19 disease.</description>
      <author> (Harvey W. Kaufman,)</author>
      <guid>https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0239252</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 21:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying ASP.NET Core applications to Kubernetes - Part 3 by @andrewlocknet - Abundant Code</title>
      <link>https://abundantcode.com/story/deploying-asp-net-core-applications-to-kubernetes-part-3-by-andrewlocknet/</link>
      <description>This is the third post in the series: Deploying ASP.NET Core applications to Kubernetes. Part 1 – An Introduction to Kubernetes Part 2 – Configuring resources with YAML manifests Part 3 – An introduction to deploying applications with Helm (this post) Related Content :Configuring resources with YAML manifests by @andrewlocknetDeploying ASP.NET Core applications to Kubernetes - Part 1 via @andrewlocknetDeploying SQL Server 2019 in Kubernetes...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://abundantcode.com/story/deploying-asp-net-core-applications-to-kubernetes-part-3-by-andrewlocknet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 20:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>watchOS 7 Removes Force Touch Support From Your Apple Watch, Here's Everything That's Changed</title>
      <link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/watchos-7-force-touch-gone/</link>
      <description>With the release of watchOS 7, Apple has added several new features to compatible Apple Watch models, such as new watch faces and sleep tracking, but...</description>
      <author> (Thursday September 17, 2020 2:20 PM PDT by Tim Hardwick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/watchos-7-force-touch-gone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 18:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASS Summit 2020 &gt; Register Now</title>
      <link>https://www.pass.org/summit/2020/Register-Now</link>
      <description>We are excited to offer our global community PASS Virtual Summit 2020. Over 200 hours of expert-led content, on-demand access and PASS networking opportunities for just $599 - $200 less than our standard non-attendee download price. Don’t miss the chance to connect and learn with a global community of data professionals just like you. Join us November 10-13!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pass.org/summit/2020/Register-Now</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 18:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Does Culturally Responsive Teaching Mean in an Online Environment? [w/ASL Interpreting]</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R9__M7a8wHM</link>
      <description>Culturally responsive teaching (CRT) is an instructional approach that seeks to ensure academic success while developing students' sense of culture and social-political awareness. CRT allows students to see themselves in the curriculum and assignments provided by the teacher. In the online and traditional classroom, CRT provides opportunities for students to learn how to value their culture. During this time in America, it is especially important for students to have opportunities to express themselves while using online technology.
---
Dr. Tressa Matthews
Clever Math LLC , Co-Founder
Dr. Tressa Matthews has been teaching math to middle and high school students for 18 years. She has a Bachelor's in Industrial and Operations Engineering from the University of Michigan. After two years in corporate America, she decided to pursue her passion for secondary mathematics. After earning a Masters and Doctorate in Education, Dr. Matthews co-founded Clever Math to provide online educational services for students and parents. She has a passion for building supportive classroom environments for African-American students which became the basis for her doctoral research.

Dr.  Jennifer Banks
Clever Math, LLC Co-Founder
Jennifer D. Banks, Ph.D. is currently the Mathematics and Science Coordinator for Washtenaw County. For nearly 20 years, Dr. Banks has served as a teacher and instructional leader at various levels. Jennifer is passionate about empowering educators and learners, to ensure that all students have equitable access and opportunities to learn and engage in high-quality rigorous mathematics. Over the past ten years, she has intently worked to expand K-12 educators' understanding of culturally responsive instruction, specifically in the area of mathematics. Dr. Banks holds a bachelors' Industrial and Operations Engineer and worked in the corporate sector for 4 years. She has been recognized by various community organizations for her work in expanding access to STEM education, including the Rhonda Walker Foundation and DAPCEP. She currently serves on the Michigan Early Mathematics Taskforce and is a lecturer for the University of Michigan. Furthermore, she is the Co-Founder of Clever Math, LLC.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R9__M7a8wHM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 16:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The .NET Stacks #17: EF Core 5, Blazor + CSS, and community!</title>
      <link>https://daveabrock.com/2020/09/19/dotnet-stacks-17</link>
      <description>EF Core 5 is done, Blazor CSS isolation, and more!</description>
      <author> (Dave Brock)</author>
      <guid>https://daveabrock.com/2020/09/19/dotnet-stacks-17</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 15:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Discussions - Isaac Abraham</title>
      <link>https://daveabrock.com/2020/09/19/dev-discussions-isaac-abraham</link>
      <description>In the latest interview, I talk with Isaac Abraham about his journey to F#.</description>
      <author> (Dave Brock)</author>
      <guid>https://daveabrock.com/2020/09/19/dev-discussions-isaac-abraham</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 15:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Index of /hovalaag/size</title>
      <link>http://silverspaceship.com/hovalaag/size/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://silverspaceship.com/hovalaag/size/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 14:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Internals - Learn by Building Your Own Git</title>
      <link>https://www.leshenko.net/p/ugit/</link>
      <description>Welcome aboard! We're going to implement Git in Python to learn more about how Git works on the inside.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.leshenko.net/p/ugit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 14:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Index of /hovalaag/speed</title>
      <link>http://silverspaceship.com/hovalaag/speed/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://silverspaceship.com/hovalaag/speed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 14:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poncelet's Porism - Numberphile</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n5bw-Y13pdY</link>
      <description>Featuring Daniel Litt.
Check out Brilliant (get 20% off their premium service): https://brilliant.org/numberphile (sponsor)
More links &amp; stuff in full description below ↓↓↓

Daniel Litt: https://www.daniellitt.com/

See Daniel previously on Numberphile: https://youtu.be/eYfpSAxGakI

Numberphile is supported by the Mathematical Sciences Research Institute (MSRI): http://bit.ly/MSRINumberphile

We are also supported by Science Sandbox, a Simons Foundation initiative dedicated to engaging everyone with the process of science. https://www.simonsfoundation.org/outreach/science-sandbox/

And support from Math For America - https://www.mathforamerica.org/

NUMBERPHILE
Website: http://www.numberphile.com/
Numberphile on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/numberphile
Numberphile tweets: https://twitter.com/numberphile
Subscribe: http://bit.ly/Numberphile_Sub

Video by Brady Haran and Pete McPartlan

Patreon: http://www.patreon.com/numberphile

Numberphile T-Shirts and Merch: https://teespring.com/stores/numberphile

Brady's videos subreddit: http://www.reddit.com/r/BradyHaran/

Brady's latest videos across all channels: http://www.bradyharanblog.com/

Sign up for (occasional) emails: http://eepurl.com/YdjL9</description>
      <author> (Numberphile)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n5bw-Y13pdY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 14:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Christopher Nolan Actually Blew Up A Real Plane For Tenet</title>
      <link>https://www.cinemablend.com/news/2546992/why-christopher-nolan-actually-blew-up-a-real-plane-for-tenet</link>
      <description>There's more to it than just being "dramatic."</description>
      <author> (Jason Ingolfsland









Published:
May. 27. 2020 10:04 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cinemablend.com/news/2546992/why-christopher-nolan-actually-blew-up-a-real-plane-for-tenet</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotnet-trace for .NET Core tracing in PerfView, SpeedScope, Chromium Event Trace Profiling, Flame graphs and more!</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/dotnettraceForNETCoreTracingInPerfViewSpeedScopeChromiumEventTraceProfilingFlameGraphsAndMore.aspx</link>
      <description>Speedscope.app is an online 'flamegraph visualizer' that you can also install offline. It's open source and on GitHub. ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/dotnettraceForNETCoreTracingInPerfViewSpeedScopeChromiumEventTraceProfilingFlameGraphsAndMore.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 09:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>