<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Toyota migrates mobile app to Uno Platform</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/toyota-migrates-mobile-app-to-uno-platform/</link>
      <description>Toyota&amp;#39;s strategic pivot from Xamarin Forms to Uno Platform, exploring the intricacies of migrating critical mobile applications within a global enterprise</description>
      <author> (Uno Platform Team)</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/toyota-migrates-mobile-app-to-uno-platform/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity extension for Visual Studio Code - Now Generally Available - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/unity-extension-for-visual-studio-code-now-generally-available/</link>
      <description>We are thrilled to announce the general availability of the Unity extension for Visual Studio Code. This extension, built upon the C# Dev Kit and C# extensions, gives you a comprehensive toolkit for your Unity development in Visual Studio Code across Windows, macOS, and Linux.</description>
      <author> (Jb Evain)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/unity-extension-for-visual-studio-code-now-generally-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Cosmos DB — Using EF Core with a NoSQL Database in a&amp;#160;.NET Web API</title>
      <link>https://henriquesd.medium.com/azure-cosmos-db-using-ef-core-with-a-nosql-database-in-a-net-web-api-fce11c5802bd</link>
      <description>Azure Cosmos DB is a globally distributed database service that offers high availability, global distribution, automatic scalability and…</description>
      <author> (https://henriquesd.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquesd.medium.com/azure-cosmos-db-using-ef-core-with-a-nosql-database-in-a-net-web-api-fce11c5802bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More options for apps distributed in the European Union - Latest News - Apple Developer</title>
      <link>https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=8c1m8hqt</link>
      <description>We’re providing more flexibility for developers who distribute apps in the European Union (EU), including introducing a new way to distribute apps directly from a developer’s website.More flexibilityDevelopers who’ve agreed to the Alternative Terms Addendum for Apps in the EU have new options for their apps in the EU:
Alternative app marketplaces. Marketplaces can choose to offer a catalog of apps solely from the developer of the marketplace.
Linking out to purchase. When directing users to complete a transaction for digital goods or services on an external webpage, developers can choose how to design promotions, discounts, and other deals. The Apple-provided design templates, which are optimized for key purchase and promotional use cases, are now optional. 
Distributing directly from your websiteWeb Distribution, available with a software update later this spring, will let authorized developers distribute their iOS apps to EU users directly from a website owned by the developer. Apple will provide authorized developers access to APIs that facilitate the distribution of their apps from the web, integrate with system functionality, back up and restore users’ apps, and more. For details, visit Getting ready for Web Distribution in&amp;#160;the&amp;#160;EU. </description>
      <author> (Apple Inc.)</author>
      <guid>https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=8c1m8hqt</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect Sizes and Asymmetry | Andrey Akinshin</title>
      <link>https://aakinshin.net/posts/asymmetry-es/</link>
      <description>Cohen&amp;amp;rsquo;s d is one of the most popular measures of the effect size. Unfortunately, it was designed for the normal distribution, which may make it a misleading measure in the non-normal case. And the real distributions are never normal. When we discuss d...</description>
      <author> (Andrey Akinshin)</author>
      <guid>https://aakinshin.net/posts/asymmetry-es/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How well does _com_ptr_t support class template argument deduction (CTAD)? - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240312-00/?p=109526</link>
      <description>Not very well, thanks to storing the pointer and IID pair in a helper type.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240312-00/?p=109526</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:03:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Down Tasks - Jacob Kaplan-Moss</title>
      <link>https://jacobian.org/2024/mar/11/breaking-down-tasks/</link>
      <description>Something missing from this series on estimation, until now, has been a discussion of how to “break down” a project into a well-defined task list. I’d not previously written about this because, to me, it’s largely intuitive. But it isn’t for everyone, so this post fills the gap, and explains in detail how I break down projects into a task list.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jacobian.org/2024/mar/11/breaking-down-tasks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - openai/transformer-debugger</title>
      <link>https://github.com/openai/transformer-debugger</link>
      <description>Contribute to openai/transformer-debugger development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (openai)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/openai/transformer-debugger</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 14:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloning a laptop over NVME TCP</title>
      <link>https://copyninja.in/blog/clone_laptop_nvmet.html</link>
      <description>Recently, I got a new laptop and had to set it up so I could start using it. But I wasn&amp;#39;t really in the mood to go through the same old steps which I had explained in this post earlier. I was complaining about this to my colleague, and there came the suggestion of why not copy the entire disk to the new laptop. Though it sounded like an interesting idea to me, I had my doubts, so here is what I told him in return.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://copyninja.in/blog/clone_laptop_nvmet.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 14:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Tips to Clean Exception Handling</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XtUftqJK8mE</link>
      <description>Tidy your exception handling code with 3 quick clean code tips.&amp;#128142; Be a Patreon to get the source code: https://patreon.com/gsferreira&amp;#127891; Join the Course waiti...</description>
      <author> (Gui Ferreira
  
  
  
    Gui Ferreira
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XtUftqJK8mE</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 13:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plugin Architecture in C# for Improved Software Design</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/12/plugin-architecture-in-c-for-improved-software-design/</link>
      <description>Learn about plugin architecture in C# to create extensible apps! This article provides examples with code snippets to explain how to start with C# plugins.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/12/plugin-architecture-in-c-for-improved-software-design/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 13:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trangram</title>
      <link>https://www.trangram.com/</link>
      <description>Trangram is a free one-stop platform to create, animate and share motion graphics.</description>
      <author> (HPythagorean Theorem Hilbert)</author>
      <guid>https://www.trangram.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 11:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MediatR: How to Quickly Test Your Handlers with Unit Tests</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/mediatr-quickly-test-handlers-with-unit-tests/</link>
      <description>Ensuring code quality and reliability is crucial in software development. MediatR, a popular library for the in-process request/response pattern, simplifies component communication but requires thorough testing. Unit testing with MediatR offers a swift way to validate development, and contrary to popular belief, it speeds up development by detecting bugs</description>
      <author> (Pierre Belin)</author>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/mediatr-quickly-test-handlers-with-unit-tests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mocking HttpClient requests for C# unit tests</title>
      <link>https://blog.elmah.io/mocking-httpclient-requests-for-csharp-unit-tests/</link>
      <description>Learn how to mock requests made through a HttpClient in C#. Unit testing code that makes external requests is easy using this simple approach.</description>
      <author> (Written by Thomas Ardal, March 12, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.elmah.io/mocking-httpclient-requests-for-csharp-unit-tests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 09:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Data Protection API Key Ring Debugger – Tore Nestenius</title>
      <link>https://nestenius.se/2024/03/12/introducing-the-data-protection-api-key-ring-debugger/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nestenius.se/2024/03/12/introducing-the-data-protection-api-key-ring-debugger/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 08:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kdenlive 24.02.0 released - Kdenlive</title>
      <link>https://kdenlive.org/en/2024/03/kdenlive-24-02-0-released/</link>
      <description>The team is thrilled to introduce the much-anticipated release of Kdenlive 24.02, featuring a substantial upgrade to our frameworks with the adoption of Qt6 and KDE Frameworks 6. This significant under-the-hood transformation establishes a robust foundation, shaping the trajectory of Kdenlive for the next decade. The benefits of this upgrade are particularly noteworthy for Linux users, as improved Wayland support enhances the overall experience. Additionally, users on Windows, MacOS, and Linux will experience a substantial performance boost since Kdenlive now runs natively on DirectX, Metal, and Vulkan respectively, replacing the previous abstraction layer reliance on OpenGL and Angle, resulting in a more efficient and responsive application. This upgrade brings significant changes to packaging, featuring the introduction of a dedicated package for Apple Silicon, the discontinuation of PPA support and an enhanced method for installing the Whisper and Vosk speech-to-text engines.</description>
      <author> (Farid Abdelnour)</author>
      <guid>https://kdenlive.org/en/2024/03/kdenlive-24-02-0-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 07:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resiliency and Low Level Improvements in Marten 7</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/03/10/resiliency-and-low-level-improvements-in-marten-7/</link>
      <description>Just continuing a loose series about recent improvements in the big Marten 7.0 release: Revisioned Documents in Marten&amp;#160;7 Marten 7 makes “Write Model” Projections&amp;#160;Super Recent Critter Stack Multi-Te…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/03/10/resiliency-and-low-level-improvements-in-marten-7/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to tackle compatibility issues in ECMA Script modules (and in general) - Event-Driven.io</title>
      <link>https://event-driven.io/en/how_to_tackle_esmodules_compatibility_issues/</link>
      <description>Event-Driven by Oskar Dudycz</description>
      <author> (Oskar Dudycz)</author>
      <guid>https://event-driven.io/en/how_to_tackle_esmodules_compatibility_issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 06:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building A Real-Time App with React, Node and WebSockets</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/building-real-time-app-react-node-websockets</link>
      <description>Learn to integrate WebSockets with React and Node.js by delving into the foundational elements of real-time web applications.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/building-real-time-app-react-node-websockets</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 06:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion models from scratch</title>
      <link>https://www.chenyang.co/diffusion.html</link>
      <description>This tutorial aims to give a gentle introduction to diffusion models, with a running example to illustrate how to build, train and sample from a simple diffusion model from scratch.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.chenyang.co/diffusion.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 06:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Automatically Cast Between Types in C#</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/11/how-to-automatically-cast-between-types-in-c/</link>
      <description>Learn how to automatically cast between types in C#! Leveraging implicit operators in C#, we can do away with explicit casts to convert between types.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/11/how-to-automatically-cast-between-types-in-c/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 06:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AspNetCore.Http.Abstractions is deprecated</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/03/aspnetcorehttpabstractions-is-deprecated.html</link>
      <description>While working on some class library code in C#, I noticed deprecation warnings in Visual Studio for the following NuGet packages:      NuGet...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/03/aspnetcorehttpabstractions-is-deprecated.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 06:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configure Azure connection strings and keys in Azure Bicep | johnnyreilly</title>
      <link>https://johnnyreilly.com/configure-azure-connection-strings-keys-in-azure-bicep</link>
      <description>Learn how to configure Azure resources like Azure Static Web Apps and Azure Container Apps with connection strings and access keys in Azure with Bicep.</description>
      <author> (https://johnnyreilly.com/about)</author>
      <guid>https://johnnyreilly.com/configure-azure-connection-strings-keys-in-azure-bicep</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 06:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundaries are explicit</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/03/11/boundaries-are-explicit/</link>
      <description>A reading of the first Don Box tenet, with some commentary.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/03/11/boundaries-are-explicit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Template Selector for XAML Applications for Windows and Uno Platform - Nick&amp;#39;s .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/conditional-template-selector/</link>
      <description>Ok this post took a bit of inspiration from the C# Markup support that’s available for the Uno Platform where it’s easy to build a template selector (for a ListView for example) using a set of Case statements. This got me thinking that there must be a way that we can use a similar technique ... Read more</description>
      <author> (Nick)</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/conditional-template-selector/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 04:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webb &amp;amp; Hubble confirm Universe’s expansion rate</title>
      <link>https://www.esa.int/Science_Exploration/Space_Science/Webb/Webb_Hubble_confirm_Universe_s_expansion_rate</link>
      <description>Webb measurements shed new light on a decade-long mystery.The rate at which the Universe is expanding, known as the Hubble constant, is one of the fundamental parameters for understanding the evolution and ultimate fate of the cosmos. However, a persistent difference, called the Hubble Tension, is seen between the value of the constant measured with a wide range of independent distance indicators and its value predicted from the afterglow of the Big Bang. The NASA/ESA/CSA James Webb Space Telescope has confirmed that the Hubble Space Telescope’s keen eye was right all along, erasing any lingering doubt about Hubble’s measurements.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.esa.int/Science_Exploration/Space_Science/Webb/Webb_Hubble_confirm_Universe_s_expansion_rate</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:03:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C and C++ Prioritize Performance over Correctness</title>
      <link>https://research.swtch.com/ub</link>
      <description>The original ANSI C standard, C89, introduced the concept of “undefined behavior,”
which was used both to describe the effect of outright bugs like
accessing memory in a freed object
and also to capture the fact that existing implementations differed about
handling certain aspects of the language,
including use of uninitialized values,
signed integer overflow, and null pointer handling.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://research.swtch.com/ub</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plonk&amp;#39;s permutation, the definitive explanation</title>
      <link>https://www.cryptologie.net/article/610/plonks-permutation/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve recorded a video on how the plonk permutation works here, but I thought I would write a more incremental explanation about it for those who want MOAR! If things don&amp;#39;t make sense in this explanation, I&amp;#39;m happy to dig into specifics in more detail, just ask in the comments! Don&amp;#39;t forget your companion eprint paper.
Multiset equality check
Suppose that you have two ordered sets) of values $D = { ...</description>
      <author> (david wong)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cryptologie.net/article/610/plonks-permutation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPP with Babel - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ipng.ch/s/articles/2024/03/06/vpp-babel-1.html</link>
      <description>IPng Networks GmbH provides networking consultancy, hosting, colocation, internet connectivity options primarily tailored for the Zurich metropolitan area.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ipng.ch/s/articles/2024/03/06/vpp-babel-1.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apps sold as single purchases are back, but with steep prices</title>
      <link>https://notes.ghed.in/posts/2024/apps-sold-as-single-purchaes-are-back/</link>
      <description>Remember when the App Store was a universe of genius and cheap apps? Then, circa 2015, came the subscription era. Now, I’ve noticed a kind of return to the o...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.ghed.in/posts/2024/apps-sold-as-single-purchaes-are-back/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Kafka&amp;#39;s Potential: Tackling Tail Latency with eBPF</title>
      <link>https://blog.allegro.tech/2024/03/kafka-performance-analysis.html</link>
      <description>At Allegro, we use Kafka as a backbone for asynchronous communication between microservices. With up to
300k messages published and 1M messages consumed every second, it is a key part of our infrastructure. A few months ago, in our main Kafka cluster, we noticed
the following discrepancy: while median response times for produce requests
were in single-digit milliseconds, the tail latency was much worse. Namely, the
p99 latency was up to 1 second, and the p999 latency was up to 3 seconds. This was unacceptable for a new project that we were about to start, so we
decided to look into this issue. In this blog post, we would like to describe our journey — how we used Kafka protocol sniffing and eBPF to identify and remove
the performance bottleneck.

</description>
      <author> (maciej.moscicki, piotr.rzysko)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.allegro.tech/2024/03/kafka-performance-analysis.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting Atlantis At Risk</title>
      <link>https://waynehale.wordpress.com/2024/03/10/putting-atlantis-at-risk/</link>
      <description>Warning: A long story that has a lot of technical details – and a moral. Reflecting on my career as a Space Shuttle Flight Director, there were many difficult decisions to make and sometimes …</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://waynehale.wordpress.com/2024/03/10/putting-atlantis-at-risk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Childhoods of exceptional people</title>
      <link>https://www.henrikkarlsson.xyz/p/childhoods</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s do more of those</description>
      <author> (Henrik Karlsson)</author>
      <guid>https://www.henrikkarlsson.xyz/p/childhoods</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much should you be charging as a consultant?</title>
      <link>https://www.partly.work/p/how-much-should-you-be-charging-as</link>
      <description>Around double your current rate as a full time employee.</description>
      <author> (Sanjay Saraf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.partly.work/p/how-much-should-you-be-charging-as</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debugging a Golang Bug with Non-Blocking Reads | Scratch Data</title>
      <link>https://scratchdata.com/blog/go-nonblocking-pipes-bug/</link>
      <description>We found a bug when doing non-blocking IO in Go. Here&amp;#39;s our workaround.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scratchdata.com/blog/go-nonblocking-pipes-bug/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Issue 51: Your Art or Your Life</title>
      <link>https://www.bramadams.dev/issue-51/</link>
      <description>Why a Personal Domain is your Domain</description>
      <author> (Bram Adams)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bramadams.dev/issue-51/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable and Secure VxLAN Multisite using NetBird - Part 1:Initial Config-L3VPN - Level Zero Networking</title>
      <link>https://lev-0.com/2024/03/11/scalable-and-secure-vxlan-multisite-using-netbird-part-1initial-config-l3vpn/</link>
      <description>In a previous article, we deployed DMVPN over NetBird to improve encrypted performance using WireGuard. You can find that post here:https://lev-0.com/2024/01/29/dmvpn-opennhrp-over-wireguard-netbird-on-vyos/ While that can be a great solution, the extensibility of that solution is limited. Functionality like L3VPN, L2VPN, Multitenancy, or Microsegementation are not possible. For that reason, the solution was really only good within […]</description>
      <author> (R C)</author>
      <guid>https://lev-0.com/2024/03/11/scalable-and-secure-vxlan-multisite-using-netbird-part-1initial-config-l3vpn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>smeso - Memory ordering and atomic operations synchronization</title>
      <link>https://smeso.it/2024/03/04/memory-ordering-and-atomic-operations-synchronization.html</link>
      <description>Every time I need to play with atomic variables and I try to be clever and optimize them as much as possible I need to re-learn what the various memory ordering options do. It doesn&amp;#39;t help that memory ordering is easily one of the most complex topics I ever worked with. For this reason I decided to finally write down what I (think) I know about memory ordering, making it easier for the future me …</description>
      <author> (smeso)</author>
      <guid>https://smeso.it/2024/03/04/memory-ordering-and-atomic-operations-synchronization.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning is Compression</title>
      <link>https://eitanporat.github.io/posts/learning-is-compression/</link>
      <description>In this blog post, we explore how compressing data is equivalent to learning data distributions. Not in the sense that neural networks are compressing data in their weights, but in an information theoretic sense. Following up on Shannon&amp;#39;s work, we use a GPT-2 model from Karpathy&amp;#39;s nanoGPT repo to create a compression algorithm which combines Shannon encoding with next-token prediction. Using this model, we get a compression algorithm which beats the native python implementation (18.9% vs 44.73%)</description>
      <author> (Eitan Porat)</author>
      <guid>https://eitanporat.github.io/posts/learning-is-compression/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The complete story of G&amp;#246;del (in)completeness. [290 views]</title>
      <link>https://billwadge.com/2024/03/11/the-complete-story-of-godel-incompleteness/</link>
      <description>The famous mathematician Kurt G&amp;#246;del proved two “incompleteness” theorems. This is their story. By the 1930s logicians, especially Tarski, had figured out the semantics of predicate logi…</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://billwadge.com/2024/03/11/the-complete-story-of-godel-incompleteness/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Frustration With Tech - Chris Wiegman</title>
      <link>https://chriswiegman.com/2024/01/my-frustration-with-tech/</link>
      <description>I’ve written about it before but I still say that, for all its faults, the best computing stack I ever had was when most of our data was in Google. Others have come close but that was, by far, the most convenient combination of features and access. I realize most people don’t mind using multiple […]</description>
      <author> (Chris Wiegman)</author>
      <guid>https://chriswiegman.com/2024/01/my-frustration-with-tech/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How async/await works in Lwan — L. Pereira&amp;#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://tia.mat.br/posts/2024/02/29/async-await-in-lwan.html</link>
      <description>How async/await works in Lwan 2024-02-29</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tia.mat.br/posts/2024/02/29/async-await-in-lwan.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Fearing Incidental Findings</title>
      <link>https://ostro.ws/post-healthcare</link>
      <description>We have two options for the next hundred years of healthcare: gather as much data as possible and make healthcare better, or – don’t – because we’re afraid that people will get scared and act unwisely when they see an incidental finding.</description>
      <author> (Robbie Ostrow)</author>
      <guid>https://ostro.ws/post-healthcare</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To Low Latency Programming: External Processing</title>
      <link>https://tech.davidgorski.ca/introduction-to-low-latency-programming-external-processing/</link>
      <description>This post originally appears as a chapter in my new book: ‘Introduction…</description>
      <author> (David Gorski)</author>
      <guid>https://tech.davidgorski.ca/introduction-to-low-latency-programming-external-processing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Words are Worse than Weights</title>
      <link>https://breckyunits.com/wordsAreWorseThanWeights.html</link>
      <description>January 12, 2024 — For decades I had a bet that worked in good times and bad: time you invest in word skills easily pays for itself via increased value you can provide to society. If the tide went out for me I&amp;#39;d pick up a book on a new programming language so that when the tide came back in I&amp;#39;d be b</description>
      <author> (January 12, 2024 —)</author>
      <guid>https://breckyunits.com/wordsAreWorseThanWeights.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure AD B2C: Call an External API Using Client Credentials in an User Journey</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/03/azure-ad-b2c-call-external-api-using.html</link>
      <description>.NET, .NET Core, ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/03/azure-ad-b2c-call-external-api-using.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding System.Diagnostics DiagnosticSource and DiagnosticListener (Part 1) - Steve Gordon - Code with Steve</title>
      <link>https://www.stevejgordon.co.uk/understanding-system-diagnostics-diagnosticsource-and-diagnosticlistener-part-1</link>
      <description>In this post, we focus on some of the core details of the DiagnosticSource and DiagnosticListener types, touching on the IObservable interface.</description>
      <author> (Steve Gordon)</author>
      <guid>https://www.stevejgordon.co.uk/understanding-system-diagnostics-diagnosticsource-and-diagnosticlistener-part-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:03:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Value Streaming?</title>
      <link>https://shiftmag.dev/benefits-of-value-stream-2833/</link>
      <description>Technical excellence is more satisfying for developers than delivering customer value? This is where value streaming comes into play.</description>
      <author> (Frane Bebic)</author>
      <guid>https://shiftmag.dev/benefits-of-value-stream-2833/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supergroup</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2905/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2905/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gh-116167: Allow disabling the GIL with `PYTHON_GIL=0` or `-X gil=0` by swtaarrs &amp;#183; Pull Request #116338 &amp;#183; python/cpython</title>
      <link>https://github.com/python/cpython/pull/116338</link>
      <description>In free-threaded builds, running with PYTHON_GIL=0 or -X gil=0 will now disable the GIL. #116322 and #116329 track follow-up work to re-enable the GIL when loading an incompatible extension, and to...</description>
      <author> (python)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/python/cpython/pull/116338</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSON Canvas</title>
      <link>https://jsoncanvas.org/</link>
      <description>An open file format for infinite canvas data.</description>
      <author> (JSON Canvas)</author>
      <guid>https://jsoncanvas.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>