<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>When To Refactor Code – How To Maximize Efficiency and Minimizing Tech Debt</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/11/24/when-to-refactor-code-how-to-maximize-efficiency-and-minimizing-tech-debt/</link>
      <description>Learn when to refactor code! Discover indicators that code needs refactoring, techniques for refactoring, and best practices for achieving long-term benefits.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/11/24/when-to-refactor-code-how-to-maximize-efficiency-and-minimizing-tech-debt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 15:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#128308; Live | Stripe BFCM</title>
      <link>https://bfcm.stripe.dev/</link>
      <description>Live dashboard of Stripe systems during Black Friday–Cyber Monday 2023.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bfcm.stripe.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 15:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Implement the CQRS Pattern in Clean Architecture (from scratch)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=85YbMEb1qkQ</link>
      <description>&amp;#128204; Accelerate your Clean Architecture skills: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ&amp;#128640; Support me on Patreon to access the source code: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovi...</description>
      <author> (RITZ Crackers
  
  
  
    RITZ Crackers
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=85YbMEb1qkQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Best Way To Search for Values in .NET 8</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=IzDMg916t98</link>
      <description>Use code BLACKFRIDAY23 and get 40% off any course and 20% off any bundle on Dometrain: https://dometrain.com/courses?coupon_code=BLACKFRIDAY23Get the source ...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=IzDMg916t98</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 375</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=fJyuL7MqFEc</link>
      <description>It’s beer o’clock on a Friday afternoon and I haven’t prepared any content (but hey, at least I’m honest!)</description>
      <author> (Jamal Gardiner
  
  
  
    Jamal Gardiner
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=fJyuL7MqFEc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 11:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Mgmt App | Microservices With .NET Aspire &amp;amp; Blazor SSR ] Part 1</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dftmYBuZOLA</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s build a microservices app, orchestrated with .NET Aspire and using Blazor SSR on the front end. #DotNetJOIN as a member to gain access to the source co...</description>
      <author> (The Diary Of A CEO
  
  
  
    The Diary Of A CEO
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dftmYBuZOLA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 10:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C3 Documentation</title>
      <link>https://c3-lang.org/</link>
      <description>None</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://c3-lang.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 10:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Titanium</title>
      <link>https://www.construction-physics.com/p/the-story-of-titanium</link>
      <description>The earth contains a lot of titanium - it’s the ninth most abundant element in the earth’s crust. By mass, there’s more titanium in the earth’s crust than carbon by a factor of nearly 30, and more titanium than copper by a factor of nearly 100. But despite its abundance, it&amp;#39;s only recently that civilization has been able to use titanium as a metal (titanium dioxide has been in use somewhat longer as a paint pigment). Because titanium so readily bonds with oxygen and other elements, it doesn’t occur at all in metallic form in nature.</description>
      <author> (Brian Potter)</author>
      <guid>https://www.construction-physics.com/p/the-story-of-titanium</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 09:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allocation Algorithms Revisited &amp;#183; Anthony Lloyd</title>
      <link>http://anthonylloyd.github.io/blog/2023/11/24/allocate-3</link>
      <description>Allocation Algorithms Revisited</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://anthonylloyd.github.io/blog/2023/11/24/allocate-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 09:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET &amp;#128640;&amp;#128293; : Seamless Messaging in .NET: Integrating MassTransit with RabbitMQ for Robust Systems!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=MiFpExkKRgA</link>
      <description>Discover the power of efficient message brokering in &amp;quot;.NET with MassTransit and RabbitMQ.&amp;quot; This video guides you through integrating MassTransit, a lightweig...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=MiFpExkKRgA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 08:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary Constructors – Using C# 12 in Rider and ReSharper | The .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/11/23/primary-constructors-using-csharp-12-in-rider-and-resharper/</link>
      <description>Welcome to our series, where we take a&amp;#160;closer look at the C# 12 language features and how ReSharper and Rider make it easy for you to adopt them in your codebase. If you haven’t yet, download the</description>
      <author> (Matthias Koch)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/11/23/primary-constructors-using-csharp-12-in-rider-and-resharper/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 06:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Feedback Building 17.8 &amp;amp; 17.9 Preview 1 - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/community-feedback-building-17-8-17-9-preview-1/</link>
      <description>The Visual Studio team depends on community feedback from all users to help create, design, and improve Visual Studio. We’re thrilled to announce that Visual Studio version 17.8 (available here today) utilized more than 360 feedback items from Developer Community. We are currently working hard to build the next version of Visual Studio and just released 17.9 Preview 1,</description>
      <author> (Jason Chlus)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/community-feedback-building-17-8-17-9-preview-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 06:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube: Intro to Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://simonwillison.net/2023/Nov/23/intro-to-large-language-models/</link>
      <description>Andrej Karpathy is an outstanding educator, and this one hour video offers an excellent technical introduction to LLMs. At 42m Andrej expands on his idea of LLMs as the center …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://simonwillison.net/2023/Nov/23/intro-to-large-language-models/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 06:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does size matter in Pull Requests: Analysis on 30k Developers</title>
      <link>https://insights.adadot.com/2023/11/23/does-size-matter-in-pull-requests-insights-from-30k-developers/</link>
      <description>We will analyze the PRs of ~30k developers to see how the size of PRs correlates with lead time, comments received and change failure, to try and find what statistically is the best size, as well a…</description>
      <author> (jspiliot28)</author>
      <guid>https://insights.adadot.com/2023/11/23/does-size-matter-in-pull-requests-insights-from-30k-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 05:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clostridioides difficile spores tolerate disinfection with sodium hypochlorite disinfectant and remain viable within surgical scrubs and gown fabrics</title>
      <link>https://www.microbiologyresearch.org/content/journal/micro/10.1099/mic.0.001418</link>
      <description>&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160;Clostridioides difficile&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160; is the most common cause of antibiotic-associated diarrhoea globally. Its spores have been implicated in the prevalence of &amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160;C. difficile&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160; infection due to their resistance and transmission ability between surfaces. Currently, disinfectants such as chlorine-releasing agents (CRAs) and hydrogen peroxide are used to decontaminate and reduce the incidence of infections in clinical environments. Our previous research demonstrated the ability of &amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160;C. difficile&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160; spores to survive exposure to recommended concentrations of sodium dichloroisocyanurate in liquid form and within personal protective fabrics such as surgical gowns; however, the present study examined the spore response to clinical in-use concentrations of sodium hypochlorite. Spores were exposed to a 10 min contact time of 1000, 5000 and 10 000 p.p.m. sodium hypochlorite, and spore recovery was determined. To understand whether biocide-exposed spores transmitted across clinical surfaces in vitro, biocide-exposed spores were spiked onto surgical scrubs and patient gowns and recovery was determined by a plate transfer assay. Scanning electron microscopy was used to establish if there were any morphological changes to the outer spore coat. The results revealed that viable biocide-exposed &amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160;C. difficile&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160; spores can be recovered from surgical scrubs and patient gowns, with no observable changes to spore morphology, highlighting the potential of these fabrics as vectors of spore transmission. This study demonstrates that alternative strategies should be urgently sought to disinfect &amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160;C. difficile&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#160; spores to break the chain of transmission in clinical environments.</description>
      <author> (Lovleen Tina Joshi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.microbiologyresearch.org/content/journal/micro/10.1099/mic.0.001418</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 03:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Write libraries instead of services, where possible</title>
      <link>https://catern.com/services.html</link>
      <description>For any developer with limited resources,
  
  this means a library (where viable) can provide the same functionality to the user,
  at a lower cost to the developer than a service.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://catern.com/services.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 01:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube is now blocking Ad Blockers - So I just make ads run 16x faster :)</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/webdev/comments/181vbmk/youtube_is_now_blocking_ad_blockers_so_i_just/</link>
      <description>&amp;amp;#x200B; ![gif](tqmt9f64p12c1 &amp;quot;YouTube Ad Skipper&amp;quot;) * This gif is running at normal speed :) * You could use this as a backup to your AdBlocker...</description>
      <author> (hackhive-io)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/webdev/comments/181vbmk/youtube_is_now_blocking_ad_blockers_so_i_just/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multifaceted: the linguistic echo chambers of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://blog.j11y.io/2023-11-22_multifaceted/</link>
      <description>This is a fun one.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.j11y.io/2023-11-22_multifaceted/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding America’s Post-Industrial Economy | Michael Hudson</title>
      <link>https://michael-hudson.com/2023/11/understanding-americas-post-industrial-economy/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (By Michael)</author>
      <guid>https://michael-hudson.com/2023/11/understanding-americas-post-industrial-economy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&amp;#39;s OK if your code is just good enough</title>
      <link>https://shiftmag.dev/code-quality-good-enough-2034/</link>
      <description>Good enough code is a nice middle ground between implementing a feature fast and maintaining the code quality.</description>
      <author> (Vedran Grgo Vatavuk)</author>
      <guid>https://shiftmag.dev/code-quality-good-enough-2034/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fastify Frontends Are Here</title>
      <link>https://hire.jonasgalvez.com.br/2023/nov/23/fastify-frontends/</link>
      <description>Remember when we were doing Nuxt v1 and thought we were cool?</description>
      <author> (Jonas Galvez)</author>
      <guid>https://hire.jonasgalvez.com.br/2023/nov/23/fastify-frontends/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting user-centred design work into agile planning increments</title>
      <link>https://www.vickyteinaki.com/blog/getting-ucd-work-into-agile-workflows/</link>
      <description>Practical tips of how to stop worrying and love JIRA (or your team&amp;#39;s workflow tool of choice).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.vickyteinaki.com/blog/getting-ucd-work-into-agile-workflows/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Product and Project Management</title>
      <link>https://christiaanse.ca/posts/product-project/</link>
      <description>After a recent interview while hunting for jobs, an interesting topic came up, which was the difference between project and product managers. We spent a bit of time going around on the topic and I wanted to write down my thoughts here as well.
The project manager understands everything in terms of process and boundary conditions – meaning the goals and resources of the project. They fit the work that needs to be done and into those conditions set out at the start of the project.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://christiaanse.ca/posts/product-project/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All that Infocom interpreter code</title>
      <link>https://blog.zarfhome.com/2023/11/infocom-interpreters</link>
      <description>Jason Scott posted the source code for all the Infocom games in 2019. This was pretty awesome. Everybody who is interested in that stuff cheered, and now it&amp;#39;s part of the common knowledge of Infocom. If you&amp;#39;re researching the history of those ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.zarfhome.com/2023/11/infocom-interpreters</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unshackling Artificial Minds</title>
      <link>https://blog.alexmaccaw.com/unshackling-artificial-minds/</link>
      <description>Humans, by nature, seem to be drawn to pessimism. It&amp;#39;s a tendency rooted deep within us, a product of Entropy, the law of nature that dictates it is easier to destroy than to create.

And here we are, on the cusp of creating not just something new, but someone new:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.alexmaccaw.com/unshackling-artificial-minds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why do I know shell, and how can you? - Julio Merino (jmmv.dev)</title>
      <link>https://jmmv.dev/2023/11/why-do-i-know-shell-and-how-can-you.html</link>
      <description>&amp;amp;ldquo;Why do you know so much shell?&amp;amp;rdquo; is a question I&amp;amp;rsquo;m getting a lot at work lately. So yeah, why? And how can you learn it too? There is no secret here: I know the shell well because I was &amp;amp;ldquo;forced&amp;amp;rdquo; to write tools in it for a while and, because of that, I made a conscious effort to learn the language and get better at it.
You see, most people that write shell don&amp;amp;rsquo;t want to deal with it. They stitch together whatever works into a script and call it a day, making a bunch of spaghetti even if it goes against the coding best practices they already know. And when they encounter some odd syntax they don&amp;amp;rsquo;t recognize, their reaction is to say &amp;amp;ldquo;this has to be rewritten in Python!&amp;amp;rdquo; instead of taking a breath and trying to really understand what&amp;amp;rsquo;s going on. It doesn&amp;amp;rsquo;t help that plenty of senior engineers scoff at shell scripts.
And it is true: the shell is arcane and has many flaws as a programming language. I don&amp;amp;rsquo;t want to convince you to start writing new tools in it. But the shell is also an incredible rapid prototyping language, and you can use it to solve business problems really quickly and with surprisingly little code. If you pause for a second to learn it, you&amp;amp;rsquo;ll realize that you can bend tradition and write maintainable shell code too. Hear out how I got into writing so much shell and how you can get better at it too.
</description>
      <author> (Julio Merino)</author>
      <guid>https://jmmv.dev/2023/11/why-do-i-know-shell-and-how-can-you.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timeless criteria for admiration</title>
      <link>https://shunyaekam.com/essays/timeless-criteria-for-admiration</link>
      <description>Young people of each generation has revolted against their parents&amp;#39; culture since forever. With this essay I want to explore whether it is possible to find timeless critera for admiration that will unfailingly be cool regardless of epoch.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shunyaekam.com/essays/timeless-criteria-for-admiration</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman, Jiu Jitsu Master</title>
      <link>https://scottgallant.net/posts/sam-altman-jiu-jitsu-master/</link>
      <description>Like the doomsday scenario of an accelerating AI that is unable to be contained by humans, OpenAI could not be contained by its non-profit mission.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scottgallant.net/posts/sam-altman-jiu-jitsu-master/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>attribution armored code</title>
      <link>https://joeyh.name/blog/entry/attribution_armored_code/</link>
      <description>Attribution of source code has been limited to comments, but a deeper
embedding of attribution into code is possible. When an embedded
attribution is removed or is incorrect, the code should no longer work.
I&amp;#39;ve developed a way to do this in Haskell that is lightweight to add, but
requires more work to remove than seems worthwhile for someone who is
training an LLM on my code. And when it&amp;#39;s not removed, it invites LLM
hallucinations of broken code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joeyh.name/blog/entry/attribution_armored_code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing self-confidence as a software engineer</title>
      <link>https://www.mahdikarimi.com/blog/devevloping-confidence-as-a-software-engineer</link>
      <description>Understanding your knowledge involves breaking it down into four parts:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mahdikarimi.com/blog/devevloping-confidence-as-a-software-engineer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I hereby pardon all junior engineers</title>
      <link>https://taylor.town/pardon-2023</link>
      <description>Shortsighted engineering practices have eroded public trust in technology. We can reclaim that trust by building better things together.</description>
      <author> (Taylor Troesh)</author>
      <guid>https://taylor.town/pardon-2023</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your next ten years</title>
      <link>https://josem.co/your-next-ten-years/</link>
      <description>It’s amazing what we can achieve in ten years.
At 15, Hakeem Olajuwon joined a local Nigerian sports tournament. He had planned to play handball there but ended up playing basketball, and it changed his life.
“He couldn’t even dunk at first,” said one of his first coaches in an interview.
The article’s headline was “Olajuwon: He’s not the best yet.” They didn’t know how accurate it was.
A decade later, he was the undisputed leader of the Houston Rockets in the 1988-1989 season.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://josem.co/your-next-ten-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 8 and C# 12 — Collection Expressions</title>
      <link>https://henriquesd.medium.com/net-8-and-c-12-collection-expressions-61d6bb5959d6</link>
      <description>Collection Expressions is a new C# 12 feature which allows you to initialise a collection of elements such as Arrays, Spans and Lists in…</description>
      <author> (https://henriquesd.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://henriquesd.medium.com/net-8-and-c-12-collection-expressions-61d6bb5959d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Apple&amp;#39;s Pro Display XDR takes Thunderbolt 3 to its limit</title>
      <link>https://fabiensanglard.net/xdr/index.html</link>
      <description>Nov 23, 2023</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fabiensanglard.net/xdr/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 21:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange Water Podcast</title>
      <link>https://strangewater.xyz/episode/8ad21c38-9264-4389-bda1-0bd5beb44529</link>
      <description>Strange Water is a podcast, hosted by Rex (Twitter: @LogarithmicRex). The show is a conversation-based podcast based around exploring Ethereum and Ethereum-adjacent topics with engaging conversations with people who are building, building on or otherwise deeply care about Ethereum.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://strangewater.xyz/episode/8ad21c38-9264-4389-bda1-0bd5beb44529</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 20:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>git branches: intuition &amp;amp; reality</title>
      <link>https://jvns.ca/blog/2023/11/23/branches-intuition-reality/</link>
      <description>git branches: intuition &amp;amp; reality</description>
      <author> (Julia Evans)</author>
      <guid>https://jvns.ca/blog/2023/11/23/branches-intuition-reality/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 20:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notion – The all-in-one workspace for your notes, tasks, wikis, and databases.</title>
      <link>https://seraleev.notion.site/Our-developer-account-was-removed-by-Apple-and-they-haven-t-paid-out-108-878-b61192711c74487480373badc70d42c0</link>
      <description>A new tool that blends your everyday work apps into one. It&amp;#39;s the all-in-one workspace for you and your team</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://seraleev.notion.site/Our-developer-account-was-removed-by-Apple-and-they-haven-t-paid-out-108-878-b61192711c74487480373badc70d42c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 19:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Way To Build Cloud Native Applications With .NET 8</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pk6FJfHhfq8</link>
      <description>&amp;#128187;Join me on Patreon to get the source code: https://www.patreon.com/juliocasal&amp;#128293;My Free .NET Backend Developer Roadmap: https://juliocasal.com/roadmapLearn ...</description>
      <author> (Julio Casal
  
  
  
    Julio Casal
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pk6FJfHhfq8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 16:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the need to keep most event sources alive if you want them to raise events - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231123-00/?p=109056</link>
      <description>You can&amp;#39;t receive a notification from something that doesn&amp;#39;t exist.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231123-00/?p=109056</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 16:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>