<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome’s next weapon in the War on Ad Blockers: Slower extension updates</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/google/2023/12/chromes-next-weapon-in-the-war-on-ad-blockers-slower-extension-updates/</link>
      <description>When ad blocking is a cat-and-mouse game, make the mouse slower.</description>
      <author> (Ron Amadeo
    -    12/1/2023, 3:30 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/google/2023/12/chromes-next-weapon-in-the-war-on-ad-blockers-slower-extension-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 17:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POV Candle - mitxela.com</title>
      <link>https://mitxela.com/projects/candle</link>
      <description>Tiny volumetric display</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mitxela.com/projects/candle</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 16:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Everything Is Google’s Fault (Just Many Things)</title>
      <link>https://blog.railway.app/p/gcp-incidents</link>
      <description>Over the last 18 months, we’ve had more than a handful of issues with Google. I was waiting to write about them until AFTER we got off Google, but, now seems like a good time as any.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.railway.app/p/gcp-incidents</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 16:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf 2023 - Comunidad de Desarrolladores .NET</title>
      <link>https://devscommunity.net/netconf2023virtual/</link>
      <description>Un evento en l&amp;#237;nea sobre .NET organizado por la Comunidad de Desarrolladores .NET del 4 al 7 de diciembre de 2023.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devscommunity.net/netconf2023virtual/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 16:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unit Testing VS Functional Testing – Dev Leader Weekly 20</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/12/02/unit-testing-vs-functional-testing-dev-leader-weekly-20/</link>
      <description>Welcome to another issue of Dev Leader Weekly! In this issue I&amp;#39;ll dive into comparing unit testing vs functional testing!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/12/02/unit-testing-vs-functional-testing-dev-leader-weekly-20/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 15:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You don&amp;#39;t need JavaScript for that - HTMHell</title>
      <link>https://www.htmhell.dev/adventcalendar/2023/2/</link>
      <description>A collection of bad practices in HTML, copied from real websites.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.htmhell.dev/adventcalendar/2023/2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 15:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 8 + MAUI + Blazor = &amp;#161;&amp;#201;PICO!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wZML7KscjRo</link>
      <description>Imaginate ser desarrollador y de pronto eres dios. Asi se siente usar Blazor y saber que solo con C# y .NET programas el mismo codigo y lo despliegas en web,...</description>
      <author> (Javier Su&amp;#225;rez
  
  
  
    Javier Su&amp;#225;rez
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wZML7KscjRo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 14:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Permission Authorization in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=7BzfIm6PtVg</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=7BzfIm6PtVg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 14:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Mgmt App | Microservices With .NET Aspire &amp;amp; Blazor SSR | Part 2</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=LWZaEjUPcVA</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s build a microservices app, orchestrated with .NET Aspire and using Blazor SSR on the front end. #dotnet JOIN as a member to gain access to the source c...</description>
      <author> (Codewrinkles &amp;#183; Playlist
  
  
  
    Codewrinkles &amp;#183; Playlist
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=LWZaEjUPcVA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 12:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trip to  NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=JkG5rTYF7p8</link>
      <description>Aimed to be the next level of cross-platform development, .NET MAUI is intended for devs who want to know more about mobile development. Before .NET Core, th...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=JkG5rTYF7p8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 12:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busy, Busy, Busy! – Behind The Screen – 2023 December, Week 1</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/12/02/busy-busy-busy-behind-the-screen-2023-december-week-1/</link>
      <description>Welcome to another Behind The Screen vlog. This week I recap on how I was unexpectedly busy with work and how that impacted everything else.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/12/02/busy-busy-busy-behind-the-screen-2023-december-week-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 12:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Are .NET APIs So Much Faster than Everything Else?</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=RNC422F-C4E%3Flist%3DRDCMUCrkPsvLGln62OMZRO6K-llg</link>
      <description>Use code REFAC20 and get 20% off the brand new &amp;quot;Refactoring for C# Developers&amp;quot; course on Dometrain: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactorin...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=RNC422F-C4E%3Flist%3DRDCMUCrkPsvLGln62OMZRO6K-llg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 07:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pitching a Tech Book to a Publisher</title>
      <link>https://newdevsguide.com/2023/12/02/pitching-tech-books/</link>
      <description>How to succeed when approaching a publisher about writing a programming book. Covers the proposal, scheduling, and contracts of book writing.</description>
      <author> (Matt Eland)</author>
      <guid>https://newdevsguide.com/2023/12/02/pitching-tech-books/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 07:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Constructors</title>
      <link>https://gieseanw.wordpress.com/2023/11/30/smart-constructors/</link>
      <description>(Photo by Michael Dziedzic on Unsplash) The validation problem At some point, every developer writing user-facing code has asked themselves the question “How should I validate input?”</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gieseanw.wordpress.com/2023/11/30/smart-constructors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebSummit 2023: Where are AI and Web3 heading&amp;#160;to? - Lejdi Prifti</title>
      <link>https://lejdiprifti.com/2023/11/20/websummit-2023-where-are-ai-and-web3-heading-to/</link>
      <description>Learn about this year&amp;#39;s WebSummit and what the biggest companies are predicting the future of AI and Web3 is heading to.</description>
      <author> (lejdiprifti)</author>
      <guid>https://lejdiprifti.com/2023/11/20/websummit-2023-where-are-ai-and-web3-heading-to/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote collaboration fuses fewer breakthrough ideas? Probably not.</title>
      <link>https://jrhawley.ca/2023/12/01/remote-work-disruption</link>
      <description>An interesting paper was published in Nature two days ago, titled &amp;#39;Remote collaboration fuses fewer breakthrough ideas&amp;#39;. I believe it should be retracted.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jrhawley.ca/2023/12/01/remote-work-disruption</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My first microservice solution - great mentorship, companionship and an unforgettably enjoyable development adventure</title>
      <link>https://blog.benjaminvr.net/2023/11/my-first-microservice-solution-great-mentorship-companionship-rabbitmq-dotnet.html</link>
      <description>Software developer from Belgium. Member of the nonprofit construct0 software development organisation.</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.benjaminvr.net/2023/11/my-first-microservice-solution-great-mentorship-companionship-rabbitmq-dotnet.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noiselith</title>
      <link>https://noiselith.com/</link>
      <description>The easiest local image generate tool</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://noiselith.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Error Handling in ASP.NET Core 8</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/global-error-handling-in-aspnetcore-8</link>
      <description>Exceptions are for exceptional situations. But they will inevitably happen in your applications, and you need to handle them. You can implement a global exception handling mechanism or handle only specific exceptions. ASP.NET Core gives you a few options on how to implement this. So which one should you choose? Today, I want to show you an old and new way to handle exceptions in ASP.NET Core 8.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/global-error-handling-in-aspnetcore-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The joys of self-hosting and tiny side-projects</title>
      <link>https://jarv.org/posts/joys-self-hosting/</link>
      <description>random thoughts and posts on tech</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jarv.org/posts/joys-self-hosting/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recognizing string prefixes with SIMD instructions</title>
      <link>https://lemire.me/blog/2023/07/14/recognizing-string-prefixes-with-simd-instructions/</link>
      <description>Suppose that I give you a long list of string tokens (e.g., “A”, “A6”, “AAAA”, “AFSDB”, “APL”, “CAA”, “CDS”, “CDNSKEY”, “CERT”, “CH”, “CNAME”, “CS”, “CSYNC”, “DHC”, etc.). I give you a pointer inside a much larger string and I ask you whether you are pointing at one of these tokens, and if so, which one. … Continue reading Recognizing string prefixes with SIMD instructions</description>
      <author> (Published by)</author>
      <guid>https://lemire.me/blog/2023/07/14/recognizing-string-prefixes-with-simd-instructions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rails Executor: increasingly everywhere</title>
      <link>https://island94.org/2023/11/rails-executor-increasingly-everywhere</link>
      <description>The Rails Executor rules everything around you your code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://island94.org/2023/11/rails-executor-increasingly-everywhere</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life as a Self-Employed Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://16x.engineer/2023/10/20/life-as-a-self-employed-software-engineer.html</link>
      <description>In this post, I will go into more depth on how exactly my business works, and what my daily life looks like.</description>
      <author> (Zhu Liang)</author>
      <guid>https://16x.engineer/2023/10/20/life-as-a-self-employed-software-engineer.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code</title>
      <link>https://andrewbadr.com/log/32/advent-of-code/</link>
      <description>Nov. 30, 2023</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewbadr.com/log/32/advent-of-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Decade of Developing a Programming Language: A Response Response</title>
      <link>https://gavinhoward.com/2023/12/a-decade-of-developing-a-programming-language-a-response-response/</link>
      <description>Two people wrote posts about developing programming languages for a decade. I did too, so I wrote one of my own.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gavinhoward.com/2023/12/a-decade-of-developing-a-programming-language-a-response-response/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>w/re Invent 23.md</title>
      <link>https://serprex.github.io/w/re%20Invent%2023</link>
      <description>Walking looking for dml  or whatever. Gotta get swag. Line up. Hate lines. Pretty quick line. Scans badge &amp;amp; asks size. M. Wasn’t sure whether to run for it, was handed water thermos. Ended up at Theater 1. Some bullshit about gathering everybody’s data I’m so out of here. Bunch of brands for products I’d never use. Snyk had a big booth glad we stopped using them. Eventually sit down in a sparse spot, woman asks to scan, I tell her I’m lost, gives me card, card says RAG so I ask what’s RAG she says retrieval augmented generation. I say oh. Some guy comes out &amp;amp; starts talking about RAG  &amp;amp; how every year he gets a flight here on Sunday after Thanksgiving &amp;amp; stays at same hotels &amp;amp; I’m thinking damn does that sound like a groundhogs day nightmare &amp;amp; he’s saying why can’t his airline give him a personalized package &amp;amp; then they get to the architecture diagram &amp;amp; have interesting data being chat logs &amp;amp; I’m thinking fuck if I want my chat logs deriving data. So I get up &amp;amp; leave while he’s talking about chat bots. So I start heading to area on ceiling saying DATA because that’s what we do &amp;amp; some guy says I look stressed handing me a stress ball, I reply “Yes I am”. We get talking about tinybird &amp;amp; he agrees AI is getting pretty overhyped &amp;amp; he’s talking snowflake tax but wasn’t clear on why people use snowflake, Got talking about his role being dev outreach &amp;amp; he wasn’t sure if they support geometry columns. Conversation dies &amp;amp; my phone alarm goes off for 1utc so I step away &amp;amp; see Sai called an hour ago, call him he asks what’s going on, I’m not sure, says he’s in a meeting talk in an hour. At some point I see coats being given out at CapitalOne booth, Large smallest available, get talking about CapitalOne open source after I say “I thought you were just a credit card” &amp;amp; they’re showing some Python data synthesis thing anyways they didn’t have much to say so I walked on. Figured I should see snowflake booth to umderstand it better but it was packed with some talk about dome bullshit I forget so walked over to Mongo where they seemed to have comfortable seats &amp;amp; got talking with a nice guy, taught him cosmos is a suite of databases which was news to him &amp;amp; we got talking about mongo documents before moving conversation to something more interesting like 3d graphics programming &amp;amp; how he’s on imdb for working on some French video game in the 90s. Eventually conversation died &amp;amp; he left but I stayed a few minutes longer for a breather. Sit down at Snowflake with even cushier seats where tv is playing some shit about zero data movement while having shots of blue matrix effect coming out of people’s phones so I walk around until a couple guys ask if I want to talk about Snowflake &amp;amp; we get into it I tell them I’ve started at peerdb &amp;amp; we do pg/snowflake cdc &amp;amp; I’d like to know what my job is because I don’t know so they explain snowflake is decoupled storage/compute compared to traditional sql having to pay for vcores which I can agree with how expensive Citus clusters were. Explains they haven’t released OLTP but it’ll be 55ms nothing webscale maybe good for B2B apps. They’re more for analytics. Get talking about AI &amp;amp; cloud I assert it’s a bad match because GPU on cloud seems lacking they disagree, companies are paying out the nose for GPU on cloud because it’s an arm’s race &amp;amp; you always need latest gen for better perf per watt &amp;amp; cloud data centers have the megawatts that you just can’t get on prem. Snowflake is elastic. Get talking about peerdb psql interface &amp;amp; they recall some gal sitting on 5tran ui tweaking a hundred mongo snowflake mirrors. I get snowflake socks joking you get to an age where socks for Christmas is exciting. I’m ready to leave so start funneling out. Sit down to check on wifi decide to play space invaders arcade game it’s awkward with one hand, guy starts telling me it’s running on kubernetes &amp;amp; I’m annoyed because I was in the middle of playing space invaders &amp;amp; now I’m talking to this guy about kubernetes &amp;amp; it takes me five minutes to find out AKS is amazon kubernetes not azure kubernetes &amp;amp; Spot isn’t a service it’s a new aks tier where you’re premptible but you get a 2 minute heads up when your aks is going to spin down so you can react. Leave &amp;amp; figure out wifi password is on badge which helps because I’m on a prepaid phone plan &amp;amp; still riding US minutes/texts I bought when interviewing with Citus so I could call Sumedh. Sai texts to meet at Grand Lux Caf&amp;#233; 630pm. There’s two Grand Lux Caf&amp;#233;s in Venetian hope we go to same one</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://serprex.github.io/w/re%20Invent%2023</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typical Seating Chart</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2862/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2862/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Annotation Updates in .NET 8</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SCDiuvK-GI8</link>
      <description>In .NET 8, we were given some new data annotation options for validating our properties. Let&amp;#39;s look at these new options and how to use them in this 10-minut...</description>
      <author> (IAmTimCorey
  
  
  
    IAmTimCorey
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SCDiuvK-GI8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Hybrid User Interfaces with Blazor Hybrid [Pt 4] | Blazor Hybrid for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pWDf1AnJ4ds</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s start to build out a full application with Blazor Hybrid inside of .NET MAUI. Join James as he walks through building out a full to do application with...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pWDf1AnJ4ds</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro EP 94&amp;#160;: How to perform simple background jobs in&amp;#160;.NET&amp;#160;?</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/net-tips/pro-ep-94-how-to-perform-simple-background-jobs-in-net-31ff0857deb5</link>
      <description>How to perform simple background jobs in&amp;#160;.NET&amp;#160;?</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@mwaseemzakir)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/net-tips/pro-ep-94-how-to-perform-simple-background-jobs-in-net-31ff0857deb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does it mean to prove?</title>
      <link>https://nmohnblatt.github.io/zk-jargon-decoder/intro_to_zk/what_is_proving.html</link>
      <description>This article aims to be a gentle introduction to the notions of decision problems, relations, languages and the  complexity class.
We follow a running example and rephrase it each time we cover a new term.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nmohnblatt.github.io/zk-jargon-decoder/intro_to_zk/what_is_proving.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 480 - Ignite 2023 Updates</title>
      <link>https://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-480-Ignite-2023-Updates</link>
      <description>Episode 248 - Updates from Ignite 2018A whole bunch of Azure updates were announced at Ignite so Cynthia, Cale and Sujit try to cover as m...Episode 303 - Azure Backup - Road to Ignite 2019Vijay Sistla, a&amp;#160;Principal PM in Azure Backup, gives us a sneak peak at some exciting announceme...Episode 287 - Cognitive Services UpdatesAnna Roth, a Senior PM in the Computer Vision team&amp;#160;and Anand Raman, Group PM of Cognitive Servi...</description>
      <author> (Sujit D&amp;#39;Mello)</author>
      <guid>https://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-480-Ignite-2023-Updates</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 23:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro EP 89&amp;#160;: How to create a custom reusable fluent validator in&amp;#160;.NET&amp;#160;?</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/net-tips/pro-ep-89-how-to-create-a-custom-reusable-fluent-validator-in-net-21bf9878b6ba</link>
      <description>Fluent Validation is a powerful library in the&amp;#160;.NET ecosystem for handling validation logic with a fluent and expressive syntax.</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@mwaseemzakir)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/net-tips/pro-ep-89-how-to-create-a-custom-reusable-fluent-validator-in-net-21bf9878b6ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-Means Data Clustering from Scratch Using C# -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/12/01/k-means-data-clustering.aspx</link>
      <description>K-means is comparatively simple and works well with large datasets, but it assumes clusters are circular/spherical in shape, so it can only find simple cluster geometries.</description>
      <author> (By James McCaffrey12/01/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/12/01/k-means-data-clustering.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why does the Windows Portable Executable (PE) format have both an import section and input directory? - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231201-17/?p=109090</link>
      <description>They seem to be the same thing. Do we need both?</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231201-17/?p=109090</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 20:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2023</title>
      <link>https://adventofcode.com/2023</link>
      <description>Our sponsors help make Advent of Code possible:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://adventofcode.com/2023</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 19:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seamless Communication - AI at Meta</title>
      <link>https://ai.meta.com/research/seamless-communication/</link>
      <description>A significant step towards removing language barriers through expressive, fast and high-quality AI translation</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ai.meta.com/research/seamless-communication/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 18:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Kernel’s Ignite release: Beta8 for the .NET SDK | Semantic Kernel</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/semantic-kernels-ignite-release-beta8-for-the-net-sdk/</link>
      <description>Yesterday’s and today’s &amp;#160;Ignite sessions have been jam packed with updates. From new AI infrastructure to the new Copilot Studio, Microsoft has had a lot to share! At the center of it all, however, is still AI Orchestration: the layer that uses AI to retrieve data,</description>
      <author> (Matthew Bolanos)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/semantic-kernels-ignite-release-beta8-for-the-net-sdk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 18:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>