<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>R1-Zero and R1 Results and Analysis</title>
      <link>https://arcprize.org/blog/r1-zero-r1-results-analysis</link>
      <description>An analysis of Deepseek&amp;#39;s R1</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://arcprize.org/blog/r1-zero-r1-results-analysis</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 22:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Seagate customers say their &amp;#39;new&amp;#39; hard drives were actually used – resold HDDs reportedly used for tens of thousands of hours</title>
      <link>https://www.tomshardware.com/pc-components/hdds/german-seagate-customers-say-their-new-hard-drives-were-actually-used-resold-hdds-reportedly-used-for-tens-of-thousands-of-hours</link>
      <description>The plot thickens.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tomshardware.com/pc-components/hdds/german-seagate-customers-say-their-new-hard-drives-were-actually-used-resold-hdds-reportedly-used-for-tens-of-thousands-of-hours</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lago Blog - Why DeepSeek had to be open-source (and why it won&amp;#39;t defeat OpenAI)</title>
      <link>https://www.getlago.com/blog/deepseek-open-source</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.getlago.com/blog/deepseek-open-source</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 18:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The hidden benefit of OSS</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=NCJdkZFWe4E</link>
      <description>In this edition of #tech on ice, I talk about one of the biggest benefits of Open Source, the innovation it forces.
#llm #DeepSeek #technology #developer #programming #coldplunge #oss</description>
      <author> (Isaac Levin)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=NCJdkZFWe4E</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 18:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CI/CD with GitHub Actions: Build &amp;amp; Push Docker Images to Docker Hub</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=zpX8emdGOPg</link>
      <description>Hi there! Today we are going to see how to build and push a Docker image to Docker Hub, as part of your CI/CD pipeline, using GitHub Workflows.

yaml file:

name: Build and push to Dockerhub

on:
  push:
    branches:
      - main
    
jobs:
  push:
    runs-on: ubuntu-latest
    
    steps:
      - name: Checkout
        uses: actions/checkout@v4
        
      - name: Login
        uses: docker/login-action@v3.3.0
        with:
          username: ${{ secrets.DOCKER_USERNAME }}
          password: ${{ secrets.DOCKER_PASSWORD }}
          
      - name: Build and push Docker image
        uses: docker/build-push-action@v6.13.0
        with:
          context: .
          file: ./Weather.Api/Dockerfile
          push: true
          tags: |
            repo-name:${{ github.sha }}
            repo-name/weather-api:latest

#GitHubActions #Docker</description>
      <author> (Spyros Katsios)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=zpX8emdGOPg</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 18:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP NET Core - Working With XML Results On Web APIs</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YCVB4bOoWOk</link>
      <description>JSON is the way of the web API! But... What about XML? Surely we no longer need to be concerned with that?

Well... There are still some use cases! Check out this video for returning XML data from web APIs in ASP NET Core.

----
&amp;#128273; Membership &amp;amp; Subscriptions:
- &amp;#128232; Weekly Newsletter: https://weekly.devleader.ca
- &amp;#127960;️ Private Discord Community: https://sidestack.io/devleader

&amp;#129504; Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Get Promoted As A Software Engineer: https://dometrain.com/course/career-getting-promoted-as-a-software-engineer/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Soft Skills For Software Engineers: https://dometrain.com/course/career-soft-skills-for-software-engineers/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?ref=nick-cosentino
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

&amp;#128483;️ Social Media &amp;amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs:  @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp;amp; Products/Services That I Love:
- @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper Opus Clip: https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----

#softwareengineering #softwaredeveloper #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YCVB4bOoWOk</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bacteria (and Their Metabolites) and Depression</title>
      <link>https://www.science.org/content/blog-post/bacteria-and-their-metabolites-and-depression</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.science.org/content/blog-post/bacteria-and-their-metabolites-and-depression</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Includes: The Art of Fetching Just Enough Data in EF Core - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/explicit-includes-the-art-of-fetching-just-enough-data-in-ef-core/</link>
      <description>If you’ve ever gone grocery shopping while hungry, you know how easy it is to end up with more than you need. The same thing happens in EF Core when you’re too eager with your Include statements—you fetch all the data, even the stuff you don’t need, and suddenly, your app feels sluggish. That’s where Explicit Includes comes in, allowing you to fetch only what you need when needed, making your development process more efficient. Think of it as grocery shopping with a list, but for your code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/explicit-includes-the-art-of-fetching-just-enough-data-in-ef-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 13:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I still like Sublime Text in 2025 | OhDoyleRules</title>
      <link>https://ohdoylerules.com/workflows/why-i-still-like-sublime-text-in-2025/</link>
      <description>I still use Sublime Text in 2025 even after trying a lot of other editors</description>
      <author> (james2doyle@gmail.com James Doyle)</author>
      <guid>https://ohdoylerules.com/workflows/why-i-still-like-sublime-text-in-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek&amp;#39;s Multi-Head Latent Attention and Other KV Cache Tricks</title>
      <link>https://www.pyspur.dev/blog/multi-head-latent-attention-kv-cache-paper-list</link>
      <description>How a Key-Value (KV) cache reduces Transformer inference time by trading memory for computation</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pyspur.dev/blog/multi-head-latent-attention-kv-cache-paper-list</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 10:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L: Marketing 2 (Category Compilation) #08～#09</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=aapNzQq4yyo</link>
      <description>In Category L:  Marketing, I discuss strategies for getting the word out about your game. No matter how good your game is, it may as well not exist if people don&amp;#39;t know about it.

[Index]
0:00 Opening
0:12 L-08 Targeting and Market Research
4:32 L-09 Smash Bros. DOJO!!

[Playlist L: Marketing]
https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLgKCjZ2WsVLTwxbJjYoPyXUOik_ZiTxIE</description>
      <author> (Masahiro Sakurai on Creating Games)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=aapNzQq4yyo</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 10:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexey Staroselets | Goodbye, Slopify</title>
      <link>https://alexeystar.com/blog/slopify/</link>
      <description>My Discover Weekly playlist on Spotify is finally poisoned by AI slop.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alexeystar.com/blog/slopify/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 04:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using uv as your shebang line</title>
      <link>https://akrabat.com/using-uv-as-your-shebang-line/</link>
      <description>An article by Rob Allen</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://akrabat.com/using-uv-as-your-shebang-line/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform 5.6 - 2.5x Perf Improvements, Turbocharged Hot Reload and expanded App Packaging</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/5-6/</link>
      <description>Uno Platform 5.6 is packed with productivity and performance boosts, including 10x faster Wasm AOT, enhanced Hot Reload, new macOS app packaging, and memory optimizations.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/5-6/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,156 Questions Censored by DeepSeek | promptfoo</title>
      <link>https://www.promptfoo.dev/blog/deepseek-censorship/</link>
      <description>DeepSeek-R1 is a blockbuster open-source model that is now at the top of the U.S. App Store.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.promptfoo.dev/blog/deepseek-censorship/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Accumulation of Regulation</title>
      <link>https://coyoteblog.com/coyote_blog/2025/01/the-accumulation-of-regulation.html</link>
      <description>Like many who do business in California, I often complain about the regulatory burden (free at last!)&amp;#160; People will ask, &amp;quot;So what one regulation would you get</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://coyoteblog.com/coyote_blog/2025/01/the-accumulation-of-regulation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek Didn’t Invent the Wheel — It Just Put a New Sticker on It</title>
      <link>https://blog.ryanmerket.com/deepseek-didnt-invent-the-wheel-it-just-put-a-new-sticker-on-it-9e07f3d0039f</link>
      <description>AI has a hype problem. Every few months, a new model drops, and people start asking if it’s the next big thing. OpenAI, Anthropic, Google…</description>
      <author> (https://blog.ryanmerket.com)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ryanmerket.com/deepseek-didnt-invent-the-wheel-it-just-put-a-new-sticker-on-it-9e07f3d0039f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analytical Intelligence Is Coming - Developer forever</title>
      <link>https://manidoraisamy.com/developer-forever/post/analytical-intelligence-is-coming.anc-ac83b8cf-a25c-4e12-9ee5-ad160b802fd4.html</link>
      <description>The release of Deepseek R1 has made headlines, but the unsung hero is its sibling: R1 Zero. While R1 showcases reasoning through human feedback, R1 Zero demonstrates something far more transformative—reasoning without human feedback. This works only in analytical tasks like math and coding, but it removes the cost of hiring humans for feedback (bye, bye, Scale AI). This shift is poised to divide the AI landscape into two: analytical AI (like R1 Zero) that will thrive without human feedback, and creative AI (like ChatGPT-4) that relies on human feedback for understanding human ambiguity.This moment marks AI’s Vertical SaaS transformation, but not in the way we expected. For years, we assumed AI verticalization would be domain-specific—targeting industries like healthcare, finance, or logistics. Instead, the future of AI lies in intelligence-specific verticals: analytical and creative intelligences, much like how people are—some are more left-brained (analytical), while others are more right-brained (creative).How R1 Zero Achieves Deterministic ReasoningTraditional AI models like GPT rely on probabilistic reasoning, predicting the most likely sequence of words or outcomes. This requires human feedback to address the ambiguities of human language through a technique called supervised fine-tuning (SFT). R1 Zero, however, focuses on verifiable outcomes like chess or math using reinforcement learning (RL), eliminating the need for human feedback. Here’s how it works:Reinforcement Learning with Binary Rewards:R1 Zero trains on tasks where outputs are either correct or incorrect, like solving math problems or generating code. This allows the system to refine its reasoning iteratively without relying on expensive, human-labeled datasets.Execution and Validation:After generating a solution, R1 Zero executes it (e.g., running a program or applying a formula) to confirm its correctness. This ensures repeatable, deterministic outputs—a stark contrast to the variability of LLMs.Narrow Focus:R1 Zero excels in structured tasks like coding or financial modeling by avoiding ambiguous, subjective problems. Its narrow specialization enables higher accuracy and efficiency.For example, imagine you’re solving how far a ladder needs to be placed to reach 12 feet on a wall with a 13-foot ladder. R1 Zero would apply the Pythagorean theorem deterministically to calculate the correct result every time—placing the base 5 feet from the wall. This ability to reason and execute precise logic makes it incredibly powerful for analytical tasks. (For more details, see my earlier essay on how reasoning AI thinks).Why R1 Zero Matters More Than R1Analytical Intelligence Will Be a Cottage Industry:By avoiding reliance on costly data labeling or human feedback, R1 Zero allows smaller companies to build low-cost, deterministic AI systems. Startups can now create AI for niche tasks like coding or math because they don’t need to hire people to clean up the data for training. They can run RL, which only requires compute costs instead of people costs.Super Intelligence Will Be Like a Ferrari:While LLMs like GPT excel in creative and ambiguous tasks, R1 Zero specializes in precision and logic. Together, they can form a mixture of experts, as I had predicted in my super intelligence article. This will be useful for high end tasks like scientific research, but doing both might be expensive. So, they may struggle to compete with analytical intelligence startups on pricing. They&amp;#39;ll need to price tokens differently only for analytical tasks, which will complicate pricing.Will Desktops Replace Mainframes?Eventually, analytical intelligence like R1 Zero might become cheaper to build and deploy on low-end devices like desktops, robots, or phones. They may not even need to connect to multi-billion-dollar AI clusters. This is reminiscent of desktops taking over mainframes, as explained by Clayton Christensen in his book The Innovator’s Dilemma, where disruption happens when a cheaper product—like analytical intelligence—becomes increasingly capable, pushing super intelligence into niche applications and eventually making it less relevant.In essence, this is a Vertical SaaS moment for AI. We are witnessing the birth of intelligence-specific verticalization:Analytical Intelligence: Deterministic reasoning for math, logic, and coding. (e.g., R1 Zero)Creative Intelligence: Generating ideas, designs, and narratives. (e.g., ChatGPT-4)Artistic Intelligence: Producing visuals, music, and other forms of artistic expression. (e.g., DALL-E)This shift mirrors the rise of vertical SaaS in software, where tools went from Shopify to Toast to Slice and became narrowly focused on one vertical. Similary, AI will become specialized intelligences, with analytical intelligence leading the way.SummarySo far, humans have economically valued analytical skills more than artistic skills, leading to a world where logical reasoning and structured problem-solving dominate white-collar jobs. But what happens when analytical AI becomes not only smarter but also far cheaper than artistic AI?Consider this: tools like Stockfish are available to every chess player, but no one allows it to play on behalf of the player. Now imagine analytical AI systems replacing financial analysts, engineers, or coders. Will we still value these roles as highly when the &amp;quot;intelligence&amp;quot; behind them is automated?This isn’t just a shift in how we think about AI—it’s a shift in how we value human skills. Analytical intelligence is coming, and it will reshape not just industries but our economy and our sense of purpose in a world where reasoning machines take over tasks we once prized most.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://manidoraisamy.com/developer-forever/post/analytical-intelligence-is-coming.anc-ac83b8cf-a25c-4e12-9ee5-ad160b802fd4.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UV tricks</title>
      <link>https://www.bitecode.dev/p/uv-tricks</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t forget to uv self update before trying those</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bitecode.dev/p/uv-tricks</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Hit DeepSeek 0</title>
      <link>https://slakinski.com/2025/01/28/to-hit-deepseek/</link>
      <description>Update: I was using the following models: deepseek-r1:7b and llama3:latest (7b)


DeepSeek-R1 came out generally over the weekend, and a lot was talked about the cost to generate such a complete and capable model. I am happy to see that it is an open model that I could</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://slakinski.com/2025/01/28/to-hit-deepseek/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building My E-Ink Tea Labeling System - Tynan.com</title>
      <link>https://tynan.com/tealabels/</link>
      <description>My life sometimes seems to consist of long periods of intense effort to help me save seconds or minutes from my day. This latest project must be the most extreme example of that. I store my tea in identical metal tins. Years ago I went down a rabbit hole of designing custom labels for each […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tynan.com/tealabels/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allegory of the Tsunami</title>
      <link>https://blog.evan.hu/p/allegory-of-the-tsunami</link>
      <description>Change is on the horizon, AGI approaches</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.evan.hu/p/allegory-of-the-tsunami</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give People Something To Disagree With - Don&amp;#39;t Break Prod</title>
      <link>https://dontbreakprod.com/posts/give-people-something-to-disagree-with</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t Break Prod provides bite-sized pieces of career advice for software engineers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dontbreakprod.com/posts/give-people-something-to-disagree-with</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polymarket Paradox | Rakshith Aloori</title>
      <link>https://rakshithxaloori.com/writings/polymarket-paradox</link>
      <description>Take this poll.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rakshithxaloori.com/writings/polymarket-paradox</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spice up with Nix: Scripts with magical dependencies | yukiisbo.red</title>
      <link>https://yukiisbo.red/notes/spice-up-with-nix-scripts/</link>
      <description>Hey there, Instead of reading this outdated article, I highly recommend consulting nix.dev’s First Steps which is official documentation!

F…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yukiisbo.red/notes/spice-up-with-nix-scripts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manager vs Craftsman — Derrick Persson</title>
      <link>https://www.derrickpersson.com/manager-vs-craftsmen</link>
      <description>Programming in the era of LLM&amp;#39;s</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.derrickpersson.com/manager-vs-craftsmen</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I&amp;#39;m Ditching poetry for uv</title>
      <link>https://thijsnieuwdorp.com/posts/uv/</link>
      <description>How I cut my Python working environment&amp;#39;s headaches in half with Astral&amp;#39;s uv - a Rust-powered Swiss Army knife for Python workflows.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thijsnieuwdorp.com/posts/uv/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT1 Implemented with NumPy : Generate Jokes</title>
      <link>https://mburaksayici.com/blog/2025/01/27/GPT1-Implemented-NumPy-only.html</link>
      <description>I love implementing DL algorithms with NumPy, it’s best way to learn the engine. I’ve implemented SHAP, and CNNs, and GradCAM methods with pure numpy before, you can refer to my Github Page for this.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mburaksayici.com/blog/2025/01/27/GPT1-Implemented-NumPy-only.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking in community systems</title>
      <link>https://rosie.land/posts/thinking-in-community-systems/</link>
      <description>Community can be a bit fluffy. A bit intangible. A bit directionless at times. We can believe in something, yet actioning it into reality is a whole other story.

This year I&amp;#39;ve learned we can do better. We can be more focused. We can double down on what matters. We</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rosie.land/posts/thinking-in-community-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why (Open Source) DeepSeek&amp;#39;s shock is important</title>
      <link>https://aien.me/why-open-source-deepseeks-shock-is-important/</link>
      <description>How a Chinese startup is challenging AI giants with open-source innovation, achieving ChatGPT-level performance at 2% of the cost. Is this the future of accessible AI?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aien.me/why-open-source-deepseeks-shock-is-important/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making LLM workflows human friendly</title>
      <link>https://bluenotebook.io/posts/streaming-fuction-calling/post</link>
      <description>Validate the data as it streams, don’t make your users wait.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bluenotebook.io/posts/streaming-fuction-calling/post</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What we got wrong about the cloud</title>
      <link>https://bitmasonsllc.blogspot.com/2025/01/what-we-got-wrong-about-cloud.html</link>
      <description>&amp;#160;Not everyone bought my comparison of how the cloud developed and AI is developing that I posted the other day . But I wanted to flesh out s...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bitmasonsllc.blogspot.com/2025/01/what-we-got-wrong-about-cloud.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a (T1D) smartwatch from scratch</title>
      <link>https://andrewchilds.com/posts/building-a-t1d-smartwatch-from-scratch</link>
      <description>Documenting an attempt to build a single-purpose smartwatch.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewchilds.com/posts/building-a-t1d-smartwatch-from-scratch</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Waveforms in Kdenlive: Technical Upgrades for Speed, Precision, and better UX</title>
      <link>https://etiand.re/posts/2025/01/audio-waveforms-in-kdenlive-technical-upgrades-for-speed-precision-and-better-ux/</link>
      <description>I recently worked on audio waveform generation in Kdenlive, an actively developed free and open-source non-linear video editor. It boasts a user base of over 100,000 users per release on Linux, Windows, and macOS.
The Kdenlive video editor.
To improve user experience and overall performance, one focus was enhancing audio thumbnails—the small waveforms displayed on the timeline and in the clip player.
Previously, generating these was slow, leading to frustrating delays for users starting their projects.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://etiand.re/posts/2025/01/audio-waveforms-in-kdenlive-technical-upgrades-for-speed-precision-and-better-ux/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing a .NET Garbage Collector in C#  -  Part 1</title>
      <link>https://minidump.net/2025-28-01-writing-a-net-gc-in-c-part-1/</link>
      <description>First part of a series of articles about writing a .NET Garbage Collector in C# using NativeAOT. This part sets the expectations and setups the project, dealing with the first difficulties.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://minidump.net/2025-28-01-writing-a-net-gc-in-c-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Shall Not Get Access &amp;#129497;&amp;#127995;‍♂️: Browser Permissions</title>
      <link>https://albertofdr.github.io/web-security-class/browser/browser.permissions</link>
      <description>Web Security Educational Blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://albertofdr.github.io/web-security-class/browser/browser.permissions</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Content Overflow Era – the end of the Long Tail?</title>
      <link>https://afewthingz.com/contentoverflowera</link>
      <description>What follows might be trivial by now, but it is always good to put a word on it. I&amp;#39;m speaking about...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://afewthingz.com/contentoverflowera</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Colorado&amp;#39;s EV incentive worth it?</title>
      <link>https://mattsayar.com/is-colorados-ev-incentive-worth-it/</link>
      <description>I wasn&amp;#39;t even looking for a new car when my coworker told me, &amp;#39;You can lease a Nissan Leaf for like $20 a month.&amp;#39; That sounded too good to be true. Spoiler alert: it was. How are electric vehicle leases so cheap here in Colorado?…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mattsayar.com/is-colorados-ev-incentive-worth-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Gambling is (more) Rational (than you think)</title>
      <link>https://lucaspauker.com/articles/gambling-rationality/</link>
      <description>I remember watching a video a while ago where a pro card counter answers questions about gambling. In one of his answers, he said that what makes someone a true gambler is that the joy of winning a bet is more than the sadness from losing a bet. This has stuck with me since I watched the video over a year ago. Since then, I sometimes think about why people gamble and what makes some people more prone to gambling.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lucaspauker.com/articles/gambling-rationality/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Complexity Gap</title>
      <link>https://seanpedersen.github.io/posts/semantic-complexity-gap</link>
      <description>Another place for thought infusion</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://seanpedersen.github.io/posts/semantic-complexity-gap</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Chiang | Confidential Compute and GPUs</title>
      <link>https://ericchiang.github.io/post/confidential-gpus/</link>
      <description>Recently, I’ve had a few conversations about NVIDIA Confidential Compute, usually in the context of startups trying to sell security products to AI companies.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ericchiang.github.io/post/confidential-gpus/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>correcting my model</title>
      <link>https://dymchenko.com/blog_correcting_my_model.html</link>
      <description>go home</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dymchenko.com/blog_correcting_my_model.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>