<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - TagzApp - An app that discovers content on social media using hashtags</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=WMdZPuMaGIM</link>
      <description>Jeff Fritz shows us how he built TagzApp, an app that discovers content on social media using hashtags.Links: https://www.theurlist.com/aspnet-standup-2024-0...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=WMdZPuMaGIM</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making my bookshelves clickable | James&amp;#39; Coffee Blog</title>
      <link>https://jamesg.blog/2024/02/14/clickable-bookshelves/</link>
      <description>You can make regions of an image clickable with a number of techniques, from overlyaing an SVG that contains onclick JavaScript handlers all the way to using image maps. I love this idea. I started to think about how I could create an image of my bookshelves that you could click to learn more about each book I am reading. This would be more engaging than a traditional list of text.</description>
      <author> (James&amp;#39; Coffee Blog ☕)</author>
      <guid>https://jamesg.blog/2024/02/14/clickable-bookshelves/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No one cares about open-source, until …</title>
      <link>https://blog.cryptpad.org/2024/02/15/no-one-cares-intil/</link>
      <description>If you follow privacy news, you have probably heard that Skiff, an end-to-end encrypted productivity suite, announced that it has been acquired by Notion. We could not resist chiming in since Skiff was compared with CryptPad in the past.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cryptpad.org/2024/02/15/no-one-cares-intil/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Developer Relations?</title>
      <link>https://polar.sh/danielapassos/posts/what-is-developer-relations</link>
      <description>Developer Relations (DevRel) serves as the bridge between companies and developers, ensuring that both sides understand and benefit from each other&amp;#39;s work. In the tech industry, building relationships with the developer community is essential. At its core, our work as DevRels builds and nurtures relationships with a dev-focused community, focusing on communication, support, and feedback loops between developers and the companies. Often times, DevRel teams wear many hats. They</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://polar.sh/danielapassos/posts/what-is-developer-relations</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Talk to Your Date versus Your Customer</title>
      <link>https://jerry.wtf/posts/how-to-talk-to-your-date/</link>
      <description>
Introduction
When I was younger, I thought dating was primarily about “impressing” someone enough that they would somehow find you attractive. After discussing this with my therapist, I now understand that my lack of self-confidence led me to feel like I had to “deceive” others to be liked because I didn’t like myself. Thus, inauthenticity.
That line of thinking and mindset led me to be single for a long time, and since then I’ve always paid attention to how I communicate and how I might communicate better. Coming from a nerdy, introverted, engineering background, it has taken me some time to reach my somewhat adequate level of socialization, but I’m enthusiastic to inform the reader that a psychologist friend recently dubbed me “almost certainly not autistic” &amp;#128526;&amp;#128077;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jerry.wtf/posts/how-to-talk-to-your-date/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Generative Internet</title>
      <link>https://joanfihu.com/2024/02/14/the-generative-internet/</link>
      <description>Generative AI is opening the doors to new products. It’s great to witness in real time how the Internet is evolving and to imagine what it might become in the coming years. Search, UI navigat…</description>
      <author> (joanfihu)</author>
      <guid>https://joanfihu.com/2024/02/14/the-generative-internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>varoa.net | Galo Navarro</title>
      <link>https://varoa.net/2024/02/06/how-about-we-forget-the-concept-of-test-types.html</link>
      <description>I have found that the concept of test types (unit, integration, and soon) does more harm than good. People often give me odd looks when I saythis, so having ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://varoa.net/2024/02/06/how-about-we-forget-the-concept-of-test-types.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keywords for Top 10 Languages</title>
      <link>https://breadchris.com/thinkies/keywords-for-top-10-languages/</link>
      <description>note: this does not include symbolic operators (*, ||, &amp;amp;&amp;amp;, etc.)
Python: 35
False, None, True, and, as, assert, async, await, break, class, continue, def, del, elif, else, except, finally, for, from, global, if, import, in, is, lambda, nonlocal, not, or, pass, raise, return, try, while, with, yield Java: 52
abstract, assert, boolean, break, byte, case, catch, char, class, const, continue, default, do, double, else, enum, extends, final, finally, float, for, goto, if, implements, import, instanceof, int, interface, long, native, new, package, private, protected, public, return, short, static, strictfp, super, switch, synchronized, this, throw, throws, transient, try, void, volatile, while JavaScript: 50</description>
      <author> (breadchris)</author>
      <guid>https://breadchris.com/thinkies/keywords-for-top-10-languages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let CRS 4 be your valentine! – OWASP ModSecurity Core Rule Set</title>
      <link>https://coreruleset.org/20240214/let-crs-4-be-your-valentine/</link>
      <description>What a Valentine’s Day present we have got for you: today, the Core Rule Set project is releasing CRS 4!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://coreruleset.org/20240214/let-crs-4-be-your-valentine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A beginners guide to fine tuning LLM using LoRA</title>
      <link>https://zohaib.me/a-beginners-guide-to-fine-tuning-llm-using-lora/</link>
      <description>Discover how to create a synthetic dataset, select the right metrics for evaluation, and fine-tune your model using LoRA for a narrow scenario. Plus, learn how to serve your model efficiently using LLaMa.cpp on Mac/Linux.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zohaib.me/a-beginners-guide-to-fine-tuning-llm-using-lora/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocular IQ EV Chargers, or how not to leverage open source</title>
      <link>https://benchilds.dev/blog/2024/02/ocular-iq-ev-chargers-or-how-not-to-leverage-open-source</link>
      <description>Like most people in the IT industry, I love new tech. I would consider myself an early adopter on most things, unless I can see a clear reason not</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://benchilds.dev/blog/2024/02/ocular-iq-ev-chargers-or-how-not-to-leverage-open-source</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nerd Sniped - Solving for Jumbles and Letter Boxed</title>
      <link>https://hlfshell.ai/posts/letter-puzzles/</link>
      <description>tl;dr I got nerd sniped by a problem and wrote a solver for it. You can find it here.
The Problem Apparently it’s impossible to determine if someone is capable of coding without asking them arbitrary puzzles that are in no way related to a realistic job. Resumes and previous job experience are so passe - puzzles are where it’s at.
I received one of these coding challenges - given a jumble of letters, find all possible words you could spell.</description>
      <author> (Keith Chester)</author>
      <guid>https://hlfshell.ai/posts/letter-puzzles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe hostnames and IP addresses for examples</title>
      <link>https://sundry.jerryorr.com/2023/09/29/example-hostnames-ip-addresses</link>
      <description>Various thoughts on programming and technology.</description>
      <author> (Jerry Orr)</author>
      <guid>https://sundry.jerryorr.com/2023/09/29/example-hostnames-ip-addresses</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should I record my life?</title>
      <link>https://matiroy.com/writings/Should-I-record-my-life.html</link>
      <description>
    Say audio or video record most or all of my conversations
    </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matiroy.com/writings/Should-I-record-my-life.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Poor Prompting Can Lead to Biased Results from LLM Applications</title>
      <link>https://teddyrendahl.github.io/2024/02/12/bias_with_poor_prompting.html</link>
      <description>Personal Portfolio for Teddy Rendahl</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://teddyrendahl.github.io/2024/02/12/bias_with_poor_prompting.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Guide for Crafting Tech Talks in 2024</title>
      <link>https://kelset.dev/blog/guide-craft-tech-talks-for-conferences-2024/</link>
      <description>My process and self-imposed rules for writing tech talks. Because it’s 2024, it’s also a GPT you can play with.</description>
      <author> (Lorenzo &amp;#39;kelset&amp;#39; Sciandra)</author>
      <guid>https://kelset.dev/blog/guide-craft-tech-talks-for-conferences-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing SQLite for servers</title>
      <link>https://kerkour.com/sqlite-for-servers</link>
      <description>SQLite is often misconceived as a &amp;amp;#34;toy database&amp;amp;#34;, only good for mobile applications and embedded systems because it&amp;amp;#39;s default configuration is optimized for embedded use cases, so most people trying it will encounter poor performances and the dreaded SQLITE_BUSY error. But what if I told you that by tuning a</description>
      <author> (Sylvain Kerkour)</author>
      <guid>https://kerkour.com/sqlite-for-servers</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node People vs. Edge People</title>
      <link>https://www.joshcsimmons.com/nodes-vs-edges</link>
      <description>Over the course of my study and career, I&amp;#39;ve come to realize that people largely
fall into one of two groups of thinkers - they&amp;#39;re either node people or edge
people. With most dichotomies, there is usually a huge amount of grey area. This
is one of the rare cases where I&amp;#39;ve found that people fall pretty fully into one
category or the other.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.joshcsimmons.com/nodes-vs-edges</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naming is Important</title>
      <link>https://breadchris.com/blog/naming-is-important/</link>
      <description>Why should we care so much about naming as developers? Code comes and goes, but language prevails. When a team is working on a project, they must develop a shared language on how things work, how they are structured, and how they are related. A database schema or language specification is such an important document that many developers will battle passionately over what columns are called. Mental models of how things go together are at odds when there are multiple words to describe the same thing.</description>
      <author> (breadchris)</author>
      <guid>https://breadchris.com/blog/naming-is-important/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chasing a bug in a SAT solver</title>
      <link>https://ochagavia.nl/blog/chasing-a-bug-in-a-sat-solver/</link>
      <description>Recently I spent two weeks collaborating with Prefix.dev to further develop resolvo, their SAT-based dependency solver. The main goal was to fix a nasty bug, where the solver unexpectedly panicked upon hitting code that was supposed to be unreachable. “That will make for a good war story!”, I thought, so I kept notes of my debugging process to serve as a basis for this article.
I was being overly pessimistic, though, thinking it would take days to find the source of the bug… In reality it took me only a few hours, so there’s not much to tell about the chase itself.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ochagavia.nl/blog/chasing-a-bug-in-a-sat-solver/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing Truth Tables in Org</title>
      <link>http://yummymelon.com/devnull/computing-truth-tables-in-org.html</link>
      <description>Truth tables are great way to design and verify combinational logic. Useful as truth tables are, they however can be onerous to write: as the number of inputs grow, so does the size of table...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://yummymelon.com/devnull/computing-truth-tables-in-org.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 01:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple confirms it&amp;#39;s breaking iPhone web apps in the EU on purpose | TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/02/15/apple-confirms-its-breaking-iphone-web-apps-in-the-eu-on-purpose/</link>
      <description>Well, it turns out it&amp;#39;s not a bug that broke iPhone web apps, also known as progressive web apps (PWAs), in the EU. Following developer complaints and</description>
      <author> (Sarah Perez)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2024/02/15/apple-confirms-its-breaking-iphone-web-apps-in-the-eu-on-purpose/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 23:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Answering Some Concerns about Wolverine</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/02/15/answering-some-concerns-about-wolverine/</link>
      <description>Nick Chapsas just released a video about Wolverine with his introduction and take on the framework. Not to take anything away from the video that was mostly positive, but I thought there were quite…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/02/15/answering-some-concerns-about-wolverine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 23:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polly Core Rate Limiter | no dogma blog</title>
      <link>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2024/02/polly-core-rate-limiter/</link>
      <description>In the new Polly version, the rate limiter has replaced bulkhead isolation. This post shows how to use the rate limiter.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2024/02/polly-core-rate-limiter/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>uv: Python packaging in Rust</title>
      <link>https://astral.sh/blog/uv</link>
      <description>uv is an extremely fast Python package installer and resolver, designed as a drop-in alternative to pip and pip-tools.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://astral.sh/blog/uv</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asahi Linux project’s OpenGL support on Apple Silicon officially surpasses Apple’s</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2024/02/asahi-linux-projects-opengl-support-on-apple-silicon-officially-surpasses-apples/</link>
      <description>Newest driver supports the latest versions of OpenGL and OpenGL ES.</description>
      <author> (Andrew Cunningham
    -    2/14/2024, 2:00 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2024/02/asahi-linux-projects-opengl-support-on-apple-silicon-officially-surpasses-apples/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Observable 2.0 | Observable</title>
      <link>https://observablehq.com/blog/observable-2-0</link>
      <description>Launch of Observable 2.0: an open-source tool for building data apps and dashboards with a seamless developer workflow and optimal user experience.</description>
      <author> (Mike BostockFounder / Office of the CEO)</author>
      <guid>https://observablehq.com/blog/observable-2-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>squillace (@squillace@hachyderm.io)</title>
      <link>https://hachyderm.io/@squillace/111937148867849325</link>
      <description>Following on the first post about #hyperlight, @arschles has posted the second: bare metal, #webassembly, #wamr, #unikernels, the whole ball of wax: https://ecomaz.net/blog/hyperlight-overview-2/</description>
      <author> (By Mark Russinovich)</author>
      <guid>https://hachyderm.io/@squillace/111937148867849325</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_30Ee_VrCsw</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
  
    .NET Foundation
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_30Ee_VrCsw</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every Default macOS Wallpaper – in Glorious 6K Resolution</title>
      <link>https://512pixels.net/projects/default-mac-wallpapers-in-5k/</link>
      <description>Every major version of Mac OS X macOS has come with a new default wallpaper. As you can see, I have collected them all here. While great in their day, the early wallpapers are now quite small in the world of 5K and 6K displays. If you want to see detailed screenshots of every release [...]</description>
      <author> (https://512pixels.net/author/stephen/)</author>
      <guid>https://512pixels.net/projects/default-mac-wallpapers-in-5k/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Schlesinger&amp;#39;s Personal Site</title>
      <link>https://ecomaz.net/blog/hyperlight-overview-1/</link>
      <description>After I wrote those posts about C#-to-Rust and Rust-to-C# communication (part 1 and part 2), a lot of people reached out with questions about what Hyperlight is in the first place. There&amp;#39;s not a lot of information out there about the project besides what I&amp;#39;ve written, what&amp;#39;s been presented at Microsoft Build (more on that in a second), and word-of-mouth, so I&amp;#39;m going to fill in the gaps here.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ecomaz.net/blog/hyperlight-overview-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why software &amp;#39;security debt&amp;#39; is becoming a serious problem for developers</title>
      <link>https://www.itpro.com/security/why-software-security-debt-is-becoming-a-serious-problem-for-developers</link>
      <description>The majority of organizations have some level of software security debt, with experts warning firms to reassess how they maintain third party code</description>
      <author> (Solomon KlappholzSocial Links NavigationStaff Writer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.itpro.com/security/why-software-security-debt-is-becoming-a-serious-problem-for-developers</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 19:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sora: Creating video from text</title>
      <link>https://openai.com/sora</link>
      <description>We’re teaching AI to understand and simulate the physical world in motion, with the goal of training models that help people solve problems that require real-world interaction.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://openai.com/sora</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 19:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor Web App Project Structure [Pt 5] | Front-end Web Development with .NET for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=JcOAtSU-jJ0</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s take a look at all the files that make up a Blazor web app project and understand what they do.Follow along: https://aka.ms/dotnet/beginnervideos/repoC...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=JcOAtSU-jJ0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 19:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web API Clients with Meadow.Cloud</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=vkVv1M8inVc</link>
      <description>In this video Jorge shows us how he turned a Project Lab into a Meadow.Cloud client, and uses its Web API to get data logs and shows them on a LineChart usin...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=vkVv1M8inVc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 19:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surely dark UX doesn&amp;#39;t work in the long run</title>
      <link>https://www.pcloadletter.dev/blog/dark-ux/</link>
      <description>What the **** does that mean?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pcloadletter.dev/blog/dark-ux/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 19:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our next-generation model: Gemini 1.5</title>
      <link>https://blog.google/technology/ai/google-gemini-next-generation-model-february-2024/</link>
      <description>Gemini 1.5 delivers dramatically enhanced performance, with a breakthrough in long-context understanding across modalities.</description>
      <author> (Sundar Pichai
  
    
      CEO of Google and Alphabet)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.google/technology/ai/google-gemini-next-generation-model-february-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect Project Structure for Production Ready Serverless Rust</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=C5R0NjTn7w0</link>
      <description>When you&amp;#39;re building production ready serverless applications, how do you set yourself up for success? How do you define a project structure that will meet y...</description>
      <author> (Aztechs Academy
  
  
  
    Aztechs Academy
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=C5R0NjTn7w0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Wants To Kill PWAs</title>
      <link>https://itnext.io/apple-wants-to-kill-pwas-0895be2e497b?source=friends_link</link>
      <description>It’s now more clear than ever</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@dannymoerkerke)</author>
      <guid>https://itnext.io/apple-wants-to-kill-pwas-0895be2e497b?source=friends_link</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Registered command lines are just command lines, not a programming language - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240215-00/?p=109407</link>
      <description>If you want a programming language, you know where to find one.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240215-00/?p=109407</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT vs. Advent of Code 2023 Day 21</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=AEBFF711S8Y</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Martin Zikmund
  
  
  
    Martin Zikmund
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=AEBFF711S8Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 16:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Worlds: Integrating the Enable Design System with a Blazor Web Application</title>
      <link>https://blog.enable.engineering/bridging-worlds-integrating-the-enable-design-system-with-a-blazor-web-application-a94738b5a7e8</link>
      <description>As Enable experiences rapid growth, we have to constantly strive to improve the efficiency of our engineering practices. Recently, the user…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@alexvale242)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.enable.engineering/bridging-worlds-integrating-the-enable-design-system-with-a-blazor-web-application-a94738b5a7e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 16:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aldi Price Map - Navel Oranges</title>
      <link>https://www.aldipricemap.com/navel_oranges.html</link>
      <description>How much do &amp;#160; &amp;#160;cost at Aldi?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.aldipricemap.com/navel_oranges.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 16:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivery Day! We&amp;#39;re finishing the Blazor App</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=APLIcuze1ow</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.ioToday, we&amp;#39;re finishing the Blazor version of TagzApp! You can find it at https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/TagzApp</description>
      <author> (John Savill&amp;#39;s Technical Training
  
  
  
    John Savill&amp;#39;s Technical Training
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=APLIcuze1ow</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 15:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Clean Messaging in .NET with Wolverine</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=p1gsK69m94Y</link>
      <description>Use code MODULAR and get 20% off the brand new &amp;quot;Getting Started with Modular Monoliths&amp;quot; course on Dometrain: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-mod...</description>
      <author> (ThePrimeTime
  
  
  
    ThePrimeTime
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=p1gsK69m94Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 15:03:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Sheets in C# – How to Build Your Own Levels.fyi!</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/02/15/google-sheets-in-c-how-to-build-your-own-levels-fyi/</link>
      <description>Interested in using Google Drive and Google Sheets in C#? Get started with the Google Sheets API to access spreadsheets in C# in your own dotnet applications!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/02/15/google-sheets-in-c-how-to-build-your-own-levels-fyi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 14:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPTO TSDR Case Viewer</title>
      <link>https://tsdr.uspto.gov/documentviewer?caseId=sn97733259&amp;docId=FREF20240206125856&amp;linkId=1#docIndex=0&amp;page=1</link>
      <description>Case Id</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tsdr.uspto.gov/documentviewer?caseId=sn97733259&amp;docId=FREF20240206125856&amp;linkId=1#docIndex=0&amp;page=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 13:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSilver 2.1 Brings F# Support for the Silverlight Reimplementation </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2024/02/opensilver-21-fsharp/</link>
      <description>OpenSilver 2.1, an update for the remake of the discontinued Silverlight web application framework, introduces support for F# language. The update also contains migrated samples from the original toolkit and allows developers to use themes.</description>
      <author> (Edin Kapić
                
            
            
        Lead Software EngineerFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2024/02/opensilver-21-fsharp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 13:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 8  .&amp;#128640;&amp;#128293;:  Aspire Preview 3 : Whats new &amp;amp; Upgrade Guide</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=d9_0Ep6d3As</link>
      <description>Dive into the latest advancements in .NET technology with our comprehensive guide on .NET Aspire Preview 3. Support me on Patreon to access the source code:h...</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand
  
  
  
    Mohamad Lawand
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=d9_0Ep6d3As</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>String Performance: String&amp;#160;Compression</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/02/15/string-performance-string-compression/</link>
      <description>The content discusses the significance of string compression in programming, outlining four available data formats and demonstrating how to compress and decompress strings using Brotli. It also men…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/02/15/string-performance-string-compression/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 11:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enumerating over Select’s index | tabs ↹ over ␣ ␣ ␣ spaces by Jiř&amp;#237; {x2} Činčura</title>
      <link>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233932-enumerating-over-select-index</link>
      <description>15 Feb 2024
	
	 2 mins
	
	 .NET, C#</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233932-enumerating-over-select-index</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 11:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks! Improving Your CSS Game with Martine Dowden</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/details/1885</link>
      <description>How do you improve your CSS skills? Carl and Richard talk to Martine Dowden about her new book, Tiny CSS Projects. The book is built around twelve progressively more complex CSS tasks - you can follow along to learn in general or pick a particular chapter for a specific skill you want to exercise. The conversation digs into thinking about the architecture of styling beyond the particular page and how those styles can be updated version-to-version without frustration. You can improve your CSS game!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/details/1885</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Visual Studio 17.10 – Preview 1 is Here! - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/introducing-visual-studio-17-10-preview-1-is-here/</link>
      <description>Download Visual Studio 2022 17.10 Preview 1. The fastest coding experience with GitHub Copilot Chat, brings enhancements in productivity, debugging, C++, and game development.</description>
      <author> (Mark Downie)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/introducing-visual-studio-17-10-preview-1-is-here/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 06:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters Weekly 270 -  Entity Framework JSON Columns</title>
      <link>https://www.aspnetmonsters.com/2024/02/monsters-weekly%5Cep270/</link>
      <description>Entity framework has support as of EF7 for JSON column types. Is this a good idea? Should you use it and if you do how do you use it? All questions will be answered in this video.</description>
      <author> (The Monsters)</author>
      <guid>https://www.aspnetmonsters.com/2024/02/monsters-weekly%5Cep270/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 06:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Static Web App–Authorization</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/02/azure-static-web-appauthorization.html</link>
      <description>As a follow-up on the presentation I did at CloudBrew  about Azure Static Web Apps I want to write a series of blog posts.      Part I - Usi...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/02/azure-static-web-appauthorization.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 06:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release v8.1.0-preview1 &amp;#183; dotnet/orleans</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/orleans/releases/tag/v8.1.0-preview1</link>
      <description>New features
Integration with Aspire
This release includes initial integration with Aspire Preview 3 and later, allowing you to configure an Orleans cluster in your Aspire app host, specifying the ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/orleans/releases/tag/v8.1.0-preview1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 06:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specflow has died; long live Reqnroll!</title>
      <link>https://kaylumah.nl/2024/02/09/long-live-reqnroll.html</link>
      <description>SpecFlow rebooted; please welcome Reqnroll!</description>
      <author> (Max Hamuly&amp;#225;k)</author>
      <guid>https://kaylumah.nl/2024/02/09/long-live-reqnroll.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 06:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From SpecFlow to Reqnroll: Why and How • Reqnroll</title>
      <link>https://reqnroll.net/news/2024/02/from-specflow-to-reqnroll-why-and-how/</link>
      <description>Please, welcome Reqnroll, a fork of SpecFlow with the aim of rebooting the open-source project!</description>
      <author> (Gaspar Nagy)</author>
      <guid>https://reqnroll.net/news/2024/02/from-specflow-to-reqnroll-why-and-how/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 06:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Conditional Required Attributes for Validation in .NET Web API - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/aspnetcore-conditional-required-attributes/</link>
      <description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll learn the approaches to creating conditional required attributes for validation in ASP.NET Core.</description>
      <author> (Ainea Wabwoba)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/aspnetcore-conditional-required-attributes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Proton, the ‘Most Complicated Thing’ Imaginable</title>
      <link>https://www.quantamagazine.org/inside-the-proton-the-most-complicated-thing-imaginable-20221019/</link>
      <description>The positively charged particle at the heart of the atom is an object of unspeakable complexity, one that changes its appearance depending on how it is probed. We’ve attempted to connect the proton’s many faces to form the most complete picture yet.</description>
      <author> (By Charlie Wood +1 authorsMerrill ShermanOctober 19, 2022)</author>
      <guid>https://www.quantamagazine.org/inside-the-proton-the-most-complicated-thing-imaginable-20221019/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - reorproject/reor: AI note-taking app that runs models locally.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/reorproject/reor</link>
      <description>AI note-taking app that runs models locally. Contribute to reorproject/reor development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (reorproject)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/reorproject/reor</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATS Aspire container by mtmk &amp;#183; Pull Request #1175 &amp;#183; dotnet/aspire</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/1175</link>
      <description>This PR is an effort to introduce NATS container and client support.
Implemented most of the features as much as I could gather from other implementations. There are a few open tasks as far as I ca...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/1175</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Aspire overview - .NET Aspire</title>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/aspire/get-started/aspire-overview</link>
      <description>Learn about .NET Aspire, an application stack designed to improve the experience of building cloud-native applications.</description>
      <author> (IEvangelist)</author>
      <guid>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/aspire/get-started/aspire-overview</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>announcing freenginx.org</title>
      <link>https://mailman.nginx.org/pipermail/nginx/2024-February/GPXQY27UA5SJJZ2Y6JWTRWJB2TKPTJR7.html</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mailman.nginx.org/pipermail/nginx/2024-February/GPXQY27UA5SJJZ2Y6JWTRWJB2TKPTJR7.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>