<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Exoplanet System</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3103/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3103/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 19:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working on databases from prison: How I got here, part 2.</title>
      <link>https://turso.tech/blog/working-on-databases-from-prison</link>
      <description>I'm very excited to announce that I have recently joined Turso as a software engineer. For many in the field, including myself, getting to work on databases and solve unique challenges with such a talented team would be a dream job, but it is that much more special to me because of my unusual and unlikely circumstances. As difficult as it might be to believe, I am currently incarcerated and I landed this job from my cell in state prison. If you don’t know me, let me tell you more about how I got here.</description>
      <guid>https://turso.tech/blog/working-on-databases-from-prison</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start your own Internet Resiliency Club – Bow Shock Systems Consulting</title>
      <link>https://bowshock.nl/irc/</link>
      <description>Thanks to war, geopolitics, and climate change, Europe will have more
frequent and more severe internet
disruptions
in the very near future. Governments and businesses need to prepare
for catastrophic loss of communications. Unfortunately, the necessary
changes are risky and expensive, which means they won’t do it until a
crisis is already here. However, small
groups of volunteers with a little bit of time and money can provide
crucial initial leadership to bootstrap recovery.</description>
      <guid>https://bowshock.nl/irc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 13:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Standards and Name Changes in the Browser Wars</title>
      <link>https://tim.dierks.org/2014/05/security-standards-and-name-changes-in.html</link>
      <description>The Netscape/Microsoft browser wars in the mid-90's were really vicious and competitive. They really had it out for each other. Netscape had...</description>
      <guid>https://tim.dierks.org/2014/05/security-standards-and-name-changes-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>blog/posts/2025-06-03.md at master · frankmcsherry/blog</title>
      <link>https://github.com/frankmcsherry/blog/blob/master/posts/2025-06-03.md</link>
      <description>Some notes on things I find interesting and important. - frankmcsherry/blog</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/frankmcsherry/blog/blob/master/posts/2025-06-03.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 04:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to modify Starlink Mini to run without the built-in WiFi router – Oleg Kutkov personal blog</title>
      <link>https://olegkutkov.me/2025/06/15/how-to-modify-starlink-mini-to-run-without-the-built-in-wifi-router/</link>
      <description>The Starlink Mini terminal is designed as a compact, all-in-one solution with an integrated Wi-Fi router. While this design is ideal for typical consumer use, certain applications—such as custom networking setups, embedded installations, or power-constrained environments—may benefit from removing the internal router entirely. In this article, I’ll detail the process of physically removing the built-in Wi-Fi router board from the Starlink Mini, allowing the terminal to operate solely via Ethernet and offering greater flexibility for advanced users.</description>
      <guid>https://olegkutkov.me/2025/06/15/how-to-modify-starlink-mini-to-run-without-the-built-in-wifi-router/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 01:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Motivation in Software Engineering - Dev Leader Weekly 98</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/06/14/uncovering-motivation-in-software-engineering-dev-leader-weekly-98</link>
      <description>Welcome to another issue of Dev Leader Weekly! In this issue, I discuss how to breakdown what keeps you engaged as a software engineer.
</description>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/06/14/uncovering-motivation-in-software-engineering-dev-leader-weekly-98</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dnsimg - storing images in txt records</title>
      <link>https://asherfalcon.com/blog/posts/2</link>
      <description>I was intrigued by the idea of storing images in DNS records, and I wanted to test out how effectively images could be stored in DNS records. I've always been interested in TXT records because they seem to be a useful way of storing arbitrary data, and in this blog post I'll discuss how I went from an idea to developing the project into almost a protocol sort of method for storing an image on a domain name.</description>
      <guid>https://asherfalcon.com/blog/posts/2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HR is not your friend</title>
      <link>https://www.miserablyemployed.com/blogs/rants/hr-is-not-your-friend</link>
      <description>This is a public service announcement from your friends at Miserably Employed.  Early in most people’s careers, you’re first exposed to Human Resources when you’re hired. They interview you, onboard you, and get things rolling. You think they are nice, but the truth is that they are paid to pretend to be nice. HR acts </description>
      <guid>https://www.miserablyemployed.com/blogs/rants/hr-is-not-your-friend</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing FIX Data With ClickHouse | BenjaminWootton.com</title>
      <link>https://benjaminwootton.com/insights/analysing-fix-data-with-clickhouse/</link>
      <description>Using ClickHouse String and Array Processing functions to analyse FIX Protocol data.</description>
      <guid>https://benjaminwootton.com/insights/analysing-fix-data-with-clickhouse/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Model Write the Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.dbreunig.com/2025/06/10/let-the-model-write-the-prompt.html</link>
      <description>Notes from a talk I delivered at the 2025 Data + AI Summit, detailing the problem with prompts in your code and how DSPy can make everything better.</description>
      <guid>https://www.dbreunig.com/2025/06/10/let-the-model-write-the-prompt.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing for Longevity</title>
      <link>https://ente.io/blog/longevity/</link>
      <description>How a company like Ente optimizes for longevity</description>
      <guid>https://ente.io/blog/longevity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsing, Not Guessing | Francis Sunday</title>
      <link>https://codehakase.com/shorts/parsing-not-guessing/</link>
      <description>Using ASTs over regex to build a predictable, lightweight, theme-aware Markdown renderer in Go.</description>
      <guid>https://codehakase.com/shorts/parsing-not-guessing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I fight bots in my free time</title>
      <link>https://xeiaso.net/talks/2025/bsdcan-anubis/</link>
      <description>I made Anubis, a lightweight, open-source Web Application Firewall designed to block automated bot attacks without frustrating real users. Anubis uses techniques like TLS fingerprinting and JavaScript proof of work to keep your site safe while staying flexible, fast, and easy to deploy.
</description>
      <guid>https://xeiaso.net/talks/2025/bsdcan-anubis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding .md URLs for Raw Markdown Content in Next.js</title>
      <link>https://www.bengubler.com/posts/2025-06-14-raw-markdown-urls-nextjs</link>
      <description>How to add .md URLs to your Next.js blog to serve raw markdown content, inspired by Vercel's docs.</description>
      <author> (Ben Gubler)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bengubler.com/posts/2025-06-14-raw-markdown-urls-nextjs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things that influence my mental state -Louis-André Labadie</title>
      <link>https://louis-andre.net/journal/what-influences-my-mental-state</link>
      <description>I've been thinking lately about what actually keeps me balanced, as opposed to activities that I think should. I don't want to fall into prescriptive thinking about wellness - meditation is good, exercise is good, social connection is good - without paying attention to what specifically works for a given temperament.</description>
      <guid>https://louis-andre.net/journal/what-influences-my-mental-state</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Live In a Golden Age of Interoperability</title>
      <link>https://borretti.me/article/we-live-in-a-golden-age-of-interoperability</link>
      <description>On the growth of open standards.</description>
      <guid>https://borretti.me/article/we-live-in-a-golden-age-of-interoperability</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your idea probably sucks</title>
      <link>https://kyrylo.org/software/2025/06/15/your-idea-probably-sucks.html</link>
      <description>If you think you have a brilliant idea, I have bad news: your idea probably sucks.</description>
      <guid>https://kyrylo.org/software/2025/06/15/your-idea-probably-sucks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>