<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Creating reusable build scripts with NUKE components</title>
      <link>https://www.erikheemskerk.nl/nuke-build-components/</link>
      <description>How can we take advantage of the latest C# features to create highly reusable build scripts with NUKE?</description>
      <author> (Erik Heemskerk


2021-07-10

• 8 minutes)</author>
      <guid>https://www.erikheemskerk.nl/nuke-build-components/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 09:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spill single-def variable at definition to avoid further spilling by kunalspathak &amp;#183; Pull Request #54345 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/54345</link>
      <description>If a variable is a single-def and it was ever decided to be spilled during register allocation, spill it at its first and only definition so we can skip further spilling throughout the method since...</description>
      <author> (dotnet-issue-labeler)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/54345</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 08:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Minimal APIs with Maria Naggaga | Web Wednesday</title>
      <link>https://socx.ly/3jr7kf</link>
      <description>What is the session about? Minimal apps minimal code!  Express, Django and Lumen provide their developers with the options to build great apps with less code...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://socx.ly/3jr7kf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 08:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>romeovs/creep</title>
      <link>https://github.com/romeovs/creep</link>
      <description>a pretty sweet 4px wide pixel font. Contribute to romeovs/creep development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/romeovs/creep</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 07:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy coding in Oodle Data: the big picture</title>
      <link>https://fgiesen.wordpress.com/2021/07/09/entropy-coding-in-oodle-data-the-big-picture/</link>
      <description>April 26, 2016 was the release date of Oodle 2.1.5 which introduced Kraken, so it celebrated its 5-year anniversary recently. A few months later we launched Selkie and Mermaid, which were already d…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fgiesen.wordpress.com/2021/07/09/entropy-coding-in-oodle-data-the-big-picture/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 05:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Audio is Dead | Non</title>
      <link>https://non.tuxfamily.org/wiki/2021-02-07%20Linux%20Audio%20is%20Dead</link>
      <description>In early 2020, most of the world was concerned with matters of great import, myself included. But three men, Filipe Coelho, David Runge, and Nils Hilbrect had more trivial things on their minds. At this time they came to me, not announcing themselves as a formal alliance, but pretending to be separate, disconnected parties suddenly showing up all at once. Each one had a list of demands for changes that I should make to NSM. I responded politely to each of these demands in turn, inquiring about why they believed them to be necessary, important, or appropriate, and I offered detailed explanations as to how they were not. They refused to participate in a discourse and reiterated their demands. I asked them why, if these trivial matters were so important to them, did they come to me with demands instead of patches to contribute? They became irate and threatened to fork my project. But of course, because they apparently lacked either the skill or the intention to make the changes themselves (as contributions), I didn&amp;#39;t take this threat seriously, as creating a fork would require them to actually do something.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://non.tuxfamily.org/wiki/2021-02-07%20Linux%20Audio%20is%20Dead</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 03:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Collection of 2020 Recorded Presentations</title>
      <link>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2021/07/a-collection-of-2020-recorded.html</link>
      <description>   2020 was &amp;quot;interesting&amp;quot;. One good thing that came out of it is that I had the   chance to speak remotely for some user groups and conferen...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2021/07/a-collection-of-2020-recorded.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 01:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn functional programming with JavaScript through this friendly, gentle introduction course to the functional programming paradigm with Anjana Vakil.</title>
      <link>https://frontendmasters.com/courses/functional-first-steps/</link>
      <description>Learn core functional JavaScript programming techniques by coding everything with pure functions, learning recursion, higher-order functions, closures, currying, and function composition. Also, learn how immutable data is essential for functional programming.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://frontendmasters.com/courses/functional-first-steps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Richard Lander on the New .NET Platform - Episode 148</title>
      <link>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/richard-lander-on-the-new-net-platform-episode-148</link>
      <description>Richard is a Principal Program Manager on the .NET Core team at Microsoft. He&amp;#39;s been with Microsoft for a total of 21 years, 18 of which have been with the .NET team (since 2003 when the codename was Whidbey!) Richard is truly a mover and shaker when it comes to pushing the .NET platform forward! Currently, he’s working on runtime features and performance, CLI experience, docker container experience, ARM32 and ARM64 support, IoT/GPIO/PWM support, blogging and customer engagement, and speaking at conferences. He&amp;#39;s also part of the design team that defines new .NET runtime capabilities and features. And in his spare time, he enjoys British rock and Doctor Who! &amp;amp;nbsp; A lot has changed since Richard was last on the show! In this episode, he is here to discuss all of the changes to the new .NET platform, how he’s continuing to push the .NET platform forward together with his team, the current state-of-the-art tools and techniques in the .NET IoT space and .NET applications, exciting developments with his current .NET blog series on DevBlogs.Microsoft.com, and much more! &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [:14] About The Azure DevOps Podcast, Clear Measure, the new podcast Architect Tips, and Jeffrey’s offer to speak at virtual user groups. [1:23] About today’s episode with Richard Lander! [2:07] Jeffrey welcomes Richard Lander back to the podcast. [2:24] Richard shares what has changed on his team in the last two years and what they have been recently up to. [4:19] Richard shares about his role with the .NET team and what he mainly works on. [5:54] Richard’s vision and goals with the new .NET blog series. [7:56] About the various topics Richard has covered thus far with his blog series and a sneak preview of some upcoming blog topics he will be covering. [8:42] Richard shares what he and his team are doing on the front of platform OS enablement and Apple Silicon. [13:04] Jeffrey and Richard discuss Microsoft’s focus on backwards compatibility. [14:44] The current state-of-the-art in the .NET IoT space. [18:51] Have the .NET and IoT teams had conversations around Terminal.Gui? [19:20] A word from Azure DevOps Podcast’s sponsor: Clear Measure. [21:00] What is the current method with IoT devices? Are there any built-in testing capabilities? [24:19] Richard shares what the current state-of-the-art is for those doing regular .NET applications. [29:22] If a developer just deploys to App Service, are they using Azure containers under the covers regardless? [30:50] Richard shares his predictions on what he sees as being the most general-purpose runtime (AKS, App Service, ACI, etc.) in Azure for regular Blazor applications that developers are starting to build. [34:40] Jeffrey and Richard reflect on why it is such an interesting and exciting time to be a developer. [35:45] Does .NET and C# have the fastest mainstream execution? [39:48] Jeffrey thanks Richard for joining the podcast. &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:  — New video podcast!   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!  — Click here to download the .NET DevOps for Azure ebook!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!                  &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/richard-lander-on-the-new-net-platform-episode-148</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpriteStack.io</title>
      <link>https://spritestack.io/</link>
      <description>3D pixelart editor based on sprite stacking technique.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://spritestack.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 23:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Still Recommend that Developers Learn Elm</title>
      <link>https://spin.atomicobject.com/2021/07/07/recommend-learning-elm/</link>
      <description>Elm has something for everyone to learn. Its principles are nearly universally applicable to other development environments.</description>
      <author> (By: Andy Peterson)</author>
      <guid>https://spin.atomicobject.com/2021/07/07/recommend-learning-elm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How We Found Our First 30 Clients</title>
      <link>https://www.karllhughes.com/posts/journey-to-30</link>
      <description>It’s been less than a year since I started Draft.dev and we’ve already built up a roster of 32 clients, over 60 freelance writers, and a full-time ...</description>
      <author> (https://www.karllhughes.com)</author>
      <guid>https://www.karllhughes.com/posts/journey-to-30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 22:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>r/crypto - My breakdown on Partition Oracle Attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/crypto/comments/n17k3t/my_breakdown_on_partition_oracle_attacks/</link>
      <description>34 votes and 15 comments so far on Reddit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/crypto/comments/n17k3t/my_breakdown_on_partition_oracle_attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 22:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Validate Your Startup Idea in One Day for $0</title>
      <link>https://blog.wobaka.com/how-to-validate-your-startup-idea-in-one-day/</link>
      <description>So, you&amp;#39;ve got a brand new idea for a startup and are looking to validate it to see if anyone is interested in your new thing? Sounds good! This will let you know how the market responds to it and give you valuable information and fuel to keep going and</description>
      <author> (Fredrik)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.wobaka.com/how-to-validate-your-startup-idea-in-one-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 22:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto and Monetization</title>
      <link>https://www.tiagosada.com/notes/monetization</link>
      <description>Don’t underestimate the ability of crypto protocols and clients to make money. One of the big promises of crypto is that it will significantly lower the fees of financial services by removing middlemen, enabling competition, and giving users a voice on the prices themselves. No more shelling out 3-10% to our payment processor overlords. Perhaps counterintuitively, even if this promise is fulfilled, many crypto protocols and clients will become incredible businesses...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiagosada.com/notes/monetization</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 22:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-platform Awesome with Shiny 2.0 | The Xamarin Show</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XEOw4Qe_fQk</link>
      <description>Today, James is joined by Allan Ritchie, Microsoft MVP, who shows off the latest version of his cross-platform library Shiny.&amp;#160;Shiny is a cross platform frame...</description>
      <author> (Tobias Hoppenthaler
  
  
  
    Tobias Hoppenthaler
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XEOw4Qe_fQk</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 21:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java on VS Code Plans: Improve Inner Loop, Security, Remote Development &amp;amp; More -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/07/09/vscode-java-june21.aspx</link>
      <description>The regular monthly update to Java tooling on Visual Studio Code is light on new features but does provide a peek into future plans, which include improving the fundamental inner loop experience, security, remote development and much more.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel07/09/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/07/09/vscode-java-june21.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 21:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ‘mirror’ fabric can cool wearers by nearly 5&amp;#176;C</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2021/07/new-mirror-fabric-can-cool-wearers-nearly-5-c</link>
      <description>Synthetic material emits infrared radiation, cooling the body</description>
      <author> (By Alex ViverosJul. 8, 2021 , 2:10 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2021/07/new-mirror-fabric-can-cool-wearers-nearly-5-c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 19:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do patents kill innovation? The US patent office is asking.</title>
      <link>https://www.eenewseurope.com/news/do-patents-kill-innovation-us-patent-office-asking</link>
      <description>The US Patent Office is looking at the impact of patents on areas such as quantum computing, AI and networking</description>
      <author> (July 09, 2021						 //
						
							By  Nick Flaherty)</author>
      <guid>https://www.eenewseurope.com/news/do-patents-kill-innovation-us-patent-office-asking</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 19:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Scanning C++ with GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/code-scanning-with-github-actions/</link>
      <description>Last year, GitHub released code scanning, which enables developers to incorporate security checks into their CI/CD environment and developer workflow. This post demonstrates the basics of using CodeQL, the analysis engine behind code scanning, with GitHub Actions. What is CodeQL? CodeQL is an analysis engine that automates security checks by running queries against a database generated from your codebase.</description>
      <author> (Nick Uhlenhuth)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/code-scanning-with-github-actions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 18:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMNB answers all your questions about NFTs</title>
      <link>https://russianmachineneverbreaks.com/2021/07/09/rmnb-answers-all-your-questions-about-nfts/</link>
      <description>This week the Washington Capitals announced they would debut their very first collection of NFTs, prompting some questions such as: what?, huh?, and um, why? Here are some answers. What is an NFT? An NFT is a non-fungible token. What?...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://russianmachineneverbreaks.com/2021/07/09/rmnb-answers-all-your-questions-about-nfts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 17:07:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Arti, a pure-Rust Tor implementation | Tor Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.torproject.org/announcing-arti</link>
      <description>Greetings!
Today I&amp;#39;m happy to announce a new era in Tor implementation.
Over the past year or so, we&amp;#39;ve been working on &amp;quot;Arti&amp;quot;, a project to rewrite Tor in Rust. Thanks to funding from Zcash Open Major Grants (ZOMG), we can finally put the Arti project up in our priorities list, and devote more time to it.
Below I&amp;#39;ll talk about why we&amp;#39;re doing this project, what it means for Tor users and operators, where it&amp;#39;s going in the future, and how people can help.</description>
      <author> (by nickm | July 08, 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.torproject.org/announcing-arti</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 16:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s New in .NET for Apache Spark v1.1.1</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1le0E52aoFc</link>
      <description>.NET for Apache Spark empowers .NET developers to participate in the world of big data analytics. In this episode, Jeremy chats with Michael Rys to discuss s...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •
  
  
    
      14K views
    
      1 year ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1le0E52aoFc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 15:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work offloading and controlled parallelism</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/194146-A/work-offloading-and-controlled-parallelism?Key=67a22edd-ed24-404e-8067-ff317d9e4341</link>
      <description>For a database engine, controlling the amount of work that is being executed is a very important factor for the stability of the system. If we can’t control ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/194146-A/work-offloading-and-controlled-parallelism?Key=67a22edd-ed24-404e-8067-ff317d9e4341</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 15:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does 100% mean in CSS?</title>
      <link>https://wattenberger.com/blog/css-percents</link>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the CSS units I use most is the wonderful &amp;lt;b&amp;gt;%&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; — so handy for positioning elements on the page.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unfortunately, the rules aren’t exactly straightforward. One question I’m always asking myself is: Percent of what?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wattenberger.com/blog/css-percents</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 15:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the perils of holding a lock across a coroutine suspension point, part 3: Solutions</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210709-00/?p=105425</link>
      <description>So far, we’ve been looking at the horrible things that can happen if you hold a lock across a coroutine suspension point. What can we do to avoid the problem? For reference, here’s the code in question: IAsyncAction MyObject::RunOneAsync() {  std::lock_guard guard(m_mutex);</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210709-00/?p=105425</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 15:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ban Eproctoring</title>
      <link>https://www.baneproctoring.com/#letter</link>
      <description>Digital and human rights groups are calling on schools to end the use of invasive eproctoring apps.</description>
      <author> (Fight for the Future)</author>
      <guid>https://www.baneproctoring.com/#letter</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 14:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How The Chronicle is trying to malign Sci-Hub</title>
      <link>https://engineuring.wordpress.com/2021/07/09/how-the-chronicle-is-trying-to-malign-sci-hub/</link>
      <description>A new article was published in The Chronicle about me running Sci-Hub, a project dedicated to providing free access to academic journals all over the world. Their goal is to present Sci-Hub and its…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://engineuring.wordpress.com/2021/07/09/how-the-chronicle-is-trying-to-malign-sci-hub/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 14:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The hidden cost of Exceptions in .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2f2elFRmeLE</link>
      <description>Subscribe: http://bit.ly/ChapsasSubBecome a Patreon and get source code access: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsasHello everybody I&amp;#39;m Nick and in this video...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2f2elFRmeLE</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 13:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Maze Weekly #84 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-84/</link>
      <description>Issue #84 of the Code Maze weekly. Check out what’s new this week and enjoy the read. .NET and C# How&amp;#160;Does the StringBuilder Work in .NET? (Part 1) [www.stevejgordon.co.uk] Properly understanding and using the StringBuilder class is the topic of this series of articles by Steve Gordon. If you’re not sure when you should use […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-84/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 13:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streambus, Video Podcasting over RSS</title>
      <link>https://streambus.com/</link>
      <description>When you publish with Streambus, you create a website, on your own domain name. Reach your audience over RSS on the podcast apps they already have on their phone.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://streambus.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 13:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDA Expired - let&amp;#39;s spill the beans on a weird startup</title>
      <link>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2021/07/nda-expired-lets-spill-the-beans-on-a-weird-startup/</link>
      <description>Many moons ago, when I was very young and you were even younger… London was in full bloom of tech-startups. I was running my own consultancy. Dashing from business to business, trying to pick…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2021/07/nda-expired-lets-spill-the-beans-on-a-weird-startup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 12:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>