<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>What does culturally responsive teaching mean in an online environment?</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7nYMoAs98Es</link>
      <description>Culturally responsive teaching (CRT) is an instructional approach that seeks to ensure academic success while developing students' sense of culture and social-political awareness. CRT allows students to see themselves in the curriculum and assignments provided by the teacher. In the online and traditional classroom, CRT provides opportunities for students to learn how to value their culture. During this time in America, it is especially important for students to have opportunities to express themselves while using online technology.
---
Dr. Tressa Matthews
Clever Math LLC , Co-Founder
Dr. Tressa Matthews has been teaching math to middle and high school students for 18 years. She has a Bachelor's in Industrial and Operations Engineering from the University of Michigan. After two years in corporate America, she decided to pursue her passion for secondary mathematics. After earning a Masters and Doctorate in Education, Dr. Matthews co-founded Clever Math to provide online educational services for students and parents. She has a passion for building supportive classroom environments for African-American students which became the basis for her doctoral research.

Dr.  Jennifer Banks
Clever Math, LLC Co-Founder
Jennifer D. Banks, Ph.D. is currently the Mathematics and Science Coordinator for Washtenaw County. For nearly 20 years, Dr. Banks has served as a teacher and instructional leader at various levels. Jennifer is passionate about empowering educators and learners, to ensure that all students have equitable access and opportunities to learn and engage in high-quality rigorous mathematics. Over the past ten years, she has intently worked to expand K-12 educators' understanding of culturally responsive instruction, specifically in the area of mathematics. Dr. Banks holds a bachelors' Industrial and Operations Engineer and worked in the corporate sector for 4 years. She has been recognized by various community organizations for her work in expanding access to STEM education, including the Rhonda Walker Foundation and DAPCEP. She currently serves on the Michigan Early Mathematics Taskforce and is a lecturer for the University of Michigan. Furthermore, she is the Co-Founder of Clever Math, LLC.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7nYMoAs98Es</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shukri Abdullahi - Through Programming I became a better Artist</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJJcMpsYWUI</link>
      <description>Code is my new favorite artistic medium. Creating art was once the only activity that put me in a flow state that was until I started coding. Programming like art is full of processes, speed bumps, errors, eustress, and joy. My skills as an artist have proven to be an asset in programming. While programming has cultivated artistic improvements.

What: More artists should learn to code.
Why: You’re skills as an artist are an asset in the programming world and vice versa programming can cultivate artistic improvements.
How: Personal Anecdote detailing skills.
---
Shukri Abdullahi is a Self-Taught Programmer and Multi-disciplinary Artist based in New York.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJJcMpsYWUI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Us, Without Us: Addressing Tech’s Shortcomings in Creating Equity for Black People</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qzc6D8NZo-4</link>
      <description>Many consider technology to be the “great equalizer”, but it’s evident that Black people are not benefiting at the same rates as others. This session will discuss how the forces that limit Black people’s ability to navigate the physical also prevent us from exerting agency via the digital. Together, we’ll discuss the ways that anti-Blackness is replicated in technology, the discrepancies faced by Black communities due to the digital divide, and the changes required for us to have a more equitable future. Because we can never fully benefit if technology continues to be made for us, without us.
---
Jacqueline Gibson
Software Engineer focusing on accessibility at Microsoft

Jacqueline is a Digital Equity Advocate &amp; Software Engineer building change from the code up. She's interested in leveraging technology for social good, particularly identifying ways in which current technology maintains social inequities and working to eliminate these biases. She strives to understand what is necessary to create systems that everyone, regardless of ability, can use with ease.

She graduated with dual degrees in Computer Science and African &amp; African Diaspora Studies from the University of Texas at Austin. She's currently developing tools to create accessible applications for Android, Windows, and web as part of Microsoft's Accessibility Insights team.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qzc6D8NZo-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSS Box</title>
      <link>https://rssbox.herokuapp.com/</link>
      <description>Get RSS feeds for services</description>
      <author> (Stefan Sundin)</author>
      <guid>https://rssbox.herokuapp.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawood Iddris - The future of tech and how to keep in touch while it evolves</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_eJzPgThuM8</link>
      <description>Building and leading communities, one of the common pitfall many people fall in whiles trying to gain grounds in technology has to do with learning every new thing they hear of. It is quite clear that these people think they are doing the right thing until they realize years have passed by and yet they can't build a single project with their knowledge gained. As several people share their stories with me about the same problem, I notice I was in their shoes for my first two years career. In this session, we will address how people who find their self in this category can progress while staying up to date with all new technologies.
---
Dawoodiddris is a software developer, passionately creating products and changing lives with his soft and technical skills by training others in event, workshops and providing platforms for coders to think beyond the limit.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_eJzPgThuM8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashley Janelle - Why You're Not Landing That UX Role</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PA1Rho75qzQ</link>
      <description>As a UX Coach, the question I am asked the most is "How do I actually land that UX role?". While the question is broad, I've identified a few areas where aspiring UX Designers really struggle getting their foot in the door at companies of their choice. In my talk, attendees will walk away being able to not only identify their key problem areas, but have action items around overcoming those obstacles to land their dream role.
---
As a seasoned User Experience and User Interface Designer, Ashley Janelle focuses on designing customer centered experiences that target her users everyday challenges. At Caterpillar Inc., Ashley taps into user needs while designing solutions that allow them to save time, money, and increase their productivity.

As a UX coach and course creator, she’s developed an online course, “Learn UX Online in 16 Weeks” to help aspiring UX designers go from beginner to experienced UX Designers to land jobs at top companies. Using her UX expertise and passion for working with people, Ashley’s not only helped others land their dream roles, but build the confidence to become successful UX Designers.


https://www.ashleyjanelle.com</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PA1Rho75qzQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorting and information theory</title>
      <link>https://guille.site/sorting-bounds.html</link>
      <description>Category: math</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://guille.site/sorting-bounds.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse-engineering and comparing two Game Boy audio amplifier chips</title>
      <link>http://www.righto.com/2020/06/reverse-engineering-and-comparing-two.html</link>
      <description>  The Nintendo Game Boy contains an audio amplifier chip for sound through a speaker or headphones. In this post, I reverse-engineer this ch...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.righto.com/2020/06/reverse-engineering-and-comparing-two.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head Up, Head Down</title>
      <link>https://martinrue.com/head-up-head-down/</link>
      <description>There are few things more enjoyable to me than the mental solitude that hand-delivers interesting shower thoughts, or that let’s me sit in a bustling coffee shop contemplating life.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martinrue.com/head-up-head-down/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Advantage of the App Store That’s Gone</title>
      <link>https://inessential.com/2020/06/20/one_advantage_of_the_app_store_thats_gon</link>
      <description>The best part of the App Store, years ago, from this developer’s point of view, was that it was easy to charge money for an app. No need to set up a system — just choose the price, and Apple takes care of everything. So easy!</description>
      <author> (by Brent Simmons)</author>
      <guid>https://inessential.com/2020/06/20/one_advantage_of_the_app_store_thats_gon</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kara Swisher: ‘Is It Finally Hammer Time for Apple and Its App Store?’</title>
      <link>https://daringfireball.net/linked/2020/06/19/swisher-app-store-hey</link>
      <description>Link to: https://www.nytimes.com/2020/06/19/opinion/apple-app-store-hey.html</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://daringfireball.net/linked/2020/06/19/swisher-app-store-hey</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proofs and computation with trees</title>
      <link>https://bor0.wordpress.com/2020/06/20/proofs-and-computation-with-trees/</link>
      <description>In this post, I will make the analogy between trees and proofs and computation. Lately (after a long pause), I started reading Logical Foundations again and started re-doing the exercises for the l…</description>
      <author> (Boro Sitnikovski)</author>
      <guid>https://bor0.wordpress.com/2020/06/20/proofs-and-computation-with-trees/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons Learned: Giving Feedback as an Engineering Manager</title>
      <link>http://alexeymk.com/2020/06/20/lessons-learned-in-giving-feedback-as-an-engineering-manager.html</link>
      <description>“Alexey, do you feel the points you bring up during our post-mortems are productive?” my tech lead asked at our 1:1.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://alexeymk.com/2020/06/20/lessons-learned-in-giving-feedback-as-an-engineering-manager.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A NVIDIA Engineer In His Spare Time Wrote A Vulkan Driver That Works On Older Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RPi-VK-Driver</link>
      <description>Phoronix is the leading technology website for Linux hardware reviews, open-source news, Linux benchmarks, open-source benchmarks, and computer hardware tests.</description>
      <author> (Written by Michael Larabel in Vulkan on 20 June 2020 at 08:45 AM EDT. 21 Comments)</author>
      <guid>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RPi-VK-Driver</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 22:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Dennis Ritchie’s Lost Dissertation - CHM</title>
      <link>https://computerhistory.org/blog/discovering-dennis-ritchies-lost-dissertation/</link>
      <description>Until recently, across a half-century perhaps fewer than a dozen people had ever had the opportunity to read Dennis Ritchie’s dissertation—the intellectual and biographical fork-in-the-road separating an academic career in computer science from the one at Bell Labs leading to C and Unix. Why?</description>
      <author> (David C. Brock)</author>
      <guid>https://computerhistory.org/blog/discovering-dennis-ritchies-lost-dissertation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 20:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 2</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mCrhSBCju4E</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mCrhSBCju4E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 18:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual:  Steve Collins - .NET Core Dependency Injection – The Booster Jab</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Milton-Keynes-NET-Meetup-Group/events/271371131/</link>
      <description>Tue, Jul 14, 2020, 7:00 PM: Hello MK.NET folks,We're proud to present another virtual MK .NET meetup for July;As before, we'll be hosting on Zoom.We're excited to be joined by Steve Collins who will b</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/Milton-Keynes-NET-Meetup-Group/events/271371131/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 1</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ysmejeF5umg</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ysmejeF5umg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bug #1463112 “Cat sitting on keyboard crashes lightdm” : Bugs : Unity</title>
      <link>https://bugs.launchpad.net/unity/+bug/1463112</link>
      <description>14.04, locked screen to go to lunch, upon return from lunch cat was sitting on keyboard, login screen was frozen &amp; unresponsive.

To replicate:  In unity hit ctrl-alt-l, place keyboard on chair.  Sit on keyboard.  

Resolution: Switched to virtual terminal, restarted lightdm, lost all open windows in X session.

What should have happened: lightdm not becoming unresponsive.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bugs.launchpad.net/unity/+bug/1463112</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 15:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair Programming - Dan Clarke</title>
      <link>https://www.danclarke.com/2020-pair-programming</link>
      <description>20 June 2020</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.danclarke.com/2020-pair-programming</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 14:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 1</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2-4Dvc9WO9E</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2-4Dvc9WO9E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 06:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud to be |_____|</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@martin_29969/proud-to-be-e19375a0bd89</link>
      <description>If someone you knew exclaimed “I’m proud to be French!”, what would be your first thought? The Louvre? French cuisine? The Eiffel Tower…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@martin_29969)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@martin_29969/proud-to-be-e19375a0bd89</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 05:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The live coders conference</title>
      <link>https://atndesign.github.io/Live-coders-conference/</link>
      <description>An online-only conference put on by The Live Coders team on Twitch! You may be wondering who we are! We are The Live Coders, an outgoing and enthusiastic group of friendly channels that write code, teach about technology, and promote the technical community.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://atndesign.github.io/Live-coders-conference/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 05:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 2</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OLWlY3j-u0M</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OLWlY3j-u0M</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 05:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Queer Living: A history of DIY culture in the Black LBGT+ community</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UV3uPtzDoyA</link>
      <description>What is DIY culture? How does DIY culture intertwine with the Black LGBT+ culture? Get these questions answered, and learn a few easy beginner DIY tutorials to do on t-shirts! No previous experience required!
---
Harold studied computer science at the University of Texas at Austin. He's started Black Queer Living, a youtube channel dedicated to teaching life skills 101, centering queer and trans* people of color: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCx3ihWKRcPrTDdhk87M2yeg</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UV3uPtzDoyA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What they don't teach you about fundraising as a Black Founder</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=leetllfwNTI</link>
      <description>useneu.com has made 3 attempts at raising capital for our business. Each attempt brought with it some valuable, and often unintuitive, lessons about the fundraising process. Join me as I recount our fundraising experiences and the main lessons learned after each one. Should you ever need to fundraise, you'll know the key DOs and DONTs.
---
Claudius Mbemba was born in Cameroon, Africa to hard-working blue-collar parents who taught him the value of hard work, being a self-starter, and always learning. Immigrating to the US at the age of 7, Claudius saw how technology vastly improved the lives of Americans. It was then his love for technology was born. Following high school, Claudius pursued his Bachelors Degree in Computer Science while on the Varsity Football team at The Ohio State University. Upon completing his degree he accepted employment at Microsoft in Seattle, WA where he worked as a Software Engineer, largely focusing his time on Voice, Mobile, Cloud, Bots, DevOps, ML/AI, &amp; Blockchain. Claudius is currently CTO of Neu Inc, a startup building a marketplace that provides automated hotel-grade turnovers for Airbnb/vacation rentals.

Learn more about Claudius on his website: www.claudiusmbemba.com</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=leetllfwNTI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowerment to the People! What You Need to Know about Black People, Disability, and Accessibility</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2W7QCYzOn_U</link>
      <description>About one fifth (20%) of the global population lives with disabilities.​ According to the 2017 American Community Survey, 13.6 percent of Black and African Americans have a disability. Further, the unemployment rate for people with disabilities is almost double of other people, and the people with disabilities who are employed have lower earnings, in general.

This means we have an opportunity and a duty to empower Black people with technology. One of the most powerful ways we can do this is to make our messaging accessible—no matter the platform or media.

While many of us have heard that accessibility is important, we seldom hear about how to implement it in our everyday work. Angela will discuss how people in every discipline—including PMs, content writers, designers, engineers, and more—can do so and further amplify the voices of Black people.
---
Angela Hooker is a Senior Accessibility Program Manager at Microsoft, where she's built a center of expertise for accessibility, user experience, and universal design. She's brought her web management, development, design, accessibility, and editorial and content management expertise to the government and private sector for over 20 years.

Angela also advocates for role-based accessibility and believes that teaching people how to incorporate principles of accessibility in their everyday work creates a sustainable program and produces the most accessible user experiences. Angela speaks on and writes about accessibility, disability, user experience, and plain language.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2W7QCYzOn_U</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combatting Bias in ML</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NIxUAlmnqz0</link>
      <description>In this talk I cover how to see the bias in your data and machine learning models. By giving examples from recent research on biased facial recognition systems as well as cutting edge explainability algorithms, attendees can expect clarification on what bias means in machine learning.
---
Ayodele Odubela is a Data Scientist working on driver risk mitigation at SambaSafety in Denver, CO. Previously she earned her Master's degree in Data Science after transitioning to tech from social media marketing. She's created algorithms that predict consumer segment movement, goals in hockey, and the location of firearms using radio frequency sensors.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NIxUAlmnqz0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Combat To Code  How Vets Who Code Trained Over 250 veterans how to Code and Get Jobs For Free</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CESi0jv4B_E</link>
      <description>A detailed origin story of how I became known as the Web's Captain America and how Vets Who Code trains veterans for free. We will go over how we came to be, how we train our troops, our teams and how you can help us continue our mission.

Jerome Hardaway is a Google Developer Expert (Web) UI/UX engineer, Dev Advocate and Geek At Arms (Founder and Executive Director) of Vets Who Code, a 501(c)3 veteran-led charitable non-profit dedicated to filling the nation’s technical skills gap with early-stage transitioning veterans and military spouses through remote software development training.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CESi0jv4B_E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving Back to Tech without Burnout</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dOmzzo0vTUI</link>
      <description>You did it! You’re a Software Engineer! After many hours of studying and learning difficult concepts, you made it through. Now you want to volunteer and give back your tech skills to a needed cause. Exciting, right? Wait…here’s a few tips to avoid giver burnout before you start.

In this talk, Mo will discuss ways tech givers can continue to volunteer without spreading themselves too thin. Tips will include: how do you give your talent without depleting your energy, choosing volunteer opportunities or open source projects with great impact, and how to say no.
---
Mo Hampton is a Software Engineer at GDIT. Her passion for web application development led her to the Open Source community to learn full-stack JavaScript. When not thriving off of coffee, meditation or travel, she builds cost-effective, user-friendly business applications.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dOmzzo0vTUI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journaling as a Dev</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UYiAlmTr_dA</link>
      <description>Are you working with impact and purpose? Are you solidly attuned on what you're doing month-to-month with your role? How difficult is it for you to track your accomplishments at work? If any of these questions lead to uncertain answers, then you should learn what it means to journal professionally as a dev. This talk will cover my exploration into journaling and its application to tracking my goals and progress as a software engineer. I will discuss how to set up your journal for any goals and how to score on your performance review!
-----
Brittney is a software engineer who loves a good cup of tea. In her spare time, she draws illustrations for teaNotes.dev on Instagram. Brittney strives to connect with folks who geek out over code with hopes to contribute to a friendly and inviting tech community.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UYiAlmTr_dA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keynote: The Journey To Inclusive Innovation Incubator (In3DC)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8cgPjeVhlEI</link>
      <description>How we ended up building an innovation space for black and underrepresented communities. Our focus on tech enabled startups and small business is driven by our roots in the development firm Clearly Innovative Inc, mobile partners for NMAAHC.
---
Aaron Saunders CEO Inclusive Innovation Incubator, Clearly Innovative, 30 years in technology /entrepreneurship space as developer, manager, founder and CEO</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8cgPjeVhlEI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ideal Community Model:  Lessons Learned</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d0QRQWhej-s</link>
      <description>There are many ways to push your career to a point it takes a great turn, but I found out in 2017 that community participation is a must. Community involvement can be anything from Open Source Contributions, Writing articles, answering questions on social media/StackOverflow to speaking at conferences. Participation in your community will expand your network.

By attending small meetups or having conversations in slack channels will lead you to meet new people in your industry. Sharing will increase your visibility in the ecosystem by Founders, people of related skill sets, recruiters, and more.

There isn’t just one way to share your expertise with your community. Open Source Contributions isn't just code, you can write articles/documentation about the product you would like to contribute to about your experiences or speak at conferences. Collaboration helps you to be seen as a leader in your community. You can collaborate with others in your network by mentoring, organizing an event, or working together on a personal project/ideas

I learned most of the things I know today about the community the hard way because I never saw it as anything important, and all I cared about was just write the code and today I am a Senior Developer Advocate at Fleek, and also the lead organizer of some major communities in Africa which included, unStack, Developers Circles Lagos from Facebook, Open Source Community Africa, NaijaHacks, and AfricaHacks.

Key Takeaways:

1) Attendees will learn how to build a community on their own
2) Attendees will learn how open-source works in a community
3) Attendees will learn how to contribute to ideas to a community

----------------

Shodipo Ayomide is a Developer Advocate, Engineer, and Occasional Designer, who also contributes to a lot of open-source projects over on GitHub, he also runs some major communities like unStack, Developers Circles Lagos from Facebook, Open Source Community Africa and NaijaHacks driving Nigeria &amp; Africa forward in Technology, he is an international speaker who has spoken at a lot of conferences over time in various locations, in his free time he loves to, Read, See a Movie and Occasionally play video games, Loves Travelling and Family.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d0QRQWhej-s</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking into Tech  From the Trenches</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2N5fI5j-IIs</link>
      <description>Bottom Line: Grit is required from historically underrepresented groups to change the demographic of Software Engineers and Developers. This talk will share my personal obstacles from a non-traditional career path (Veteran, women of color, mother and coding bootcamp graduate) to a Software Engineer.

The intent is to encourage passionate developers who are members of historically underrepresented groups, but not limited to new developers from non-tech industries, developers starting second careers, re-entering the workforce, and those who have attended coding bootcamps, to build and support a community in Open Source.
---
Mo Hampton is a Software Engineer at GDIT. Her passion for web application development led her to the Open Source community to learn full-stack JavaScript. When not thriving off of coffee, meditation or travel, she builds cost-effective, user-friendly business applications.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2N5fI5j-IIs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your next open source contribution</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UzI2Wdl3arE</link>
      <description>Today Open Source is ubiquitous and comprises nearly 80% – 90% of the code in a “typical” application. There is a need to use Open Source to stay competitive, but what about the need to use open source to advance your career?

In this talk, I will talk through actionable ways to make open-source contributions to grow your career.
---
Brian Douglas is a Developer Advocate at GitHub where he works on increasing use of the GitHub API by iterating on the onboarding process and helping users with evergreen technical content.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UzI2Wdl3arE</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowered By Imposter Syndrome</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qheqnbhldI8</link>
      <description>Imposter syndrome is something that the industry continues to represent as a negative. My take on this as a black woman in tech is we need to turn all of our disadvantages into growth opportunities. Adding structure to our learning path is the best way of removing the negative image of feeling like an imposter and allows us to flourish.
---
Valerie Phoenix is a Founder &amp; CEO at Tech By Choice and a Senior Software Engineer at Mastery Logistics. She holds a BS in Psychology &amp; Art. Valerie is passionate about creating secure human-centered digital experiences. As a successful self-taught developer, Valerie started Tech By Choice to give back to the community that helped her succeed.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qheqnbhldI8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 04:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth History</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/hh6i_SjfCYI</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/hh6i_SjfCYI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:41:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth History</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hh6i_SjfCYI</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hh6i_SjfCYI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:41:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Juneteenth – GenX Jamerican</title>
      <link>https://www.genxjamerican.com/2020/06/19/my-first-juneteenth/</link>
      <description>Today marks the date in 1865 when General Gordon Granger read General Order 3 to the people of Galveston Bay, Texas, informing the enslaved there and in all of Texas of freedom that had been rightfully theirs two years earlier.  That was essentially the full extent of my understanding of Juneteenth until recently, so I’ve taken the additional time off my employer gave us today to dig a bit deeper.  Juneteenth.com, the Wikipedia entry about Juneteenth, and this explainer by Dr. Henry Louis Gates, Jr. have been my starting points.  I shared these links with my direct reports as well as my co-workers before our 2PM close today, and was heartened by how generously they were received.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.genxjamerican.com/2020/06/19/my-first-juneteenth/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workshop: Docker and Kubernetes - 1/2 - NDC Melbourne 2020</title>
      <link>https://ndcmelbourne.com/talk/workshop-docker-and-kubernetes-1-4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;Module 1/4&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
Containers such as Docker and container orchestration such as Kubernetes are hot topics right now, if you’re working on microservice architectures it very likely you’ll be looking at these technologies as they are a natural fit for microservices. Containers are also a great way of dealing with legacy applications and allowing you to use modern deployment techniques for these older applications.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ndcmelbourne.com/talk/workshop-docker-and-kubernetes-1-4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home : Hypothesis</title>
      <link>https://web.hypothes.is/</link>
      <description>Homedwhly2020-06-19T15:25:55-07:00</description>
      <author> (dwhly)</author>
      <guid>https://web.hypothes.is/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emancipation Statue - Barbados Pocket Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.barbadospocketguide.com/our-island-barbados/monuments/emancipation-statue.html</link>
      <description>Welcome to the Barbados Pocket Guide, a comprehensive source of information about our island, it's people, culture and life in general.</description>
      <author> (Gloria)</author>
      <guid>https://www.barbadospocketguide.com/our-island-barbados/monuments/emancipation-statue.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 01:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>