<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>When is a product &amp;quot;done&amp;quot; and what do you do next?</title>
      <link>https://kashishhora.com/when-is-a-product-done-and-what-do-you-do-next/</link>
      <description>Some teams continue building new features and improvements to products without stepping back and considering whether it makes sense to stop When is a product considered good enough or done? And what should a team do once it’s done? In this post I share a common framework I use to help answer this question and evaluate relevant tradeoffs.</description>
      <author> (Kashish Hora)</author>
      <guid>https://kashishhora.com/when-is-a-product-done-and-what-do-you-do-next/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style scoping versus shadow DOM: which is fastest?</title>
      <link>https://nolanlawson.com/2022/06/22/style-scoping-versus-shadow-dom-which-is-fastest/</link>
      <description>Last year, I asked the question: Does shadow DOM improve style performance? I didn’t give a clear answer, so perhaps it’s no surprise that some folks weren’t sure what conclusion …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nolanlawson.com/2022/06/22/style-scoping-versus-shadow-dom-which-is-fastest/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Nobody is Happy with Hybrid</title>
      <link>https://www.zagaja.com/2022/06/why-nobody-is-happy-with-hybrid/</link>
      <description>Meetings where people are co-located and streaming on Zoom are the WORST. It sounds terrible, no one who isn&amp;#39;t there can understand you, and I have no idea who is talking. Glad the people in the office are having a good time</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/mzagaja)</author>
      <guid>https://www.zagaja.com/2022/06/why-nobody-is-happy-with-hybrid/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A journey into the Linux scheduler</title>
      <link>https://blog.maxgio.me/posts/linux-scheduler-journey/</link>
      <description>Two years ago more or less I started my journey in Linux. I was scared at first and I didn’t know where to start from. But then I decided to buy a book - and what a book! - in order to follow a path.
Along the way, I integrated the material with up-to-date documentation from kernel.org and source code. In the meantime, I started to learn C a bit so that I also could have played with what I was learning, step by step.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.maxgio.me/posts/linux-scheduler-journey/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What every new software developer should know</title>
      <link>https://bhave.sh/new-dev-history/</link>
      <description>The tech landscape changes dramatically every 5-10 years. And we poor software developers have to constantly run and re-skill just to catch up. Was it always like this?</description>
      <author> (Bhavesh Kakwani)</author>
      <guid>https://bhave.sh/new-dev-history/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Software Development &amp;#183; Mike Klimek</title>
      <link>https://mike.cloud/tech%20industry/2022/06/24/autonomous-teams.html</link>
      <description>Why do traditional companies struggle with software development and what can be done about it?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mike.cloud/tech%20industry/2022/06/24/autonomous-teams.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roman Numerals</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2637/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2637/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 23:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thomas H. Ptacek</title>
      <link>https://flaked.sockpuppet.org/2022/06/21/because-ive-obviously.html</link>
      <description>Because I’ve obviously gone all “Slurp Juice” on this MEGA attack thing, an attempt at a decoder ring.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://flaked.sockpuppet.org/2022/06/21/because-ive-obviously.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 22:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A simple but effective data grid for Blazor</title>
      <link>https://aspnet.github.io/quickgridsamples/</link>
      <description>Samples using the QuickGrid component for Blazor.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aspnet.github.io/quickgridsamples/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi Global Lists Mina Protocol</title>
      <link>https://minaprotocol.com/blog/huobi-lists-mina</link>
      <description>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi Global has listed Mina (MINA) for trading on its platform.&amp;#160;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://minaprotocol.com/blog/huobi-lists-mina</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 19:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair Programming</title>
      <link>https://jeeb.uk/collaboration/pair-programming/</link>
      <description>I  am James and below are some words on Software Engineering as well as some programming-related projects.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jeeb.uk/collaboration/pair-programming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 17:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Data Community Standup - TPH, TPT, and TPC Inheritance mapping with EF Core</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/HaL6DKW1mrg</link>
      <description>Type inheritance hierarchies as used in object-oriented programming do not map naturally to relational database schemas. In this live stream, we will look at...</description>
      <author> (Eniola Benjamin
            
          
        
        
        
        7 days ago)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/HaL6DKW1mrg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remove Duplicates From a List in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/remove-duplicates-from-a-list-in-c/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to learn different methods to remove duplicates from a list in C# and see which one performs the best.</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/remove-duplicates-from-a-list-in-c/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 15:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Gateway + CASB</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/announcing-gateway-and-casb/</link>
      <description>Find and fix shadow IT with Cloudflare’s Secure Web Gateway and API-driven Cloud Access Security Broker (CASB)</description>
      <author> (Corey Mahan)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/announcing-gateway-and-casb/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Andrew Lock: Web Applications in .NET6 - Episode 198</title>
      <link>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/andrew-luck-web-applications-in-net6-episode-198</link>
      <description>Andrew Lock is a senior software engineer at Datadog, working out of Devon, in the UK. He is a Microsoft MVP, Author of  Core in Action, and has an active blog all about his experience working with .NET and  Core. &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [3:35] Andrew discusses the high points in his programming career that steered him to work with .Net6. [5:30] Andrew walks us through all the .NET frameworks and demystifies the overwhelm around all the options. [9:38] Andrew’s favorite method at the moment for web applications on top of .NET is  [12:53] Does anyone really want web applications? [15:31] Andrew explains his philosophy and experience and guidance on testing. [19:18] Is there any kind of structure or pattern that people should be thinking about to keep the classroom lessons not overflowing? [26:16] What web applications would Andrew recommend? [30:19] The topic of custom applications and components comes up. &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:  — New video podcast!   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!  — email jeffrey@clear-measure.com for a chance to win a free copy of  Core in Action from Andrew Lock. — available book discount code: — Permanent discount code for Manning publications (35% off I believe), for all listeners, podazdev19   |  |  |  &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/andrew-luck-web-applications-in-net6-episode-198</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 12:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undefined behavior in C is a reading error. – keeping simple</title>
      <link>https://www.yodaiken.com/2021/05/19/undefined-behavior-in-c-is-a-reading-error/</link>
      <description>Considering how important “undefined behavior” has become to C semantics and the ISO/IEC JTC1/SC22/WG14 Committee, the lack of any reference to it in the K&amp;amp;R ANSI book is notable and the description in the 1999 C Rationale was quite modest.</description>
      <author> (vy)</author>
      <guid>https://www.yodaiken.com/2021/05/19/undefined-behavior-in-c-is-a-reading-error/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 11:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we built a $1M ARR open source SaaS</title>
      <link>https://plausible.io/blog/open-source-saas</link>
      <description>We’ve reached a significant milestone of $1 million in annual recurring revenue (ARR) with Plausible Analytics. This post is a recap of how we got to this point.</description>
      <author> (Marko Saric)</author>
      <guid>https://plausible.io/blog/open-source-saas</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 10:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 101 - Open Source .NET for Fun with Drake Williams</title>
      <link>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-101-open-source-net-for-fun-with-drake-williams/</link>
      <description>In this episode, Drake Williams joined us to talk about some of his Open Source projects which he started for fun, including Rom Sorter and the GPS game server Praxis Mapper. He also shares some top tips for building applications without breaking out of your personal bandwidth.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-101-open-source-net-for-fun-with-drake-williams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 09:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 301</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/pBmNHh8xgpk</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Tom Bilyeu
  
  
  
    Tom Bilyeu
  




  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/pBmNHh8xgpk</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 07:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Subsystem for Android and .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://dvlup.com/2022/06/22/windows-subsystem-for-android-and-net-maui/</link>
      <description>
Did you know you can deploy and debug your Android projects from Visual Studio 2022 (17.3+) to WSA (Windows Subsystem for Android)? This is a quick post to show you how to have your WSA appear in the list of target Android devices in Visual Studio.



WSA as the target device



First, make sure you have WSA installed and enabled, find the instructions here Windows Subsystem for Android™️ | Microsoft Docs. Once it is installed, start the Amazon App Store app to ensure WSA has been started. 



Starting up WSA



Open the Windows Subsystem for Android™ Settings app (this gets installed with WSA) and make sure the Developer &amp;gt; Developer Mode setting is enabled. After it is enabled, you should now see an loopback IP address (127.0.0.1) and a port number (58526).



WSA IP address and port number for ADB



With WSA setup and running you can now deploy from Visual Studio 2022. The first step is in Visual Studio, expand the Tools &amp;gt; Android menu and select Android Adb Command Prompt menu item.



ADB Command Prompt



When the ADB command prompt window is opened, you can connect ADB to WSA using the &amp;#39;connect&amp;#39; command and IP:port number for WSA. Here is the full command: adb connect 127.0.0.1:58526and here&amp;#39;s a screenshot of a successful connection:



Successful ADB connection



Finally, in your MAUI project; make sure the target framework is set to net6.0-android and you should find WSA listed under the Android Local Devices menu.



WSA listed as a local Android device in Visual Studio 2022 Preview



Here&amp;#39;s what it looks like after I deployed an early prototype of my current Microsoft Store app Hacked? as a .NET MAUI Android app!



.NET MAUI app running in WSA



Troubleshooting



Troubleshooting Tip 1 - Missing &amp;#39;Android Local Devices&amp;#39;



Problem: If you do not see Android Local Devices in the menu, then it means your WSA is probably put back to sleep by Windows because it wasn&amp;#39;t being used.



Solution 1: Just open any Android app, like the Amazon App Store, to start WSA again (you can keep that app open to prevent WSA from going back to sleep). Note: After it has been stopped and started, you&amp;#39;ll need to reconnect ADB again.



Solution 2: Another option is to tell Windows 11 to never put WSA to sleep. It will start up with Windows and always use system resources. Open the Windows Subsystem for Android Settings app and change the System &amp;gt; Subsystem Resources setting to Continuous (see screenshot)







Troubleshooting Tip 2 - No Internet in WSA



Problem: If you do not have any internet in your WSA apps, check to see if you have a VPN active. It is known that Cisco AnyConnnect&amp;#39;s network adapter can interfere if the split tunnel routes traffic with the same IP as the WSA vm. 



Solution 1: If you disconnect the VPN, the internet will work in WSA again. 



Disconnect option in the AnyConnect tray icon&amp;#39;s context menu



Solution 2: There is a semi-permanent solution for this by changing the AnyConnect network adapter to have a higher InterfaceMetric value than the WSA Hyper-V adapter one has. Here&amp;#39;s a screenshot of the two PowerShell commands I used to do that:



Increasing AnyConnect&amp;#39;s InterfaceMetric value
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dvlup.com/2022/06/22/windows-subsystem-for-android-and-net-maui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps 101: Introducing Database DevOps</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/database-devops/devops-101-introducing-database-devops</link>
      <description>What are the challenges - and the opportunities - waiting for you when introducing Database DevOps? Grant Fritchey explains.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/GFritchey)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/database-devops/devops-101-introducing-database-devops</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Layout Options in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/exploring-layout-options-dotnet-maui</link>
      <description>.NET MAUI has four layout classes to help you organize the user interface of your app. Let’s look at them!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/exploring-layout-options-dotnet-maui</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asked and answered: the results for the 2022 Developer survey are here!</title>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.blog/2022/06/22/asked-and-answered-the-results-for-the-2022-developer-survey-are-here/</link>
      <description>The state of software development is...</description>
      <author> (David Gibson and Ryan Donovan)</author>
      <guid>https://stackoverflow.blog/2022/06/22/asked-and-answered-the-results-for-the-2022-developer-survey-are-here/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perhaps Too Much Validation &amp;#183; Aspiring Craftsman</title>
      <link>http://aspiringcraftsman.com/2022/06/22/perhaps-too-much-validation.html</link>
      <description>22 June, 2022. It was a Wednesday.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://aspiringcraftsman.com/2022/06/22/perhaps-too-much-validation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Simple .NET Lambda Function | no dogma blog</title>
      <link>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2022/06/creating-a-simple-net-lambda-function/</link>
      <description>This post shows how easy it is to create a simple Lambda function written in C#.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2022/06/creating-a-simple-net-lambda-function/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a React-based app with ASP.NET Minimal APIs and MongoDB storage</title>
      <link>https://stvansolano.github.io/2022/06/20/Creating-a-react-app-with-AspNet-Minimal-APIs-and-MongoDb-CosmosDb/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been using React for while by mixing it up with .NET stuff and enjoying it a lot. For this post, I decided to combine them along Compose containers, ASP.NET Minimal APIs and MongoDB support!</description>
      <author> (Esteban Solano G.)</author>
      <guid>https://stvansolano.github.io/2022/06/20/Creating-a-react-app-with-AspNet-Minimal-APIs-and-MongoDb-CosmosDb/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RequestDelegateFactory Class (Microsoft.AspNetCore.Http)</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/api/microsoft.aspnetcore.http.requestdelegatefactory</link>
      <description>Creates RequestDelegate implementations from Delegate request handlers. </description>
      <author> (dotnet-bot)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/api/microsoft.aspnetcore.http.requestdelegatefactory</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 03:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draknek New Voices Puzzle Grant</title>
      <link>https://grants.draknek.org/</link>
      <description>The Draknek New Voices Puzzle Grant is a grant opportunity for game developers from traditionally underrepresented groups and backgrounds who are interested in designing and developing puzzle games.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://grants.draknek.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 03:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interchain Security is Coming to the Cosmos Hub</title>
      <link>https://blog.cosmos.network/interchain-security-is-coming-to-the-cosmos-hub-f144c45fb035</link>
      <description>One of the features that make blockchain technology so appealing is its high degree of security and resistance to attack. In a…</description>
      <author> (https://billyrennekamp.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cosmos.network/interchain-security-is-coming-to-the-cosmos-hub-f144c45fb035</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 01:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>