<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>New .NET 7 Feature - Regex Source Generator #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=6x3IYxDtpSo</link>
      <description>Take a quick look at the new .NET 7 source generator for Regex. Check out the full video here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6USQ3_81wQMHere&amp;#39;s how you can ...</description>
      <author> (CodeWithStu
  
  
  
    CodeWithStu
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=6x3IYxDtpSo</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korean nuclear fusion reactor achieves 100 million&amp;#176;C for 30 seconds</title>
      <link>https://www.shiningscience.com/2022/09/korean-nuclear-fusion-reactor-achieves.html</link>
      <description>A sustained, stable experiment is the latest demonstration that nuclear fusion is moving from being a physics problem to an engineering one.</description>
      <author> (byEditorial Team)</author>
      <guid>https://www.shiningscience.com/2022/09/korean-nuclear-fusion-reactor-achieves.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Decide: Simple Tools for Making Better Choices</title>
      <link>https://www.kevinslin.com/notes/a8jwloovyhl2a1pw0iyrzmd/</link>
      <description>Building hierarchal tools of thought @ dendron.so</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.kevinslin.com/notes/a8jwloovyhl2a1pw0iyrzmd/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Your Customers Struggle</title>
      <link>https://shermanonsoftware.com/2022/09/06/when-your-customers-struggle/</link>
      <description>When your customers struggle with a non-intuitive interface, would they rather: Wait 6 months while you work on an amazing redesign and brand refresh, or get weekly tweaks that make using your prod…</description>
      <author> (Published by jeffpsherman			
		

		
						
				View all posts by jeffpsherman)</author>
      <guid>https://shermanonsoftware.com/2022/09/06/when-your-customers-struggle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A review of my time at Remix</title>
      <link>https://kentcdodds.com/blog/a-review-of-my-time-at-remix</link>
      <description>As I move on to my next adventure, I want to take this opportunity to review what I accomplished while at Remix.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kentcdodds.com/blog/a-review-of-my-time-at-remix</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dart is Boring | akos.ma</title>
      <link>https://akos.ma/blog/dart-is-boring/</link>
      <description>Lately, I’ve been playing with Dart, the programming language powering the cross-platform Flutter UI framework. I’ve added a Dart implementation to my collection of (now 21) programming languages in the Conway project, and another to the collection of sample Fortune web APIs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://akos.ma/blog/dart-is-boring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://davidyat.es/2022/08/31/stable-diffusion/</link>
      <description>On the 22nd of this month, Stability.ai released Stable Diffusion, a free, open-source AI tool for generating images from text prompts (and other images). Previously, access to this technology was available through Open AI’s commercial, invite-only DALL-E 2 platform, Midjourney’s commercial Discord bot, and, in a significantly reduced free-to-use form, Craiyon/DALL-E Mini. Basically, you had to use a hosted service and pay per image, or use something too simple to be much user for anything more than amusing jokes to post on social media.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidyat.es/2022/08/31/stable-diffusion/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Image-text Classification</title>
      <link>https://vaclavkosar.com/ml/Multimodal-Image-Text-Classification</link>
      <description>Understand the top deep learning image and text classification models CMA-CLIP, CLIP, CoCa, and MMBT used in e-commerce.</description>
      <author> (Vaclav Kosar)</author>
      <guid>https://vaclavkosar.com/ml/Multimodal-Image-Text-Classification</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On chosing the ideal architecture of the web application</title>
      <link>https://dmitrytsepelev.dev/on-ideal-architecture</link>
      <description>An essay about my criteria for the ideal architecture</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dmitrytsepelev.dev/on-ideal-architecture</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scroll Restoration with Client Side Routing</title>
      <link>https://steve.dignam.xyz/2022/07/15/scroll-restoration/</link>
      <description>Instagram’s vs Flickr’s approach</description>
      <author> (Steve Dignam)</author>
      <guid>https://steve.dignam.xyz/2022/07/15/scroll-restoration/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six Months of Full Time Open Source</title>
      <link>https://blog.joshuakgoldberg.com/six-months-of-full-time-open-source/</link>
      <description>What it&amp;#39;s like to quit your job and try to work on open source tooling full time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.joshuakgoldberg.com/six-months-of-full-time-open-source/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Cherny&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://borischerny.com/2022/09/07/time-and-timing.html</link>
      <description>You often hear that “timing matters”. It helps to think about this as two related concepts: time and timing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://borischerny.com/2022/09/07/time-and-timing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the SQLite Virtual Machine Works</title>
      <link>https://fly.io/blog/sqlite-virtual-machine/</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s look at how SQLite parses, optimizes, and compiles every query that it receives.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fly.io/blog/sqlite-virtual-machine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 22:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Security Against Time Traveling Adversaries</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2022/1148</link>
      <description>If you had a time machine, what cryptography would you be able to break?

In this work, we investigate the notion of time travel, formally defining models for adversaries equipped with a time machine, and exploring the consequences for cryptography. We find that being able to rewind time breaks some cryptographic schemes, and being able to freely move both forwards and backwards in time breaks even more schemes.

We look at the impacts of time travel on encryption and signatures in particular, finding that the  and  security games are broken, while  and  remain secure.</description>
      <author> (L&amp;#250;c&amp;#225;s Cr&amp;#237;ost&amp;#243;ir Meier)</author>
      <guid>https://eprint.iacr.org/2022/1148</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 21:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things You Should Not Do</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2669/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2669/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 21:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Improvements in .NET MAUI | .NET Conf: Focus on MAUI</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Wsizdg3xnf4</link>
      <description>A deep dive into the performance improvements that went into .NET MAUI. Learn techniques for optimizing your own cross-platform .NET MAUI applications as wel...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •
  
  
    
      5.2K views
    
      4 weeks ago)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Wsizdg3xnf4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 20:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - &amp;#127874;8 Years of .NET Community Standups&amp;#127874;</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XW978upAGZs%3Flist%3DPLdo4fOcmZ0oX-DBuRG4u58ZTAJgBAeQ-t</link>
      <description>Join Scott Hanselman, Damian Edwards, and Jon Galloway for the 8th anniversary of the ASP.NET Community Standup.Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/as...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XW978upAGZs%3Flist%3DPLdo4fOcmZ0oX-DBuRG4u58ZTAJgBAeQ-t</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 19:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved IntelliSense Support for Jupyter Notebooks in VS Code -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/09/07/vs-code-python-sep22.aspx</link>
      <description>&amp;#39;Not only you will get improved auto complete suggestions when writing Python code in notebook files, but you will also be able to leverage refactoring features such as extract variable, extract method as well as auto imports.&amp;#39;</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel09/07/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/09/07/vs-code-python-sep22.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 19:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring I/O inside of RavenDB</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/198180-A/monitoring-i-o-inside-of-ravendb?Key=fe5628aa-84ce-4931-a578-d44b52b0b48e</link>
      <description>Earlier this year I talked about the reasoning behind the RavenDB team spending so much time building self monitoring diagnostics. Today I&amp;amp;rsquo;m happy to...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/198180-A/monitoring-i-o-inside-of-ravendb?Key=fe5628aa-84ce-4931-a578-d44b52b0b48e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 17:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Mathias Brandewinder: Math and Machine Learning using .NET - Episode 208</title>
      <link>http://feed.azuredevops.show/mathias-brandewinder-math-and-machine-learning-using-net-episode-208</link>
      <description>Mathias Brandewinder enjoys solving challenging business problems with software engineering and applied mathematics techniques, and some creativity. His current focus is on functional programming with F#, machine learning, and data science, and on putting them together to help companies make smarter decisions with their data. He loves teaching and mentoring, and is a regular speaker at conferences and community events all over the world. A former Microsoft F# MVP, he holds an MS in Operations Research from Stanford, an MS in Economics from University of Paris X, and an MBA from ESSEC. &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [3:15] Mathias talks about how his love of math got him into programming. [5:57] Mathias discusses what intrigued him about F# and the scripting environment. [6:29] What about when a computer’s version of a number doesn’t really line up with the math version of a number? [11:51] What issues does F# help more than C#? [15:22] What is Mathias’s favorite charting component for .NET? [18:27] What inspired Mathias to write his book, , and is there a new book on the horizon? [20:09] Mathias is here to say math can be genuinely fun! [24:03] Jupiter appears to be an on-the-fly evaluator of code that runs on a server somewhere through the browser. [29:13] What other math-related libraries should we be aware of, and what are some other resources we can check out? &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:  — New video podcast!   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!  programming@palermo.net   mathias@brandewinder.com       &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://feed.azuredevops.show/mathias-brandewinder-math-and-machine-learning-using-net-episode-208</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 17:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Live: Build mobile and desktop apps with .NET MAUI - Events</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learn-events/learnlive-mobile-desktop-apps-dotnet-maui/</link>
      <description>Every week starting September 7, 2022 through November 16, 2022 (7 episodes)</description>
      <author> (lbugnion)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learn-events/learnlive-mobile-desktop-apps-dotnet-maui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 17:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It rather involved being on the other side of this airtight hatchway: Replacing a service binary</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220907-00/?p=107132</link>
      <description>Looking for misconfigured services.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220907-00/?p=107132</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 17:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiHouse</title>
      <link>https://www.wikihouse.cc/</link>
      <description>WikiHouse is a digitally-manufactured building system that makes it simple for anyone to build beautiful, zero-carbon homes.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.wikihouse.cc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 16:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&amp;#39;s New iPhone Gets The Worst Reception Since iPhone 6S</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/etfs-and-funds/sectors/sp500-apples-new-iphone-gets-the-worst-reception-since-iphone-6s/</link>
      <description>Apple is the most important stock in the S&amp;amp;P 500.</description>
      <author> (Investor&amp;#39;s Business Daily)</author>
      <guid>https://www.investors.com/etfs-and-funds/sectors/sp500-apples-new-iphone-gets-the-worst-reception-since-iphone-6s/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Data Explorer Supports Native Ingestion from Amazon S3 </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2022/09/azure-adx-s3/</link>
      <description>Microsoft recently announced the ability to natively ingest data from Amazon S3 into Azure Data Explorer (ADX). The new feature simplifies multi-cloud data analytics deployments, bringing data from Amazon S3 to Azure, without relying on custom ETL pipelines.</description>
      <author> (Renato Losio)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2022/09/azure-adx-s3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragos Inc. - SkillBridge Project Manager Intern</title>
      <link>https://jobs.lever.co/dragos/fdf57840-a0a4-4ea2-b4fb-a081de2fe46f</link>
      <description>Our mission at Dragos is to protect the world’s most critical infrastructure from adversaries who wish to do it harm. Dragos is proud to support transitioning service members from all U.S. military branches to prepare for their post-military careers by providing opportunities to learn and grow their skill sets. We are looking for active duty service members who wish to take their experience and understanding of the value of project management in an agile environment, and can facilitate technical conversations towards a deliverable, to join our team while preparing for their post military career. The project management team is looking for a SkillBridge Project Manager Intern to lead projects that cross IT, Engineering, Security, and Product. As this occurs, the right person will see areas to strategically implement agile best practices and have the opportunity to learn from Dragos teams.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jobs.lever.co/dragos/fdf57840-a0a4-4ea2-b4fb-a081de2fe46f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 14:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragos Inc. - SkillBridge Reverse/Dissector Engineer Intern</title>
      <link>https://jobs.lever.co/dragos/49fc9f04-e2d8-4c88-886c-d1c29b1513bf</link>
      <description>Our Mission at Dragos is to protect the world’s most critical infrastructure from adversaries who wish to do it harm. We help defend industrial organizations that provide us with the tenets of modern civilization: running water, functioning electricity, and safe industrial working environments. Dragos is proud to support transitioning service members from all U.S. military branches to prepare for their post-military careers by providing opportunities to learn and grow their skill sets. Our Engineering Department is seeking a SkillBridge Reverse/Dissector Engineer Intern to join its Research &amp;amp; Development - Content Engineering Team. In this position, you will work closely with partner teams to support Dragos customers via researching new protocols and detections by working closely with new and existing customers and our solution architects. You will collaborate closely with the Engineering and Intelligence teams to drive insights into industrial protocol analysis, network situationa</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jobs.lever.co/dragos/49fc9f04-e2d8-4c88-886c-d1c29b1513bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 14:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WTF Just Happened? Why Your Org Needs a Cybersecurity Incident Review Board</title>
      <link>https://www.pcmag.com/news/wtf-just-happened-why-your-org-needs-a-cybersecurity-incident-review-board</link>
      <description>Researchers at Black Hat 2022 urge organizations to create their own &amp;#39;Cyber NTSBs.&amp;#39;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pcmag.com/news/wtf-just-happened-why-your-org-needs-a-cybersecurity-incident-review-board</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird Al had 100 gigs of RAM</title>
      <link>https://rubenerd.com/weird-al-had-100-gb-of-ram/</link>
      <description>So many lines in that song have been surpassed, but RAM sticks out as something that hasn’t.</description>
      <author> (http://rubenschade.com/)</author>
      <guid>https://rubenerd.com/weird-al-had-100-gb-of-ram/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - MyOwnClone/quake_watch: Quake 1 game port to Apple Watch</title>
      <link>https://github.com/MyOwnClone/quake_watch</link>
      <description>Quake 1 game port to Apple Watch. Contribute to MyOwnClone/quake_watch development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (MyOwnClone)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/MyOwnClone/quake_watch</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 11:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difftastic, the Fantastic Diff</title>
      <link>https://www.wilfred.me.uk/blog/2022/09/06/difftastic-the-fantastic-diff/</link>
      <description>programming, language design, and human factors</description>
      <author> (Wilfred Hughes)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wilfred.me.uk/blog/2022/09/06/difftastic-the-fantastic-diff/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 10:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filtering Results Using Filtered Include Method in EF Core</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/ef-core-filtered-include/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to show you how to use Filtered Include method in EF Core to filter results inside the include method.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/ef-core-filtered-include/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 08:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draw the Light, Not the Asset</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FuAtKjEuck8</link>
      <description>In the Graphics category, we&amp;#39;ll talk about making art for games. I won&amp;#39;t be sharing tool tutorials and such, but rather practical points to consider when cre...</description>
      <author> (Veritasium
  
  
  
    Veritasium
  




  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FuAtKjEuck8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 07:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s Inside Of a Distroless Image - Taking a Deeper Look</title>
      <link>https://iximiuz.com/en/posts/containers-distroless-images/</link>
      <description>What are these distroless images, really? Why are they needed? What&amp;#39;s the difference between a container started from a distroless base and a container started from scratch? Let&amp;#39;s take a deeper look.</description>
      <author> (Ivan Velichko)</author>
      <guid>https://iximiuz.com/en/posts/containers-distroless-images/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 07:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customize The Authorization Pipeline In ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/customize-the-authorization-pipeline-in-aspnet-core</link>
      <description>Using implementations of IAuthorizationHandler, IAuthorizationMiddlewareResultHandler, and more to customize the aspnetcore authorization pipeline</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/customize-the-authorization-pipeline-in-aspnet-core</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 06:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Request Batch</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/request-batch.html</link>
      <description>Combine multiple requests to optimally utilise the network.</description>
      <author> (Unmesh Joshi)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/request-batch.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 06:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State pattern and the State monad</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2022/09/05/the-state-pattern-and-the-state-monad/</link>
      <description>The names are the same. Is there a connection? An article for object-oriented programmers.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2022/09/05/the-state-pattern-and-the-state-monad/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 06:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use dependency injection and .NET logging with Microsoft.Data.SqlClient</title>
      <link>https://erikej.github.io/dotnet/sqlclient/2022/09/06/sqlclient-di-dotnet.html</link>
      <description>Microsoft.Data.SqlClient is the open source .NET data provider for Microsoft SQL Server. It allows you to connect and interact with SQL Server and Azure SQL Database using .NET.</description>
      <author> (Erik Ejlskov Jensen)</author>
      <guid>https://erikej.github.io/dotnet/sqlclient/2022/09/06/sqlclient-di-dotnet.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 06:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TailwindCSS Tip: Arbitrary Values in Utility Classes
</title>
      <link>https://wildermuth.com/2022/09/06/tailwindcss-arbitrary-values/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wildermuth.com/2022/09/06/tailwindcss-arbitrary-values/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 04:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Riff — Determinate Systems</title>
      <link>https://determinate.systems/posts/introducing-riff</link>
      <description>Riff is a tool that automatically provides external dependencies for Rust projects</description>
      <author> (Sep 6
            
            Written By Graham Christensen)</author>
      <guid>https://determinate.systems/posts/introducing-riff</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 03:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Can Now Reliably Produce a Tree&amp;#39;s Worth of Oxygen on Mars</title>
      <link>https://singularityhub.com/2022/09/04/nasa-says-it-can-now-reliably-produce-a-trees-worth-of-oxygen-on-mars/</link>
      <description>A machine called MOXIE, stowed on NASA&amp;#39;s Perseverence rover, is steadily breathing in the Martian atmosphere and breathing out oxygen.</description>
      <author> (Jason Dorrier)</author>
      <guid>https://singularityhub.com/2022/09/04/nasa-says-it-can-now-reliably-produce-a-trees-worth-of-oxygen-on-mars/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 02:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Let&amp;#39;s chat about code quality &amp;amp; performance!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=4WX14dsnKsg</link>
      <description>Improve the quality of your code to get the most performance out of it. Featuring: David McCarter (@realDotNetdave)Get your questions answered on the Microso...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=4WX14dsnKsg</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>