<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Scale or Surrender: When watts determine freedom — TD</title>
      <link>https://www.timdavis.com/blog/scale-or-surrender-when-watts-determine-freedom</link>
      <description>Consider this provocative framing: what if we viewed our collective future not through the lens of human populations and national borders, but through available compute capacity? In this view, the race to build massive datacenter infrastructure becomes humanity's defining competition. This perspecti</description>
      <guid>https://www.timdavis.com/blog/scale-or-surrender-when-watts-determine-freedom</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Async Traits Can Be Directly Backed By Manual Future Impls</title>
      <link>https://blog.yoshuawuyts.com/async-traits-can-be-directly-backed-by-manual-future-impls/</link>
      <description>There’s a fun little tidbit that most people don’t seem to be aware of when
writing async functions in traits (AFITs) and that is: they allow you to
directly return futures from methods. Sounds confusing? Let me illustrate what I
mean with a simple example. Assume we have an a trait AsyncIterator which has an async fn next method that is defined as follows:</description>
      <guid>https://blog.yoshuawuyts.com/async-traits-can-be-directly-backed-by-manual-future-impls/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My best advice about preparing for difficult conversations</title>
      <link>https://shaungallagher.pressbin.com/blog/preparation.html</link>
      <description>Don't try to anticipate the other person's reactions.  Do this instead.</description>
      <guid>https://shaungallagher.pressbin.com/blog/preparation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe code isn't meant to be reviewed *</title>
      <link>https://monadical.com/posts/vibe-code-how-to-stay-in-control.html</link>
      <description>How to stay in control of codebase and not lose vibe code productivity boost. Explicit vibe/human code separation through modular approach</description>
      <guid>https://monadical.com/posts/vibe-code-how-to-stay-in-control.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>domains i love</title>
      <link>https://www.ahmedsaoudi.com/blog/domains-i-love/</link>
      <description>published on Jun 09, 2025</description>
      <guid>https://www.ahmedsaoudi.com/blog/domains-i-love/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Who Forgets You - kupajo</title>
      <link>https://kupajo.com/youre-so-quickly-forgotten/</link>
      <description>The people who actually think about you often, like your family, partner, and closest friends, like you because they get to see the rawest form of you.</description>
      <guid>https://kupajo.com/youre-so-quickly-forgotten/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alert Sound</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3100/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3100/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why We Moved Our ECS Services from Fargate to EC2 | Tines</title>
      <link>https://www.tines.com/blog/migrating-ecs-fargate-ec2/</link>
      <description>At Tines, we migrated our ECS services from Fargate to EC2 to improve performance, reliability, and flexibility. Here’s what we learned.</description>
      <guid>https://www.tines.com/blog/migrating-ecs-fargate-ec2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding My Spark Again | Peter Steinberger</title>
      <link>https://steipete.me/posts/2025/finding-my-spark-again</link>
      <description>I reflect on my post-exit journey from emptiness to rediscovering my passion for building, sparked by AI's transformative potential.</description>
      <guid>https://steipete.me/posts/2025/finding-my-spark-again</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Interest Indicates 8% Q2 Sales Growth for Acushnet</title>
      <link>https://jackdry.com/search-interest-indicates-8-q2-sales-growth-for-acushnet</link>
      <description>Based on regression analysis of search interest/ sales growth data, Acushnet’s FY25 Q2 (Apr – Jun 2025) sales are forecast to increase 7.9% YoY on a constant-currency basis – following a 1.2% increase in Q1 – driven by 9.7% and 15.1% increases in the US and EMEA respectively.</description>
      <guid>https://jackdry.com/search-interest-indicates-8-q2-sales-growth-for-acushnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baking the Y Combinator from scratch, Part 2: Recursion and its consequences</title>
      <link>https://the-nerve-blog.ghost.io/baking-the-y-combinator-from-scratch-part-2-recursion-and-its-consequences/</link>
      <description>It's a pedagogical pet peeve of mine when technical concepts are simply listed in their fully developed state, with little in the way of motivation, derivation, or historical context. This, I think, is like publishing a cookbook filled with beautiful pictures of cakes, but no recipes.

My aim with the</description>
      <guid>https://the-nerve-blog.ghost.io/baking-the-y-combinator-from-scratch-part-2-recursion-and-its-consequences/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Theory – Kelvin Zhang</title>
      <link>https://kelvinzhang.com/bubble-theory</link>
      <description>We live our lives inside invisible bubbles.</description>
      <guid>https://kelvinzhang.com/bubble-theory</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life and Insecurities</title>
      <link>https://www.jerry.wtf/posts/life-and-insecurities/</link>
      <description>
In this world nothing can be said to be certain, except that life comes with insecurities.
Insecurity is a near-universal human condition.
Ironically, people who appear most confident often turn out to be driven by the deepest insecurities. They may dominate conversations, make grand pronouncements, or display what looks like pride. In reality this betrays a defense mechanism against a sensitive area in themselves that they have yet to address.
This suggests that insecurity works differently than most people think. It’s not simply about lacking confidence or self-esteem. There’s a more specific mechanism at play that needs to be understood in order to move past the platitudes of “Just be yourself” or “Fake it until you make it”.</description>
      <guid>https://www.jerry.wtf/posts/life-and-insecurities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Agenix with Home Manager | Mitchell Hanberg</title>
      <link>https://www.mitchellhanberg.com/using-agenix-with-home-manager/</link>
      <description>Home Manager (also styled as home-manager) allows you to configure your programs and configuration with Nix code, similar to NixOS modules.</description>
      <guid>https://www.mitchellhanberg.com/using-agenix-with-home-manager/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use a proxy for LLM app development — The Sharat's</title>
      <link>https://sharats.me/posts/use-proxy-for-llm-app-dev/</link>
      <description>Most everybody is developing LLM applications these days. New frameworks and libraries show up nearly every week. A common theme is easy switching...</description>
      <guid>https://sharats.me/posts/use-proxy-for-llm-app-dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Prototyped an IDE for How We Actually Code Now</title>
      <link>https://fulghum.io/ide</link>
      <description>Moving beyond the 'horseless carriage' phase of AI-assisted development. A conversational IDE prototype that makes LLMs the primary interface, not an afterthought.</description>
      <author> (Jordan Fulghum)</author>
      <guid>https://fulghum.io/ide</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>crawshaw - 2025-06-08</title>
      <link>https://crawshaw.io/blog/programming-with-agents</link>
      <description>2025-06-08</description>
      <guid>https://crawshaw.io/blog/programming-with-agents</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple supercharges its tools and technologies for developers</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/06/apple-supercharges-its-tools-and-technologies-for-developers/</link>
      <description>Apple announced new technologies and enhancements to its developer tools to help developers create more beautiful, intelligent, and engaging apps.</description>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/06/apple-supercharges-its-tools-and-technologies-for-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple introduces a delightful and elegant new software design</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/06/apple-introduces-a-delightful-and-elegant-new-software-design/</link>
      <description>Apple previewed a new software design, crafted with Liquid Glass, that makes apps and system experiences more expressive and delightful.</description>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/06/apple-introduces-a-delightful-and-elegant-new-software-design/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs are cheap</title>
      <link>https://www.snellman.net/blog/archive/2025-06-02-llms-are-cheap/</link>
      <description>A lot of people think LLMs are expensive to operate. That was true a couple of years ago, but these people haven't updated their views after an approximately 1000x reduction in prices over two years.</description>
      <guid>https://www.snellman.net/blog/archive/2025-06-02-llms-are-cheap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruteforcing the phone number of any Google user</title>
      <link>https://brutecat.com/articles/leaking-google-phones</link>
      <description>From rate limits to no limits: How IPv6's massive address space and a crafty botguard bypass left every Google user's phone number vulnerable</description>
      <guid>https://brutecat.com/articles/leaking-google-phones</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust is Officially in the Linux Kernel</title>
      <link>https://weeklyrust.substack.com/p/rust-is-officially-in-the-linux-kernel?r=327yzu&amp;amp;showWelcomeOnShare=false&amp;triedRedirect=true</link>
      <description>Today’s Issue: Designing Error Types in Rust Libraries, 10 Years of Betting on Rust, and C++ to Rust Phrasebook</description>
      <guid>https://weeklyrust.substack.com/p/rust-is-officially-in-the-linux-kernel?r=327yzu&amp;amp;showWelcomeOnShare=false&amp;triedRedirect=true</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devlog ⚡ Zig Programming Language</title>
      <link>https://ziglang.org/devlog/2025/#2025-06-08</link>
      <description>This page contains a curated list of recent changes to main branch Zig.</description>
      <guid>https://ziglang.org/devlog/2025/#2025-06-08</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FSE Meets the FBI! — FSE Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.freespeechextremist.com/blog/fse-vs-fbi.html</link>
      <description>I have for you a bizarre tale of scrapers, feds, data poisoning, Torswats, and everyone's favorite fedi instance.  It veers technical, because I suspect it will be of interest to other people running servers with UGC (i.e., every fedi instance), and also because the mechanics of how I figured out what I figured out might be useful.  It's also got information about how the FBI collects data, which is of interest to everyone, but especially US citizens.  I have a few pieces of the puzzle, maybe someone with interlocking pieces can say more; I'm happy to compare notes.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.freespeechextremist.com/blog/fse-vs-fbi.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kagi Search Stats</title>
      <link>https://kagi.com/stats?stat=members</link>
      <description>Better search results with no ads. Welcome to Kagi (pronounced kah-gee), a paid search engine that gives power back to the user.</description>
      <guid>https://kagi.com/stats?stat=members</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building supercomputers for autocrats probably isn’t good for democracy, actually</title>
      <link>https://helentoner.substack.com/p/supercomputers-for-autocrats</link>
      <description>The shameless spin around Stargate UAE</description>
      <guid>https://helentoner.substack.com/p/supercomputers-for-autocrats</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 07:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Not "Just A Button"</title>
      <link>https://candrewlee.com/blog/2025-06-07_software-development-lifecycle</link>
      <description>What do software engineers really do? - Written by Andrew Lee</description>
      <guid>https://candrewlee.com/blog/2025-06-07_software-development-lifecycle</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next bubble that will pop: Big Social Media</title>
      <link>https://blog.hermesloom.org/p/the-next-bubble-that-will-pop-big</link>
      <description>Right now, it’s still private companies controlling most of social media, for example X, Reddit or Facebook.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.hermesloom.org/p/the-next-bubble-that-will-pop-big</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicDoor – Cracking SonicWall’s SMA 500 – SCRT Team Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.scrt.ch/2025/06/04/sonicdoor-attacking-sonicwalls-sma-500/</link>
      <description>While attempting to compare the security level of various VPN vendors, I kept falling down the path of searching for vulnerabilities instead. This blog post details the ones I discovered in SonicWall’s SMA 500, which were patched in December 2024. This post has been delayed to coincide with my talk at SecurityFest on this exact subject.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.scrt.ch/2025/06/04/sonicdoor-attacking-sonicwalls-sma-500/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So, you screwed up your EAA compliance. What now? · Eric Eggert</title>
      <link>https://yatil.net/blog/so-you-screwed-up-your-eaa-compliance-what-now</link>
      <description>The deadline of the European Accessibility Act (EAA) is near (June 28 is just 20 days away as I write this), and you just realized that …</description>
      <guid>https://yatil.net/blog/so-you-screwed-up-your-eaa-compliance-what-now</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with QT, without the nonsense</title>
      <link>https://sebastiano.tronto.net/blog/2025-04-04-qt-minimal/</link>
      <description>At work I have recently (yesterday) ended working on a big project and
I am now waiting for a new assignment. While I wait, I decided that I
should take some time to learn something that could be useful both at
work and for my personal projects.  After some thought, I settled on QT
development with C++.</description>
      <guid>https://sebastiano.tronto.net/blog/2025-04-04-qt-minimal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junited 2025</title>
      <link>https://birming.com/2025/06/01/junited/</link>
      <description>Junited is a collaborative blogging initiative encouraging …</description>
      <guid>https://birming.com/2025/06/01/junited/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When the Assistant Becomes the Attacker: Hidden Risks of Tool-Enabled LLMs</title>
      <link>https://www.sakana.fr/blog/2025-06-08-llm-hidden-risks/</link>
      <description>LLMs aren’t just chatbots anymore. Once you give them tools, they stop suggesting and start acting. This piece explores the real—and often overlooked—risks of giving LLMs the ability to affect the world.</description>
      <guid>https://www.sakana.fr/blog/2025-06-08-llm-hidden-risks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Thousand Tiny Optimisations</title>
      <link>https://leejo.github.io/2025/06/08/alttpr/</link>
      <description>A Thousand Tiny Optimisations</description>
      <guid>https://leejo.github.io/2025/06/08/alttpr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No JS, No BS Ethical Web Analytics — Andrew Tropin</title>
      <link>https://trop.in/blog/no-js-no-bs-ethical-web-analytics</link>
      <description>I had two goals: to count AI crawlers DDoSing my nginx
infrastructure and to see if anybody reads at least one of my
three posts in the blog.  To achieve both, I needed to gather
data and transform it into meaningful insights, so basically I needed
web analytics.</description>
      <guid>https://trop.in/blog/no-js-no-bs-ethical-web-analytics</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus and Context and LLMs</title>
      <link>https://taras.glek.net/posts/focus-and-context-and-llms/</link>
      <description>I decided to write down some thoughts on agentic coding and why it’s a very hyped wrong turn.
Let me start with some background on my LLM experience. I adopted LLMs into my work in Aug 2020. I was sold when I saw that GPT-3 could generate usable SQL statements. Something that used to take 4-8 hours of RTFMing, now took 15min. I have since worked on chatcraft.org, various RAG frameworks, etc. I use aider heavily for work, frequently switch models, have been struggling with tool calling during dark ages before MCP.</description>
      <guid>https://taras.glek.net/posts/focus-and-context-and-llms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ditching HAProxy (in my homelab)</title>
      <link>https://arch.dog/bark/ditching-haproxy</link>
      <description>I'm always bothered by single points of failure. For my homelab, this quickly became a single HAProxy virtual machine. It existed on only one of my Proxmox instances (I can't replicate between them because the original instance doesn't use zfs. oops) so if the virtual machine or physical machine was unreachable for whatever reason, it effectively blocked my access to any service in my homelab Kubernetes cluster, and also broke communication between nodes and the Kubernetes API. It didn't happen often, and the fix was often trivial, but it still bothered me. Coupled with the fact that until recently the Kubernetes cluster also acted as a reverse proxy to services hosted on Proxmox and my NAS (read more about that stuff here), it could cause a wider outage than just what's on the cluster.</description>
      <guid>https://arch.dog/bark/ditching-haproxy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I program with Agents</title>
      <link>https://sketch.dev/blog/programming-with-agents</link>
      <description>2025-06-08 by David Crawshaw</description>
      <guid>https://sketch.dev/blog/programming-with-agents</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>