<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>nickcraver.com</title>
      <link>https://laptrinhx.com/tag/nickcraver-com/</link>
      <description>Blog about Programming, Open Source, Technology, Software and IT Jobs.</description>
      <author> (LaptrinhX)</author>
      <guid>https://laptrinhx.com/tag/nickcraver-com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 11:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVIF for Next-Generation Image Coding</title>
      <link>https://netflixtechblog.com/avif-for-next-generation-image-coding-b1d75675fe4?gi=fec55ac02887</link>
      <description>By Aditya Mavlankar, Jan de Cock, Cyril Concolato, Kyle Swanson, Anush Moorthy and Anne Aaron</description>
      <author> (https://netflixtechblog.com/@NetflixTechBlog)</author>
      <guid>https://netflixtechblog.com/avif-for-next-generation-image-coding-b1d75675fe4?gi=fec55ac02887</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 05:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>960620 - Support AVIF - chromium</title>
      <link>https://bugs.chromium.org/p/chromium/issues/detail?id=960620</link>
      <description>About Monorail
 User Guide
 Release Notes
 Feedback on Monorail
 Terms
 Privacy</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bugs.chromium.org/p/chromium/issues/detail?id=960620</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 04:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Liddle'est President: Padellan, Majid M, Kelly, John: 9781734666427: Amazon.com: Books</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/Liddleest-President-Majid-M-Padellan/dp/1734666420?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202007</link>
      <description>The Liddle'est President [Padellan, Majid M, Kelly, John] on Amazon.com. *FREE* shipping on qualifying offers. The Liddle'est President</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/Liddleest-President-Majid-M-Padellan/dp/1734666420?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202007</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 04:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA Lounge</title>
      <link>https://www.dnalounge.com/backstage/log/2020/07/10.html</link>
      <description>Uber just bought Postmates. Consequently, I'm closing the DNA Pizza Postmates account. And I encourage you to close your Postmates account as well. There are almost innumerable reasons to not do business with Uber, but let's start with: it is literally blood money: Saudi Prince Mohammed bin Salman owns more than 10% of Uber, at over $3.5 billion of investment. The CIA concluded that bin ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dnalounge.com/backstage/log/2020/07/10.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 03:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bdougie/awesome-black-developers</title>
      <link>https://github.com/bdougie/awesome-black-developers</link>
      <description>Amplifying the voices of Black developers in open source because #BlackLivesMatter ✊🏾 - bdougie/awesome-black-developers</description>
      <author> (bdougie)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/bdougie/awesome-black-developers</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 03:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBv4n1v4</title>
      <link>https://people.csail.mit.edu/rivest/pubs/Riv98a.pdf</link>
      <description />
      <author> (tlaw)</author>
      <guid>https://people.csail.mit.edu/rivest/pubs/Riv98a.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 02:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I’m leaving Sleeping Giants, but not because I want to</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@nandoodles/im-leaving-sleeping-giants-but-not-because-i-want-to-d9c4f488642</link>
      <description>How my white male co-founder gaslighted me out of the movement we built together.</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@nandoodles)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@nandoodles/im-leaving-sleeping-giants-but-not-because-i-want-to-d9c4f488642</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 02:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Span Symmetric ICryptoTransform by vcsjones · Pull Request #38722 · dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/38722</link>
      <description>This changes the underlying UniversalCryptoTransform, derived types, and symmetric cryptographic primitives to operate on span.
This gains some performance benefits already, either by avoiding temp...</description>
      <author> (Dotnet-GitSync-Bot)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/38722</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 01:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing TLS Certificate Lifespans to 398 Days – Mozilla Security Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.mozilla.org/security/2020/07/09/reducing-tls-certificate-lifespans-to-398-days/</link>
      <description>We intend to update Mozilla’s Root Store Policy to reduce the maximum lifetime of TLS certificates from 825 days to 398 days, with the aim of protecting our user's HTTPS ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.mozilla.org/security/2020/07/09/reducing-tls-certificate-lifespans-to-398-days/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 01:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't close your MacBook, MacBook Air, or MacBook Pro with a cover over the camera</title>
      <link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT211148</link>
      <description>Closing your Mac notebook with a camera cover on it might damage your display. Designed to protect your privacy, Mac notebooks have a camera indicator light to let you know when the camera is on.

</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT211148</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1651828 - DigiCert: Delay of revocation for EV audit inconsistency incident</title>
      <link>https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=1651828</link>
      <description>ASSIGNED (brenda.bernal) in NSS - CA Certificate Compliance. Last updated 2020-07-10.</description>
      <author> (Ryan Sleevi)</author>
      <guid>https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=1651828</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, node_modules are not heavy - Chaotic good engineering</title>
      <link>https://korshakov.com/posts/no-node-modules-are-not-heavy/</link>
      <description>node_modules are often discussed as a sink hole of a disk space, but is't that different from other platforms?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://korshakov.com/posts/no-node-modules-are-not-heavy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing CPAs, Explained</title>
      <link>https://mackgrenfell.com/blog/marketing-cpas-explained</link>
      <description>In marketing, what is a CPA? This sounds like a simple question, but understanding its answer in detail can teach you a huge amount about the fundamentals of marketing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mackgrenfell.com/blog/marketing-cpas-explained</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyboardio Atreus Review - sulami's blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.sulami.xyz/posts/atreus/</link>
      <description>I recently received my early bird Keybardio Atreus Promotional photo courtesy of Keyboardio from the Kickstarter and have now been using it for about three weeks, so I am writing a review for folks considering buying one after release.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sulami.xyz/posts/atreus/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Frink is Good, the Unit is Evil • Hillel Wayne</title>
      <link>https://www.hillelwayne.com/post/frink/</link>
      <description>One day Alan Eliasen read a fart joke and got so mad he invented a programming language. 20 years later Frink is one of the best special purpose languages for dealing with units.
“But why do we need a language just for dealing with units?” Glad you asked!
Intro to Units A unit is the physical property a number represents, like distance or time. We almost always are talking about SI units, or Système international.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hillelwayne.com/post/frink/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This blog is now running on solar power</title>
      <link>https://louwrentius.com/this-blog-is-now-running-on-solar-power.html</link>
      <description>This blog is now running on solar power.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://louwrentius.com/this-blog-is-now-running-on-solar-power.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Alternative Investments · Sturm Mabie</title>
      <link>https://cryptm.org/posts/2020/07/09/alt.html</link>
      <description>A retail investor would be forgiven for assuming that there are really
only two assets classes one should consider for personal investments:
equities (stocks) and fixed income (bonds). Wherever you look, these two
asset classes dominate the financial landscape. All robo-advisors and
most personal advisors implement a mix of bonds and equities for the
portfolio's of their clients. The idea behind this mix is simple: bonds
are low risk and will earn you a marginal return, while equities are
riskier and will be the real engine of returns in good times. In bad
times, bonds will rise, mitigating some of the losses of your equity
portfolio: it's been long known and accepted that stocks and bonds have
a negative correlation. Tying this strategy together is periodic
rebalancing, taking money off the table during bull markets (and moving
them to the safer bonds), and deploying money to the equity portion
during bear markets. This in effect overlays a mean-reversion strategy
onto the portfolio, boosting the returns of an otherwise static
portfolio. The archetypal allocation is 60% equities, and 40% bonds,
though each investor's allocation is going to differ based on his risk
tolerance, age, and personal goals.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cryptm.org/posts/2020/07/09/alt.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Polymath Playbook</title>
      <link>https://salman.io/posts/polymath-playbook/</link>
      <description>An exploration of my learnings and experiences with the polymath lifestyle. In a world built for specialization, the polymath approach can help us build unique mental models to differentiate ourselves, and the opportunity to discover meaningful work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://salman.io/posts/polymath-playbook/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving Therapy - Now on YouTube — cdahmedeh</title>
      <link>https://www.cdahmedeh.net/blog/2020/7/5/therapeutic-driving</link>
      <description>I personally find driving to be very therapeutic and many others do as well. Not only does it allow time for pondering and reflection but the change of scenery helps refresh our thoughts. The sights and sounds can be stimulating and can keep our minds occupied and away from unpleasant ideas.   To sh</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cdahmedeh.net/blog/2020/7/5/therapeutic-driving</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get your first Enterprise customer after having several SMB customers</title>
      <link>https://blog.luap.info/how-to-get-your-first-enterprise-customer-after-having-several-smb-customers.html?hn=</link>
      <description>You have read my article on the differences between Saas enterprise and Saas SMB you are currently selling to SMB and are wondering how you can get your first Enterprise customer, I will try to help you do so. If you have read my article carefully you know that what …</description>
      <author> (Paul)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.luap.info/how-to-get-your-first-enterprise-customer-after-having-several-smb-customers.html?hn=</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disabling Google 2FA Doesn't Need 2FA </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/07/google-password-2fa-woes/</link>
      <description>A developer's machine, compromised by attackers, was able to use Safari auto-fill to log into passwords.google.com, disable 2FA and extract passwords without notification. InfoQ spoke to Amos (@fasterthanlime) on Twitter about his experience and advice for others who might find themselves in the same situation. Read on to find out what happened, and what you should do to protect your assets.</description>
      <author> (Alex Blewitt
                
            
        Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/07/google-password-2fa-woes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 21:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong Generalization and Efficiency in Neural Programs</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2007.03629</link>
      <description>We study the problem of learning efficient algorithms that strongly
generalize in the framework of neural program induction. By carefully designing
the input / output interfaces of the neural model and through imitation, we are
able to learn models that produce correct results for arbitrary input sizes,
achieving strong generalization. Moreover, by using reinforcement learning, we
optimize for program efficiency metrics, and discover new algorithms that
surpass the teacher used in imitation. With this, our approach can learn to
outperform custom-written solutions for a variety of problems, as we tested it
on sorting, searching in ordered lists and the NP-complete 0/1 knapsack
problem, which sets a notable milestone in the field of Neural Program
Induction. As highlights, our learned model can perform sorting perfectly on
any input data size we tested on, with $O(n log n)$ complexity, whilst
outperforming hand-coded algorithms, including quick sort, in number of
operations even for list sizes far beyond those seen during training.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 7 Jul 2020 (v1), last revised 8 Jul 2020 (this version, v2)])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2007.03629</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 20:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MikeCodesDotNET/ColoredBadges</title>
      <link>https://github.com/MikeCodesDotNET/ColoredBadges</link>
      <description>Some badges I created for my GitHub profile readme.  - MikeCodesDotNET/ColoredBadges</description>
      <author> (MikeCodesDotNET)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/MikeCodesDotNET/ColoredBadges</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 19:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Startup Week | 2020 Session Selection | Building a Developer Community: Lesson Learned</title>
      <link>https://www.denverstartupweek.org/voting/6406-building-a-developer-community-lesson-learned</link>
      <description>From a small startup to a Fortune 500 company, it has been an amazing journey and a new lesson learned at each step. Join me, a program manager at Microsoft, as we take a walk down memory lane to learn about the ways you should (or should not) build your local and global developer communities. In...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.denverstartupweek.org/voting/6406-building-a-developer-community-lesson-learned</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 19:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWDC 2020 Followup Survey</title>
      <link>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/7JYKSYW</link>
      <description>Take this survey powered by surveymonkey.com. Create your own surveys for free.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/7JYKSYW</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 19:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loading Related Data - EF Core</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/ef/core/querying/related-data#single-and-split-queries</link>
      <description>Entity Framework Core allows you to use the navigation properties in your model to load related entities. There are three common O/RM patterns used to load related data.</description>
      <author> (rowanmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/ef/core/querying/related-data#single-and-split-queries</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 18:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Kubernetes for Developers </title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/metrotorontoug/events/271843529/</link>
      <description>Thu, Oct 15, 2020, 6:00 PM: Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) is a managed container orchestration service. With Kubernetes continuing to grow in popularity, many developers and IT engineers are curious </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/metrotorontoug/events/271843529/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 18:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bourne Collection: Online Search Is Older than You Think! - CHM</title>
      <link>https://computerhistory.org/blog/the-bourne-collection-online-search-is-older-than-you-think/</link>
      <description>Charlie Bourne was an expert in computerized search for 40 years before Google. CHM has recently finished cataloging his unique collection of materials documenting the history of online search and information systems from the 1950s onward, supported by a generous grant from the National Archives.</description>
      <author> (Marc Weber)</author>
      <guid>https://computerhistory.org/blog/the-bourne-collection-online-search-is-older-than-you-think/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 17:18:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LibreOffice: the next five years</title>
      <link>https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/825598/21fb7c2a3f9358e7/</link>
      <description>The LibreOffice project would
seem to be on a roll.  It produces what is widely seen as the leading
free office-productivity suite, and has managed to move out of the shadow
of the moribund (but brand-recognized) Apache
OpenOffice project.  The 
LibreOffice 7 release is coming within a month, and the tenth
anniversary of the founding of the Document Foundation arrives in
September.  Meanwhile, LibreOffice
Online is taking off and, seemingly, seeing some market success.
So it is a bit surprising to see the project's core developers
in a sort of crisis mode while users worry about a tag that showed up in
the project's repository.</description>
      <author> (By Jonathan CorbetJuly 9, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/825598/21fb7c2a3f9358e7/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 17:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Years To Make $10 in Software Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.beamjobs.com/startups/2-years-to-make-10-dollars-in-software-revenue</link>
      <description>It took us over two years to make $10 in revenue through software we made. We made a lot of mistakes we hope you can learn from on the way.</description>
      <author> (Stephen Greet, Co-founder  July 9, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://www.beamjobs.com/startups/2-years-to-make-10-dollars-in-software-revenue</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:19:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criteo R&amp;D Blog – Medium</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/criteo-labs</link>
      <description>Tech stories from the R&amp;D team.</description>
      <author> (Maxime KestemontJul 2)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/criteo-labs</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start Your Career as a Frontend Developer with Scrimba</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QdeV4qhK1KU</link>
      <description>Self-learning to become a Web Developer is not easy. Scrimba just released its Frontend Developer Career Path that will give you guidance as you look to make that transition in your career. With over 70 hours of content from amazing instructors (some big names you'll probably recognize), you'll have a ton of top-notch content to work through.

This career path full price costs $39/month, but if you sign up in July, you'll lock in a price at $25/month for life and get access to all of the amazing content Scrimba has to offer.

Career Path Sign Up - https://bit.ly/scrimbapath
_____________________________________________

Newsletter 🗞
Interested in exclusive content and discounts? 🤯 
https://www.jamesqquick.com/newsletter
_____________________________________________

Connect with me 😀
Live streams on Twitch - https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
Follow me on Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Join the 💬 Discord Server 💬 - https://discord.gg/vM2bagU
_____________________________________________

COURSES  💻
Learn how to build Fullstack apps with React and Serverless Functions - https://www.jamesqquick.com/courses/react-and-serverless-fullstack-developmnent
Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code - https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/
Build a Quiz App  - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QdeV4qhK1KU</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 14:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App suddenly crashing on startup in production due to FBSDKRestrictiveDataFilterManager.m · Issue #1427 · facebook/facebook-ios-sdk</title>
      <link>https://github.com/facebook/facebook-ios-sdk/issues/1427</link>
      <description>Checklist I&amp;#39;ve updated to the latest released version of the SDK I&amp;#39;ve searched for existing GitHub issues I&amp;#39;ve looked for existing answers on Stack Overflow, the Facebook Developer Comm...</description>
      <author> (JCBird1012)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/facebook/facebook-ios-sdk/issues/1427</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 14:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ten modern layouts in one line of CSS</title>
      <link>https://web.dev/one-line-layouts/</link>
      <description>This post highlights a few powerful lines of CSS that do some serious heavy lifting and help you build robust modern layouts.</description>
      <author> (Jul 7, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://web.dev/one-line-layouts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 13:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>