<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>AI is Creating a Generation of Illiterate Programmers</title>
      <link>https://nmn.gl/blog/ai-illiterate-programmers</link>
      <description>A couple of days ago, Cursor went down during the ChatGPT outage. I stared at my terminal facing those red error messages that I hate to see. An AWS error glared back at me. I didn’t want to figure it out without AI’s help. After 12 years of coding, I’d somehow become worse at my own craft. And this isn’t hyperbole—this is the new reality for software developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nmn.gl/blog/ai-illiterate-programmers</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 19:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Simplest Way To Deploy Containerized .NET Applications on AWS</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=L48wmpSuots</link>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;#39;m James Eastham. Portability is a key principle when building modern applications.  In this video, I demonstrate how to take a container image, &amp;#39;plant based pizza&amp;#39;, and run it on AWS using ECS Fargate.

Learn about the advantages of ECS Fargate, the importance of infrastructure as code, and the CDK (Cloud Development Kit) for simplifying deployment. By the end of this video, you&amp;#39;ll understand how to set up clusters, define task definitions, and manage networking resources for your containerized web applications on AWS.

00:00 Introduction to Portability
00:50 Running Containers on AWS
01:14 Understanding Amazon ECS and Fargate
02:42 Defining and Deploying Applications on ECS Fargate
05:31 Using AWS CDK for Infrastructure as Code
10:11 Deploying and Verifying the Application
12:37 Conclusion and Best Practices

GitHub Repo - https://github.com/jeastham1993/PlantBasedPizza/tree/microservices-module-1</description>
      <author> (James Eastham)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=L48wmpSuots</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Project Planning, Test Generation, and Docker</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DPL1Dan8A8s</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Let&amp;#39;s work on SharpSite, an open source CMS that you can contribute to and learn from.  https://sharpsite.org</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DPL1Dan8A8s</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing My New Book: htmx Essentials for ASP.NET Core Developers - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/announcing-my-new-book-htmx-essentials-for-asp-net-core-developers/</link>
      <description>As a developer, you know the web development landscape constantly evolves, and staying ahead means embracing tools and practices that simplify and enhance how we build applications. That&amp;#39;s why I&amp;#39;m thrilled to announce my latest project: &amp;quot;htmx Essentials for ASP.NET Core Developers.&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/announcing-my-new-book-htmx-essentials-for-asp-net-core-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust&amp;#39;s Superpower: Speed Meets Smarts - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/rusts-superpower-speed-meets-smarts/</link>
      <description>Regarding speed and efficiency, Rust doesn’t just run the race—it leaves other languages eating its dust. Built for blazing performance and low-level control, Rust’s unique features make it a standout choice for projects where every millisecond and megabyte count. Let’s dive into why Rust is the Usain Bolt of programming languages and how it stacks up in the performance department.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/rusts-superpower-speed-meets-smarts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Monolith Architecture: The Missing Guide to Public APIs</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=0ZrjLEIBRWw</link>
      <description>Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Get the source code here: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic

Learn how to transform a monolithic application into a well-structured modular system with clean public APIs. This guide covers essential concepts of modularity, coupling, and architecture testing to help you build maintainable applications. From basic principles to practical implementation, discover how to create explicit contracts and move from direct data access to professional public APIs.

Internal vs. Public APIs in Modular Monoliths
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/internal-vs-public-apis-in-modular-monoliths

What Is a Modular Monolith?
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/what-is-a-modular-monolith

Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters
0:00 Modular Monolith intro
1:26 Modularity and Coupling
3:16 Improving the design
5:07 Defining a Public Contract
6:43 Enforcing Modularity - Architecture tests
9:14 Exposing a Public API - Extract interface
10:32 Make Coupling explicit and controlled
11:03 Testing the improved implementation
12:32 Moving from direct data access to Public API</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=0ZrjLEIBRWw</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T. Rex Evolution</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3042/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3042/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t Use the New HybridCache of .NET 9</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SNoJtwiY4c4</link>
      <description>Check out my workshops and use code WORKSHOP20S for 20% off: https://bit.ly/4jmXbpI
Subscribe to my weekly newsletter: https://nickchapsas.com

Become a Patreon and get special perks: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsas

Hello, everybody. I&amp;#39;m Nick, and in this video, I will show you why you shouldn&amp;#39;t use the new HybridCache of .NET 9 and use FusionCache v2 instead!

Give FusionCache a star on GItHub: https://github.com/ZiggyCreatures/FusionCache

Workshops: https://bit.ly/nickworkshops

Don&amp;#39;t forget to comment, like and subscribe :)

Social Media:
Follow me on GitHub: https://github.com/Elfocrash
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/nickchapsas
Connect on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick-chapsas

Keep coding merch: https://keepcoding.shop

#csharp #dotnet</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SNoJtwiY4c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>almost_pwned.md</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/zachlatta/f86317493654b550c689dc6509973aa4</link>
      <description>GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/zachlatta/f86317493654b550c689dc6509973aa4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Walther (@isziaui@mstdn.social)</title>
      <link>https://mstdn.social/@isziaui/113874436953157913</link>
      <description>Attached: 1 image

@gvy_dvpont@mastodon.social Got me thinking… can it be done without the lens? This one seems to work!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mstdn.social/@isziaui/113874436953157913</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 06:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefly III - Backup / Restore volume</title>
      <link>https://slothycode.com/firefly-finance-manager-restore-volume/</link>
      <description>Firefly is an amazing web-app that helps you keep track of your expenses, split them into categories, add tags, income sources and liabilities and many other features.  Recently I switched to a new laptop and could not start using it until I had also transferred the said application (easy part)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://slothycode.com/firefly-finance-manager-restore-volume/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 03:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the most unhinged AVX-512 instruction to make the fastest phrase search algo</title>
      <link>https://gab-menezes.github.io/2025/01/13/using-the-most-unhinged-avx-512-instruction-to-make-the-fastest-phrase-search-algo.html</link>
      <description>Disclaimers before we start For those who don’t want to read/don’t care that much, here are the results. I hope after seeing them you are compelled to read. TL;DR: I wrote a super fast phrase search algorithm using AVX-512 and achieved wins up to 1600x the performance of Meilisearch. The source code can be found here, and here is the crate. The contents of this blog post are inspired by the wonderful idea of Doug Turnbull from the series of blog posts about Roaringish. Here we will take these ideas to an extreme, from smart algorithms to raw performance optimization. I highly recommend reading the Roaringish blog post, but if you don’t want to, there will be a recap on how it works. This project has been almost 7 months in the making, with thousands and thousands of lines of code written and rewritten, so bear with me if I sound crazy. At the moment of writing, there are almost 2.7k LOC, but I have committed around 17k LOC (let’s take a few thousand because of .lock files) (probably at the time of publishing this number has increased), so the project has been rewritten almost 6 times.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gab-menezes.github.io/2025/01/13/using-the-most-unhinged-avx-512-instruction-to-make-the-fastest-phrase-search-algo.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating SotA LLM Models trying to solve a net-new LeetCode style puzzle</title>
      <link>https://arnav.tech/evaluating-sota-llm-models-trying-to-solve-a-net-new-leetcode-style-puzzle</link>
      <description>Claude, GPT, Gemini and DeepSeek try to find optimal placement for men occupying urinal stalls in a restroom!</description>
      <author> (https://hashnode.com/@arnavgupta)</author>
      <guid>https://arnav.tech/evaluating-sota-llm-models-trying-to-solve-a-net-new-leetcode-style-puzzle</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C Is Not Suited to SIMD</title>
      <link>http://blog.vmchale.com/article/notes-c-simd</link>
      <description>C (C++) is used to write performant software, however it is ill-suited to
SIMD. In particular, its compilation of stepped reduction with lexical scoping opposes parallel execution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://blog.vmchale.com/article/notes-c-simd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogging with Friction</title>
      <link>https://rishikeshs.com/blogging-friction/</link>
      <description>A reflection on my journey from WordPress to Hugo, embracing the challenges, creativity, and joy of blogging with friction—written as my entry for January&amp;#39;s IndieWeb Carnival.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rishikeshs.com/blogging-friction/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>:hover &amp;gt; :not(:hover), sorry not sorry &amp;#183; January 6, 2025</title>
      <link>https://nerdy.dev/hover-not-hover-sorry-not-sorry</link>
      <description>Focus by demotion.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nerdy.dev/hover-not-hover-sorry-not-sorry</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
      Noteworthy LLM Research Papers of 2024
    </title>
      <link>https://sebastianraschka.com/blog/2025/llm-research-2024.html</link>
      <description>
        This article covers 12 influential AI research papers of 2024, ranging from mixture-of-experts models to new LLM scaling laws for precision..
      </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sebastianraschka.com/blog/2025/llm-research-2024.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I Would Want From a New Job</title>
      <link>https://technobabble.bearblog.dev/what-i-would-want-from-a-new-job/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been working as a software engineer for a number of years now, at the same company I joined after graduating as an undergrad. I&amp;#39;m reasonably happy with ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://technobabble.bearblog.dev/what-i-would-want-from-a-new-job/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can&amp;#39;t Escape Good Old SQL</title>
      <link>https://mattrighetti.com/2025/01/14/ditching-sea-query</link>
      <description>Query builders and ORMs have been around for as long as I can remember, eachserving different purposes. ORMs, for example, allow you to focus on applicationl...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mattrighetti.com/2025/01/14/ditching-sea-query</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replit, the Figma Replacement | Nic Bertino</title>
      <link>https://nicbertino.com/blog/figma-replit/</link>
      <description>Nic Bertino is a design leader, music maker, and disco lover out here getting people close to good design.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicbertino.com/blog/figma-replit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking together a Job Runner using Supabase Edge Functions</title>
      <link>https://duggan.ie/posts/hacking-together-a-job-runner-using-supabase-edge-functions</link>
      <description>subhead</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://duggan.ie/posts/hacking-together-a-job-runner-using-supabase-edge-functions</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becoming Literate Again | Jordan Koschei</title>
      <link>https://jordankoschei.com/becoming-literate-again/</link>
      <description>It’s almost impossible to talk about attention spans, the modern media environment, and “kids these days” without sounding like a self-righteous prig who’s r...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jordankoschei.com/becoming-literate-again/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invalid Niger Nameservers in the com zone</title>
      <link>https://0xda.de/blog/2025/01/invalid-niger-nameservers-in-the-com-zone/</link>
      <description>A recent post by Krebs On Security about a mastercard mistake in their nameservers got me thinking. I recently got access to the .com zone file, I could just… grep for this common type of mistake.
Towards the bottom of the article, he mentions that there is an awsdns-06.ne registered some time ago that fits a similar bill. This sparked a particular interest, because I happen to know that AWS uses an absolute ton of domains for their dns infrastructure, each would have to be registered individually in order to mitigate this issue.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://0xda.de/blog/2025/01/invalid-niger-nameservers-in-the-com-zone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Audio Madness: Setting a negative playback rate on an AudioBufferSourceNode</title>
      <link>https://andy-gallagher.com/blog/web-audio-madness-negative-playback-rate/</link>
      <description>Can I get a rewind?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andy-gallagher.com/blog/web-audio-madness-negative-playback-rate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://www.jmilinovich.com/writing/the-great-acceleration/</link>
      <description>This is the first essay in a series exploring how artificial general intelligence will transform the human experience. Each piece examines a different dimension of this unprecedented transition. Future essays will be shared via my newsletter.

Time does not flow evenly through history. Some years contain more transformation than entire</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jmilinovich.com/writing/the-great-acceleration/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why you’ll leave X (as well as Instagram and all the other private platforms)</title>
      <link>https://allr.cat/why-youll-leave-x-as-well-as-instagram-and-all-the-other-private-platforms/</link>
      <description>(translated from Catalan by Alain Gertrand)



You too will leave X, Instagram and all the other big platforms that, for now, seem like irreplaceable components of our lives. The golden age of these social networks is behind us. And yes, that means for you, too.



The 2.0 boom lasted a good ten yea</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://allr.cat/why-youll-leave-x-as-well-as-instagram-and-all-the-other-private-platforms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be afraid of rabbit holes</title>
      <link>https://branislavjenco.github.io/rabbit-holes/</link>
      <description>I’ve gotten myself into some deep rabbit holes in the course of everyday software development. I find some surprising behavior, or an apparent bug, and before I know it, 57 tabs are open in my browser. They hold a record of my journey through the source code of 5 different codebases, their GitHub Issues, their fork’s GitHub Issues, Stack Overflow, paywalled Medium articles that weren’t worth opening and, these days, a conversation with a helpful-but-not-really LLM.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://branislavjenco.github.io/rabbit-holes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - ggml-org/llama.vim: Vim plugin for LLM-assisted code/text completion</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ggml-org/llama.vim</link>
      <description>Vim plugin for LLM-assisted code/text completion. Contribute to ggml-org/llama.vim development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ggml-org/llama.vim</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 23:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVSS is dead to us</title>
      <link>https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2025/01/23/cvss-is-dead-to-us/</link>
      <description>CVSS is short for Common Vulnerability Scoring System and is according to Wikipedia a technical standard for assessing the severity of vulnerabilities in computing systems. Typically you use an online CVSS calculator, click a few checkboxes and radio buttons and then you magically get a number from 0 to 10. There are also different versions … Continue reading CVSS is dead to us →</description>
      <author> (https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/author/daniel/)</author>
      <guid>https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2025/01/23/cvss-is-dead-to-us/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 20:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>