<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/introduction-github-actions</link>
      <description>In this post, you&amp;#39;ll learn the building blocks of GitHub Actions (which allows you to automate your development task), with two basic workflows as examples.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/introduction-github-actions</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 06:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing safe deployment with AIOps—introducing Gandalf</title>
      <link>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/advancing-safe-deployment-with-aiops-introducing-gandalf/?WT.mc_id=DOP-MVP-4025064</link>
      <description>The continuous monitoring of health metrics is a fundamental part of this process, and this is where AIOps plays a critical role. In the post that follows, we introduce how AI&amp;#160;and machine learning&amp;#160;are used to empower DevOps engineers,&amp;#160;monitor the Azure deployment process at scale, detect issue...</description>
      <author> (Mark Russinovich
            Chief Technology Officer and Technical Fellow, Microsoft Azure)</author>
      <guid>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/advancing-safe-deployment-with-aiops-introducing-gandalf/?WT.mc_id=DOP-MVP-4025064</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 06:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follower Reads</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/follower-reads.html</link>
      <description>Serve read requests from followers to achieve better throughput 
          and lower latency</description>
      <author> (by Unmesh Joshi)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/follower-reads.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 06:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing TypeScript 4.4 Beta</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-4-4-beta/</link>
      <description>Today we are excited to announce the beta release of TypeScript 4.4! To get started using the beta, you can get it&amp;#160;through NuGet, or use npm with the following command: npm install typescript@beta You can also get editor support by Downloading for Visual Studio 2019/2017 Following directions for&amp;#160;Visual Studio Code&amp;#160;and&amp;#160;Sublime Text 3.</description>
      <author> (Daniel Rosenwasser)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-4-4-beta/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 06:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Locks API - Web APIs | MDN</title>
      <link>https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/Web_Locks_API</link>
      <description>The Web Locks API allows scripts running in one tab or worker to asynchronously acquire a lock, hold it while work is performed, then release it. While held, no other script executing in the same origin can acquire the same lock, which allows a web app running in multiple tabs or workers to coordinate work and the use of resources.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/Web_Locks_API</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 05:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document</title>
      <link>https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1783879/000162828021013318/robinhoods-1.htm</link>
      <description>As filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission on July 1, 2021.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1783879/000162828021013318/robinhoods-1.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 05:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com: Quarter Share: A Trader&amp;#39;s Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper, Book 1 (Audible Audio Edition): Nathan Lowell, Jeffrey Kafer, Podium Audio: Audible Audiobooks</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/Quarter-Share-Nathan-Lowell-audiobook/dp/B01ETJATYY?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202107</link>
      <description>Amazon.com: Quarter Share: A Trader&amp;#39;s Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper, Book 1 (Audible Audio Edition): Nathan Lowell, Jeffrey Kafer, Podium Audio: Audible Audiobooks</description>
      <author> (Nathan Lowell







(Author),)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/Quarter-Share-Nathan-Lowell-audiobook/dp/B01ETJATYY?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202107</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 04:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotnet/roslyn-analyzers</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/roslyn-analyzers/blob/main/src/Microsoft.CodeAnalysis.BannedApiAnalyzers/BannedApiAnalyzers.Help.md</link>
      <description>Contribute to dotnet/roslyn-analyzers development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/roslyn-analyzers/blob/main/src/Microsoft.CodeAnalysis.BannedApiAnalyzers/BannedApiAnalyzers.Help.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 03:04:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualtrics Survey | Qualtrics Experience Management</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_bxsyEPpffF3cqQm</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://microsoft.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_bxsyEPpffF3cqQm</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 02:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Foundation Project Spotlight - Wix</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qzapPthJBQM</link>
      <description>.NET Foundation Marketing Committee member Isaac Levin spoke to Rob Mensching, one the maintainers of WiX Toolset. For more detail, be sure to check out the ...</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
  
    .NET Foundation
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qzapPthJBQM</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 01:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 383 - Something cool in Azure</title>
      <link>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-383-Something-cool-in-Azure</link>
      <description>Episode 248 - Updates from Ignite 2018A whole bunch of Azure updates were announced at Ignite so Cynthia, Cale and Sujit try to cover as m...Episode 316 - SAP on AzureMicrosoft Cloud Solution Architect, Marc B&amp;#246;hnke, gives us the low-down on the partnership betwe...Episode 271 - Azure Stack - Tales from the fieldAzure Stack experts from Microsoft Services, Heyko Oelrichs and Rathish Ravikumar, give us an update...</description>
      <author> (Evan Basalik)</author>
      <guid>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-383-Something-cool-in-Azure</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 01:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legion 7 Gen 6 (16&amp;quot; AMD) QHD Gaming Laptop | Lenovo US</title>
      <link>https://www.lenovo.com/us/en/laptops/legion-laptops/legion-7-series/Legion-7-16ACH6/p/88GMY701639</link>
      <description>Shop the NEW Lenovo Legion 7 Gen 6 gaming laptop with the WORLD’S FIRST 16” QHD display ✅ NVIDIA&amp;#174; GeForce RTX™ 30 Series ✅ AMD Ryzen™ ✅ FREE SHIPPING</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lenovo.com/us/en/laptops/legion-laptops/legion-7-series/Legion-7-16ACH6/p/88GMY701639</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com: Ozgoe Happy Bell (14 Pack) Universal Mount Metal Plate with Adhesive for All Magnetic Car Mount Cell Phone Holder Cradle-Less Air Vent Mount -– Rectangular and Round,Black</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/dp/B073NZ68M1?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202107</link>
      <description>Buy Ozgoe Happy Bell (14 Pack) Universal Mount Metal Plate with Adhesive for All Magnetic Car Mount Cell Phone Holder Cradle-Less Air Vent Mount -– Rectangular and Round, Black: Cradles - Amazon.com ✓ FREE DELIVERY possible on eligible purchases</description>
      <author> (Brand: Ozgoe)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/dp/B073NZ68M1?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202107</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Saving to Disk with C# Asynchronous Streams</title>
      <link>http://www.leerichardson.com/2021/07/csharp-asynchronous-streams.html</link>
      <description>Explains what asynchrnous streams are, and shows a real world performance problem they can solve.</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>http://www.leerichardson.com/2021/07/csharp-asynchronous-streams.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 23:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These old programming languages are still critical to big companies. But nobody wants to learn them</title>
      <link>https://www.techrepublic.com/article/these-old-programming-languages-are-still-critical-to-big-companies-but-nobody-wants-to-learn-them/</link>
      <description>Large organizations still rely on ageing IT systems and programming languages to run their mainframes. But as traditional developers reach retirement age, new hires are reluctant to pick up old skills.</description>
      <author> (Owen Hughes)</author>
      <guid>https://www.techrepublic.com/article/these-old-programming-languages-are-still-critical-to-big-companies-but-nobody-wants-to-learn-them/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 23:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptology ePrint Archive: Report 2021/616</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2021/616</link>
      <description>An  Efficient   and  Generic  Construction  for  Signal&amp;#39;s  Handshake (X3DH):  Post-Quantum,  State  Leakage  Secure,   and  Deniable</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://eprint.iacr.org/2021/616</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 22:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Codespaces Alternative: AWS Cloud9, SSH &amp;amp; VS Code -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/07/01/aws-vscode.aspx</link>
      <description> Amazon Web Services offers up a remote development setup for Visual Studio Code developers that involves an SSH connection to leverage the AWS Cloud9 IDE and other functionality. </description>
      <author> (By David Ramel07/01/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/07/01/aws-vscode.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 21:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An update on report of scraped data</title>
      <link>https://news.linkedin.com/2021/june/an-update-from-linkedin</link>
      <description>Our teams have investigated a set of alleged LinkedIn data that has been posted for sale. We want to be clear that this is not a data breach and no private LinkedIn member data was exposed. Our initial investigation has found that this data was scraped from LinkedIn and other various websites and includes the same data reported earlier this year in our April 2021 scraping update. Members trust LinkedIn with their data, and any misuse of our members’ data, such as scraping, violates LinkedIn terms of service. When anyone tries to take member data and use it for purposes LinkedIn and our members haven’t agreed to, we work to stop them and hold them accountable. For additional information about our policies and how we protect member data from misuse: https://www.linkedin.com/help/linkedin/answer/56347/prohibited-software-and-extensions</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://news.linkedin.com/2021/june/an-update-from-linkedin</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 21:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Most useful Note taking tool</title>
      <link>https://mark.mcnally.je/blog/post/My%20Most%20useful%20Note%20taking%20tool</link>
      <description>I take a lot of notes, most of the time I use my normal note taking system which I am not going to go into detail on this post.</description>
      <author> (Author: 
    Mark)</author>
      <guid>https://mark.mcnally.je/blog/post/My%20Most%20useful%20Note%20taking%20tool</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 21:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking The Monolith I</title>
      <link>https://paprikati.github.io/2021/07/01/breaking-the-monolith-1.html</link>
      <description>It is a truth universally acknowledged that a scale-up in possession of a monolith must be in want of microservices.</description>
      <author> (Lisa Karlin Curtis)</author>
      <guid>https://paprikati.github.io/2021/07/01/breaking-the-monolith-1.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 21:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do Open Source Companies Make Money?</title>
      <link>https://www.karllhughes.com/posts/open-source-companies</link>
      <description>A few weeks ago post, I wrote about the case for simple business models in startups. This sparked a later conversation about open source companies ...</description>
      <author> (https://www.karllhughes.com)</author>
      <guid>https://www.karllhughes.com/posts/open-source-companies</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 21:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geeking out to Visual Studio with Kendra Havens</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Milton-Keynes-NET-Meetup-Group/events/276272009/</link>
      <description>Tue, Sep 14, 2021, 6:00 PM: Greetings .NET lovers!The awesome Kendra Havens will be joining is to geek out on all things Vidual Studio!!About KendraKendra Havens is a program manager at Microsoft on t</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/Milton-Keynes-NET-Meetup-Group/events/276272009/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 21:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome will get an HTTPS-Only Mode for secure browsing</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-will-get-an-https-only-mode-for-secure-browsing/</link>
      <description>Google is working on adding an HTTPS-Only Mode to the Chrome web browser to protect users&amp;#39; web traffic from eavesdropping by upgrading all connections to HTTPS.</description>
      <author> (Sergiu Gatlan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-will-get-an-https-only-mode-for-secure-browsing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 21:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Commands, Queries, and Clean Architecture</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IRvDGPbxdTs</link>
      <description>Our friend Ian Cooper returns for another live session to talk to us about implementing  clean architecture in our .NET applications Featuring: Ian Cooper (@...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •
  
  
    
      1K views
    
      Streamed 3 hours ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IRvDGPbxdTs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 21:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIOS settings are LOCKED! Can&amp;#39;t change boot order, upgrade storage, or disable UEFI for Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/RKILN7HFLF4CS/?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202107</link>
      <description>I bought this to replace a 7 year old Linux gaming computer (dual-boot, multi-drive) with a corroded power supply, expecting to install a couple extra hard drives, while still playing a few games on the original Windows drive it shipped with. After a little research, it looked like I wouldn&amp;#39;t have a lot of trouble installing drivers for the hardware that comes with this model, and the price was reasonably low compared with System76, so I went ahead and ordered it.BIOS and hardware upgrades: Once the 2nd drive I ordered arrived (separate packages, couple days later), I proceeded to install the 1 TB drive along with the 500 GB drive from my old system, using the upgrade kit which came with this computer. Taking apart the computer was fairly straightforward, but because Linux requires you to disable Secure Boot, I proceeded into the BIOS to enable booting from USB and turn off Secure Boot and UEFI. The BIOS password was NOT set, and I was allowed to add one of my own, but all the settings related to security and boot order were still greyed out. Despite installing 2 additional drives, and being allowed to set a password for one of them, I was not allowed to boot from anything except the 500 GB drive this computer shipped with or any kind of external media.I called the support number in the pamphlet that came with the computer, and asked about this, but was told that Acer locks the BIOS on all computers shipped through Amazon in order to &amp;quot;protect&amp;quot; customers from changing things that might break the computer if they don&amp;#39;t know what they&amp;#39;re doing. He explained that all computer vendors do this to one extent to another, such as Apple with iPhones, and refused to provide me any means to unlock it no matter how technical I am. He continued that if I want to upgrade anything, I should call Acer&amp;#39;s main customer service line and order it from them, instead of trying to modify it myself. At this point, I demanded a refund because the item was materially different from what was advertised, and effectively unusable for my purposes as a result, but he refused because the package was already opened. I pointed out the product description did not list the BIOS being locked, and based on forum postings about this model on Acer&amp;#39;s website, locking the BIOS did not appear to be a standard configuration for this model, but he stated that&amp;#39;s what Acer wanted for Amazon-shipped computers, and that they&amp;#39;re under no obligation to disclose this information prior to purchase, so I replied I will simply complain to Amazon and seek a refund through them. I did try contacting Acer&amp;#39;s customer support number listed on Amazon, and on their own website; after a few days of trying, I did eventually reach someone (average wait time of 60 minutes), who ultimately confirmed Acer intends to limit customers&amp;#39; ability to change boot sequence for their &amp;quot;protection&amp;quot;.Keyboard: This was a real nuisance. The 1 key, Q key, Z key, and I think a couple others make a distinct &amp;quot;clicking&amp;quot; noise when I press them, sometimes don&amp;#39;t press in properly, and feel like they will pop out or otherwise break within about a month or so of use. It also has some weird light-up pattern that runs from left to right and flickers a bit as soon as it lights up. Almost looks like something is wrong, and might burn out in a few months.Battery life: While waiting for the 2nd hard drive to arrive, I played Elder Scrolls Online over Wifi a little bit. Computer was fast enough to handle it, but the battery died within about an hour, despite being brand new. Given how batteries decline over time, I worry about how it will perform after a few years.Screen quality: Says it&amp;#39;s 1920x1080, but looks a little pixelated, which is kind of weird. I don&amp;#39;t know how to describe it, but the pixels look a little larger than I&amp;#39;d expect, and the computer defaulted to a lower resolution out of the box for some reason. Nothing too special or standout-ish, I&amp;#39;ve seen better, but also not terrible.</description>
      <author> (byAcer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/RKILN7HFLF4CS/?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202107</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 21:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java on Azure: Azure Spring Cloud Integrates with New Relic One Performance Monitoring -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/07/01/new-relic-azure.aspx</link>
      <description>  Microsoft&amp;#39;s Java on Azure team announced the integration of New Relic One performance monitoring in Azure Spring Cloud, used to deploy Spring Boot–based microservice applications to Azure.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel07/01/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/07/01/new-relic-azure.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 19:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>angularsen/UnitsNet</title>
      <link>https://github.com/angularsen/UnitsNet</link>
      <description>Makes life working with units of measurement just a little bit better. - angularsen/UnitsNet</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/angularsen/UnitsNet</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Account Takeover Protection and WAF mitigations to help stop Global Brute Force Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/patching-the-internet-against-global-brute-force-campaigns/</link>
      <description>Today, we are making our Account Takeover Protection capabilities available to all paid plans at no additional charge.</description>
      <author> (Michael Tremante)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/patching-the-internet-against-global-brute-force-campaigns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 18:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timekeeper Tutorial V0.6.2 (obsolete)</title>
      <link>https://yewtu.be/watch?v=dMjiX2NFIrg</link>
      <description>See the new version of this video at http://gslb.ch/timekeeper-tutorial</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yewtu.be/watch?v=dMjiX2NFIrg</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 18:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British right to repair law excludes smartphones and computers - 9to5Mac</title>
      <link>https://9to5mac.com/2021/07/01/british-right-to-repair-law/</link>
      <description>A British right to repair law comes into force today, requiring manufacturers to make spares available to both consumers and third-party ...</description>
      <author> (Ben Lovejoy)</author>
      <guid>https://9to5mac.com/2021/07/01/british-right-to-repair-law/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 18:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the new Azure Data Tables Libraries</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/announcing-the-new-azure-data-tables-libraries/</link>
      <description>We’re excited to announce that the Azure Data Tables libraries have been released for .NET, Java, JavaScript/TypeScript, and Python.</description>
      <author> (Sean Kane)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/announcing-the-new-azure-data-tables-libraries/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 18:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding, Cloud &amp;amp; Technology | An In Depth Look into Random Number Generation in .NET</title>
      <link>https://blogs.siliconorchid.com/post/coding-inspiration/randomness-in-dotnet/</link>
      <description>Working with the .NET System.Random class is, for a majority of usage scenarios, the appropriate “go-to” choice that developers should use.   There are very minor nuances to be mindful of, but working with this class is mostly straightforward.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.siliconorchid.com/post/coding-inspiration/randomness-in-dotnet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 17:28:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Object Allocation Tool Performance</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/net-object-allocation-tool-performance/</link>
      <description>With the release of Visual Studio 16.10 comes a new analysis engine for the Performance Profiler, with the .NET Object Allocation Tool being the first tool to be onboarded. This provides the tool with some new features and a significant perf boost.</description>
      <author> (Nik Karpinsky)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/net-object-allocation-tool-performance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 17:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dodyg/practical-aspnetcore</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dodyg/practical-aspnetcore/tree/net5.0/projects/net6/map-4</link>
      <description>Practical samples of ASP.NET Core 2.1, 2.2, 3.1, 5.0 and 6.0 Preview 5 projects you can use. Readme contains explanations on all projects. - dodyg/practical-aspnetcore</description>
      <author> (dodyg)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dodyg/practical-aspnetcore/tree/net5.0/projects/net6/map-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 17:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encoding data for POST requests</title>
      <link>https://jakearchibald.com/2021/encoding-data-for-post-requests/</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t do it like GitHub Copilot!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jakearchibald.com/2021/encoding-data-for-post-requests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 16:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Community Standup - Visual Studio Live Preview with Olia!!!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FwYf1FDsjXQ</link>
      <description>Join Maddy Leger, David Ortinau, and Olia Gavrysh for a .NET MAUI update and a demo of the new Live Preview feature in Visual Studio!Community Links: https:/...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FwYf1FDsjXQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:06:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studying linker error messages to find the cause of the unresolved external: Character sets</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210701-00/?p=105387</link>
      <description>A customer was encountering an unresolved external linker error when trying to link a plug-in with a static library. // header.h #define UNICODE #define _UNICODE #include &amp;lt;windows.h&amp;gt;  BOOL SetSessionName(LPCTSTR name);  This header file is used both by the implementation: // implementation.cpp #include &amp;quot;pch.h&amp;quot; #include &amp;lt;header.h&amp;gt;</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210701-00/?p=105387</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retro Reversing - Peek behind the curtain to see how your favourite video games were made.</title>
      <link>https://www.retroreversing.com/official-playStation-devkit</link>
      <description>This post covers the hardware used to develop Playstation One games by major studios back in the day, for the software side see the post on PsyQ.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.retroreversing.com/official-playStation-devkit</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exxon Lobbyists Reveal Climate Delay Strategy in Secret Recordings</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/exxon-lobbyists-reveal-in-secret-recordings-how-they-ma-1847205392</link>
      <description>A sting by Greenpeace UK exposes how the company talks a big climate game while ensuring nothing actually gets done.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gizmodo.com/exxon-lobbyists-reveal-in-secret-recordings-how-they-ma-1847205392</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:06:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of Android App Bundles is here</title>
      <link>https://android-developers.googleblog.com/2021/06/the-future-of-android-app-bundles-is.html</link>
      <description>    Posted by Dom Elliott, Product Manager at Google Play          Since we launched the Android App Bundle  in May 2018, we’ve seen our dev...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://android-developers.googleblog.com/2021/06/the-future-of-android-app-bundles-is.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bibliothecula - tagged document storage</title>
      <link>https://epilys.github.io/bibliothecula/notekeeping.html</link>
      <description>document organizer with tags and full-text-search, in a simple and clean sqlite3 schema</description>
      <author> (epilys)</author>
      <guid>https://epilys.github.io/bibliothecula/notekeeping.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fullstorydev/grpcui</title>
      <link>https://github.com/fullstorydev/grpcui</link>
      <description>An interactive web UI for gRPC, along the lines of postman - fullstorydev/grpcui</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/fullstorydev/grpcui</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:05:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grpc.AspNetCore.Server.Reflection 2.38.0</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Grpc.AspNetCore.Server.Reflection</link>
      <description>Automatic discovery of services for Grpc.Reflection</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Grpc.AspNetCore.Server.Reflection</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET R&amp;amp;D Digest (June, 2021)</title>
      <link>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2021/06/30/net-rd-digest-june-2021/</link>
      <description>This issue includes bits of .NET, .NET Internals, Computer Science, Visual Studio, Cloud and Software Engineering.</description>
      <author> (Oleg Karasik)</author>
      <guid>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2021/06/30/net-rd-digest-june-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-07-01</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/07/app-developer-links-2021-07-01/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/07/app-developer-links-2021-07-01/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 07:06:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Precious Resource is Agency</title>
      <link>https://simonsarris.substack.com/p/the-most-precious-resource-is-agency</link>
      <description>The world is a very malleable place. When I read biographies, early lives leap out the most. Leonardo da Vinci was a studio apprentice to Verrocchio at 14. Walt Disney took on a number of jobs, chiefly delivering papers, from 11 years old. Vladimir Nabokov published his first book (a collection of poems) at 16, while still in school. Andrew Carnegie</description>
      <author> (Simon Sarris)</author>
      <guid>https://simonsarris.substack.com/p/the-most-precious-resource-is-agency</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 07:06:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Continuous Integration Important For Testing?</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/why-is-continuous-integration-important-testing</link>
      <description>Continuous integration will help you run automated testing regularly. Here are some reasons why you should consider implementing a CI pipeline in your project.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/why-is-continuous-integration-important-testing</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 06:07:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning for Beginners, Curriculum</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-developer-community-blog/machine-learning-for-beginners-curriculum/ba-p/2502024</link>
      <description>It is our very great pleasure to announce the release of a new, free, MIT-licensed open-source curriculum all about classic Machine Learning:&amp;#160;Machine Learning for Beginners. Brought to you by a team of Azure Cloud Advocates and Program Managers, we hope to empower students of all ages to learn the b...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/266804)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-developer-community-blog/machine-learning-for-beginners-curriculum/ba-p/2502024</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 06:07:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boost ASP.NET Core Performance with Static Content</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/boost-aspnet-core-performance-with-static-content</link>
      <description>Use a command-line tool to generate ASP.NET Core endpoints to static HTML files.</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/boost-aspnet-core-performance-with-static-content</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 06:07:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIEF: Everything We Know About 1970s Mainframe RPGs We Can No Longer Play</title>
      <link>http://crpgaddict.blogspot.com/2021/06/brief-everything-we-know-about-1970s.html</link>
      <description>A blog in which a dedicated addict plays through all PC computer role-playing games (CRPGs), in chronological order.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://crpgaddict.blogspot.com/2021/06/brief-everything-we-know-about-1970s.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 06:07:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tip 322 - How to perform opinion mining with Azure Cognitive Services</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/blog/tip322.html</link>
      <description>The Azure Cognitive Services Text Analytics API (opens new window) provides the sentiment analysis feature. You can use this to analyze if a sentence is positive, negative, or neutral. And to get a more advanced analysis, you can use the opinion mining feature of sentiment analysis (opens new window), which analyzes a sentence on a deeper level and can identify multiple different sentiments in a sentence. For instance, the sentence &amp;quot;I love spicy food, but I hate how it makes me feel&amp;quot;, is both positive and negative. Opinion mining can detect those sentiments.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/blog/tip322.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 06:07:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 9 in-process Azure Functions | I CAN MAKE THIS WORK</title>
      <link>https://blog.johnnyreilly.com/2021/07/01/c-sharp-9-azure-functions-in-process/</link>
      <description>C# 9 has some amazing features. Azure Functions are have two modes: isolated and in-process. Whilst isolated supports .NET 5 (and hence C# 9), in-process supports .NET Core 3.1 (C# 8). This post shows how we can use C# 9 with in-process Azure Functions running on .NET Core 3.1.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.johnnyreilly.com/2021/07/01/c-sharp-9-azure-functions-in-process/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 06:07:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>