<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Learn C# with CSharpFritz - Get Started with ASP.NET Core MVC</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LnfZ23an4eA</link>
      <description>Fritz introduces the MVC architecture for ASP.NET Core and walks through Views, Action methods, and building forms with MVCContents:00:00:00 - Starting timer...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LnfZ23an4eA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sync Obsidian Between Laptop and Android</title>
      <link>https://nsirap.com/posts/050-sync-obsidian-between-laptop-and-android/</link>
      <description>How to sync your Obsidian vault between devices, and between a linux or windows desktop or laptop and a Android phone.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nsirap.com/posts/050-sync-obsidian-between-laptop-and-android/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laurence Tratt: Static Integer Types</title>
      <link>https://tratt.net/laurie/essays/entries/static_integer_types.html</link>
      <description>Over several years I’ve had several conversations with people about static integer
types in programming languages. Given the number of subtleties in the design, and pitfalls in the
use, of integer types it’s not surprising that most programmers are
unaware of at least some of them. However, what is perhaps more surprising is that most
programming language designers and implementers aren’t fully aware of
some of the subtleties and pitfalls either. That leads to languages and their
implementations baking in unintended, and sometimes unfortunate, design decisions.
At the end of conversations on this topic, I’ve sometimes said “this stuff
is hard and someone should think more about this and write it up” but it’s an
unsatisfying conclusion. So even though I don’t have all the answers – indeed, I’m
fairly sure that I don’t know all the questions – I’m going to jot down my
current thinking on this subject.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tratt.net/laurie/essays/entries/static_integer_types.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining a Dispensary</title>
      <link>https://lerielab.wordpress.com/2022/04/16/mining-a-dispensary/</link>
      <description>This article is about mining data from dispensaries to build a product list for a freelance programming contract. I will be attempting to build and store a formatted list of Marijuana products. I w…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lerielab.wordpress.com/2022/04/16/mining-a-dispensary/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florence: the Short Masterpiece that Goes Past a Love Story – doamatto</title>
      <link>https://www.maatt.ch/blog/florence-a-short-masterpiece/</link>
      <description>A short, breathtaking story, complemented amazingly with gorgeous music compositions.</description>
      <author> (Matt Ronchetto)</author>
      <guid>https://www.maatt.ch/blog/florence-a-short-masterpiece/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A real life use-case for generics in Go: API for client-side pagination</title>
      <link>https://vladimir.varank.in/notes/2022/05/a-real-life-use-case-for-generics-in-go-api-for-client-side-pagination/</link>
      <description>Let’s say we have a RESTful API for a general ledger, with the endpoints, that return a paginated collection of resources:

GET /accounts, retrieves a list of accounts, filtered and sorted by some query parameters;
GET /accounts/:uuid/transactions, retrieves a list of transactions for account;
GET /postings, retrieves a list of postings stored in the ledger.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vladimir.varank.in/notes/2022/05/a-real-life-use-case-for-generics-in-go-api-for-client-side-pagination/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steps towards debugging and resolving Android bootloops</title>
      <link>https://johannes.truschnigg.info/writing/2022-05_android_bootloop_debugging/</link>
      <description>Many users have good reasons to flash custom ROMs and Android distributions like LineageOS onto their phones: If you make the right choice, using these alternative operating system releases on your mobile device will make your digital life more private, potentially more secure, and - at least for a certain kind of folk - also more fun.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://johannes.truschnigg.info/writing/2022-05_android_bootloop_debugging/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Thoughts About Fly.io (So Far) and Other New-ish Technology I&amp;#39;m Getting Into</title>
      <link>https://blog.hartleybrody.com/thoughts-on-flyio/</link>
      <description>Hartley writes about full stack software development, marketing, and web scraping. Based in Boston, MA.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.hartleybrody.com/thoughts-on-flyio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calculating type sets is harder than you think</title>
      <link>https://blog.merovius.de/posts/2022-05-16-calculating-type-sets/</link>
      <description>I try to explain why the problem of calculating the exact contents of a type set in Go is harder than it might seem on the surface.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.merovius.de/posts/2022-05-16-calculating-type-sets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thorsten Ball - Professional Programming: The First 10 Years</title>
      <link>https://thorstenball.com/blog/2022/05/17/professional-programming-the-first-10-years/</link>
      <description>17 May 2022</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thorstenball.com/blog/2022/05/17/professional-programming-the-first-10-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macOS tips and tricks - saurabhs.org</title>
      <link>https://saurabhs.org/macos-tips</link>
      <description>A collection of nifty tips and tricks for macOS.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://saurabhs.org/macos-tips</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make video calls almost as good as face-to-face</title>
      <link>https://www.benkuhn.net/vc/</link>
      <description>I spent way too long figuring out the how to make video calls feel natural. Here’s the best advice I came up with.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.benkuhn.net/vc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSON is not a YAML subset</title>
      <link>https://john-millikin.com/json-is-not-a-yaml-subset</link>
      <description>People on the internet believe that JSON is a subset of YAML, and that it&amp;#39;s safe to parse JSON using a YAML parser:</description>
      <author> (John Millikin)</author>
      <guid>https://john-millikin.com/json-is-not-a-yaml-subset</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zstandard Worked Example Part 1: Concepts</title>
      <link>https://nigeltao.github.io/blog/2022/zstandard-part-1-concepts.html</link>
      <description>This blog post is one of a seven part series.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nigeltao.github.io/blog/2022/zstandard-part-1-concepts.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search results  | Find available job openings at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/search-results</link>
      <description>Search results. Find available job openings at Microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/search-results</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 21:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using a &amp;quot;Proper&amp;quot; Camera as a Webcam</title>
      <link>https://tratt.net/laurie/blog/2022/using_a_proper_camera_as_a_webcam.html</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s 2022, so many of us now have 2 years experience of online meetings.
My experience is that the better that I can see and
hear someone in an online call, the more natural the conversation feels. Put
another way, I think one does a courtesy to the other person by improving the
quality of how you appear in a video call.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tratt.net/laurie/blog/2022/using_a_proper_camera_as_a_webcam.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 20:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Careers at Microsoft | Microsoft jobs</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/job/1338106/Principal-Product-Management</link>
      <description>Do what you love. Create the future you want. Explore the career options that Microsoft has to offer.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/job/1338106/Principal-Product-Management</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 20:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The impact of digital media on children’s intelligence while controlling for genetic differences in cognition and socioeconomic background - Scientific Reports</title>
      <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-022-11341-2</link>
      <description>Digital media defines modern childhood, but its cognitive effects are unclear and hotly debated. We believe that studies with genetic data could clarify causal claims and correct for the typically unaccounted role of genetic predispositions. Here, we estimated the impact of different types of screen time (watching, socializing, or gaming) on children’s intelligence while controlling for the confounding effects of genetic differences in cognition and socioeconomic status. We analyzed 9855 children from the USA who were part of the ABCD dataset with measures of intelligence at baseline (ages 9–10) and after two years. At baseline, time watching (r = −&amp;amp;nbsp;0.12) and socializing (r = −&amp;amp;nbsp;0.10) were negatively correlated with intelligence, while gaming did not correlate. After two years, gaming positively impacted intelligence (standardized β =  + 0.17), but socializing had no effect. This is consistent with cognitive benefits documented in experimental studies on video gaming. Unexpectedly, watching videos also benefited intelligence (standardized β =  + 0.12), contrary to prior research on the effect of watching TV. Although, in a posthoc analysis, this was not significant if parental education (instead of SES) was controlled for. Broadly, our results are in line with research on the malleability of cognitive abilities from environmental factors, such as cognitive training and the Flynn effect.</description>
      <author> (Klingberg, Torkel)</author>
      <guid>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-022-11341-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 19:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winning Marathons Before Getting New Shoes</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2022/05/17/winning-marathons-before-getting-new-shoes/</link>
      <description>I am a big fan of the Rands Leadership Slack, and I learn something multiple times per day. Today, of course, is no different. Because of the Chatham house Rules, I can’t link to exactly what…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2022/05/17/winning-marathons-before-getting-new-shoes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 19:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s new with ML.NET Automated ML (AutoML) and tooling</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/whats-new-with-mldotnet-automl/</link>
      <description>Check out what&amp;#39;s new with ML.NET Automated ML (AutoML), tooling, and notebooks!</description>
      <author> (Luis Q)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/whats-new-with-mldotnet-automl/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 18:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphin Progress Report: February, March, and April 2022</title>
      <link>https://dolphin-emu.org/blog/2022/05/17/dolphin-progress-report-february-march-and-april-2022/</link>
      <description>After a long wait, the Progress Report is back! This time it wasn&amp;#39;t so much from a lack of content, but from a lack of content creators. The past three months had illnesses hit one of our writers and the other had a very challenging move. Even with these major hurdles jumped, we&amp;#39;re not even close to 100% yet. It&amp;#39;s been a battle to get caught up with all of the big changes to Dolphin the past couple of months and because of that this report is a tad late.
Needless to say, there&amp;#39;s only one way to start catching up, and that&amp;#39;s to get to digging through the past three months of Notable Changes. Enjoy!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dolphin-emu.org/blog/2022/05/17/dolphin-progress-report-february-march-and-april-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 17:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-In-One Search Is Getting Slicker</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/all-in-one-search-is-getting-slicker/</link>
      <description>Since we first previewed a brand new way to search your code called the All-In-One Search with Visual Studio 17.2, we’ve been making updates to the UI to make it feel slicker and help you search your code faster! In 17.3,</description>
      <author> (Denizhan Y)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/all-in-one-search-is-getting-slicker/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 17:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptology ePrint Archive: Report 2022/595</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2022/595</link>
      <description>On  the  Cryptographic  Fragility  of  the  Telegram  Ecosystem</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://eprint.iacr.org/2022/595</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 17:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Network Analytics Logs with your SIEM dashboard</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/network-analytics-logs/</link>
      <description>We’re excited to announce the availability of Network Analytics Logs for maximum visibility into L3/4 traffic and DDoS attacks</description>
      <author> (Omer Yoachimik)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/network-analytics-logs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 16:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hog Bay Software – Bike: Tool for thought</title>
      <link>https://www.hogbaysoftware.com/bike/</link>
      <description>Hog Bay Software</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hogbaysoftware.com/bike/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 16:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pegasus Mail and Mercury Developer News</title>
      <link>http://www.pmail.com/devnews.htm</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.pmail.com/devnews.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 16:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I want a small Android phone!</title>
      <link>https://smallandroidphone.com/</link>
      <description>
    Do you think all Android phones are too big? I agree! We need to work together to convince someone to build a small Android phone again.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://smallandroidphone.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 16:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevDay Denmark Talk about gRPC in ASP.NET Core
</title>
      <link>https://wildermuth.com/2022/05/17/devday-denmark-2022-grpc-talk/</link>
      <description>just got out of the DevDay Denmark, a one-day event put together by the incomparable Tibi Covaci at the Copenhagen Microsoft office. Was a great set of talks.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wildermuth.com/2022/05/17/devday-denmark-2022-grpc-talk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 15:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to open and read XML files in C# .NET 6 | Pro Code Guide</title>
      <link>https://procodeguide.com/csharp/open-and-read-xml-files-in-csharp/</link>
      <description>we will learn about how to work with XML files in C# .NET 6 i.e. in particular how to open and read XML files in C# .NET 6</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://procodeguide.com/csharp/open-and-read-xml-files-in-csharp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 15:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 ways to check the object passed to mocks with Moq in C# - Code4IT</title>
      <link>https://www.code4it.dev/blog/check-objects-called-mocks-in-moq/</link>
      <description>In unit tests, sometimes you need to perform deep checks on the object passed to the mocked service. We will learn 3 ways to do that with Moq and C#</description>
      <author> (code4it)</author>
      <guid>https://www.code4it.dev/blog/check-objects-called-mocks-in-moq/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 13:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debugging Hardware Performance on Gen X Servers</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/debugging-hardware-performance-on-gen-x-servers/</link>
      <description>In Cloudflare’s global network, every server runs the whole software stack. Therefore, it&amp;#39;s critical that every server performs to its maximum potential capacity</description>
      <author> (Yasir Jamal)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/debugging-hardware-performance-on-gen-x-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 13:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rewriting git history simply with git-filter-repo</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/rewriting-git-history-simply-with-git-filter-repo/</link>
      <description>In this post I describe how I used git-filter-repo in Docker to rewrite the history of a git repository to move files into a subfolder</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/rewriting-git-history-simply-with-git-filter-repo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 13:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Package Management for .NET Projects - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/central-package-management-dotnet/</link>
      <description>The central package management&amp;#160;feature has been released and it can help us organize our NuGet packages from one centralized place.</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/central-package-management-dotnet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 11:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using MySQL in a Docker container with EF Core</title>
      <link>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2022/05/17/mysqlwithefcoreanddocker/</link>
      <description>Running MySQL in a Docker container, and accessing it from EF Core</description>
      <author> (Published by
	Christian Nagel)</author>
      <guid>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2022/05/17/mysqlwithefcoreanddocker/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 11:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - tezc/sc: Common libraries and data structures for C.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/tezc/sc</link>
      <description>Common libraries and data structures for C. Contribute to tezc/sc development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (tezc)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/tezc/sc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 11:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDD South West 2022 session voting is now open!</title>
      <link>https://dddsouthwest.com/news/70/ddd-south-west-2022-session-voting-now-open</link>
      <description>First of all, we&amp;#39;d like to thank all speakers who have submitted potential sessions for DDD South West 2022.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dddsouthwest.com/news/70/ddd-south-west-2022-session-voting-now-open</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 10:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meld for OSX by yousseb</title>
      <link>https://yousseb.github.io/meld/</link>
      <description>Homepage for Meld macOS port. Meld is a visual diff and merge tool targeted at developers. Meld helps you compare files, directories, and version controlled projects. It provides two- and three-way comparison of both files and directories, and has support for many popular version control systems such as git, mercurial and others.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yousseb.github.io/meld/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 08:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Fix SqlException Database Is Not Currently Available On Azure (0x80131904) - CodeJourney.net</title>
      <link>https://www.codejourney.net/2022/05/how-to-fix-sqlexception-database-is-not-currently-available-on-azure-0x80131904/</link>
      <description>Database is not currently available SQL error (0x80131904) in Microsoft Azure. How to solve it? How to solve database not available on Azure?</description>
      <author> (Dawid Sibiński				
			
			.NET/Full Stack Developer and digital nomad)</author>
      <guid>https://www.codejourney.net/2022/05/how-to-fix-sqlexception-database-is-not-currently-available-on-azure-0x80131904/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 07:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case Study – How the Profilers Uncover Critical Issues That Mimic Apps’ Normal Behavior | The .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/05/16/case-study-how-the-profiler-uncovers-critical-issues-that-mimic-apps-normal-behavior/</link>
      <description>Today, we would like to share a few user stories about using the dotTrace performance profiler. We will tell you how a flaw was found in the new Intel CPUs&amp;#39; architecture, as well as how to find applic</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/05/16/case-study-how-the-profiler-uncovers-critical-issues-that-mimic-apps-normal-behavior/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Babylon.js 5.0: News Tools – Part 2</title>
      <link>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2022/05/13/babylon-js-5-0-news-tools-part-2/</link>
      <description>We are artists, developers, creators, and dreamers and we want to make it as simple as possible to enable everyone to bring their ideas to life. With this new version of Babylon.js, we set out to make it even easier to develop thanks to a suite of ne</description>
      <author> (Windows Developer Blog)</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2022/05/13/babylon-js-5-0-news-tools-part-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Principles for the Web</title>
      <link>https://www.w3.org/blog/2022/05/privacy-principles/</link>
      <description>Hello W3C Friends and Web Community! Today I’m proud to announce that the TAG Privacy Principles Task Force, initiated last year, has released a first public working draft of the Privacy Principles.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.w3.org/blog/2022/05/privacy-principles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Identity monad</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2022/05/16/the-identity-monad/</link>
      <description>Probably one of the least useful monads. An article for object-oriented developers.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2022/05/16/the-identity-monad/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Download Inkscape 1.2 | Inkscape</title>
      <link>https://inkscape.org/release/inkscape-1.2/</link>
      <description>Inkscape 1.2 is the latest major Inkscape release that brings you many fresh new features and new functionality.</description>
      <author> (Inkscape Website Developers)</author>
      <guid>https://inkscape.org/release/inkscape-1.2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 05:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 424 - Landing Zone Accelerator for API Management</title>
      <link>https://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-424-Landing-Zone-Accelerator-for-API-Management</link>
      <description>Our very own Cynthia Kreng, who is a PM in the Worldwide Customer Success Unit focused on Developer acceleration, talks to us about one their first offerings in API Management.</description>
      <author> (Sujit D&amp;#39;Mello)</author>
      <guid>https://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-424-Landing-Zone-Accelerator-for-API-Management</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 04:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>