<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate CSS Grid Challenges (Live Stream)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PvezIMj9aOc</link>
      <description>Watch me try to solve Intermediate CSS Grid challenges in real-time!

References
CSS Grid Course by Wes Bos - https://CSSGrid.io/friend/QUICK
Complete Guide to CSS Grid - https://css-tricks.com/snippets/css/complete-guide-grid/
Practical CSS Grid by Bryan Robinson - https://www.udemy.com/course/practical-css-grid/

https://www.jamesqquick.com
https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
https://www.learnbuildteach.com/

Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code!!
https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/

Build a Quiz App with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/

Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/jamesqquick</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PvezIMj9aOc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 15:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>uops.info</title>
      <link>https://uops.info/</link>
      <description>For Instructions on Recent x86 Microarchitectures</description>
      <author> (For Instructions on Recent x86 Microarchitectures)</author>
      <guid>https://uops.info/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 15:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS live reloading on Blazor</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/j_sakamoto/css-live-reloading-on-blazor-27nc</link>
      <description>Take back "CSS live reloading" on Blazor App Development!</description>
      <author> (jsakamoto)</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/j_sakamoto/css-live-reloading-on-blazor-27nc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 15:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frog Jumping - Numberphile</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X3HDnrehyDM</link>
      <description>Featuring Gordon Hamilton from Math Pickle. More links below.
Numberphile T-Shirts: https://teespring.com/stores/numberphile

Gordon and the Mondrian Art Problem: https://youtu.be/49KvZrioFB0

Math Pickle (Gordon's website): http://mathpickle.com

Numberphile is supported by the Mathematical Sciences Research Institute (MSRI): http://bit.ly/MSRINumberphile

We are also supported by Science Sandbox, a Simons Foundation initiative dedicated to engaging everyone with the process of science.

NUMBERPHILE
Website: http://www.numberphile.com/
Numberphile on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/numberphile
Numberphile tweets: https://twitter.com/numberphile
Subscribe: http://bit.ly/Numberphile_Sub

Videos by Brady Haran

Patreon: http://www.patreon.com/numberphile

Brady's videos subreddit: http://www.reddit.com/r/BradyHaran/

Brady's latest videos across all channels: http://www.bradyharanblog.com/

Sign up for (occasional) emails: http://eepurl.com/YdjL9</description>
      <author> (Numberphile)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X3HDnrehyDM</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 14:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using open source software to connect charities with people in need of social housing - Microsoft Industry Blogs - United Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://cloudblogs.microsoft.com/industry-blog/en-gb/technetuk/2020/03/16/using-open-source-software-to-connect-charities-with-people-in-need-of-social-housing/</link>
      <description>We speak to Chris Sainty, who proved anything is possible in OS by using it to develop the Blazor app that connects charities to people in need of social housing. </description>
      <author> (Chris Sainty				
									Microsoft MVP, software engineer and blogger)</author>
      <guid>https://cloudblogs.microsoft.com/industry-blog/en-gb/technetuk/2020/03/16/using-open-source-software-to-connect-charities-with-people-in-need-of-social-housing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 13:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Blazor actually any good, beyond "demo-ware"</title>
      <link>https://jonhilton.net/blazor-any-good/</link>
      <description>So Blazor is getting plenty of attention at the moment, but is it actually any good?</description>
      <author> (Jon Hilton)</author>
      <guid>https://jonhilton.net/blazor-any-good/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 13:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 47: Hacking .NET with Michal Strehovský</title>
      <link>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-47-hacking-net-with-michal-strehovsky/</link>
      <description>In this episode of The .NET Core podcast we talked with Michal Strehovský about his experience with hacking around in CoreRT</description>
      <author> (Jamie Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-47-hacking-net-with-michal-strehovsky/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 13:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK Act - Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/STOCK_Act</link>
      <description>The Stop Trading on Congressional Knowledge (STOCK) Act (Pub.L. 112–105, S. 2038, 126 Stat. 291, enacted April 4, 2012) is an Act of Congress designed to combat insider trading. It was signed into law by President Barack Obama on April 4, 2012. The bill prohibits the use of non-public information for private profit, including insider trading by members of Congress and other government employees. It confirms changes to the Commodity Exchange Act, specifies reporting intervals for financial transactions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/STOCK_Act</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 12:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updating Farm Wi-Fi with Ubiquiti Unify</title>
      <link>https://larsklint.com/updating-farm-wi-fi-with-ubiquiti-unify/</link>
      <description>TL;DR: I upgraded part of my Wi-Fi network on my farm with Unify equipment after years of “making do”.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://larsklint.com/updating-farm-wi-fi-with-ubiquiti-unify/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 11:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buzz Aldrin has some advice for Americans in quarantine</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2020/03/dont-worry-buzz-aldrin-is-protecting-himself-from-the-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>"We looked at this one crack in the floor, and there were ants crawling in and out."</description>
      <author> (Eric Berger
    -  3/17/2020, 3:12 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/science/2020/03/dont-worry-buzz-aldrin-is-protecting-himself-from-the-coronavirus/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 11:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 183</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-183/</link>
      <description>Geez, where do I even begin? I honestly wasn't sure, then I could hear the kids playing in the background whilst I was setting up and per the video thought "yeah, stuff it, I'll leave that in" because as messed up as a bunch of stuff is, life goes on.</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-183/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 10:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chronicle - Backstory</title>
      <link>https://chronicle.security/enterprise-security</link>
      <description>Chronicle fights cybercrime on a global scale.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chronicle.security/enterprise-security</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 10:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Async Expert by Dotnetos - your path to excel at async in .NET. Dotnetos training</title>
      <link>https://asyncexpert.com/</link>
      <description>Async Expert is a 9-weeks on-line course in which we will guide you from async basics through synchronization and concurrent collections. To allow you to verify possessed knowledge, we prepared suitable homeworks. 3 LIVE meetings with our mentors during which they will help to answer all your extra questions are an additional bonus. Our course platform will help us to keep in touch.</description>
      <author> (Dotnetos sp. z o.o.)</author>
      <guid>https://asyncexpert.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 10:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to launch 247 petabytes of data into AWS – but forgot about eye-watering cloudy egress costs before lift-off</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.co.uk/2020/03/19/nasa_cloud_data_migration_mess/</link>
      <description>Audit finds that error could actually mean less data flows to boffins because space agency may not be able to afford downloads</description>
      <author> (19 Mar 2020 at 08:29)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.co.uk/2020/03/19/nasa_cloud_data_migration_mess/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 10:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Digression on Divergence</title>
      <link>https://tangentvector.wordpress.com/2013/04/12/a-digression-on-divergence/</link>
      <description>Most people who do serious GPU work understand that shaders and other GPU programs are executed in a SIMD or “SIMT” fashion using “warps” or “wavefronts” that gr…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tangentvector.wordpress.com/2013/04/12/a-digression-on-divergence/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 08:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The End of Starsky Robotics</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/starsky-robotics-blog/the-end-of-starsky-robotics-acb8a6a8a5f5</link>
      <description>In 2015, I got obsessed with the idea of driverless trucks and started Starsky Robotics. In 2016, we became the first street-legal vehicle…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@stefan_66577)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/starsky-robotics-blog/the-end-of-starsky-robotics-acb8a6a8a5f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 07:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specification by Example, 10 years later</title>
      <link>https://gojko.net/2020/03/17/sbe-10-years.html</link>
      <description>It's now been ten years since I submitted the final manuscript of Specification by Example to the publisher. During the last two months, I've been conducting...</description>
      <author> (Gojko Adzic)</author>
      <guid>https://gojko.net/2020/03/17/sbe-10-years.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 06:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the New Pull Request Experience for Azure Repos | Azure DevOps Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-the-new-pull-request-experience-for-azure-repos/</link>
      <description>Pull Requests are a vital feature for many Azure Repos customers. We are excited to announce that our new pull request web experience is now available in preview! Not only is the new experience mobile-friendly and faster, we have also added several new features to help you review pull requests quicker and improve your overall pull request experience.</description>
      <author> (Apeksha AwasthiProgram Manager, Azure DevOpsFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-the-new-pull-request-experience-for-azure-repos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 06:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Management Preview 2 Release | PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/secret-management-preview-2-release/</link>
      <description>We are excited to release a second preview of the Secret Management Module. Thanks to the tremendous feedback we received from the first preview release of this module, you will notice a number of breaking changes to the module. This release is still a preview release meaning that it is not feature complete,</description>
      <author> (Sydney SmithFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/secret-management-preview-2-release/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 06:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s no place like home to join us at Redgate Streamed</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/redgate-events/theres-no-place-like-home</link>
      <description>We'd like you to join us at Redgate Streamed, a free 3-day virtual event with expert speakers talking about DevOps, databases, DBAs and Azure.</description>
      <author> (Red Gate Software Ltd)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/redgate-events/theres-no-place-like-home</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 06:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned porting Octopus Server to .NET Core 3.1 - Octopus Deploy</title>
      <link>https://octopus.com/blog/octopus-server-dotnet-core-lessons-learned</link>
      <description>We ported Octopus Server to .NET Core 3.1 to unlock the ability to run on Linux, Docker Containers, and Kubernetes. This post shares lessons learned along the way.</description>
      <author> (Octopus Deploy)</author>
      <guid>https://octopus.com/blog/octopus-server-dotnet-core-lessons-learned</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 06:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subscribe to read | Financial Times</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/b7a21a16-6a1f-11ea-800d-da70cff6e4d3</link>
      <description>News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the worldʼs leading global business publication</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ft.com/content/b7a21a16-6a1f-11ea-800d-da70cff6e4d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpsAI – OpsAI can help you optimize your infrastructure landscape, improve your security and compliance throughout the IT environment, and eliminates wasteful spending.</title>
      <link>https://www.opsai.com/</link>
      <description>The Cloud Automation Platform</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.opsai.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 02:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home - CLOUDEON</title>
      <link>https://www.cloudeon.com/en/</link>
      <description>Cloudeon is a 100% cloud and digital focused company, delivering innovative digital services and cloud technology.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cloudeon.com/en/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 02:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body Camera Once Again Catches An NYPD Officer Planting Drugs In Someone's Car</title>
      <link>https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20200318/19164444128/body-camera-once-again-catches-nypd-officer-planting-drugs-someones-car.shtml</link>
      <description>If at first you don't get punished, plant, plant again.
 
 
 
 When a police officer in Staten Island was caught by his own body camera in the apparent act of planting marijuana in the car of a group of young men, the video evidence against him...</description>
      <author> (Thu, Mar 19th 2020 11:00am —
Tim Cushing)</author>
      <guid>https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20200318/19164444128/body-camera-once-again-catches-nypd-officer-planting-drugs-someones-car.shtml</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 01:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorful Git Prompt for Azure Cloud Shell and Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/azure/colorful-git-prompt-for-azure-cloud-shell-and-visual-studio-code-3oh4</link>
      <description>A brand new Git prompt for Azure Cloud Shell</description>
      <author> (Michael Crump)</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/azure/colorful-git-prompt-for-azure-cloud-shell-and-visual-studio-code-3oh4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 01:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDC Security Australia - Hack Yourself First with Troy Hunt and Scott Helme</title>
      <link>https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ndc-security-australia-hack-yourself-first-with-troy-hunt-and-scott-helme-tickets-99858553622</link>
      <description>NDC Security Australia - Hack Yourself First Workshop (Online):
Troy Hunt and Scott Helme will be running an online Hack Yourself First Workshop with NDC Conferences through Zoom.us. Please note that the workshop hours are 09:00-17:00 and is scheduled in Canberra / Melbourne / Sydney time (AEDT). The 09:00 start is firm on both days, however, other timings in the schedule below can be fluid based on how long the modules are running for. Troy and Scott will be doing an "unplugged" session together over the lunch breaks both days. Questions can be asked by attendees on any topic and Troy and Scott will both be there responding together. In addition to the unplugged sessions, Troy will hang around at the end of day two for a "virtual mingle" where he will discuss whatever the workshop attendees feel like. 
Online workshop ticket is 800 AUD + GST (total 880 AUD).
Course Description:
Cyber-attacks have become a reality of running software on the web today. We find ourselves under a constant barrage of malicious activity from hacktivists, online criminals and increasingly, nation states. Successful attacks from these adversaries are predominantly via flaws in the software products they target – flaws that could have been prevented by developers understanding how online attackers work and what the appropriate defensive measures are.
"Hack Yourself First" is all about building up defensive skills in developers. It looks at security from the attacker's perspective and takes them through the steps necessary to exploit vulnerable software on the web so that they can experience hacking first hand. Workshop participants are set specific goals they must complete that involve probing for risks and then exploiting discrete vulnerabilities in a specially built vulnerable application. The interactive nature of the workshop means that multiple attack vectors are usually identified across the spectrum of participants and each person contributes their own unique perspective as to how specific risks are exploited.
The Objective
The objective of the workshop is that each person walks away with demonstrated experience across a broad spectrum of specific risks. They not only learn about but also demonstrate practical experience across a range of different vulnerabilities targeted to the specific needs of the group.
Courses run for two days on the following schedule:
Day 1
The first day build fundamental security skills that all technology professionals delivering applications on the web should posses:
- Discovering Risks via the Browser- Using an HTTP proxy - XSS- SQL Injection- CSRF - HTTPS- Framework Disclosure 
Day 2
The second day delves deeper into online risks, covering more advanced topics in greater depth:
- Password Cracking- Account Enumeration - FiddlerScript- Content Security Policy- Session Hijacking- Subresource integrity- Brute Force Attacks- Automating Attacks and Review
What attendees learn
Attendees will get taught the mechanics of each of these risks and of course the defensive patterns required to defend against them. But more than that, they get exposed to how to think about security; how to apply it in depth via multiple defences, how to choose appropriate controls based on the specific risk of the feature and how to have the discussion about what makes sense in different circumstances.
Above all though, security is just one factor in delivering working software and it has to be applied appropriately. Sometimes it comes with a trade-off against usability or cost and decisions have to be made about not what's just most secure, but what's in the overall best interests of the product being built. This workshop helps those who attend have the right discussions about when and where to invest in security.
Intended audience
- Software Developers- System Administrators- Testers
This workshop is aimed at any software developer, system admin or tester who wants to get a better understanding what is going on in cyber space if it comes to hacking and cracking of systems. This workshop enables you to take a pro-active approach and you learn how hackers will try to break your system. This workshop will be an eye opener for most attendees and it is the starting point of becoming a better developer. It all starts with awareness and improving your own habits. So start hacking yourself first, to become a better developer!
Required equipment
Attendees will need to use their own computer with one of following software options installed: Fiddler: http://www.telerik.com/download/fiddler Charles Proxy: http://www.charlesproxy.com/download/ Burp Suite: https://portswigger.net/burp/communitydownload
If possible please also bring your smartphone.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ndc-security-australia-hack-yourself-first-with-troy-hunt-and-scott-helme-tickets-99858553622</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iAnimate.net - Online Animation School</title>
      <link>https://ianimate.net/</link>
      <description>iAnimate.net is an online animation school like no other. We offer a complete set of workshops designed to target all your animation needs</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ianimate.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retweeting Twitter Mentions On Demand with Twilio SMS and ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.twilio.com/blog/retweeting-twitter-mentions-on-demand-twilio-sms-asp-net-core-azure</link>
      <description>Programming tutorial demonstrating how to retweet Twitter mentions on demand from SMS messages sent through Twilio Programmable SMS and the Twitter API using an ASP.NET Core app running on an Azure app service.</description>
      <author> (By David Pine
      2020-03-19)</author>
      <guid>https://www.twilio.com/blog/retweeting-twitter-mentions-on-demand-twilio-sms-asp-net-core-azure</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 22:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Mac Dev Setup</title>
      <link>https://arschles.com/blog/my-mac-dev-setup/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Aaron Schlesinger)</author>
      <guid>https://arschles.com/blog/my-mac-dev-setup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 20:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>  Is It Time to Rethink Globalized Supply Chains?</title>
      <link>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-it-time-to-rethink-globalized-supply-chains/</link>
      <description>The COVID-19 pandemic underscores why disaster preparedness is vital for supply chain resilience.</description>
      <author> (Willy Shih)</author>
      <guid>https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/is-it-time-to-rethink-globalized-supply-chains/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 19:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Compiler</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRAdsfhKI4OWNOSfS7EUu5GRAVmze1t2y</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Immo Landwerth
      
      

    
      Immo Landwerth
    

    
    
    
  
        •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRAdsfhKI4OWNOSfS7EUu5GRAVmze1t2y</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 18:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beauty of CSS Design</title>
      <link>http://www.csszengarden.com/</link>
      <description>A demonstration of what can be accomplished visually through CSS-based design.</description>
      <author> (Dave Shea)</author>
      <guid>http://www.csszengarden.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 18:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Reasons Why You As a Developer Should Venture Into Machine Learning Today</title>
      <link>https://www.alexanderslotte.com/5-reasons-why-you-as-a-net-developer-should-venture-into-machine-learning-today/</link>
      <description>I’m fortunate enough to occasionally be invited to speak at conferences around the world about what I’m truly passionate about. Having the opportunity to teach machine learning to groups of highly skilled .NET developers is a privilege and one of the most rewarding things I get to do. I often get questions from developers why they should invest time into learning a completely new domain, and why companies shouldn’t just hire “real” Data Scientists. I wanted to take a moment to write down why I think developers in the .NET community should take an interest, a leap of faith if you will, and venture in the world of machine learning.  </description>
      <author> (Alexander Slotte)</author>
      <guid>https://www.alexanderslotte.com/5-reasons-why-you-as-a-net-developer-should-venture-into-machine-learning-today/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 18:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acheve.Authentication.Events 3.1.3</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Acheve.Authentication.Events/</link>
      <description>Achve.Authentication.Events is a nuget package that implements authentication events with detailed log information and description about the event.
      It´s implemented to be used in learning and debug worflows related to the authentication proccess in Asp.Net Core
      For more information see https://github.com/hbiarge/Acheve.Authentication.Events</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Acheve.Authentication.Events/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 16:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>