<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Software and Game Development - Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/directory/game/Software%20and%20Game%20Development</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world&amp;#39;s leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/directory/game/Software%20and%20Game%20Development</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:05:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - KorzhCom/EasyData: An open-source framework for quick and easy implementation of CRUD operations (both API and UI) in ASP.NET Core applications.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/KorzhCom/EasyData</link>
      <description>An open-source framework for quick and easy implementation of CRUD operations (both API and UI) in ASP.NET Core applications. - GitHub - KorzhCom/EasyData: An open-source framework for quick and ea...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/KorzhCom/EasyData</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:05:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - aappleby/MetroBoy: A repository of gate-level simulators and tools for the original Game Boy.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/aappleby/MetroBoy</link>
      <description>A repository of gate-level simulators and tools for the original Game Boy. - GitHub - aappleby/MetroBoy: A repository of gate-level simulators and tools for the original Game Boy.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/aappleby/MetroBoy</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungie C++ Guidelines &amp;amp; Razors &amp;gt; News | Bungie.net</title>
      <link>https://www.bungie.net/en/News/Article/50666</link>
      <description>Bungie.net is the Internet home for Bungie, the developer of Destiny, Halo, Myth, Oni, and Marathon, and the only place with official Bungie info straight from the developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bungie.net/en/News/Article/50666</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 02:06:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s in New Productivity Power Tools for Visual Studio 2022? -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/09/02/vs-2022-tools.aspx</link>
      <description>Microsoft unveiled a suite of extensions designed to improve developer productivity and efficiency in the upcoming Visual Studio 2022 release.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel09/02/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/09/02/vs-2022-tools.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 01:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling an Azure AD secured API with Postman</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/425show/calling-an-azure-ad-secured-api-with-postman-22co</link>
      <description>Secure APIs are all the rage, but how can we easily test them. If you&amp;#39;re using Postman, then this...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/425show/calling-an-azure-ad-secured-api-with-postman-22co</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 01:06:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate Cloud Summit 2021 | Sherweb</title>
      <link>https://info.sherweb.com/accelerate</link>
      <description>North America’s premier cloud event featuring renowned industry experts with real-world insights into current and future trends, hands-on educational sessions and extensive networking</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://info.sherweb.com/accelerate</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 01:06:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experiments on a $50 DIY air purifier you can make in 30s</title>
      <link>https://dynomight.net/2020/12/15/some-real-data-on-a-DIY-box-fan-air-purifier/</link>
      <description>You can make a DIY air purifier in 30s. To test if it works, I generated smoke, and measured how well it removes tiny particles.</description>
      <author> (dynomight)</author>
      <guid>https://dynomight.net/2020/12/15/some-real-data-on-a-DIY-box-fan-air-purifier/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 01:06:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Exploring Blazorise with Mladen Macanović</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LihV9ViNtDw</link>
      <description>Mladen Macanović joins us in this edition of the Blazor community standup. We&amp;#39;ll be covering the Blazorise component ecosystem.Featuring: Safia Abdalla (@cap...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LihV9ViNtDw</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor WASM not loading appsettings.{environment}.json in Azure App Services - MSCTEK</title>
      <link>https://www.msctek.com/blazor-wasm-not-loading-appsettings-environment-json-in-azure-app-services/</link>
      <description>Workaround a configuration shortcoming in Blazor WebAssembly standalone deployments to Azure App Services.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.msctek.com/blazor-wasm-not-loading-appsettings-environment-json-in-azure-app-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 23:06:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money Ain&amp;#39;t A Thang</title>
      <link>https://dune.xyz/blog/money-aint-a-thang</link>
      <description>Ethereum Ecosystem analytics by and for the community. Explore and share data from Ethereum Mainnet, Matic, Optimism and xDai for free.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dune.xyz/blog/money-aint-a-thang</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://www.apple.com/child-safety/pdf/Apple_PSI_System_Security_Protocol_and_Analysis.pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/child-safety/pdf/Apple_PSI_System_Security_Protocol_and_Analysis.pdf</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/child-safety/pdf/Apple_PSI_System_Security_Protocol_and_Analysis.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any examples of using SAML 2 authentication with a Blazor server-side app?</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/answers/questions/360589/any-examples-of-using-saml-2-authentication-with-a.html</link>
      <description>Microsoft Q&amp;amp;A is the best place to get answers to all your technical questions on Microsoft products and services. Community. Forum.</description>
      <author> (Weebo-9652)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/answers/questions/360589/any-examples-of-using-saml-2-authentication-with-a.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noteflakes: How I Write Code: Pen &amp;amp; Paper</title>
      <link>https://noteflakes.com/articles/2021-09-02-how-i-write-code-pen-paper</link>
      <description>I am a self taught programmer. I first started programming as a kid, and have never bothered to formally study this discipline. To me, programming is first of all a pleasant creative pursuit. It’s a bit like putting together and taking apart all kinds of machines, except these machines happen to be virtual constructions, and you get to keep your hands clean (well, mostly…) Incidentally, this pleasant activity is also how I support my family.</description>
      <author> (by Sharon Rosner)</author>
      <guid>https://noteflakes.com/articles/2021-09-02-how-i-write-code-pen-paper</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPFTrace &amp;amp; Julia: An introduction to UProbes</title>
      <link>https://vchuravy.dev/notes/2021/08/bpftrace/</link>
      <description>BPFTrace is an observability tool inspired by DTrace for Linux. It uses the eBPF infrastructure in the Linux kernel to implemented lightweight tracing of the kernel and applications. This note is written from a Linux perspective, but much of this should hold on systems with DTrace.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vchuravy.dev/notes/2021/08/bpftrace/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons Learned from two years as a Data Scientist</title>
      <link>https://dawndrain.github.io/braindrain/two_years.html</link>
      <description>What I learned from my first two years as a data scientist</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dawndrain.github.io/braindrain/two_years.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A critique on project management software</title>
      <link>https://erock.io/2021/08/27/a-critique-on-project-management-software.html</link>
      <description>And some ideas on how to improve it</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://erock.io/2021/08/27/a-critique-on-project-management-software.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the &amp;quot;Bus Factor&amp;quot; of Your Project? — Vishnu&amp;#39;s Pages</title>
      <link>https://iamvishnu.com/posts/what-is-the-bus-factor-of-your-project</link>
      <description>I came across the term “bus factor” a couple of years ago, and since then I always keep an eye on the bus factor of the projects or other mission-critical th...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iamvishnu.com/posts/what-is-the-bus-factor-of-your-project</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Hacker News Ranking Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://felx.me/2021/08/29/improving-the-hacker-news-ranking-algorithm.html</link>
      <description>In our opinion, the goal of Hacker News (HN) is to find the highest quality submissions (according to its community) and show them on the front-page. While the current ranking algorithm seems to meet this requirement at first glance, we identified two inherent flaws.</description>
      <author> (Felix Dietze)</author>
      <guid>https://felx.me/2021/08/29/improving-the-hacker-news-ranking-algorithm.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start Your Day with Positive Intention — BRNSFT</title>
      <link>https://www.brnsft.com/blog/start-your-day-with-positive-intention</link>
      <description>If you have trouble getting out of bed in the morning, one thing you can do is add positive intention to your daily routine. Starting your day with positive intentions can help set the tone for a lot of amazing things to come.</description>
      <author> (Aug 31
            
            Written By Hanas Roberto)</author>
      <guid>https://www.brnsft.com/blog/start-your-day-with-positive-intention</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Persistent Gravity of Cross Platform</title>
      <link>https://allenpike.com/2021/gravity-of-cross-platform-apps</link>
      <description>Coordinating a large product org is hard.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://allenpike.com/2021/gravity-of-cross-platform-apps</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - 425show/BlazorServerAuthWithSAML</title>
      <link>https://github.com/425show/BlazorServerAuthWithSAML</link>
      <description>Contribute to 425show/BlazorServerAuthWithSAML development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (425show)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/425show/BlazorServerAuthWithSAML</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Open API (Swagger) calls with Azure Active Directory</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/425show/secure-open-api-swagger-calls-with-azure-active-directory-jj7</link>
      <description>We have talked about secure web apps and APIs many times here. In this blog post we&amp;#39;ll examine how to...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/425show/secure-open-api-swagger-calls-with-azure-active-directory-jj7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 21:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What UWP Deprecation? Community Celebrates Innovative Apps in Launch 2021 Contest -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/09/02/uwp-launch-2021.aspx</link>
      <description>  For all the talk of the deprecation of Microsoft&amp;#39;s Universal Windows Platform, it still thrives in places, including the UWP Community, which just announced the winners of its Launch 2021 event that celebrates UWP apps and their development.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel09/02/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/09/02/uwp-launch-2021.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 21:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use of artificial intelligence for image analysis in breast cancer screening programmes: systematic review of test accuracy</title>
      <link>https://www.bmj.com/content/374/bmj.n1872</link>
      <description>Objective To examine the accuracy of artificial intelligence (AI) for the detection of breast cancer in mammography screening practice.

Design Systematic review of test accuracy studies.

Data sources Medline, Embase, Web of Science, and Cochrane Database of Systematic Reviews from 1 January 2010 to 17 May 2021.

Eligibility criteria Studies reporting test accuracy of AI algorithms, alone or in combination with radiologists, to detect cancer in women’s digital mammograms in screening practice, or in test sets. Reference standard was biopsy with histology or follow-up (for screen negative women). Outcomes included test accuracy and cancer type detected.

Study selection and synthesis Two reviewers independently assessed articles for inclusion and assessed the methodological quality of included studies using the QUality Assessment of Diagnostic Accuracy Studies-2 (QUADAS-2) tool. A single reviewer extracted data, which were checked by a second reviewer. Narrative data synthesis was performed.

Results Twelve studies totalling 131 822 screened women were included. No prospective studies measuring test accuracy of AI in screening practice were found. Studies were of poor methodological quality. Three retrospective studies compared AI systems with the clinical decisions of the original radiologist, including 79 910 women, of whom 1878 had screen detected cancer or interval cancer within 12 months of screening. Thirty four (94%) of 36 AI systems evaluated in these studies were less accurate than a single radiologist, and all were less accurate than consensus of two or more radiologists. Five smaller studies (1086 women, 520 cancers) at high risk of bias and low generalisability to the clinical context reported that all five evaluated AI systems (as standalone to replace radiologist or as a reader aid) were more accurate than a single radiologist reading a test set in the laboratory. In three studies, AI used for triage screened out 53%, 45%, and 50% of women at low risk but also 10%, 4%, and 0% of cancers detected by radiologists.

Conclusions Current evidence for AI does not yet allow judgement of its accuracy in breast cancer screening programmes, and it is unclear where on the clinical pathway AI might be of most benefit. AI systems are not sufficiently specific to replace radiologist double reading in screening programmes. Promising results in smaller studies are not replicated in larger studies. Prospective studies are required to measure the effect of AI in clinical practice. Such studies will require clear stopping rules to ensure that AI does not reduce programme specificity.

Study registration Protocol registered as PROSPERO CRD42020213590.

No additional data available.</description>
      <author> (1)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bmj.com/content/374/bmj.n1872</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 21:05:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot Generated Insecure Code In 40% Of Circumstances During Experiment</title>
      <link>https://www.theinsaneapp.com/2021/09/github-copilot-generated-40-percent-insecure-code.html</link>
      <description>Github Copilot Security Study: Developer Should Remain Awake as GitHub Copilot is Generating Insecure Code In 40% Of Circumstances During Experiment. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.theinsaneapp.com/2021/09/github-copilot-generated-40-percent-insecure-code.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 21:05:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O.MG Cable - * to USB-A</title>
      <link>https://shop.hak5.org/products/o-mg-cable-usb-a</link>
      <description>To get a cable like this, you used to need a million dollar budget or to find a guy named MG at DEFCON. But Hak5 teamed up with MG to allow more people access to this previously clandestine attack hardware. Every O.MG Cable is hand made and tailored to look and feel exactly like the cable your target already has in the</description>
      <author> (Hak5)</author>
      <guid>https://shop.hak5.org/products/o-mg-cable-usb-a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 19:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers are not interested in Mac App Store, research shows - Techno Kilo</title>
      <link>https://technokilo.com/developers-not-interested-mac-app-store/</link>
      <description>New Research Shows that the interest of developers in releasing new apps in the Mac App Store is gradually decreasing.</description>
      <author> (Post author:Technokilo Staff)</author>
      <guid>https://technokilo.com/developers-not-interested-mac-app-store/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 18:07:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.​NET Core in .NET 6 - Async streaming</title>
      <link>https://asp.net-hacker.rocks/2021/09/02/aspnetcore6-async-stream.html</link>
      <description>This is the next part of the ASP.NET Core on .NET 6 series. In this post, I&amp;#39;d like to have a look into async streaming.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/juergen.gutsch)</author>
      <guid>https://asp.net-hacker.rocks/2021/09/02/aspnetcore6-async-stream.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 17:06:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - containers/podman: Podman: A tool for managing OCI containers and pods.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/containers/podman</link>
      <description>Podman: A tool for managing OCI containers and pods. - GitHub - containers/podman: Podman: A tool for managing OCI containers and pods.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/containers/podman</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 17:06:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor | Build client web apps with C# | .NET</title>
      <link>https://dotnet.microsoft.com/apps/aspnet/web-apps/blazor?WT.mc_id=onedevquestion-c9-dotnet6</link>
      <description>Blazor is a feature of ASP.NET for building interactive web UIs using C# instead of JavaScript. It&amp;#39;s real .NET running in the browser on WebAssembly.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnet.microsoft.com/apps/aspnet/web-apps/blazor?WT.mc_id=onedevquestion-c9-dotnet6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 16:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Ireland hit with record fine of €225m by DPC</title>
      <link>https://www.rte.ie/news/business/2021/0902/1244293-whatsapp-gdpr-ruling/</link>
      <description>The Data Protection Commission has fined WhatsApp Ireland €225m for infringements of data protection rules.</description>
      <author> (Will Goodbody)</author>
      <guid>https://www.rte.ie/news/business/2021/0902/1244293-whatsapp-gdpr-ruling/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 16:06:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Subscribers&amp;#39; Piracy Habits Directly Help Premier League Block Illegal Streams * TorrentFreak</title>
      <link>https://torrentfreak.com/sky-subscribers-piracy-habits-directly-help-premier-league-block-illegal-streams-210828/</link>
      <description>Sky is monitoring the IP addresses of servers suspected of streaming pirated content and supplying that data to assist the Premier League.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://torrentfreak.com/sky-subscribers-piracy-habits-directly-help-premier-league-block-illegal-streams-210828/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 16:06:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s Learn .NET: Razor Pages</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5XWgEHcTe4k</link>
      <description>Together, we will walk through the fundamentals of building web applications with Razor Pages in ASP.NET Core. Razor Pages make it easy to build web standard...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5XWgEHcTe4k</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 16:06:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21A24 Whole Woman&amp;#39;s Health v. Jackson (09/01/2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/20pdf/21a24_8759.pdf</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/20pdf/21a24_8759.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 15:05:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old and spectacular photos of Bedouin nomads, 1898 - Rare Historical Photos</title>
      <link>https://rarehistoricalphotos.com/old-spectacular-photos-of-bedouin-nomads-1898/</link>
      <description>These rare photos from the end of the 19th century capture a range of Bedouins at a time of change. An amazing and striking photo collection.</description>
      <author> (sam i am
				
					April 23, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://rarehistoricalphotos.com/old-spectacular-photos-of-bedouin-nomads-1898/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 14:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in application compatibility: The cost of forgetting to specify a calling convention</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210902-00/?p=105639</link>
      <description>We saw last time that the Windows header files sometimes look at world through __stdcall-colored glasses, and that causes problems when the header file fails to specify an explicit calling convention. The developers of one particular component made the mistake of omitting an explicit calling convention for one of their callback function pointer types,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210902-00/?p=105639</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 14:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Tunnels: Anytime, Anywhere</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/quick-tunnels-anytime-anywhere/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare Tunnel now supports a free version that includes all the latest features and does not require any onboarding to Cloudflare. With today’s change, you can begin experimenting with Tunnel in five minutes or less.</description>
      <author> (Rishabh Bector)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/quick-tunnels-anytime-anywhere/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 13:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Spotlight: GitHub</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/workshop-spotlight-github/</link>
      <description>We’re always working to help our customers improve their development processes and GitHub has become a popular focus in these learning cycles with Developer Support. If you are looking to build expertise with GitHub, there is no shortage of resources available.</description>
      <author> (Developer Support)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/workshop-spotlight-github/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 13:06:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>www.opendesktop.org</title>
      <link>https://www.opendesktop.org/</link>
      <description>Libre Cloud Services for users and developers. Keep your personal data save, start new projects, share apps, files and products, communicate freely with friends and colleagues.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.opendesktop.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 12:06:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traditional companies are losing because they mismanage software engineers</title>
      <link>https://ewattwhere.substack.com/p/traditional-company-shareholders</link>
      <description>Legacy companies are spending ever increasing budget on developers, but lack of key software management skills means they are wasting shareholder value</description>
      <author> (Emma Watterson)</author>
      <guid>https://ewattwhere.substack.com/p/traditional-company-shareholders</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 10:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deconstructing Azure PowerShell APIs with Fiddler</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/deconstructing-azure-powershell-apis-with-fiddler/</link>
      <description>Reed Robison shows how to deconstruct Azure PowerShell operations to understand how the underlying REST calls work. In my previous post, I talked about how Graph Explorer and Fiddler can be helpful tools when working with REST APIs. Both tools do a good job of showing you the details of request and response payloads.</description>
      <author> (Developer Support)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/deconstructing-azure-powershell-apis-with-fiddler/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 09:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - mTvare6/hello-world.rs: &amp;#128640;Memory safe, blazing fast, configurable, minimal hello world written in rust(&amp;#128640;) in a few lines of code with few(1061&amp;#128640;) dependencies&amp;#128640;</title>
      <link>https://github.com/mTvare6/hello-world.rs</link>
      <description>&amp;#128640;Memory safe, blazing fast, configurable, minimal hello world written in rust(&amp;#128640;) in a few lines of code with few(1061&amp;#128640;) dependencies&amp;#128640; - GitHub - mTvare6/hello-world.rs: &amp;#128640;Memory safe, blazing fast, ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/mTvare6/hello-world.rs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 08:08:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to study effectively | Psyche Guides</title>
      <link>https://psyche.co/guides/how-research-from-psychology-can-help-you-study-effectively</link>
      <description>Forget cramming, ditch the highlighter, and stop passively rereading. The psychology of learning offers better tactics</description>
      <author> (by Paul Penn&amp;#160;+ BIO)</author>
      <guid>https://psyche.co/guides/how-research-from-psychology-can-help-you-study-effectively</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 08:08:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using FbNetExternalEngine with Firebird Embedded (in .NET)</title>
      <link>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233869-using-fbnetexternalengine-with-firebird-embedded-in-net</link>
      <description>2 Sep 2021
	
	 1 mins
	
	 .NET, Firebird</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233869-using-fbnetexternalengine-with-firebird-embedded-in-net</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 07:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-09-02</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/09/app-developer-links-2021-09-02/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/09/app-developer-links-2021-09-02/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 07:07:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks! vNext</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1755</link>
      <description>.NET Rocks! is a weekly talk show for anyone interested in programming on the Microsoft .NET platform. The shows range from introductory information to hardcore geekiness.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1755</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 07:07:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Methodologies: From Requirements to Deployment</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/testing-methodologies-requirements-deployment</link>
      <description>Wrap your head around the various testing methodologies, at what point to implement them and what each methodology tests.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/testing-methodologies-requirements-deployment</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Server 2022 now generally available—delivers innovation in security, hybrid, and containers - Microsoft Windows Server Blog</title>
      <link>https://cloudblogs.microsoft.com/windowsserver/2021/09/01/windows-server-2022-now-generally-available-delivers-innovation-in-security-hybrid-and-containers/</link>
      <description>Today, we are announcing the general availability of Windows Server 2022. It’s a big step forward for the operating system&amp;#160;that is&amp;#160;trusted&amp;#160;by&amp;#160;major corporations&amp;#160;and small businesses&amp;#160;alike&amp;#160;to run their business and mission-critical workloads.&amp;#160; With Windows Server 2022, customers can continue to securely run their workloads, enable new hybrid cloud scenarios, and modernize their applications to meet evolving businessRead more</description>
      <author> (Bernardo Caldas)</author>
      <guid>https://cloudblogs.microsoft.com/windowsserver/2021/09/01/windows-server-2022-now-generally-available-delivers-innovation-in-security-hybrid-and-containers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build .NET Search Experiences With Lunr-Core</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/build-dotnet-search-experiences-with-lunr-core</link>
      <description>Using Lunr and Lunr-Core to build search experiences for .NET apps</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/build-dotnet-search-experiences-with-lunr-core</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ES2022 feature: class static initialization blocks</title>
      <link>https://2ality.com/2021/09/class-static-block.html</link>
      <description>The ECMAScript proposal “Class static initialization blocks” by Ron Buckton is at stage 4 and scheduled to be included in ECMAScript 2022.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2ality.com/2021/09/class-static-block.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:05:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Analytics for Extractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/extractive-summarization-preview/</link>
      <description>We’re delighted to announce that Text Analytics now supports extractive summarization! In general, there are two approaches for automatic text summarization: extractive and abstractive. The Text Analytics API provides extractive summarization starting in version 3.2-preview.1 Extractive Summarization Analysis Text Analytics for Extractive Summarization is a feature in Azure Text Analytics that produces a text summary by extracting sentences that collectively represent the most important or relevant information within the original content.</description>
      <author> (Shawn Fang)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/extractive-summarization-preview/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliSense for Hosted C# Script</title>
      <link>http://haacked.com/archive/2021/09/01/hosted-csharp-intellisense/</link>
      <description>We recently announced support for a local editing experience for Abbot skills that includes IntelliSense for C# Skills in Visual Studio Code. This post digs behind the scenes to talk about how that works.</description>
      <author> (Phil Haack)</author>
      <guid>http://haacked.com/archive/2021/09/01/hosted-csharp-intellisense/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify codez by davidfowl &amp;#183; Pull Request #1 &amp;#183; SpiritChrusher/Beer-API</title>
      <link>https://github.com/SpiritChrusher/Beer-API/pull/1</link>
      <description>Remove [FromServices]
Use a single instance of an HttpClient (we&amp;amp;#39;re in a singleton so I didn&amp;amp;#39;t need to make it static)
Use GetFromJsonAsync instead of manually parsing a large JSON string
S...</description>
      <author> (SpiritChrusher)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/SpiritChrusher/Beer-API/pull/1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChaosDB: How we hacked thousands of Azure customers’ databases | Wiz Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.wiz.io/blog/chaosdb-how-we-hacked-thousands-of-azure-customers-databases</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Nir Ohfeld and Sagi Tzadik)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wiz.io/blog/chaosdb-how-we-hacked-thousands-of-azure-customers-databases</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donovan Brown | Codespaces meet Dapr</title>
      <link>http://www.donovanbrown.com/post/codespaces-meet-dapr</link>
      <description>Donovan Brown - Technology Blog - In this post I will show you how to add Dapr to your Codespace.</description>
      <author> (Donovan Brown)</author>
      <guid>http://www.donovanbrown.com/post/codespaces-meet-dapr</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Server 2022 Now Generally Available</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/containers/windows-server-2022-now-generally-available/ba-p/2689973</link>
      <description>Overview Today we announced the General Availability (GA) of Windows Server 2022. It is such an exciting milestone for the Windows Server community and the broader ecosystem. As someone who shipped the last few Windows Server releases and have been working with teams across Microsoft to bring Window...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/63429)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/containers/windows-server-2022-now-generally-available/ba-p/2689973</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI movie posters</title>
      <link>https://noahveltman.com/aimovies/</link>
      <description>Guess the movie based on an AI’s visual interpretation of the plot.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://noahveltman.com/aimovies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 05:16:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>