<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>RAID-Z Expansion Feature for ZFS Goes Live | FreeBSD Foundation</title>
      <link>https://freebsdfoundation.org/blog/raid-z-expansion-feature-for-zfs-goes-live/</link>
      <description>How it works The feature reflows existing data, essentially rewriting it onto a new arrangement of disks – meaning the original group plus a newly added disk. In so doing, a new adjacent chunk of free space is created at the end of the logical RAID-Z group and thus at the end of each physical […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://freebsdfoundation.org/blog/raid-z-expansion-feature-for-zfs-goes-live/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 10:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SortedList in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-sortedlist/</link>
      <description>A SortedList in C# is a collection of key-value pairs that must be sorted at any given point in time based on its keys.</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-sortedlist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 09:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auditing Active Directory passwords against HaveIBeenPwned</title>
      <link>https://www.adainese.it/blog/2022/02/08/auditing-active-directory-passwords-against-haveibeenpwned/</link>
      <description>Any password policy, even with strict rules, can be easily bypassed with simple tricks: Passw0rd!, Passw0rd$, Password!1 can be all valid passwords for length and complexity.
It this common scenario it’s useful to regularly audit Active Directory passwords against password dictionaries (like RockYou) and/or HaveIBeenPwned.</description>
      <author> (VERSIVO)</author>
      <guid>https://www.adainese.it/blog/2022/02/08/auditing-active-directory-passwords-against-haveibeenpwned/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 09:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running SQL Server Queries In Docker</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/running-sql-server-queries-in-docker</link>
      <description>Learn to start and connect to a MS SQL Server instance running in a Docker container</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/running-sql-server-queries-in-docker</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Static Web Apps - a Netlify alternative | I CAN MAKE THIS WORK</title>
      <link>https://blog.johnnyreilly.com/2022/02/08/azure-static-web-apps-a-netlify-alternative</link>
      <description>Jamstack sites have taken the world by storm. There&amp;#39;s currently fierce competition between offerings like Netlify and Cloudflare. A new player in this space is Azure Static Web Apps. This post will look at what working with SWAs is like and will demonstrate deploying one using GitHub Actions.</description>
      <author> (https://twitter.com/johnny_reilly)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.johnnyreilly.com/2022/02/08/azure-static-web-apps-a-netlify-alternative</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the developer experience for Dependabot alerts | The GitHub Blog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/2022-02-08-improving-developer-experience-dependabot-alerts/</link>
      <description>Today, we’re shipping improvements to Dependabot alerts that make them easier to understand and remediate.</description>
      <author> (By Erin Havens				

				February 8, 2022)</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/2022-02-08-improving-developer-experience-dependabot-alerts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing In-App Subscriptions in iOS &amp;amp; Android with no backend servers</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/dotnet/implementing-in-app-subscriptions-in-ios-android-with-no-backend-servers-1pgm</link>
      <description>Over the years I have created several apps that I am super proud of, and for the most part, I have...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/dotnet/implementing-in-app-subscriptions-in-ios-android-with-no-backend-servers-1pgm</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 10.0 improves handling of nullable references in generic types - no more AllowNull | endjin</title>
      <link>https://endjin.com/blog/2022/02/csharp-10-generics-nullable-references-improvements-allownull.html</link>
      <description>C# 10.0 lets us annotate the nullability aspects of generic code more naturally than older versions. Some places where the AllowNull attribute was once required can now just use the obvious nullability syntax.</description>
      <author> (Ian Griffiths)</author>
      <guid>https://endjin.com/blog/2022/02/csharp-10-generics-nullable-references-improvements-allownull.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX</title>
      <link>https://www.spacex.com/updates/</link>
      <description>SpaceX designs, manufactures and launches advanced rockets and spacecraft.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.spacex.com/updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 04:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphin Progress Report: November and December 2021, January 2022</title>
      <link>https://dolphin-emu.org/blog/2022/02/08/dolphin-progress-report-nov-and-dec-2021-jan-2022/</link>
      <description>This year, we&amp;#39;ve hit an important milestone that&amp;#39;s been in the works for nearly a decade. In late 2012, Sonicadvance1 began work on Dolphin&amp;#39;s ARM JIT. Back then, there weren&amp;#39;t any devices that had even a sliver of hope of running Dolphin close to full speed, but that wasn&amp;#39;t really the goal. All he wanted to do was see if it could be done; it sounded like a fun, challenging project. However, as time passed the idea turned into more than just a passing curiosity. Users were more than happy to donate to cover the hardware cost of staying on the bleeding edge of a rapidly evolving ecosystem, allowing ARM development to flourish. By 2015, Sonicadvance1 astounded developers and the community alike with footage of Mario Kart: Double Dash!!&amp;#39;s time trial mode running close to full speed.
On that note, we&amp;#39;re happy to announce that Dolphin&amp;#39;s AArch64 JIT has finally reached feature parity with Dolphin&amp;#39;s x86-64 JIT. This means that every PowerPC instruction that the x86-64 JIT supports along with every major JIT feature are now supported in the AArch64 JIT! And this is a great time for ARM in general, with each generation of processor pushing the boundaries and companies like Apple adopting the architecture for larger and higher power devices like their M1 Mac line. For those on mobile phones and tablets, Adreno powered devices provide decent enough graphics drivers to get a reasonable experience at this point. And with a critical bottleneck getting fixed just days ago, performance on Adreno GPUs has skyrocketed. You won&amp;#39;t have to scroll far for that news, we promise.
But that&amp;#39;s only the tip of the iceberg; we&amp;#39;ve had three months worth of changes pile up and some other important infrastructure news. We&amp;#39;ve improved the user experience on macOS significantly and restored support for older devices. In fact, enough has happened that we&amp;#39;ll be detailing the status of Dolphin&amp;#39;s macOS support near the end of the report.
And... we haven&amp;#39;t even talked about any emulation fixes yet. The past three months have had tons of changes that would have normally been the highlight of a Progress Report. The three month gap between reports was not because of a lack of changes. Want to take Riivolution games on netplay? You can. Hate the EA VP6 bugs? Make them a thing of the past with a new option. Wish your favorite LogicOp game worked on GLES or MoltenVK? Odds are, it does now! The list goes on, but outlining everything would take way too long, so let&amp;#39;s just dive in. Please enjoy the November, December, and January Progress Report!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dolphin-emu.org/blog/2022/02/08/dolphin-progress-report-nov-and-dec-2021-jan-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 03:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refs #33476 -- Reformatted code with Black. by carltongibson &amp;#183; Pull Request #15387 &amp;#183; django/django</title>
      <link>https://github.com/django/django/pull/15387</link>
      <description>Mainly targeting coding-style.txt, but then spread to a few of the config files.

Not sure they&amp;amp;#39;re exactly how we want them?
Doesn&amp;amp;#39;t yet include the GitHub Action, which wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t pass u...</description>
      <author> (django)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/django/django/pull/15387</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 03:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nerdle - the daily numbers game</title>
      <link>https://nerdlegame.com/?a=0</link>
      <description>Nerdle - the daily numbers game</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nerdlegame.com/?a=0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 03:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does UTF-8 turn “&amp;#128514;” into “F09F9882”?</title>
      <link>https://sethmlarson.dev/blog/utf-8</link>
      <description>If you&amp;#39;re anything like me, you love emojis! Emojis appear like an image on the screen, but they aren&amp;#39;t an image like a PNG or JPEG. What do emojis look like to computers?


&amp;amp;#xa;&amp;amp;#xa;0x820x820x980...</description>
      <author> (Seth Michael Larson)</author>
      <guid>https://sethmlarson.dev/blog/utf-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 02:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laravel 9 is Now Released!</title>
      <link>https://laravel-news.com/laravel-9-released</link>
      <description>Laravel 9—the next major version of Laravel—is now released, including a minimum PHP v8.0 version, controller route groups, a new Ignition error page, and many more features.</description>
      <author> (Paul Redmond)</author>
      <guid>https://laravel-news.com/laravel-9-released</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 01:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Distribution Shifts and Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://huyenchip.com/2022/02/07/data-distribution-shifts-and-monitoring.html</link>
      <description>Note: This note is a work-in-progress, created for the course CS 329S: Machine Learning Systems Design (Stanford, 2022). For the fully developed text, see th...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://huyenchip.com/2022/02/07/data-distribution-shifts-and-monitoring.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t look for a job, find a solution</title>
      <link>https://blog.avci.me/dont-look-for-a-job-find-a-solution-aee11a421fa0?gif=true</link>
      <description>Today, the number of people who are looking for a job instead of producing solutions is very high. Parents send their children to schools…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@mavci)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.avci.me/dont-look-for-a-job-find-a-solution-aee11a421fa0?gif=true</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BastionZero Blog | In which I agree with the federal gov&amp;#39;t  and bash VPNs for fun and profit</title>
      <link>https://www.bastionzero.com/blog/bashing-vpns-for-fun-and-profit</link>
      <description>When I first read the federal government’s memo on it’s “transition zero trust”, I was jumping out of my skin with excitement. There’s lots of great stuff in that memo (see my earlier blog post) but what excited me most was the memo’s stance on VPNs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bastionzero.com/blog/bashing-vpns-for-fun-and-profit</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET | Free. Cross-platform. Open Source.</title>
      <link>https://dotnet.microsoft.com/en-us/?WT.mc_ID=20thBDay-dotNET-SocialMedia-Organic-Trivia</link>
      <description>.NET is a developer platform with tools and libraries for building any type of app, including web, mobile, desktop, games, IoT, cloud, and microservices.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnet.microsoft.com/en-us/?WT.mc_ID=20thBDay-dotNET-SocialMedia-Organic-Trivia</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I wanted to be a developer</title>
      <link>http://www.adambourg.com/programming/why/developer/2022/02/08/why_i_wanted_to_be_a_developer.html</link>
      <description>I started programming when I was 13 years old. I stole my brothers HTML and Javascript book and built some simple web forms. I had no idea that a backend was needed or even what a backend was. I just knew I had some gray buttons on the screen and it did things. I went on to play with some web forum software, launching my own unsuccessful internet forum.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.adambourg.com/programming/why/developer/2022/02/08/why_i_wanted_to_be_a_developer.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Renovation - Epiphany 2.0</title>
      <link>https://nkjemisin.com/2022/02/book-renovation/</link>
      <description>It’s been a while since I regularly used this blog! Not planning to resume, too busy, but because WordPress has implemented some new features, I decided to write this just to help myself get used to it. Anyway, right now, I’m working on the revision of Book 2 of the Great Cities. A friend asked me how to do revisions, so I figured I might as well lay out my process here. Note that this is my process; as with all other writing advice, you should look at many methods and then choose or customize something that works best for … Book Renovation KEEP READING</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nkjemisin.com/2022/02/book-renovation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single dependency stacks</title>
      <link>https://brandur.org/fragments/single-dependency-stacks</link>
      <description>Life with Postgres only.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://brandur.org/fragments/single-dependency-stacks</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before I go: When it comes to complaining about web browsers</title>
      <link>https://daverupert.com/2022/02/complaining-about-web-browsers/</link>
      <description>I’m not planning on leaving the industry (yet), but before I go I’d like to offer up what I know when it comes to complaining about web browsers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://daverupert.com/2022/02/complaining-about-web-browsers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use TaskEither in fpdart – Sandro Maglione</title>
      <link>https://blog.sandromaglione.com/techblog/how-to-use-task-either-fpdart-functional-programming</link>
      <description>TaskEither is the most used type in Functional Programming with fpdart. Do you know what TaskEither is in Functional Programming? In this post we are going to learn how to use TaskEither in fpdart.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sandromaglione.com/techblog/how-to-use-task-either-fpdart-functional-programming</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Dupr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://jonathandupre.com/blog/measure-things</link>
      <description>Successful software teams measure how effective their measurements are. If you did, you wouldn&amp;#39;t be guessing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jonathandupre.com/blog/measure-things</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qualities and Business Models</title>
      <link>https://aditya.rs/2022/02/08/qualities-and-business-models/</link>
      <description>Qualities of a product are influenced by societal expectations of the time they were built in. This acts as a non-obvious constraint in their evolution and could potentially lead to disruption of existing business models.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aditya.rs/2022/02/08/qualities-and-business-models/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Collaboration with Remote Teams</title>
      <link>https://joshghent.com/remote-collaboration/</link>
      <description>Time and distance doesn&amp;#39;t need to prevent your team being collaborative</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joshghent.com/remote-collaboration/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Dupr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://jonathandupre.com/blog/separation-of-duties</link>
      <description>You can divide critical functions among different members of your team. This will let you avoid conflicts of duty.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jonathandupre.com/blog/separation-of-duties</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counting to 10 in binary.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qraxegq1qXg</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Practical Networking
  
  
  
    Practical Networking
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qraxegq1qXg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code Gets New Side Panel in v1.64 Update -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/02/08/vs-code-1-64.aspx</link>
      <description>  Visual Studio Code 1.64 (January 2022 edition) shipped with the usual bevy of new features and functionality, including a new side panel.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel02/08/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/02/08/vs-code-1-64.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Cloud Advocate for Python in Other, Other, United States | Engineering at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/1256305/Senior-Cloud-Advocate-for-Python</link>
      <description>Apply for Senior Cloud Advocate for Python job with Microsoft in Other, Other, United States. Engineering at Microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/1256305/Senior-Cloud-Advocate-for-Python</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Software Engineer in Other, Other, United States | Engineering at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/1258508/Senior-Software-Engineer</link>
      <description>Apply for Senior Software Engineer job with Microsoft in Other, Other, United States. Engineering at Microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/1258508/Senior-Software-Engineer</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 23:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gyroflow v1.0.0-rc1 has appeared!</title>
      <link>https://gyroflow.xyz/</link>
      <description>Surprise! Gyroflow is now faster, more intuitive, and production-grade</description>
      <author> (Elvin)</author>
      <guid>https://gyroflow.xyz/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 23:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Legion: Gaming PCs, Laptops &amp;amp;amp; Gear ﻿| Stylish outside. Savage inside. | Lenovo Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.lenovo.com/au/en/gaming-pc/legion/</link>
      <description>Discover Lenovo Legion, a new line of gaming PCs and gear. Get unmatched power &amp;amp;amp; performance on the battlefield with Legion gaming computers, laptops, and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lenovo.com/au/en/gaming-pc/legion/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:03:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initial roll out of !! by stephentoub &amp;#183; Pull Request #64720 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/64720</link>
      <description>C# 11 has implemented the parameter null checking feature !!, which let&amp;amp;#39;s us replace:
void M(object arg)
{
    if (arg is null)
    {
        throw new ArgumentNullException(nameof(arg));
    }...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/64720</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r4wqWX0kVgA</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io/</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
  
    .NET Foundation
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r4wqWX0kVgA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 21:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Preview - Visual Studio Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=MadsKristensen.ColorPreview</link>
      <description>Extension for Visual Studio - Shows a color preview in front of all named colors, hex, rgb and hsl values in CSS files.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=MadsKristensen.ColorPreview</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 21:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the cost of casting in .NET (C#)?</title>
      <link>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233888-what-is-the-cost-of-casting-in-net-csharp</link>
      <description>8 Feb 2022
	
	 4 mins
	
	 .NET, C#, Performance</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233888-what-is-the-cost-of-casting-in-net-csharp</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 21:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposing a web service with Cloudflare Tunnel</title>
      <link>https://erisa.dev/exposing-a-web-service-with-cloudflare-tunnel/</link>
      <description>What if you could host a web service with no ports exposed? With Cloudflare Tunnel, you can!</description>
      <author> (Erisa A)</author>
      <guid>https://erisa.dev/exposing-a-web-service-with-cloudflare-tunnel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 20:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Blazor .NET 7 Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3o91I6lD-Bo</link>
      <description>Find out what&amp;#39;s being planned for Blazor in .NET 7, and give us your feedback!Featuring: Daniel Roth (@danroth27), Tanay Parikh (@_TanayParikh), Jon Galloway...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3o91I6lD-Bo</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 18:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple unveils contactless payments via Tap to Pay on iPhone</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2022/02/apple-unveils-contactless-payments-via-tap-to-pay-on-iphone/</link>
      <description>Apple today announced plans to introduce Tap to Pay on iPhone, empowering merchants in the US to accept contactless payments.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2022/02/apple-unveils-contactless-payments-via-tap-to-pay-on-iphone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 17:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An open-source distributed storage service</title>
      <link>https://garagehq.deuxfleurs.fr/blog/2022-introducing-garage/</link>
      <description>An open-source distributed storage service you can self-host to fullfill many needs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://garagehq.deuxfleurs.fr/blog/2022-introducing-garage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 17:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>r/hearthstone - How I hacked Hearthstone</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/hearthstone/comments/snadt6/how_i_hacked_hearthstone/</link>
      <description>948 votes and 122 comments so far on Reddit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/hearthstone/comments/snadt6/how_i_hacked_hearthstone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 16:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Selenium - C# Example - New</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tp92WDs8mLE</link>
      <description>Hey Programmers,In this video, I am showing how you can get started with Selenium for your C# web project. Selenium is a suite of tools for automating web br...</description>
      <author> (Cris Oxley)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tp92WDs8mLE</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 16:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The cats sitting on a fence in early builds of Windows 8 - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220208-00/?p=106232</link>
      <description>The Windows 8 tablet experience organized its components as a collection of layers, with each layer stacked on top of the next one. For the purpose of today’s discussion, the important layers are the Start layer and the Apps layer: If you’re using an app,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220208-00/?p=106232</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 16:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Compression</title>
      <link>https://caseymuratori.com/blog_0015</link>
      <description>An introduction to the idea that code should be approached with a mindset towards compressing it semantically, rather than orienting it around objects.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://caseymuratori.com/blog_0015</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 15:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Universe of Discourse : I would like a job writing Haskell</title>
      <link>https://blog.plover.com/2022/02/07/</link>
      <description>I would like a job writing Haskell</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.plover.com/2022/02/07/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 15:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mod the dotnet-bot</title>
      <link>https://mod-dotnet-bot.net/</link>
      <description>Coding is better with friends, especially when they bring their own mods. Create your own coding companion by modding the dotnet-bot.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mod-dotnet-bot.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 15:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design Systems for Developers</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/design-systems-developers</link>
      <description>Having a design system makes it easy for developers to onboard team members, find answers, download common assets like logos and icons, and so much more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/design-systems-developers</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 14:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Async / Await vs. PipeTo&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; in Akka.NET Actors</title>
      <link>https://petabridge.com/blog/async-await-vs-pipeto/</link>
      <description>Many years ago I wrote an article entitled “How to Do Asynchronous I/O with Akka.NET Actors Using PipeTo” - back when await support was still very much a work in progress. I subsequently wrote a major update on that article in 2016 - talking mostly about the benefits of PipeTo from a structural point of view.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://petabridge.com/blog/async-await-vs-pipeto/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 14:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improvements and Optimizations for Interpolated Strings – A Look at New Language Features in C# 10 | The .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/02/07/improvements-and-optimizations-for-interpolated-strings-a-look-at-new-language-features-in-csharp-10/</link>
      <description>Welcome to the fourth part of our series, where we take a closer look at the new C# language features the .NET team has implemented, and how ReSharper and Rider make it easy to adopt them in your code</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/02/07/improvements-and-optimizations-for-interpolated-strings-a-look-at-new-language-features-in-csharp-10/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 14:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some mistakes Rust doesn&amp;#39;t catch</title>
      <link>https://fasterthanli.me/articles/some-mistakes-rust-doesnt-catch</link>
      <description>I still get excited about programming languages. But these days, it&amp;#39;s not so
much because of what they let me do, but rather what they  don&amp;#39;t  let me do. Ultimately, what you ca...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fasterthanli.me/articles/some-mistakes-rust-doesnt-catch</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 14:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nested type-safe DI Containers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2022/02/07/nested-type-safe-di-containers/</link>
      <description>How to address the arity problem with type-safe DI Container prototypes.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2022/02/07/nested-type-safe-di-containers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 14:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs! Docs! Docs! — brandur.org</title>
      <link>https://brandur.org/nanoglyphs/031-api-docs</link>
      <description>The past couple of weeks: a lot of work building out and tightening up documentation, with special emphasis on API reference.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://brandur.org/nanoglyphs/031-api-docs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 14:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NetEscapades.EnumGenerators: a source generator for enum performance</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/netescapades-enumgenerators-a-source-generator-for-enum-performance/</link>
      <description>In this post I describe a source generator I created to improve the performance of enum operations</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/netescapades-enumgenerators-a-source-generator-for-enum-performance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 13:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Routing is now in open beta, available to everyone</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/email-routing-open-beta/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare Email Routing transitioned from closed beta to open beta. It’s now available to everyone, including free zones</description>
      <author> (Jo&amp;#227;o Sousa Botto)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/email-routing-open-beta/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 12:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KDE: A Nice Tiling Envieonment and a Surprisingly Awesome DE</title>
      <link>https://changelog.complete.org/archives/10338-kde-a-nice-tiling-envieonment-and-a-surprisingly-awesome-de</link>
      <description>I recently wrote that managing an external display on Linux shouldn’t be this hard. I went down a path of trying out some different options before finally landing at an unexpected place: KDE.…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://changelog.complete.org/archives/10338-kde-a-nice-tiling-envieonment-and-a-surprisingly-awesome-de</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 12:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from .NET Framework to .NET Core (.NET 6) - Detailed Guide | Pro Code Guide</title>
      <link>https://procodeguide.com/dotnet/migrate-net-framework-to-net-core/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will learn about the things you should consider and focus on while migrating your existing applications from .NET Framework to .NET Core</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://procodeguide.com/dotnet/migrate-net-framework-to-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 11:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>