<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How to Reclaim Your Dev Team’s Focus w/ Ambassador Labs’ Katie Wilde</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/dev-interrupted/how-to-reclaim-your-dev-teams-focus-w-ambassador-labs-katie-wilde-2b134da329e</link>
      <description>Katie Wilde, VP of Engineering at Ambassador Labs, knows your pain and she’s on a crusade to help devs everywhere reclaim their focus.</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@conor_53205)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/dev-interrupted/how-to-reclaim-your-dev-teams-focus-w-ambassador-labs-katie-wilde-2b134da329e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 23:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Only Three Classes That Mattered From My College Degree</title>
      <link>https://www.developing.dev/p/the-only-three-classes-that-mattered</link>
      <description>Only 3 of the 56 classes I took at UCLA matter in my daily software engineering work. Any engineer would agree that those three courses are worth their weight in gold.</description>
      <author> (Ryan Peterman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.developing.dev/p/the-only-three-classes-that-mattered</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing a Tampermonkey Script with GPT-4 | David Bieber</title>
      <link>https://davidbieber.com/snippets/2023-03-15-tampermonkey-gpt-4/</link>
      <description>Today I used GPT-4 to implement my first ever Tampermonkey script. It took well under half an hour, which is likely many times faster than it would have taken me alone. I am blown away by GPT-4’s programming capabilities.
It started with a simple feature request for the Hypothesis browser extension. For context, Hypothesis is a tool for taking notes on the web, including on PDFs. I use it to take notes on machine learning pdfs on Arxiv.</description>
      <author> (David Bieber)</author>
      <guid>https://davidbieber.com/snippets/2023-03-15-tampermonkey-gpt-4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything I know | Everything I know</title>
      <link>https://wiki.nikiv.dev/sharing/everything-I-know</link>
      <description>Page of things I consider myself knowledgeable of. Similar in spirit to Dan&amp;#39;s post on things he doesn&amp;#39;t know.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wiki.nikiv.dev/sharing/everything-I-know</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I identify? – Codewalkers</title>
      <link>https://codewalkers.net/2023/03/04/how-do-i-identify/</link>
      <description>A few months ago, I interviewed for a director-level position at a Fortune 500 company. Everything went great, and I had four total interviews, which included the hiring manager (twice), a panel of immediate peers (same manager), and a panel of other colleagues.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://codewalkers.net/2023/03/04/how-do-i-identify/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Data Community Standup - EF Core internals: IQueryable, LINQ and the EF Core query pipeline</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=1Ld3dtnTrMw</link>
      <description>In this standup, we&amp;#39;ll dive deep under the hood to see how EF Core processes LINQ queries, translates them to SQL and executes them on your database. We&amp;#39;ll i...</description>
      <author> (More from this channel for you
  
  
  
    More from this channel for you
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=1Ld3dtnTrMw</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noam&amp;#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://noamf.ink/posts/raising-software/</link>
      <description>2023-03-17</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://noamf.ink/posts/raising-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Class Classification Using a scikit Decision Tree -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/03/17/scikit-classification.aspx</link>
      <description>Decision trees are useful for relatively small datasets that have a relatively simple underlying structure, and when the trained model must be easily interpretable, explains Dr. James McCaffrey of Microsoft Research, who provides step-by-step instructions and full source code.</description>
      <author> (By James McCaffrey03/17/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/03/17/scikit-classification.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Captain Ironman — DBT Ventures</title>
      <link>http://www.dbtventures.com/blog/2021/12/31/captain-ironman</link>
      <description>Farewell, 2021  As the curtain drops on 2021, I’d like to share some learnings with you from two recent experiences:    Completing an Ironman triathlon (11/21/21)    Earning a private pilot certificate (12/30/21)    Why these two experiences?  Many of our 5,000+ readers are ambitious technology prof</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.dbtventures.com/blog/2021/12/31/captain-ironman</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future CSS: Anchor Positioning</title>
      <link>https://kizu.dev/anchor-positioning-experiments/</link>
      <description>Anchor positioning might be&amp;#160;one of&amp;#160;the most exciting features coming to&amp;#160;CSS. It&amp;#160;is&amp;#160;currently available under an&amp;#160;experimental flag in&amp;#160;Chrome Canary, and after playing with it&amp;#160;for a&amp;#160;bit, I&amp;#160;couldn’t stop myself from sharing what I&amp;#160;found. In&amp;#160;this article, I&amp;#160;will show you some of&amp;#160;my&amp;#160;experiments.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kizu.dev/anchor-positioning-experiments/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Time at Bat: My Founder Story</title>
      <link>https://www.prannoy.com/post-mortem-my-startup-journey/</link>
      <description>After my first startup ended, it felt like I was walking around with a phantom limb for months. It had been a whirlwind. From building a humble ed-tech media app, going through a wild pivot, then shutting down and selling the remnants away...there was a lot to process.

Journaling</description>
      <author> (Prannoy Nambiar)</author>
      <guid>https://www.prannoy.com/post-mortem-my-startup-journey/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Plight of  the Prompt Engineers</title>
      <link>https://elton.dev/2023/03/17/the-plight-of-the-prompt-engineers/</link>
      <description>The following article was written using Bing Chat powered by GPT-4. It is an editorial about the harsh future awaiting software engineers — now called prompt engineers — following the emergence of …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://elton.dev/2023/03/17/the-plight-of-the-prompt-engineers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simplified Guide to Creating a Pharo Smalltalk Plugin</title>
      <link>https://blog.sebastiansastre.co/article/a-simplified-guide-to-creating-a-pharo-smalltalk-plugin</link>
      <description>In my previous article, How to Create a Pharo Smalltalk Plugin, I outlined how to create a Pharo Smalltalk plugin. However, since then, I&amp;#39;ve discovered a more convenient way to produce these plugins using the PharoPluginBuilder and StarterPlugin. In this post, wanted to inform and describe the idea of this simplified process of creating a Pharo Smalltalk plugin.</description>
      <author> (Sebastian Sastre)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sebastiansastre.co/article/a-simplified-guide-to-creating-a-pharo-smalltalk-plugin</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Functional Programming? |</title>
      <link>https://zicklag.github.io/blog/hvm-what-is-functional-programming/</link>
      <description>HVM, the High Order Virtual Machine, is a new, blazing fast runtime for functional programming languages that seems to have some pretty incredible potential for the future.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zicklag.github.io/blog/hvm-what-is-functional-programming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models do Gradient Descent at runtime.</title>
      <link>https://til.nicklothian.com/AI/Large_Language_Models_Do_Gradient_Descent</link>
      <description>In [Why Can GPT Learn In-Context? Language Models Secretly Perform Gradient Descent as Meta-Optimizers](https://arxiv.org/abs/2212.10559), researchers investigate how large language models (LLMs) can perform tasks such as classification from examples given as the &amp;quot;context&amp;quot;.

The way this works is you give the model some example sentences and the output (eg &amp;quot;{This is a positive sentence}, {sentiment: positive}&amp;quot;) as the context and then give it some unclassified sentences and it will output the sentiment.

This is known as &amp;quot;in-context learning&amp;quot; (ICL) and was a surprising capability of LLMs when first discovered. 

For those who believe LLMs are just &amp;quot;stochastic parrots&amp;quot; that just output what they have read this behavior should be impossible. Typically proponents of this view make objections like &amp;quot;oh it has seen those examples somewhere before&amp;quot;, but these are easily disproved by making up your own examples. 

So how is it working?

In this paper the researchers probe the transformer state of the LLM before and after the context examples are loaded and show that the updated transformer state is similar to a large language model that has been fine tuned on the examples(!)

This is a pretty astonishing insight and raises questions about what else LLMs can do. 

It also shows the significant difference between the *training objective* of a language model (just predict the next token) and the capabilities and representation that these models learn. 

To quote the conclusion:

&amp;gt; Further, we build connections between ICL and a specific finetuning setting and find that it is reasonable to regard ICL as a kind of implicit finetuning. Empirically, in order to support our understanding that ICL performs implicit finetuning, we comprehensively compare the behavior of ICL and finetuning based on real tasks. The results prove that ICL behaves similarly to explicit finetuning at the prediction level, the representation level, and the attention behavior level. 

Exactly how LLMs have learned to do this in context learning is a mystery. Obviously compression is forcing a compact form of knowledge representation, but what makes it able to update this repsentation and then use it so easily is certianly surprising.

These experiments were performed on comparativly small models (GPT 1.3B and 2.7B). It would be interesting to see the same experiments performed on models with larger parameter counts.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://til.nicklothian.com/AI/Large_Language_Models_Do_Gradient_Descent</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I got my first Rails job</title>
      <link>https://izaguirrejoe.dev/2023/03/15/how-i-got-my-first-rails-job/</link>
      <description>My journey to a junior Rails developer position.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://izaguirrejoe.dev/2023/03/15/how-i-got-my-first-rails-job/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How processes are born, why they can be damaging, and how to fix them</title>
      <link>https://lucasfcosta.com/2023/03/16/processes.html</link>
      <description>Process-heavy engineering cultures are like my grandfather’s wallet. They’re stuffed with so many layers of procedures and checklists that by the time you ge...</description>
      <author> (Lucas Fernandes da Costa at S&amp;#227;o Paulo, Brazil)</author>
      <guid>https://lucasfcosta.com/2023/03/16/processes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did You Forget to Review Your PR? And Other Habits Worth Unlearning.</title>
      <link>https://blog.robertsimoes.org/posts/did-you-forget-to-review-your-pr/</link>
      <description>In continuing to reflect on random lessons learned while in the field, a group of nasty habits I used to have popped into mind which I feel might be worth reflecting on. If you’re the type of developer who writes PRs and often wonders why no one reviews them, well here’s some of the reasons that might quell your resentment towards your team mates.
Did You Forget to Review Your PR?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.robertsimoes.org/posts/did-you-forget-to-review-your-pr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The story of LLaMa, so far, or: How The Internet Summoned An Alien Mind On A Smartphone In Three Weeks</title>
      <link>https://leonwu.tech/posts/llama_story</link>
      <description>If you already know what LLaMa is, this probably won’t have any new information; this is primarily meant to record an interesting ongoing story for posterity so we can look back and see how fast things develop at the moment.</description>
      <author> (Leon)</author>
      <guid>https://leonwu.tech/posts/llama_story</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selling my side project</title>
      <link>https://josem.co/selling-my-side-project/</link>
      <description>In the summer of 2019, I started to build Planleave, a SaaS product to manage time off days in an organization. I did it as a side project while working full-time as a software engineer at Buffer. Three years later, in 2022, I sold it.
I’ve never worked harder on any side project than on Planleave.
When I start any project, I usually go through the first honeymoon phase of absolutely loving the idea, but that fades away quickly, and I usually stop at that point.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://josem.co/selling-my-side-project/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimize stackalloc zeroing via BLK by EgorBo &amp;#183; Pull Request #83255 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/83255</link>
      <description>Closes #63500
Let&amp;#39;s insert GT_BLK after GT_HEAPLCL to rely on the former to perform zeroing.
Codegen example:
void Test()
{
    var p = stackalloc byte[250];
    Consume(p);
}
Main:
; Method Progra...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/83255</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 20:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing multi-gigabyte JSON files locally</title>
      <link>https://thenybble.de/posts/json-analysis/</link>
      <description>I’ve had the pleasure of having had to analyse multi-gigabyte JSON dumps in a project context recently. JSON itself is actually a rather pleasant format to consume, as it’s human-readable and there is a lot of tooling available for it. JQ allows expressing sophisticated processing steps in a single command line, and Jupyter with Python and Pandas allow easy interactive analysis to quickly find what you’re looking for.
However, with multi-gigabyte files, analysis becomes quite a lot more difficult.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thenybble.de/posts/json-analysis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 20:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Open Sources Tool for GPT-4-Infused Apps -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/03/17/semantic-kernel.aspx</link>
      <description>Microsoft has open sourced an internal incubation project that can help developers integrate cutting-edge AI models quickly and easily into their apps.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel03/17/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/03/17/semantic-kernel.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 19:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to know about the end of Docker Free Teams | Docker</title>
      <link>https://www.docker.com/blog/we-apologize-we-did-a-terrible-job-announcing-the-end-of-docker-free-teams/</link>
      <description>We apologize for how we communicated and executed sunsetting Docker “Free Team” subscriptions, which alarmed the open source community. Read our FAQ to learn more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.docker.com/blog/we-apologize-we-did-a-terrible-job-announcing-the-end-of-docker-free-teams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 18:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Microsoft 365 Copilot – your copilot for work - The Official Microsoft Blog</title>
      <link>https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/03/16/introducing-microsoft-365-copilot-your-copilot-for-work/</link>
      <description>Humans are hard-wired to dream, to create, to innovate. Each of us seeks to do work that gives us purpose — to write a great novel, to make a discovery, to build strong communities, to care for the sick. The urge to connect to the core of our work lives in all of us. But...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/03/16/introducing-microsoft-365-copilot-your-copilot-for-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Microsoft 365 Copilot – your copilot for work - The Official Microsoft Blog</title>
      <link>https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/03/16/introducing-microsoft-365-copilot-your-copilot-for-work/?ocid=usoc_TWITTER_M365_spl100003915726873</link>
      <description>Humans are hard-wired to dream, to create, to innovate. Each of us seeks to do work that gives us purpose — to write a great novel, to make a discovery, to build strong communities, to care for the sick. The urge to connect to the core of our work lives in all of us. But...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/03/16/introducing-microsoft-365-copilot-your-copilot-for-work/?ocid=usoc_TWITTER_M365_spl100003915726873</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 15:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting C++/WinRT CRTP: Property and event declarations - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230317-00/?p=107946</link>
      <description>They don&amp;#39;t have to be methods; they just have to look like methods.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230317-00/?p=107946</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 15:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Maze Weekly #165 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-165/</link>
      <description>Issue #165 of the Code Maze weekly. Check out what’s new this week and enjoy the read. .NET and C# Top Picks How Async/Await Really Works in C# [devblogs.microsoft.com] Async/Await and asynchronous programming are part of our lives for a long while now (over a decade). We can never know too much about it, so […]</description>
      <author> (Vladimir Pecanac)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-165/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dan Ports (@dan@discuss.systems)</title>
      <link>https://discuss.systems/@dan/110008052977994607</link>
      <description>This is your periodic reminder that 10 years ago an audiophile forum started debating which versions of memcpy had the highest sound quality.

And that C++ new sounds better than malloc.

https://www.audioasylum.com/messages/pcaudio/119979/</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://discuss.systems/@dan/110008052977994607</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 11:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 118 - Empathy, Sympathy, and Compassion For Our Users</title>
      <link>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-118-empathy-sympathy-and-compassion-for-our-users/</link>
      <description>You’ll gain insight into the development of software from a humanitarian perspective. Hear from Jamie, who shares his experiences and skills to ensure his software works for his users. Learn how to design platforms with empathy, sympathy, and compassion in mind to make the world a better place and improve user experience. With resources such as case studies and interviews with people in the tech industry, there’s always something new and exciting to learn. Tune into The .NET Core Podcast today and become a part of the revolution!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-118-empathy-sympathy-and-compassion-for-our-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 09:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>