<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Xee: A Modern XPath and XSLT Engine in Rust</title>
      <link>https://blog.startifact.com/posts/xee/</link>
      <description>I announce Xee, the implementation of XPath and XSLT in Rust that I've been working on for the last two years.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.startifact.com/posts/xee/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to code, ignore AI, then use AI to code even better</title>
      <link>https://kyrylo.org/software/2025/03/27/learn-to-code-ignore-ai-then-use-ai-to-code-even-better.html</link>
      <description>I woke up today to an X post by Amjad Masad, the CEO of Replit, a company that sells “AI as a programming service”.</description>
      <guid>https://kyrylo.org/software/2025/03/27/learn-to-code-ignore-ai-then-use-ai-to-code-even-better.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preface</title>
      <link>https://www.cosmicpython.com/book/preface.html</link>
      <description>You may be wondering who we are and why we wrote this book.</description>
      <guid>https://www.cosmicpython.com/book/preface.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 things I would have told myself before building an autorouter</title>
      <link>https://blog.autorouting.com/p/13-things-i-would-have-told-myself</link>
      <description>Important lessons from trying to build the world's fastest autorouter for about a year</description>
      <guid>https://blog.autorouting.com/p/13-things-i-would-have-told-myself</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A note on the USB-to-PS/2 mouse adapter that came with Microsoft mouse devices - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250325-00/?p=110993</link>
      <description>It's a purely mechanical adapter that relies on smarts in the mouse itself.</description>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250325-00/?p=110993</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybridCache is finally stable!!! FAST L1 + L2 Cache in .NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wlNHmZHQ5sY</link>
      <description>Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Get the source code here: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic



Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wlNHmZHQ5sY</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering htmx Attributes: Your Toolkit for Razor Pages Awesomeness - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/mastering-htmx-attributes-your-toolkit-for-razor-pages-awesomeness/</link>
      <description>Welcome back, coders! Now that you’ve dipped your toes into the htmx waters, it’s time to wade in a little deeper. Today, we’re diving headfirst into htmx attributes — the secret sauce that makes your Razor Pages dance with interactivity. So, buckle up and get ready for some fun!</description>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/mastering-htmx-attributes-your-toolkit-for-razor-pages-awesomeness/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kagi Search Stats</title>
      <link>https://kagi.com/stats?stat=leaderboard</link>
      <description>Better search results with no ads. Welcome to Kagi (pronounced kah-gee), a paid search engine that gives power back to the user.</description>
      <guid>https://kagi.com/stats?stat=leaderboard</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tried making artificial sunlight at home</title>
      <link>https://victorpoughon.fr/i-tried-making-artificial-sunlight-at-home/</link>
      <description>Some time ago, I saw  where they make artificial sunlight at home with a 500W LED and a gigantic (1.2m) parabolic reflector. I've been fascinated by this pro...</description>
      <guid>https://victorpoughon.fr/i-tried-making-artificial-sunlight-at-home/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Needs a Snow Sequoia</title>
      <link>https://reviews.ofb.biz/safari/article/1300.html</link>
      <description>The same year Apple launched the iPhone, it unveiled a massive upgrade to Mac OS X known as Leopard, sporting “300 New Features.” Two years later, it did something almost unheard of: it released Snow Leopard, an upgrade all about how little it added and how much it took away. Apple needs to make it snow again.</description>
      <guid>https://reviews.ofb.biz/safari/article/1300.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Death of the Software Engineer by a Thousand Prompts</title>
      <link>https://verdikapuku.com/posts/the-death-of-the-software-engineer-by-a-thousand-prompts/</link>
      <description>This is Verdi's personal website. He writes about interesting ideas or projects.</description>
      <guid>https://verdikapuku.com/posts/the-death-of-the-software-engineer-by-a-thousand-prompts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Kempé - Dockerizing your .NET C# MCP Server for AI Clients like Claude Desktop</title>
      <link>https://laurentkempe.com/2025/03/27/dockerizing-your-dotnet-csharp-mcp-server-for-ai-clients-like-claude-desktop/</link>
      <description>My previous post showed how easy it is to develop a .NET C# MCP server and write a client able to communicate with it. Now, the question is how we can distribute our MCP server to be used by AI clients. In this post, we’ll leverage the knowledge acquired from my previous posts to explore how to dockerize your .NET C# MCP server.</description>
      <guid>https://laurentkempe.com/2025/03/27/dockerizing-your-dotnet-csharp-mcp-server-for-ai-clients-like-claude-desktop/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Money Habits of the Successfully Rich: Insights from “The Millionaire Next Door”</title>
      <link>https://enlight8.com/2025/03/25/8-money-habits-of-the-successfully-rich-from-the-millionaire-next-door/</link>
      <description>I’ve always been curious about the money habits of successful, wealthy people. Often, these habits are what lead them to become extremely rich. We need specific habits to help us succeed and build our wealth to achieve our financial goals and we can adopt some of these effective practices by learning from those who are…</description>
      <guid>https://enlight8.com/2025/03/25/8-money-habits-of-the-successfully-rich-from-the-millionaire-next-door/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering GPT-4o's Image Gen Process</title>
      <link>https://www.philipnielsen.info/blog/blog_posts/4o-image.md</link>
      <description>OpenAI's 4o Image Generation capability launched two days ago on March 25th, 2025. The quality of the images it creates is the best among all contemporary models by a large margin. However, what is most interesting is the way it seems to generate the image: first it quickly creates a blurry version of the final image, then sharpens it from top to bottom, as if loading an image on a dial-up connection. This shouldn't be possible using a standard latent diffusion model, which would generate the whole image at once. What could they be doing different? As why is it better?</description>
      <guid>https://www.philipnielsen.info/blog/blog_posts/4o-image.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never in a million years...</title>
      <link>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2025/never-million-years</link>
      <description>...would I have imagined my video on whether a pigeon is faster than the Internet would end up on a popular Italian quiz show, L'Eredita. Specifically, in the March 26th episode (playable in Italy, or with an account).</description>
      <guid>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2025/never-million-years</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The "No, But" Engineer</title>
      <link>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/no-but-engineer/</link>
      <description>When you're improvising a comedy scene, the golden rule is to respond with "yes, and" to everything your partners say and do. This unwavering acceptance can produce riotous bouts of laughter. In an engineering team, it just creates unholy messes.</description>
      <guid>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/no-but-engineer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron's Blog</title>
      <link>https://aaron-blog.onrender.com/post/the-beauty-in-not-knowing</link>
      <description>3/26/20251 mins read</description>
      <guid>https://aaron-blog.onrender.com/post/the-beauty-in-not-knowing</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golang on the PlayStation 2</title>
      <link>https://rgsilva.com/blog/ps2-go-part-1/</link>
      <description>The PS2 is more than capable of doing some wild things, including running Linux. I always wondered if we could just write baremetal Go code on it, so I decided to give it a try.</description>
      <guid>https://rgsilva.com/blog/ps2-go-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs - A Ghost in the Machine | zacksiri.dev</title>
      <link>https://zacksiri.dev/posts/llms-a-ghost-in-the-machine/</link>
      <description>The landscape of Large Language Models (LLMs) is evolving rapidly, with powerful and open models being released at an unprecedented pace. As these technologies advance, so does the potential to integrate them into our existing systems. Traditionally, we've built systems with distinct layers such as the Application layer and Data Persistence layer.</description>
      <guid>https://zacksiri.dev/posts/llms-a-ghost-in-the-machine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>do what i mean (dwim) - alp1n3</title>
      <link>https://alp1n3.dev/blog/0020-do-what-i-mean/</link>
      <description>a collection of cybersecurity-related notes &amp; projects.</description>
      <guid>https://alp1n3.dev/blog/0020-do-what-i-mean/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Safari bug that punishes you for using content blockers | BenHollis.net</title>
      <link>https://benhollis.net/blog/2025/01/04/the-safari-bug-that-punishes-you-for-using-content-blockers/</link>
      <description>Running content blockers in your browser is a good idea–yes, you block ads, but you also block malware, cryptominers, tracking, and more. In general, the experience of using the web with a good content blocker should be noticeably faster, as you skip downloading and executing many megabytes of code, images, and videos that provides you with no benefit. I’ve run content blocking extensions since they were first introduced and I’ve never looked back.

Safari 15, released in September 2021, was the first version to support extensions, including content blocking extensions. This was a huge improvement to mobile browsing on iOS, which doesn’t offer any choice of browser besides Safari. Safari finally had a way to fight back against intrusive ads just like other browsers. I chose to use 1Blocker, which was highly reviewed by Apple aficionados at the time, though I’m sure there are other good alternatives.

</description>
      <guid>https://benhollis.net/blog/2025/01/04/the-safari-bug-that-punishes-you-for-using-content-blockers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The False Promise of ORMs | Mike Pray</title>
      <link>https://mikepray.dev/posts/false-promise-of-orms/</link>
      <description>ORMs promise to abstract databases and SQL. At any normal scale, this promise fails and the ORM becomes a powerful multiplier of pointless complexity</description>
      <guid>https://mikepray.dev/posts/false-promise-of-orms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing MCP Tools: A Command-Line Inspector for Model Context Protocol Servers</title>
      <link>https://blog.fka.dev/blog/2025-03-26-introducing-mcp-tools-cli/</link>
      <description>Discover MCP Tools, a powerful CLI for interacting with Model Context Protocol servers using stdio transport. Learn how to discover and call tools, list resources, and interact with MCP-compatible services.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.fka.dev/blog/2025-03-26-introducing-mcp-tools-cli/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the hype | Alberto Sadde</title>
      <link>https://www.albertosadde.com/blog/beyond-the-hype/</link>
      <description>The Siren Song of New Tech Every morning, I open Twitter to find my feed transformed into an AI wonderland.</description>
      <author> (Alberto Sadde)</author>
      <guid>https://www.albertosadde.com/blog/beyond-the-hype/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take This On-Call Rotation and Shove It</title>
      <link>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/take-oncall-and-shove-it/</link>
      <description>At some companies, it is expected that certain engineers will serve as part of a formal on-call rotation. On paper, this seems like a reasonable way to ensure the reliability of the product. In practice, it is a miserable burden and you probably won't even get paid for it.</description>
      <guid>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/take-oncall-and-shove-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Open Source Journey - Ashpreet Bedi</title>
      <link>https://www.ashpreetbedi.com/articles/oss-journey</link>
      <description>My journey building one of the most popular Agent Libraries</description>
      <guid>https://www.ashpreetbedi.com/articles/oss-journey</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Execution is everything... or nothing?</title>
      <link>https://nial.se/blog/execution-is-nothing/</link>
      <description>One striking feature of modern artificial intelligence, especially in large language models like ChatGPT, Claude, and Gemini, is their ability to instantly generate surprisingly advanced software engineering solutions. One interpretation of this phenomenon is that we are in the midst of a wave of commoditization. A specific subset of cognitive work, once scarce and expensive, has become infinitely accessible at minimal cost. With the rise of “vibe coding”, where AI tools are used transform a basic idea into a functional app or website almost instantly for fun, it seems that any basic concept for a digital product can now be cloned on the spot. The barrier to entry has dropped dramatically, while the bar for uniqueness has risen just as fast. Any simple enough product can be replicated instantly. Are we witnessing the rapid commoditization of cognitive work, with software engineering at the forefront?</description>
      <guid>https://nial.se/blog/execution-is-nothing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracing the thoughts of a large language model</title>
      <link>https://www.anthropic.com/research/tracing-thoughts-language-model</link>
      <description>Anthropic's latest interpretability research: a new microscope to understand Claude's internal mechanisms</description>
      <guid>https://www.anthropic.com/research/tracing-thoughts-language-model</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 21:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>