<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Newton Papers : College Notebook</title>
      <link>http://cudl.lib.cam.ac.uk/view/MS-ADD-04000/</link>
      <description>Add. 4000 is a small notebook that Newton appears to have begun using in the winter of 1663-4. He continued to write in it extensively over the next two or three years, mostly jotting down personal annotation of his mathematical discoveries. It contains notes on his mathematical and geometrical reading, drawn from Frans van Schooten’s Exercitationummathematicarum (Leiden, 1657) and from his edition of the works of François Viète (Leiden, 1646), as well as from the writings of William Oughtred and of the Oxford mathematician, John Wallis. Newton was particularly interested in Wallis’ Arithmetica infinitorum (included in his Operum Mathematicorum Pars Altera (1656)), in which problems of mathematical methods of reasoning about the quadrature of areas and volumes through consideration of their indivisible elements of line and surface were set out. This notebook also contains evidence of the development of Newton’s own mathematical skill in this period, especially his study of infinite series and development of the binomial theorem, the evolution of the differential calculus, and its application to the problem of quadratures and integration. Although Newton had been inspired in his mathematical work on curved lines and surfaces by reading Wallis and most likely by listening to the lectures that Barrow delivered in 1664, his knowledge of Descartes’ geometry was also critical in these discoveries. This notebook also contains Newton’s investigation of the musical scale in ‘Of Musick’ (c. 1665) [fols 138r-143r]. Musical theory was at the time considered as part of the mathematical sciences. One of the later entries in this notebook derives from Newton’s knowledge of Descartes’ La dioptrique (1637), which Newton probably read in a Latin edition published at Paris in 1656. By September 1664, Newton had learned about the sine law of refraction through his reading of Descartes’ works, and, in the winter of 1665-6, he investigated Descartes’ findings about refraction at curved surfaces. This is probably the date of the composition of the essay ‘Of Refractions’ [fols 26r-33r]. Newton later told Oldenburg that he had first applied himself to grinding lenses that were not spherical in the winter of 1666 and this essay includes the detailed description of a machine for shaping a wheel to a hyperbolical profile, which could later be used for grinding lenses. Such a machine had been discussed in chapter ten of La dioptrique, but Newton improved the design and gave a geometrical demonstration of its operation. Niccolò Guicciardini, Università degli Studi di Milano, and Scott Mandelbrote, Peterhouse, Cambridge. The Key Developments in Newton's Thinking Newton and the fundamental theorem. Folio 120v</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://cudl.lib.cam.ac.uk/view/MS-ADD-04000/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 20:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Border Patrol Says They Can Create Central Repository Of Traveler Emails, Keep Them For 75 Years - View from the Wing</title>
      <link>https://viewfromthewing.com/us-border-patrol-says-they-can-create-central-repository-of-traveler-emails-keep-them-for-75-years/</link>
      <description>The U.S. government has taken the opportunity during the global pandemic, when people aren't traveling out of the country much, to roll out a new platform for storing information they believe they are entitled to take from people crossing the border.  A new filing reveals how the U.S. Border Patrol will store data from traveler devices centrally, keeping it backed up and searchable for up to 75 years.</description>
      <author> (garyleff)</author>
      <guid>https://viewfromthewing.com/us-border-patrol-says-they-can-create-central-repository-of-traveler-emails-keep-them-for-75-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 19:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making an OS (x86) - Part 1: CPU, Assembly, Booting</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MwPjvJ9ulSc</link>
      <description>In this video you will (hopefully) learn the basis of what the CPU is, what Assembly is like and even use some Assembly code to create a functioning boot sector.

New Video Next Sunday

Ben Eater: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCS0N5baNlQWJCUrhCEo8WlA

To install nasm and qemu on linux run the following commands:
sudo apt update
sudo apt install nasm
sudo apt-get install qemu-system

To install NASM on windows use this link: shorturl.at/gowT2
(Look, it wasn't even a rickroll after all!)</description>
      <author> (Daedalus Community)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MwPjvJ9ulSc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 18:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's New In DevTools (Chrome 86)  |  Web  |  Google Developers</title>
      <link>https://developers.google.com/web/updates/2020/08/devtools#capture-node-screenshot</link>
      <description>New Media panel, capture node screenshot, Issues tab updates, emulate missing local fonts, inactive users and prefers-reduced-data.</description>
      <author> (By
      
        
          Jecelyn
          Yeen)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.google.com/web/updates/2020/08/devtools#capture-node-screenshot</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 18:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atmosphere Experiment by Sebastian Lague</title>
      <link>https://sebastian.itch.io/atmosphere-experiment</link>
      <description>Available for Windows, macOS</description>
      <author> (hotwaterheater)</author>
      <guid>https://sebastian.itch.io/atmosphere-experiment</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 17:18:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding Adventure: Atmosphere</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DxfEbulyFcY</link>
      <description>The planets in my solar system project are looking a bit hostile and uninviting, so in this video I'll be attempting to add some cozy atmospheres around them.

Some notes:
• I made a little build where you can play with the atmosphere settings yourself, which you can find over here if you're interested: https://sebastian.itch.io/atmosphere-experiment

• A number of knowledgeable people have pointed out in the comments that reality is not nearly as simple as my little diagram around 4:35, and that light does not literally wiggle up and down like a wave, so please note that the diagram is incorrect!

• This project was inspired by the game Outer Wilds, which I highly recommend playing!

Project Files:
The atmosphere code is currently only available to patrons of the channel, so if you'd like to get early access to it (and support my work in the process!) you can find it here: https://www.patreon.com/posts/project-files-40730130
It will be freely available to everyone from September 15.

Resources:
https://developer.nvidia.com/gpugems/gpugems2/part-ii-shading-lighting-and-shadows/chapter-16-accurate-atmospheric-scattering
https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/28895/why-is-the-sky-not-purple
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scattering

Music:
"Brief Respite" by Antti Luode
"When Rain Comes" by Tide Electric
"Door to Door Disco" by Bright Seed
"Reflections of Space and Time" by AEROPLANES
"Frontier" by Shimmer
"In the Atmosphere" by Bad Snacks
"Reflections" by MK2
"Nidra in the Sky with Ayla" by Jesse Gallagher
"Far Away" by Antti Luode

Sections:
0:00 Intro
0:32 Setup
2:46 Resources
3:25 Light Scattering
6:15 Coding the Shader
11:55 Initial Results
13:10 Adding Colour
15:20 Colourful Results
16:40 Optimisation
17:39 Stars
18:50 Exploration</description>
      <author> (Sebastian Lague)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DxfEbulyFcY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 17:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gary Ewan Park - How to verify SQL Server connection using udl file</title>
      <link>https://www.gep13.co.uk/blog/how-to-verify-sql-server-connection-using-udl-file</link>
      <description>Ramblings and Ponderings of a Microsoft Fan Boy...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.gep13.co.uk/blog/how-to-verify-sql-server-connection-using-udl-file</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 12:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Stuff They Didn't Teach You #8 - Containers? So What? Docker 101 Explained</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0oEsMwSxBsk</link>
      <description>Containers are confusing. They are a buzzword that everyone is saying but no one understands. Why use them? Why are they better than virtual machines? How are they different than just using a machine regularly? Let's build a Dockerfile FROM Scratch and built it up to an Nginx webserver and finally a multistage Dockerfile with building, testing, and running, in production, in just 30 min!</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0oEsMwSxBsk</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 10:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sbidy/wiz_light</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sbidy/wiz_light</link>
      <description>A WiZ Light intergration for Home Assistant. Contribute to sbidy/wiz_light development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (sbidy)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sbidy/wiz_light</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 08:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking about dependencies :: sunshowers</title>
      <link>https://sunshowers.io/posts/dependencies/?twitter=</link>
      <description>Opinions about relying on other people's work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sunshowers.io/posts/dependencies/?twitter=</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 07:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hide My Secrets - Visual Studio Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=emadashi.hide-my-secrets</link>
      <description>Extension for Visual Studio Code - Hides secrets in YAML files</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=emadashi.hide-my-secrets</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 06:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosatom releases previously classified documentary video of Tsar Bomba nuke test</title>
      <link>https://thebarentsobserver.com/en/security/2020/08/rosatom-releases-previously-classified-documentary-video-50-mt-novaya-zemlya-test</link>
      <description>Photos and short video clips have previously been available, but this unseen 40 minutes declassified footage of the Soviet Union’s monster nuclear bomb give a whole new insight into what happened on Novaya Zemlya on October 30, 1961.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thebarentsobserver.com/en/security/2020/08/rosatom-releases-previously-classified-documentary-video-50-mt-novaya-zemlya-test</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 06:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExecutionContext vs SynchronizationContext | .NET Parallel Programming</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/pfxteam/executioncontext-vs-synchronizationcontext/</link>
      <description>I’ve been asked a few times recently various questions about ExecutionContext and SynchronizationContext, for example what the differences are between them, what it means to “flow” them, and how they relate to the new async/await keywords in C# and Visual Basic. </description>
      <author> (Stephen Toub Partner Software Engineer, .NET Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/pfxteam/executioncontext-vs-synchronizationcontext/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 05:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worldwide Mobile Data Pricing League | Cost of 1GB in 230 countries - Cable.co.uk</title>
      <link>https://www.cable.co.uk/mobiles/worldwide-data-pricing/</link>
      <description>Analysis of over 6,300 mobile plans in 230 countries reveals the cost of mobile data in 230 countries.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cable.co.uk/mobiles/worldwide-data-pricing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 05:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logical Increments</title>
      <link>https://www.logicalincrements.com/</link>
      <description>Logical Increments</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.logicalincrements.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 04:44:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the economic value of a face mask is $56.14</title>
      <link>https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2020/08/22/why-the-economic-value-of-a-face-mask-is-5614</link>
      <description>A new frontier in facial finance</description>
      <author> (Aug 22nd 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2020/08/22/why-the-economic-value-of-a-face-mask-is-5614</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 02:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilo: Raspberry Pi-Powered Lights-Out Remote Server Management for $60 or less</title>
      <link>https://zach.bloomqu.ist/blog/2020/08/pilo-raspberry-pi-lights-out-management.html</link>
      <description>The completed Pilo controller, before final installation. The USB capture card and Arduino Nano USB serial are soldered to the underside of the 3B+.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zach.bloomqu.ist/blog/2020/08/pilo-raspberry-pi-lights-out-management.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 23:21:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaperCall.io - .NET Conf 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.papercall.io/dotnetconf</link>
      <description>.NET Conf is a free, three day virtual developer event co-organized by the .NET community and Microsoft. This year .NET 5.0 will launch at .NET Conf 2020! Come celebrate and learn about the new release. We're also celebrating our 10th anniversary and we're working on a few more surprises. You won...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.papercall.io/dotnetconf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 22:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSBuild Log Viewer</title>
      <link>https://msbuildlog.com/</link>
      <description>or, install the Visual Studio Extension to investigate builds inside Visual Studio:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://msbuildlog.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 22:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain, the amazing solution for almost nothing</title>
      <link>https://thecorrespondent.com/655/blockchain-the-amazing-solution-for-almost-nothing/86649455475-f933fe63</link>
      <description>Blockchain technology is going to change everything: the shipping industry, the financial system, government … in fact, what won’t it change? But enthusiasm for it mainly stems from a lack of knowledge and understanding. The blockchain is a solution in search of a problem.</description>
      <author> (Jesse Frederik)</author>
      <guid>https://thecorrespondent.com/655/blockchain-the-amazing-solution-for-almost-nothing/86649455475-f933fe63</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 22:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build tools around workflows, not workflows around tools</title>
      <link>https://thesephist.com/posts/tools/</link>
      <description>This March, I spent a couple of days traveling through western Iceland.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thesephist.com/posts/tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 21:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>