<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>3D Modeling with Paper</title>
      <link>https://www.arvinpoddar.com/blog/3d-modeling-with-paper</link>
      <description>Exploring the process of designing and assembling 3D models from paper.</description>
      <guid>https://www.arvinpoddar.com/blog/3d-modeling-with-paper</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 03:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The productivity paradox of AI coding assistants</title>
      <link>https://www.cerbos.dev/blog/productivity-paradox-of-ai-coding-assistants</link>
      <description>AI coding assistants promise speed, but do they deliver? Explore data, developer insights, and security risks showing why AI feels faster but often slows production. Learn where tools like Cursor and Claude Code help, and where they fail.</description>
      <category>conference</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>git</category>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>math</category>
      <guid>https://www.cerbos.dev/blog/productivity-paradox-of-ai-coding-assistants</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 03:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Open Web Dies When We Give Up</title>
      <link>https://blog.antonlydike.de/The%20Open%20Web%20Dies%20When%20We%20Give%20Up.html</link>
      <description>I keep reading this thing, repeated as if it's fact: "The Open Web is Dead". At first I agreed, maybe because I also felt bummed out by what's happening, but I have since come 180° on this viewpoint. The Open Web cannot die. As long as there is one person believing in it, it will be there. It's not a thing that you can "turn it off", "fence it in", "exclude it", or whatever else you want to say. The Open Web is what you, as the user, do with it. It will only die if we stop believing.</description>
      <category>youtube</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <guid>https://blog.antonlydike.de/The%20Open%20Web%20Dies%20When%20We%20Give%20Up.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Babies and LLMs</title>
      <link>https://blog.karliner.net/posts/babies-and-llms/</link>
      <description>Last week, I spent some time with Haley (one year old) doing serious research into ‘putting things into other things’.
We’d brought her a soft toy squirrel and, inevitably, she had found the cardboard box it came in much more interesting. There followed a considerable period of putting various objects into the box and taking them out again. This was pretty interesting, but the discovery that closing the box made the items disappear was even more fascinating.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.karliner.net/posts/babies-and-llms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six years of Admiral Shark's Keyboards</title>
      <link>https://sharktastica.co.uk/announcements/202509A</link>
      <description>Celebration of the six-year anniversary of Admiral Shark's Keyboards!</description>
      <category>wiki</category>
      <category>sql</category>
      <guid>https://sharktastica.co.uk/announcements/202509A</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zettelkasten</title>
      <link>https://www.ssp.sh/brain/zettelkasten/</link>
      <description>Started by [[Niklas Luhmann]], also called “Slip Box”. This approach will further dilute the idea of a librarian who organizes books in main categories and sub-folder and focuses only on the thought at hand as an individual note. Instead of spending lots of your brainpower on which folder to put a specific note in, you start creating it in one folder for all and linking them together. Usually, you wouldn’t have any structure in these concepts, but I combined the two methods into my Second Brain. You also see in the above design under 💡 Resources/🗃 Zettelkasten I have its folder.</description>
      <category>2ndbrain</category>
      <category>health</category>
      <guid>https://www.ssp.sh/brain/zettelkasten/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARM is great, ARM is terrible (and so is RISC-V)</title>
      <link>https://changelog.complete.org/archives/10858-arm-is-great-arm-is-terrible-and-so-is-risc-v</link>
      <description>I’ve long been interested in new and different platforms.  I ran Debian on an Alpha back in the late 1990s and was part of the Alpha port team; then I helped bootstrap Debian on amd64.  I’ve got somewhere around 8 Raspberry Pi devices in active use right now, and the free NNCPNET Internet email service I manage runs on an ARM instance at a cloud provider.</description>
      <category>encryption</category>
      <category>hardware</category>
      <category>linux</category>
      <guid>https://changelog.complete.org/archives/10858-arm-is-great-arm-is-terrible-and-so-is-risc-v</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mirror With No Reflection</title>
      <link>https://simone.org/mirror/</link>
      <description>From lovers to spouses, from employers to parental approval, we search for ourselves in others' eyes—creating perhaps the most elaborate illusion ever sustained: that validation exists outside the self that seeks it.</description>
      <category>git</category>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <guid>https://simone.org/mirror/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I built an LLM‑assisted pipeline that removes ~95% of podcast ads -&gt; PodcastAdBlock.app - Ben Bowler</title>
      <link>https://benbowler.com/how-i-built-an-llm%E2%80%91assisted-pipeline-that-removes-95-of-podcast-ads-podcastadblock-app/</link>
      <description>Please help me out and give this post a vote over on Hacker News 😉 (if you haven’t already). I’ve been listening to podcasts for over 15 years. Back then, ads were host-read and usually relevant. Now? Many shows cram in 15+ minutes of loud, intrusive ads per hour. So, I built a system to […]</description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://benbowler.com/how-i-built-an-llm%E2%80%91assisted-pipeline-that-removes-95-of-podcast-ads-podcastadblock-app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>And</title>
      <link>https://lucasbarbosa.net/posts/and/</link>
      <description>Personal website and blog. Opinions are my own.</description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>hardware</category>
      <guid>https://lucasbarbosa.net/posts/and/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on how to disagree</title>
      <link>https://johnsillings.com/2025/09/11/thoughts-on-how-to-disagree.html</link>
      <description>Back in the day, I was on my school’s debate team.

It was basically a sport for nerds. (In hindsight, my friend group did a lot of “sports for nerds” activities: chess, quiz bowl, competitive gaming, etc.)

Anyway, back to the debate team. We treated it like a sport. We trained for it and attended competitions. It was a lot of fun – but deep down, we were there to win.

A stronger, better-researched, more clearly articulated argument was the big key to winning (obvious).

But there were lots of other ways to score points:


  by flustering your opponent with a hard question,
  catching them off-guard,
  pointing out something silly they said,
  and so on.


This is how most people think about debating, whether it’s on social media or between political candidates. It is eristic (about “winning”).

Obviously, this is a popular form of entertainment. We enjoy the drama. We like seeing other people (particularly those we disagree with) get “owned” / “dunked on” / “destroyed” / etc.

What sucks about this is how shallow it is.

Mostly in academic circles, there is a less popular and considerably less entertaining form of debate. It is dialectic (about learning through disagreement).

The ground-rules are different:


  
    You are charitable. You interpret your opponent’s argument in a strong way, not a weak way.
  
  
    You look for common ground. If you find yourself agreeing on something – however small – you build from there.
  
  
    You put your ego aside. Being wrong is not a bad thing; it means you’re learning something new.
  


In a narrow, self-serving sense, there’s obviously a lot of value in being persuasive. But in aggregate, it’s a lot more exciting to actually be right vs. simply being perceived that way.

This post, and particularly its title, was inspired by this excellent essay by Paul Graham.
</description>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <guid>https://johnsillings.com/2025/09/11/thoughts-on-how-to-disagree.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When the Job Search Becomes Impossible: Three Phases of Burnout – Holy Ghost Stories</title>
      <link>https://www.jeffwofford.com/wp/?p=2240</link>
      <description>I have the good fortune to have a job right now, but many of my friends are out of work. Most have been searching for a while. Some are encountering a problem that has my full sympathy, something I’ve experienced myself at various times. I’m not sure I can solve it, but maybe I can help put words to what some are going through.</description>
      <guid>https://www.jeffwofford.com/wp/?p=2240</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Let Your Mocks Mock You!</title>
      <link>https://revontulet.dev/p/2025-dont-let-your-mocks-mock-you/</link>
      <description>Mock testing is useful, but there is a risk of building false confidence when we don't pay close attention. </description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>sql</category>
      <guid>https://revontulet.dev/p/2025-dont-let-your-mocks-mock-you/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harmonic - News</title>
      <link>https://harmonic.fun/news</link>
      <description>AI for Formal Mathematical Reasoning</description>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>math</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>apple</category>
      <guid>https://harmonic.fun/news</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Hope the Search for Extraterrestrial Life Finds Nothing</title>
      <link>https://nickbostrom.com/papers/where-are-they/</link>
      <description>Discovering indepently evolved life
on Mars would bad news for humanity.</description>
      <category>health</category>
      <guid>https://nickbostrom.com/papers/where-are-they/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I’m Slow — LocalThunk</title>
      <link>https://localthunk.com/blog/im-slow</link>
      <description>Hello people, long time no chat!   I have some unfortunate news: The promised 2025 Balatro 1.1 update isn’t going to come out in 2025. I know, I announced that it would, but it has become clear now that it won’t happen by the end of the year and I wanted to tell you all now. I feel bad for not keepi</description>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <guid>https://localthunk.com/blog/im-slow</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magical systems thinking</title>
      <link>https://www.worksinprogress.news/p/magical-systems-thinking</link>
      <description>Systems thinkers fail because they ignore an important fact: systems fight back.</description>
      <category>health</category>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <guid>https://www.worksinprogress.news/p/magical-systems-thinking</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully autonomous robots are much closer than you think – Sergey Levine</title>
      <link>https://www.dwarkesh.com/p/sergey-levine</link>
      <description>Plus, how VLA models work, self-improvement from deployment, and China’s hardware advantage</description>
      <category>2ndbrain</category>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <category>hardware</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>visualstudio</category>
      <guid>https://www.dwarkesh.com/p/sergey-levine</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find Good Problems - Don't Break Prod</title>
      <link>https://dontbreakprod.com/posts/find-good-problems</link>
      <description>Don't Break Prod provides bite-sized pieces of career advice for software engineers.</description>
      <guid>https://dontbreakprod.com/posts/find-good-problems</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Quadrants of Personality — Ben Bernstein Psychotherapy</title>
      <link>https://benbernsteintherapy.com/writing/four-quadrants-of-personality</link>
      <description>I’ve been sitting with Dr. Matthew Bennett’s (2024) Four Quadrants of Personality from his book  Toward an Integrated Analytical Psychology . His system borrows from traditional psychoanalytic structures but reframes them in a way that feels less about pathology and more about motion. What excites m</description>
      <category>health</category>
      <guid>https://benbernsteintherapy.com/writing/four-quadrants-of-personality</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradox of Signaling – roady's rants</title>
      <link>https://think-twice.me/?p=88</link>
      <description>Social Signaling is the idea that people, through actions or even words, may be trying to get others to believe something about them. A simple example might be trying to signal you are smart by using big words. Or conversely, trying to signal you’re a chill bro™ by using all those latest slang words and memes. Or signal you’re rich by purchasing a certain item.</description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://think-twice.me/?p=88</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death💀 to type classes</title>
      <link>https://jappie.me/death-to-type-classes.html</link>
      <description>Have you ever seen a Number grazing in the fields? Or a Functor chirping in the trees? No? That’s because they’re LIES. LIES told by the bourgeoisie to keep common folk down. But I say NO, no longer shall we be kept down by deceit! Come brothers and sisters, come and let us create a system of values. Where values are no longer constrained by their type class, but instead merged as a signature into a module. Come comrades, let us open the Backpack.</description>
      <category>compilers</category>
      <guid>https://jappie.me/death-to-type-classes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Name - Academic Profile</title>
      <link>https://alejogb1.vercel.app/blog/blurring-chrome</link>
      <description>Personal academic profile showcasing research, publications, and experiments</description>
      <category>marketing</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://alejogb1.vercel.app/blog/blurring-chrome</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - qgis/QGIS: QGIS is a free, open source, cross platform (lin/win/mac) geographical information system (GIS)</title>
      <link>https://github.com/qgis/QGIS</link>
      <description>QGIS is a free, open source, cross platform (lin/win/mac) geographical information system (GIS) - qgis/QGIS</description>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>containers</category>
      <category>apple</category>
      <category>git</category>
      <guid>https://github.com/qgis/QGIS</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway's first adventure games, part 1 - Spillhistorie.no</title>
      <link>https://spillhistorie.no/2025/09/11/norways-first-adventure-games-part-1/</link>
      <description>The story of SVHA Adventure, and how it was saved after over 40 years of obscurity.</description>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <guid>https://spillhistorie.no/2025/09/11/norways-first-adventure-games-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UTF-8 is a Brilliant Design — Vishnu's Pages</title>
      <link>https://iamvishnu.com/posts/utf8-is-brilliant-design</link>
      <description>Exploring the brilliant design of UTF-8 encoding system that represents millions of characters while being backward compatible with ASCII</description>
      <guid>https://iamvishnu.com/posts/utf8-is-brilliant-design</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 22:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mantle Model</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3141/</link>
      <description></description>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3141/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting Lazy Tasks in a Cache, and Computing Only Once, When First Requested | no dogma blog</title>
      <link>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2025/09/putting-lazy-tasks-in-a-cache-and-computing-only-once-when-first-requested/</link>
      <description>This is an update to an earlier post on caching Tasks and only executing them when first accessed. This version uses Lazy&lt;Task&lt;string&gt;&gt; to hold the Task.</description>
      <guid>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2025/09/putting-lazy-tasks-in-a-cache-and-computing-only-once-when-first-requested/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The challenge of maintaining curl</title>
      <link>https://lwn.net/Articles/1034966/</link>
      <description>Keynote sessions at Open Source Summit events tend not to allow much time for detailed talks, a [...]</description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>linux</category>
      <guid>https://lwn.net/Articles/1034966/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Hard Leetcode Problems are Easy Constraint Problems</title>
      <link>https://buttondown.com/hillelwayne/archive/many-hard-leetcode-problems-are-easy-constraint/</link>
      <description>Use the right tool for the job.</description>
      <guid>https://buttondown.com/hillelwayne/archive/many-hard-leetcode-problems-are-easy-constraint/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhibiting my Game at Gamescom for the First Time!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=QV0D5bI9l7c</link>
      <description>Wishlist HomeGrown on Steam: https://store.steampowered.com/app/1894560/HomeGrown/

Support the channel on Patreon and get access to the game &amp; code for Homegrown, the city-builder, and Equilinox:
https://www.patreon.com/thinmatrix

Play my previous game "Equilinox":
https://store.steampowered.com/app/853550/Equilinox/

Gamecity Hamburg:
https://gamecity-hamburg.de/de/

Follow the game's progress on my social media:
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/thinmatrix/
Twitter: https://twitter.com/ThinMatrix
Bluesky: https://bsky.app/profile/thinmatrix.bsky.social
Trello: https://trello.com/b/W3zkIJTM/farm
Email: thinmatrix@gmail.com

Background music by Jamal Green:
https://open.spotify.com/artist/50jTMgIPZrjKFgHbCvoeRt?si=Z-xfUXEXQCuGdGRy7qf9Ug&amp;dl_branch=1

#HomeGrown</description>
      <author> (ThinMatrix)</author>
      <category>audio</category>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <category>youtube</category>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=QV0D5bI9l7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Treasury Is Expanding The Patriot Act To Attack Bitcoin Self Custody</title>
      <link>https://www.tftc.io/treasury-iexpanding-patriot-act/</link>
      <description>We shouldn't have to cater to the lowest common denominator.</description>
      <category>cryptography</category>
      <category>apple</category>
      <guid>https://www.tftc.io/treasury-iexpanding-patriot-act/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen</title>
      <link>https://qwen.ai/blog?id=4074cca80393150c248e508aa62983f9cb7d27cd&amp;from=research.latest-advancements-list</link>
      <description>Qwen Chat offers comprehensive functionality spanning chatbot, image and video understanding, image generation, document processing, web search integration, tool utilization, and artifacts.</description>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://qwen.ai/blog?id=4074cca80393150c248e508aa62983f9cb7d27cd&amp;from=research.latest-advancements-list</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why our website looks like an operating system - PostHog</title>
      <link>https://posthog.com/blog/why-os</link>
      <description>I have a problem with many large, technical websites. Often times, I’ll want to refer to different pages at the same time. So I’ll  CMD  + click “a…</description>
      <category>typescript</category>
      <category>marketing</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>git</category>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <guid>https://posthog.com/blog/why-os</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Svend Waldorff (@swaldorff@swiss.social)</title>
      <link>https://swiss.social/@swaldorff/115186445638788782</link>
      <description>Interesting: a Danish supermarket chain is setting up "Emergency Stores" that can keep open for up to three days without power or telecom and store an expanded stock of non-perishable food and essentials.
The idea is that no one should be more than 50 km from such a store and it should prevent hoarding/panic buying as people will know basic food will be available in an emergency. 
Should be rolled out in 2028 at the latest.

Article in Danish: https://www.dr.dk/nyheder/penge/se-kortet-her-kan-du-krise-handle</description>
      <guid>https://swiss.social/@swaldorff/115186445638788782</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Memory: A Different Philosophy</title>
      <link>https://www.shloked.com/writing/claude-memory</link>
      <description>A breakdown of Claude's memory implementation, how it differs from ChatGPT, and what these opposite approaches reveal about each company's philosophy.</description>
      <author> (Shlok Khemani)</author>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>cryptography</category>
      <guid>https://www.shloked.com/writing/claude-memory</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>