<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How we shrunk our Javascript monorepo git size by 94%</title>
      <link>https://www.jonathancreamer.com/how-we-shrunk-our-git-repo-size-by-94-percent/</link>
      <description>We really did this! We work in a very large Javascript monorepo at Microsoft we colloquially call 1JS. Using some new changes to the git client it went from 178GB to 5GB.</description>
      <author> (Jonathan Creamer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jonathancreamer.com/how-we-shrunk-our-git-repo-size-by-94-percent/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 15:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boost Your .NET Projects: Unleashing the Power of Spargine’s IEnumerable Extension Methods</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/10/27/boost-your-net-projects-unleashing-the-power-of-spargines-ienumerable-extension-methods/</link>
      <description>Spargine is an open-source library of assemblies and NuGet packages for .NET 8, enhancing IEnumerable collections with various utility methods. It includes functionalities like adding distinct item…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/10/27/boost-your-net-projects-unleashing-the-power-of-spargines-ienumerable-extension-methods/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 09:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Round Robin DNS</title>
      <link>https://blog.hyperknot.com/p/understanding-round-robin-dns</link>
      <description>In which I try to understand how browsers and Cloudflare choose which server to use</description>
      <author> (Zsolt Ero)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.hyperknot.com/p/understanding-round-robin-dns</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 06:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerabilities of Realtek SD card reader driver, part 1</title>
      <link>https://zwclose.github.io/2024/10/14/rtsper1.html</link>
      <description>I discovered multiple vulnerabilities in RtsPer.sys, an SD card reader driver developed by Realtek. These vulnerabilities enable non-privileged users to leak the contents of kernel pool and kernel stack, write to arbitrary kernel memory, and, the most interesting, read and write physical memory from user mode via the DMA capability of the device. The vulnerabilities have remained undisclosed for years, affecting many OEMs, including Dell, Lenovo, and others. If your laptop is equipped with an SD card reader, it is highly likely to be manufactured by Realtek, making it susceptible to these vulnerabilities as well.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zwclose.github.io/2024/10/14/rtsper1.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodrigo Rosenfeld Rosas</title>
      <link>https://rosenfeld.page/articles/ruby-rails/2024_10_25_why_is_your_rails_app_boot_slow</link>
      <description>In my previous article we explored how we can build huge web app monoliths with Ruby
that can complete simple request tests in under a second. In this article we’ll focus on
Rails apps. We’ll identify what causes a big app to take a long time to boot and run
simple tests and what we can do to improve the situation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rosenfeld.page/articles/ruby-rails/2024_10_25_why_is_your_rails_app_boot_slow</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Ahead: Pathways to Comfortable Career Satisfaction for the Aspirational • Dylan Fitzgerald</title>
      <link>https://dylanfitzgerald.net/blog/comfortable-satisfaction-pathways-for-the-aspirational/</link>
      <description>Looking at software career options from an earlier place, many folks find themselves both aspiring for career growth and wanting not to be plugging in 60+-hour weeks by mid-career (and rightly so!). There’s a lot of hustle culture out there that promises to get you there right away; while a few folks out there get lucky, most of this is just concealing the outside-the-office time its purporters are plugging in. In hopes of making this wide range of possibilities a little easier to navigate (and with the wish that I could give myself this same resource some twenty years ago), here’s a breakdown of some common and reliable actual paths towards career satisfaction, particularly for those that are young and hungry:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dylanfitzgerald.net/blog/comfortable-satisfaction-pathways-for-the-aspirational/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password managers aren&amp;#39;t replacements for passkeys</title>
      <link>https://blog.millerti.me/2024/10/18/password-managers-arent-replacements-for-passkeys/</link>
      <description>There was some recent discourse about passkeys that bemoaned that they have so many issues that it’s better to stick with a password manager. The idea is that maintaining strong, unique passwords via a password manager is easier for users to understand.
This completely misses the key point about why passkeys are such a stronger way of protecting login, though, so I decided to spend some time to compare the two approaches.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.millerti.me/2024/10/18/password-managers-arent-replacements-for-passkeys/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I made my SwiftUI calendar app 3x faster - Alin Panaitiu</title>
      <link>https://notes.alinpanaitiu.com/How-I-made-my-SwiftUI-calendar-app-3x-faster</link>
      <description> ...</description>
      <author> (Alin Panaitiu)</author>
      <guid>https://notes.alinpanaitiu.com/How-I-made-my-SwiftUI-calendar-app-3x-faster</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to configure an Ethernet connection between iPad and RaspberryPi through USB-C</title>
      <link>https://www.andreagrandi.it/posts/howto-configure-ethernet-connection-ipad-raspberrypi-usbc/</link>
      <description>This tutorial explains how to configure an Ethernet connection between an iPad and a RaspberryPi using the USB-C port.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.andreagrandi.it/posts/howto-configure-ethernet-connection-ipad-raspberrypi-usbc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why authorization architecture is probably fragile</title>
      <link>https://ennabah.com/authz</link>
      <description>We initially built our own authorization system in PostgreSQL, but as requirements grew more complex, we had to evolve toward a relation-based authorization service. We chose SpiceDB to handle advanced use cases like organizational hierarchies and temporary access. However, while solving many technical challenges, it also opened up new security risks, particularly around ensuring consistent and reliable enforcement of authorization decisions across applications.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ennabah.com/authz</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surviving the complexity winter</title>
      <link>https://petterhol.me/2024/10/26/surviving-the-complexity-winter/</link>
      <description>Complexity science in 2024: claiming to be what it has never been, but gladly giving away its Nobel prize. This is a reflection about where the science of complex systems stands today, and where it…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://petterhol.me/2024/10/26/surviving-the-complexity-winter/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 03:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Windows Driver Signature bypass allows kernel rootkit installs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-driver-signature-bypass-allows-kernel-rootkit-installs/</link>
      <description>Attackers can downgrade Windows kernel components to bypass security features such as Driver Signature Enforcement and deploy rootkits on fully patched systems.</description>
      <author> (Bill Toulas)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-windows-driver-signature-bypass-allows-kernel-rootkit-installs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>