<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Armchair Architects: Architectural Erosion and Technical Debt</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-architecture-blog/armchair-architects-architectural-erosion-and-technical-debt/ba-p/3764281</link>
      <description>Welcome back to Armchair Architects as part of the Azure Enablement Show. Today we&amp;#39;re going to talk about this architecture erosion and we&amp;#39;re also going to talk about technical debt with our Armchair Architects, Uli Homann and Eric Charran. &amp;#160; What does architecture erosion mean? &amp;#160; The way Eric think...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/1161065)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-architecture-blog/armchair-architects-architectural-erosion-and-technical-debt/ba-p/3764281</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 06:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manipulating CSV Files in .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/manipulating-csv-files-dotnet</link>
      <description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll see how we can use CSV files in our developer routine and how to implement a .NET application that reads and creates CSV files.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/manipulating-csv-files-dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 06:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A simple guide to continuous deployment</title>
      <link>https://www.architect.io/blog/2023-03-09/a-simple-guide-to-continuous-deployment/</link>
      <description>Continuous deployment can speed up time-to-market and increase developer productivity. This simple guide should help you get started.</description>
      <author> (Zachary Jansma)</author>
      <guid>https://www.architect.io/blog/2023-03-09/a-simple-guide-to-continuous-deployment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 06:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uploading Large Blobs in Parallel with the Azure SDK</title>
      <link>https://markheath.net/post/uploading-blobs-in-parallel-sdk</link>
      <description>Mark Heath&amp;#39;s Development Blog</description>
      <author> (Copyright &amp;#169; 2023 Mark Heath)</author>
      <guid>https://markheath.net/post/uploading-blobs-in-parallel-sdk</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 06:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lean BDD with even more Code Generation</title>
      <link>http://www.plainionist.net/TickSpec-More-CodeGen/</link>
      <description>TickSpec is a lean BDD framework with powerful F# integration but the resulting tests are not nicely integrated in the TestExplorer of Visual Studio. This is were code generation comes to the rescue.</description>
      <author> (Plainionist)</author>
      <guid>http://www.plainionist.net/TickSpec-More-CodeGen/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 06:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Handle Enums in the Input to a .NET AWS Lambda Function | no dogma blog</title>
      <link>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2023/03/how-to-handle-enums-in-the-input-to-a-net-aws-lambda-function/</link>
      <description>If you invoke a Lambda function passing in value that deserializes to an enum and you are using the DefaultLambdaJsonSerializer it will fail. This post shows how to get around that problem in two ways.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2023/03/how-to-handle-enums-in-the-input-to-a-net-aws-lambda-function/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 06:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stubbles - Stubbing and Doubles innit. &amp;#129492;</title>
      <link>https://thoughtbot.com/blog/stubbles-stubbing-and-doubles-innit</link>
      <description>Confession: I&amp;amp;rsquo;ve always struggled to understand the difference between stubbing and doubles&amp;amp;hellip;</description>
      <author> (Sami Birnbaum)</author>
      <guid>https://thoughtbot.com/blog/stubbles-stubbing-and-doubles-innit</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 06:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Laser Pointer</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=3gZ_HZkSzl4</link>
      <description>How to make a laser pointer for less than $2. The only things I had to buy were some button cell batteries, and the laser diode. I got them both off eBay for...</description>
      <author> (How To Do
  
  
  
    How To Do
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=3gZ_HZkSzl4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 02:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Output Caching in ASP.NET Core - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/aspnet-core-output-caching/</link>
      <description>How to configure and use output caching in ASP.NET to improve the performance and scalability of applications.</description>
      <author> (Ryan Miranda)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/aspnet-core-output-caching/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 01:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three years all-remote at GitLab: Know the unknown unknowns (growth, life, and work)</title>
      <link>https://dnsmichi.at/2023/03/02/three-years-all-remote-at-gitlab-know-the-unknown-unknowns-growth-life-work/</link>
      <description>2023-03-02 marks my third year at GitLab. I have been very busy in 2022, did not stop much to reflect on great moments. This blog post is a summary, reflection, and shows my true vulnerable self. It may not be 100% applicable to your career aspirations or path to follow.</description>
      <author> (Michael Friedrich)</author>
      <guid>https://dnsmichi.at/2023/03/02/three-years-all-remote-at-gitlab-know-the-unknown-unknowns-growth-life-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lies, Damned Lies, and Subscriptions</title>
      <link>https://blog.giovanh.com/blog/2023/02/27/lies-damned-lies-and-subscriptions/</link>
      <description>“Sub-grift-ions”, a lesser writer might have titled this</description>
      <author> (Gio)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.giovanh.com/blog/2023/02/27/lies-damned-lies-and-subscriptions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search or fabrication?</title>
      <link>https://www.aiweirdness.com/search-or-fabrication/</link>
      <description>I recently started experimenting with Bing&amp;#39;s new ChatGPT-powered chat tab. This is the first thing I asked it for:

I&amp;#39;ve put red boxes around the factual errors. What is notable is that these are not just slight typos or errors in context - those items never appeared anywhere on my</description>
      <author> (By Janelle Shane)</author>
      <guid>https://www.aiweirdness.com/search-or-fabrication/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sapphire Rapids: Golden Cove Hits Servers</title>
      <link>https://chipsandcheese.com/2023/03/12/a-peek-at-sapphire-rapids/</link>
      <description>Last year, Intel’s Golden Cove brought the company back to competitive against AMD. Unfortunately for Intel, that only applied to the client space. AMD’s Rome and Milan CPUs have steadi…</description>
      <author> (clamchowder)</author>
      <guid>https://chipsandcheese.com/2023/03/12/a-peek-at-sapphire-rapids/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API Gateway: How to authenticate using LDAP?</title>
      <link>https://juzhiyuan.me/blog/how-to-authenticate-using-ldap</link>
      <description>LDAP provides secure access control based on user identity to prevent hacks and unauthorized access to systems. This post provides step-by-step instructions for setting up API7 Enterprise with LDAP authentication, including installing and configuring API7 Enterprise and OpenLDAP, and validating the setup. This blog also highlights common pitfalls to avoid when implementing an API Gateway with LDAP authentication.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://juzhiyuan.me/blog/how-to-authenticate-using-ldap</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Product Owner vs Project Managers</title>
      <link>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/owner-vs-manager/</link>
      <description>During my career as a software developer, I’ve met many different managers. Some were the kind of “I tell — you do”, others more open and “show me what’s</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/vadim.kravcenko.dev)</author>
      <guid>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/owner-vs-manager/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Process.WaitForExit() method has been unavailable for the last decade.</title>
      <link>https://dev.lukehjo.tech/wait-for-exit</link>
      <description>The Process.WaitForExit() method is a commonly used method in .NET.
It waits until a process has finished executing. However, in the last decade or so, this method has been reported to be unavailable and throwing the error &amp;quot;System.ComponentModel.Win3...</description>
      <author> (Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://dev.lukehjo.tech/wait-for-exit</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crashes from recursion in CPython</title>
      <link>https://hauntsaninja.github.io/cpython_recursion_crash.html</link>
      <description>March 5, 2023</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hauntsaninja.github.io/cpython_recursion_crash.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to read Hacker News threads with most recent comments first</title>
      <link>https://til.simonwillison.net/hacker-news/recent-comments</link>
      <description>[Hacker News](https://news.ycombinator.com/) displays comments in a tree. This can be frustrating if you want to keep track of a particular conversation, as you constantly have to seek through the tre</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://til.simonwillison.net/hacker-news/recent-comments</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How virtual environments work</title>
      <link>https://snarky.ca/how-virtual-environments-work/</link>
      <description>After needing to do a deep dive on the venv module (which I will explain later in this blog post as to why), I thought I would explain how virtual environments work to help demystify them.


Why do virtual environments exist?

Back in my the day, there was no concept</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://snarky.ca/how-virtual-environments-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A letter to a junior developer</title>
      <link>https://hadalin.me/essays/a-letter-to-a-junior-developer</link>
      <description>First, congratulations and welcome. You&amp;#39;re in for a fun ride. There are many opportunities to explore your potential waiting for you. Yes, there are terrible bosses in this domain too, but the demand for competent programmers is high enough for you to pick and choose.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hadalin.me/essays/a-letter-to-a-junior-developer</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic Positivity</title>
      <link>https://rohanrd.xyz/posts/toxic-positivity/</link>
      <description>Imagine our ancestors, who were primarily hunter-gatherers, when faced with predator like a Lion thought “This lion will not eat me”. Or consider example of the 2008 financial crisis, people thought “mortgage backed securities will never go down”. Then every now and then throughout the world their are banks that collapsed and eventually had to be bailed out by government. In each of these examples, people failed to consider a perspective.</description>
      <author> (Rohan D)</author>
      <guid>https://rohanrd.xyz/posts/toxic-positivity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using SQLite for logging and ad-hoc profiling</title>
      <link>https://ricardoanderegg.com/posts/sqlite-logging-profiling-programs/</link>
      <description>I was recently reading the documentation of nnethercote/counts, in there, Nicholas explains a few pain points when using a table as a profiling output. But using SQLite as the “table” can relieve some …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ricardoanderegg.com/posts/sqlite-logging-profiling-programs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercharge your Kafka Clusters with Consumer Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://www.groundcover.com/blog/kafka-consumer-best-practices</link>
      <description>Discover best practices for configuring one key Kafka component: Consumers. Learn where Consumers fit within the Kafka architecture, how to set up a Consumer, and which Consumer best practices can help to supercharge Kafka clusters.</description>
      <author> (Erez Levi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.groundcover.com/blog/kafka-consumer-best-practices</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Update Prank</title>
      <link>https://fakeupdate.net/mobile/</link>
      <description>iOS</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fakeupdate.net/mobile/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 20:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeOpinion</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/@codeopinion</link>
      <description>CodeOpinion is by Derek Comartin, a software developer with over two decades of professional software development experience.

He&amp;#39;s written software for a variety of business domains such as distribution, transportation, manufacturing, and accounting. 

Derek has a very active blog @ codeopinion.com, that focuses on Software Architecture &amp;amp; Design, Messaging, CQRS, Event Sourcing and HTTP APIs.
</description>
      <author> (•
    
  
  
    
    
    •
    
      131,454 views
    
      1 year ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/@codeopinion</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 19:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choose boring tools</title>
      <link>https://sizovs.net/boring/</link>
      <description>You only start to appreciate boring tools when you run your software in production.

It’s hard to choose tools nowadays because there are so many of them, and marketing departments work hard to sell you the magic by pushing the right buttons: “infinite scale”, “cloud-native”, “edge-ready”…

But marketing teams don’t run the software. Engineers do. In prod, all marketing slogans lose their spell because the real network, hardware, and software limitations eat marketing for breakfast. Not understanding fundamental tech limitations, algorithms, and capacity planning makes engineers fall prey to marketers selling magic. And magic isn’t fun when you’re in prod.

Once you have a basic understanding of ProductionOps, your life becomes much easier, because the list of tools worth considering shrinks by 1000x. You only consider tools that have been around for decades. Reliable tools that you know, understand, and trust.


  Need a DB? Postgres or MySQL.
  Need a KV store? Redis.
  Need a load balancer? Nginx.
  Instead of k8s, shell script to deploy and run your apps. 99% of software that runs k8s doesn’t need k8s. Don’t pay complexity tax until you need it.
  Instead of microservices, scale your majestic monolith vertically until IPO.


Sounds boring? Then it’s a good tech stack.


  A word on serverless: if you think that running “serverless” saves you from learning some capacity planning, load balancing, servers, connection pooling… Then wait until production. It will quickly reveal all your blind spots and get you back to learning fundamentals. No magic.


The beauty of good old boring tools:

  They’re well-documented and open-source. You can understand how they work and ask for help.
  You can run them locally or on your infra. Not through some ugly emulators. That simplifies development and testing.
  The time you invest in learning them is a fantastic investment. They’ve been around for decades and stay even longer.


Take-away?

  In production, boring tools make you smile, and fancy tools make you cry.
  Choosing tools becomes a simple task when you shrink the list to boring and battle-proven tools.
  The administrative “complexity” vendors are trying to hide from you introduces even more complexity and mental overhead. They sell you scary things and deliberately call good things (like fundamental computer science and capacity planning) scary.
  Don’t fall victim to marketing and FOMO. Learn the basics of capacity planning, shell scripting, and learn to operate boring software. Running servers with quality software isn’t as scary as someone wants you to think.

</description>
      <author> (Eduards Sizovs)</author>
      <guid>https://sizovs.net/boring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 19:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Claims SQL Server Performs Better on Azure Than AWS </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/03/benchmark-sql-server-azure-aws/</link>
      <description>In a recent benchmark, Microsoft claims that SQL Server on Azure Virtual Machines can be up to 57% faster and cost up to 54% less than running a similar workload on AWS EC2.</description>
      <author> (Renato Losio)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/03/benchmark-sql-server-azure-aws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Lambda Supports Powertools for .NET to Simplify Observability </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/03/aws-lambda-powertools-net/</link>
      <description>AWS recently announced that the open-source library Lambda Powertools now supports .NET. The developer library helps implement observability when running Lambda functions based on .NET 6 or above, reducing the amount of custom code.</description>
      <author> (Renato Losio)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/03/aws-lambda-powertools-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>