<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding how GitHub Copilot works</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/educator-developer-blog/understanding-how-github-copilot-works/ba-p/4021562</link>
      <description>Have you ever wondered how GitHub Copilot helps you write code faster and with less work? In this article, we will learn how it works and resources that can..</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/1379878)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/educator-developer-blog/understanding-how-github-copilot-works/ba-p/4021562</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling external API errors: A transactional approach</title>
      <link>https://thoughtbot.com/blog/handling-external-api-errors-a-transactional-approach</link>
      <description>Clarifying a few possible ways to implement transactional workflows when working with external APIs.</description>
      <author> (Thiago Ara&amp;#250;jo Silva

        
          January 23, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://thoughtbot.com/blog/handling-external-api-errors-a-transactional-approach</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murmurations - Smarter Every Day 234</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=4LWmRuB-uNU</link>
      <description>Check out https://kiwico.com/smarter and get your first month free!Click here if you&amp;#39;re interested in subscribing: http://bit.ly/Subscribe2SED⇊  Click below ...</description>
      <author> (SmarterEveryDay
  
  
  
    SmarterEveryDay
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=4LWmRuB-uNU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merge feature/dashboard-oop to main by drewnoakes &amp;#183; Pull Request #1774 &amp;#183; dotnet/aspire</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/1774</link>
      <description>Fixes #1003
Fixes #851
Fixes #1753
Fixes #1688
Fixes #1687
Fixes #1686
Fixes #1639
This PR merges the feature branch for OOP dashboard work into main.
It will remain in draft until it is ready to m...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/1774</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor Basics: Component Parameters and State Management</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/blazor-basics-component-parameters-state-management</link>
      <description>In Blazor, there are several ways parent and child components communicate with each other and pass data. Let’s take a look.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/blazor-basics-component-parameters-state-management</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 06:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding CQRS Architecture</title>
      <link>https://www.codeproject.com/Articles/5376316/Understanding-CQRS-Architecture</link>
      <description>Comprehending the CQRS architecture and learning how to implement it</description>
      <author> (Nicolas DESCARTES)</author>
      <guid>https://www.codeproject.com/Articles/5376316/Understanding-CQRS-Architecture</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Share user authentication state with interactive WASM components</title>
      <link>https://jonhilton.net/blazor-share-auth-state/</link>
      <description>Your server knows your user is authenticated, but what about your interactive WASM components?</description>
      <author> (Jon Hilton)</author>
      <guid>https://jonhilton.net/blazor-share-auth-state/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Static Web App– Application configuration using staticwebapp.config.json</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/01/azure-static-web-app-application.html</link>
      <description>As a follow-up on the presentation I did at CloudBrew  about Azure Static Web Apps I want to write a series of blog posts.      Part I - Usi...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/01/azure-static-web-app-application.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Faster and Better with GitHub Copilot&amp;#39;s New Features: Slash Commands and Context Variables - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/copilot-chat-slash-commands-and-context-variables/</link>
      <description>Have you ever wished you had an AI assistant that could help you write code faster and better? That’s what Visual Studio Copilot Chat offers you: an AI-powered pair programmer that can answer your questions, suggest code snippets, explain code logic, and chat with you about your project. You can use Copilot Chat to code faster and better, as it helps you avoid errors and learn new skills.</description>
      <author> (Peter Groenewegen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/copilot-chat-slash-commands-and-context-variables/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating our first 20,000 members</title>
      <link>https://blog.kagi.com/celebrating-20k</link>
      <description>Dear Kagi community, Today, we’re happy and proud to have reached *20,000 paying members* , including over 1,500 families all over the world, in our community.</description>
      <author> (Vladimir Prelovac)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.kagi.com/celebrating-20k</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 04:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Critter Stack Application:&amp;#160;Resiliency</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/01/24/building-a-critter-stack-application-resiliency/</link>
      <description>Hey, did you know that&amp;#160;JasperFx Software&amp;#160;is ready for&amp;#160;formal support plans&amp;#160;for&amp;#160;Marten&amp;#160;and&amp;#160;Wolverine? Not only are we trying to make the “Critter Stack” tools be viable long term options for your sh…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/01/24/building-a-critter-stack-application-resiliency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we made an animated movie in 8kB - Ctrl-Alt-Test</title>
      <link>https://www.ctrl-alt-test.fr/2024/how-we-made-an-animated-movie-in-8kb/</link>
      <description>The Sheep and the Flower - a demoscene production and real-time animation that looks like a standard short animated movie, in just 8kB</description>
      <author> (LLB)</author>
      <guid>https://www.ctrl-alt-test.fr/2024/how-we-made-an-animated-movie-in-8kb/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorway: Seamless high speed BFT</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2401.10369</link>
      <description>Today&amp;#39;s practical, high performance Byzantine Fault Tolerant (BFT) consensus protocols operate in the partial synchrony model. However, existing protocols are often inefficient when networks are indeed partially synchronous. They obtain either low latency during synchrony or robust recovery from periods of asynchrony. At one end, traditional, view-based BFT protocols optimize for latency in the sunny-network case, but when faced with periods of asynchrony are subject to performance degradations (hangovers) that can last beyond the return to synchrony. At the other end, modern DAG-based BFT protocols recover gracefully from asynchrony, but exhibit lackluster latency during synchronous intervals. To close the gap, this work presents Motorway, a novel high-throughput BFT protocol that offers both low latency and seamless recovery from periods of asynchrony. Motorway combines a highly parallel asynchronous data dissemination layer with a low-latency, partially synchronous consensus mechanism to construct an efficient consensus protocol for partial synchrony. Motorway (i) avoids the hangovers incurred by traditional BFT protocols and (ii) matches the throughput of state of the art DAG-BFT protocols while reducing latency by 2.1x, matching the latency of traditional BFT protocols.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 18 Jan 2024])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2401.10369</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burke Learns Blazor - API Wrap Up</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EvZ35LtVkd0</link>
      <description>As we get ready to go live, it&amp;#39;s time to finish off a few things in the API - delete lists, update lists, etc. Let&amp;#39;s go!Community Links: https://theurlist.co...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EvZ35LtVkd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 01:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Quietly Scrapped a Promise to Disclose Key Documents to the Public</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-scrapped-promise-disclose-key-documents/</link>
      <description>From its founding, OpenAI said its governing documents were available to the public. When WIRED requested copies after the company’s boardroom drama, it declined to provide them.</description>
      <author> (Paresh Dave)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-scrapped-promise-disclose-key-documents/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 23:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Funding Simulator</title>
      <link>https://www.fundingsimulator.com/</link>
      <description>Add investors, Safes and priced rounds, simulate how much dilution you will get, and know how much money you will make at exit.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.fundingsimulator.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 23:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Hacking My Air Purifier – Unethical Info</title>
      <link>https://unethical.info/2024/01/24/hacking-my-air-purifier/</link>
      <description>I searched the web for a deal on a decent air purifier and the Xiaomi 4 Pro seemed to meet all my requirements. The filter size, scheduler and air volume ticked all the boxes. I set it up and thought nothing of it until last week my room was lit with the ‘0% remaining’ replace filter warning. I had set my unit up to disable the LCD so this was an unwelcome surprise. I dismissed the warning by clicking the user button to dismiss the error and 15 minutes later it lit up my room again…</description>
      <author> (admin)</author>
      <guid>https://unethical.info/2024/01/24/hacking-my-air-purifier/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoother sailing: Studying audio imperfections in Steamboat Willie</title>
      <link>https://www.windytan.com/2024/01/smoother-sailing-steamboat-willie-flutter.html</link>
      <description>A deep dive into investigating and reducing the flutter distortion on the soundtrack of Steamboat Willie (1928).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.windytan.com/2024/01/smoother-sailing-steamboat-willie-flutter.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using abbr Element with title Attribute</title>
      <link>https://adrianroselli.com/2024/01/using-abbr-element-with-title-attribute.html</link>
      <description>How the &amp;lt;abbr&amp;gt; element is defined and exposed, along with the title attribute: &amp;#167; 4.5.9 The abbr element from WHATWG. ARIA in HTML entry on &amp;lt;abbr&amp;gt; notes it has no implicit role and naming is prohibited. Which is probably why Core Accessibility API Mappings 1.2 does not list it. HTML…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://adrianroselli.com/2024/01/using-abbr-element-with-title-attribute.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WTF Ubiquiti</title>
      <link>https://blog.imraniqbal.org/wtf-ubiquiti/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.imraniqbal.org/wtf-ubiquiti/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short tech writing style guide for developers</title>
      <link>https://lornajane.net/posts/2024/short-tech-writing-style-guide-for-developers</link>
      <description>Style guides are vital to successful publishing projects, but they are usually too extensive for casual contributors. After running a number of projects with developers rather than specialist documentarians as the main contributors, I&amp;#39;ve started using a short-form style guide, short enough to be rea</description>
      <author> (lornajane)</author>
      <guid>https://lornajane.net/posts/2024/short-tech-writing-style-guide-for-developers</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirPods Max died after 2 years</title>
      <link>https://pepicrft.me/blog/2024/01/24/airpods-max-broke</link>
      <description>Apple might have found a legal loophole to charge users for hardware issues caused by software updates.</description>
      <author> (Pedro Pi&amp;#241;era)</author>
      <guid>https://pepicrft.me/blog/2024/01/24/airpods-max-broke</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interesting readings - January 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.roundcrisis.com/2024/01/23/jan-2024-posts/</link>
      <description>This idea, of writing a weekly(ish) post with interesting reads started of after reading Please, Own Your RSS Links. This is a post which could be summed up as</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.roundcrisis.com/2024/01/23/jan-2024-posts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design a Technical Interview</title>
      <link>https://lknuth.dev/writings/design_technical_interview/</link>
      <description>Last year, the company I work for was looking to hire a Backend Engineer. We wanted somebody who was a senior or on their way to becoming one.
The Backend Squad was tasked with designing an interview to help decide who to hire based on technical merit. Above all, we wanted our interview to favor candidates that are good fits. Now, after working with our new hire for about 11 months, we know that we succeeded.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lknuth.dev/writings/design_technical_interview/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Containerization: Unveiling the Core Concepts and Technologies</title>
      <link>https://dhruvbindra.com/blogs/containers/</link>
      <description>Containers have emerged as a revolutionary way to deploy applications, offering a unique approach to running software in an isolated environment. This isolation ensures that your application operates independently, safeguarding both the applications running on the host machine and the host machine itself. A container provides a contained space to your application where it is shielded from the external interference of the host machine or other applications running on host machines.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dhruvbindra.com/blogs/containers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The desire for admiration drives human culture</title>
      <link>https://shunyaekam.com/essays/the-desire-for-admiration-drives-human-culture</link>
      <description>We internalize the people that we admire over our lives. They become our cultural programming.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shunyaekam.com/essays/the-desire-for-admiration-drives-human-culture</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D shape matching with quaternions</title>
      <link>https://lisyarus.github.io/blog/math/2023/12/26/3d-shape-matching-with-quaternions.html</link>
      <description>I write stuff about math, simulation, graphics, gamedev, and programming.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lisyarus.github.io/blog/math/2023/12/26/3d-shape-matching-with-quaternions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Processing Background Jobs on AWS:  Lambda vs ECS vs ECS Fargate </title>
      <link>https://mkdev.me/posts/processing-background-jobs-on-aws-lambda-vs-ecs-vs-ecs-fargate</link>
      <description>Discover how to leverage AWS Lambda and other serverless services for background jobs to boost efficiency and cut costs. This article dives into the nuances of processing background jobs in the cloud, comparing traditional methods with fully serverless solutions, and pros and cons of both ways.</description>
      <author> (AUTHOR:
    
      KIRILL SHIRINKIN)</author>
      <guid>https://mkdev.me/posts/processing-background-jobs-on-aws-lambda-vs-ecs-vs-ecs-fargate</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tremendous Yet Troubled State of Gaming in 2024 — MatthewBall.co</title>
      <link>https://www.matthewball.vc/all/gaming2024</link>
      <description>If you’re a player or casual observer, the video game industry seems to have it all. Yet growth is now illusory, layoffs abundant, and game/studio shutdowns common. Why? And how might things change?</description>
      <author> (Jan 23, 2024
            
            Written By Matthew Ball)</author>
      <guid>https://www.matthewball.vc/all/gaming2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treat Your Spouse As An Investor - SKMurphy, Inc.</title>
      <link>https://www.skmurphy.com/blog/2024/01/20/treat-your-spouse-as-an-investor/</link>
      <description>Here are ten rules of thumb for treating your spouse as an investor in your startup and some tips on conversations to have before you commit.</description>
      <author> (Sean Murphy)</author>
      <guid>https://www.skmurphy.com/blog/2024/01/20/treat-your-spouse-as-an-investor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Productivity Hacking the Ultimate Procrastination Tool?</title>
      <link>https://jilles.me/is-productivity-hacking-the-ultimate-procrastination-tool/</link>
      <description>Exploring the paradox of productivity hacks: Are they boosting efficiency or just procrastination in disguise? This post covers how the constant search for new tools can distract from actual work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jilles.me/is-productivity-hacking-the-ultimate-procrastination-tool/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xcode is too magic</title>
      <link>https://pepicrft.me/blog/2024/01/24/xcode-is-too-magic</link>
      <description>Xcode is a great tool for beginners, but it makes it hard for developers to understand what&amp;#39;s going on under the hood and optimize their workflows.</description>
      <author> (Pedro Pi&amp;#241;era)</author>
      <guid>https://pepicrft.me/blog/2024/01/24/xcode-is-too-magic</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023 letter | Dan Wang</title>
      <link>https://danwang.co/2023-letter/</link>
      <description>(This piece is my year in review; here’s my letter from 2022) I. Walking The trunk of an elephant might feel cool to the touch. Not what one expects, perhaps, from 200 pounds of writhing muscle, strong enough to uproot a tree, which tapers down to two “fingers,” giving it enough delicacy to detect the […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://danwang.co/2023-letter/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context switching SPRs on PowerPC — Store Halfword Byte-Reverse Indexed</title>
      <link>https://sthbrx.github.io/blog/2024/01/23/context-switching-sprs-on-powerpc/</link>
      <description>This post is a dive (well, more of a meander) through some of the PowerPC
specific aspects of context switching, especially on the Special Purpose
Register (SPR) handling. It was motivated by my recent work on adding kernel
support for a hardware feature that interfaces with software through an SPR.</description>
      <author> (OzLabs)</author>
      <guid>https://sthbrx.github.io/blog/2024/01/23/context-switching-sprs-on-powerpc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac at 40: The eras tour</title>
      <link>https://sixcolors.com/post/2024/01/mac-at-40-the-eras-tour/</link>
      <description>Happy birthday, Mac. I bought you a cake. Before I started writing my piece on the Mac’s 40th anniversary for The Verge, I was thinking of different ways to plot out the arc of the Mac’…</description>
      <author> (by Jason Snell &amp;amp; Dan Moren)</author>
      <guid>https://sixcolors.com/post/2024/01/mac-at-40-the-eras-tour/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is GIMP Forever Stuck In The Messy Middle?</title>
      <link>https://tedium.co/2024/01/22/gimp-image-editor-critique/</link>
      <description>I took a pretty rough swipe at GIMP last week, and rather than letting sleeping dogs lie, I’d like to explain my POV on the popular open-source image editor.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tedium.co/2024/01/22/gimp-image-editor-critique/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixing Cumulative Layout Shift Problems on DavidWalshBlog</title>
      <link>https://davidwalsh.name/fixing-cumulative-layout-shift-problems-on-davidwalshblog</link>
      <description>Over 50 thousand developers visit DavidWalshBlog every month from around the world to learn JavaScript tricks and fix problems in their code.</description>
      <author> (David Walsh)</author>
      <guid>https://davidwalsh.name/fixing-cumulative-layout-shift-problems-on-davidwalshblog</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Risks of Replatforming</title>
      <link>https://www.mironov.com/replatforming/</link>
      <description>(Or How Major Platform Migrations Really Happen)

Many companies have replatforming efforts underway. &amp;#160;Architectures get old, new
kinds of partners or integrations emerge, hard-to-maintain monolithic code gets
broken into microservices, acquisitions force integration of dissimilar systems,
etc. &amp;#160;This is an essential part of the software product business, but fraught
with</description>
      <author> (Richard Mironov)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mironov.com/replatforming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love Letter &amp;#183; Patrick Juchli</title>
      <link>https://patrickjuchli.com/en/posts/love-software/</link>
      <description>A Love Letter to Building Software</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://patrickjuchli.com/en/posts/love-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Love Tailwind CSS</title>
      <link>https://ben.page/tailwind</link>
      <description>I’m a really big fan of Tailwind CSS, a framework for styling websites.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ben.page/tailwind</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 22:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Asks Devs About Visual Studio Pet Peeves: &amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Get Me Started&amp;#39; -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2024/01/24/vs-pet-peeves.aspx</link>
      <description>While the complaints are numerous and vociferous, Microsoft&amp;#39;s Mads Kristensen took pains to reply to many, sometimes educating users on how to immediately solve their issues, sometimes pointing out where they can vote on relevant feature requests to solve the peeves, sometimes commiserating.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel01/24/2024)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2024/01/24/vs-pet-peeves.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 21:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>spontaneous studio, pilot</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=A7Zi5p1KtjU</link>
      <description>this is the pilot episode of spontaneous studio. in this series i&amp;#39;ll hit record and just play, and whatever happens, happens. half hour minimum commitment, n...</description>
      <author> (Knight EDM
  
  
  
    Knight EDM
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=A7Zi5p1KtjU</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 21:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor Hybrid - Running Blazor Apps Natively on iOS, Android, macOS and Windows</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_o_6oUQrc2g</link>
      <description>With Blazor Hybrid you can create a platform native application by leveraging your existing Blazor and web skills! Having trouble understanding all the diffe...</description>
      <author> (Gerald Versluis
  
  
  
    Gerald Versluis
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_o_6oUQrc2g</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 19:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the MSTest Runner - CLI, Visual Studio, &amp;amp; More - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-ms-test-runner/</link>
      <description>MSTest runner is a new, light-weight and portable runner for MSTest tests available in the .NET CLI, Visual Studio, and more!</description>
      <author> (Amaury Lev&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-ms-test-runner/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 19:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zed is now open source - Zed Blog</title>
      <link>https://zed.dev/blog/zed-is-now-open-source</link>
      <description>We hope you&amp;#39;ll join us in our mission to fundamentally advance software collaboration.</description>
      <author> (Nathan Sobo)</author>
      <guid>https://zed.dev/blog/zed-is-now-open-source</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 19:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try THIS To Stop Enum Changes From Breaking Your C# Code</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sC7Bn2-WgoA</link>
      <description>Continuing on our journey with Enums in C#, we turn our sights toward something different... Something slightly less conventional for supporting Enums in dot...</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader
  
  
  
    Dev Leader
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sC7Bn2-WgoA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Web Framework Should I Use For My C# Project?</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EKVoLkgbn7k</link>
      <description>What is the best choice for a web framework for my C# project? Should I stick with MVC and Angular? Should I just use an API and then use React for the front...</description>
      <author> (IAmTimCorey
  
  
  
    IAmTimCorey
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EKVoLkgbn7k</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube is not currently available on this device.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?list=PLReL099Y5nRdDJre4TGscXx3EzV74O04X&amp;index=2&amp;t=2s</link>
      <description>To learn more, please visit the YouTube Help Center: https://www.youtube.com/help</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Visual Studio)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?list=PLReL099Y5nRdDJre4TGscXx3EzV74O04X&amp;index=2&amp;t=2s</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corax, Lucene, Benchmarks and lies!</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/200609-B/corax-lucene-benchmarks-and-lies?Key=d14c28d7-6b81-4927-8498-70bf7147e5c9</link>
      <description>When we started working on Corax (10 years ago!), we had a pretty simple mission statement for that: &amp;amp;ldquo;Lucene, but 10 times faster for our use case&amp;amp;rdqu...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/200609-B/corax-lucene-benchmarks-and-lies?Key=d14c28d7-6b81-4927-8498-70bf7147e5c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:03:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The dangerous implementations of the IMemory&amp;#173;Buffer&amp;#173;Reference.Closed event - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240124-00/?p=109311</link>
      <description>Mistakenly handing out COM references that don&amp;#39;t work.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240124-00/?p=109311</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:03:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishing a Nuget Package the RIGHT way</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=jt1tA0IeH-A</link>
      <description>In this video I show how to gradually go from manually publishing a nuget package, to publishing the nuget package using github workflows triggered by tags. ...</description>
      <author> (Raw Coding
  
  
  
    Raw Coding
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=jt1tA0IeH-A</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spelling</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2885/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2885/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 13:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Topic&amp;#128293;&amp;#128640; : What is OAuth? and why do we need it?</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FLqLtTvghYY</link>
      <description>In this video we will discussed what is OAuth and why do we need it?Support me on Patreon to access the source code:https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawandBase...</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand
  
  
  
    Mohamad Lawand
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FLqLtTvghYY</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 11:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trello API abused to link email addresses to 15 million accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trello-api-abused-to-link-email-addresses-to-15-million-accounts/</link>
      <description>An exposed Trello API allows linking private email addresses with Trello accounts, enabling the creation of millions of data profiles containing both public and private information.</description>
      <author> (Lawrence Abrams)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trello-api-abused-to-link-email-addresses-to-15-million-accounts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Maximize the Browser Window With Selenium in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-selenium-maximize-browser/</link>
      <description>In this article we will learn how to maximize the browser window of all major web browsers using Selenium WebDriver in C#.</description>
      <author> (Semir Teskeredzic)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-selenium-maximize-browser/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting the record straight about Trello user profile data</title>
      <link>https://community.atlassian.com/t5/Trello-articles/Setting-the-record-straight-about-Trello-user-profile-data/ba-p/2587253</link>
      <description>Hey Trello Community, &amp;#160; We are aware of claims made by a threat actor about Trello user profile data. We completed an exhaustive investigation and did not find evidence to support that this data was gathered by unauthorized access. A threat actor, who was in possession of a pre-existing list of emai...</description>
      <author> (https://community.atlassian.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/4605513)</author>
      <guid>https://community.atlassian.com/t5/Trello-articles/Setting-the-record-straight-about-Trello-user-profile-data/ba-p/2587253</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Dev Proxy v0.14: OpenAPI Spec Generation, CRUD API Simulation and Many More </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2024/01/microsoft-dev-proxy-0-14/</link>
      <description>Last week Microsoft announced Dev Proxy v0.14.0 introducing several noteworthy features. Among the additions are the ability to combine rate limiting with mock responses, simplified OpenAPI spec generation, CRUD API simulation, improved macOS setup, easy access to Dev Proxy presets, enhanced mock structures, the introduction of JSON schemas, and various performance and stability improvements.</description>
      <author> (Almir Vuk)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2024/01/microsoft-dev-proxy-0-14/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>