<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>The Fastest NuGet Package Ever Published (Probably)</title>
      <link>https://rehansaeed.com/the-fastest-nuget-package-ever-published-probably/</link>
      <description>The fastest way to create a new NuGet package project and get it published with all the bells and whistles like continuous integration (CI) builds and drafted release notes.</description>
      <author> (Muhammad Rehan Saeed)</author>
      <guid>https://rehansaeed.com/the-fastest-nuget-package-ever-published-probably/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 09:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDC Melbourne Warmup Meetup #2</title>
      <link>https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ndc-melbourne-warmup-meetup-2-tickets-112730219120</link>
      <description>Join host Lars Klint and our speaker Troy Hunt and Scott Helme for a special preview of NDC Melbourne 2020!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/ndc-melbourne-warmup-meetup-2-tickets-112730219120</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 09:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martin Björkström - gRPC Server Reflection in the .NET world</title>
      <link>https://martinbjorkstrom.com/posts/2020-07-08-grpc-reflection-in-net</link>
      <description>Driving Digital Transformation on Serverless Containers...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martinbjorkstrom.com/posts/2020-07-08-grpc-reflection-in-net</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 08:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero to Hero with App Service, Part 3: Releasing to Production</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/zero-to-hero-with-app-service-part-3-releasing-to-production/ba-p/1506722</link>
      <description>This is the third article in the Zero to Hero with App Service series. This article assumes you have already completed the previous two articles.   At this point, you have a CI/CD pipeline built on GitHub Actions that deploys your code into a staging slot whenever a commit is pushed to the main bran...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/673052)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/zero-to-hero-with-app-service-part-3-releasing-to-production/ba-p/1506722</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is MaxDOP controlling?</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server/what-is-maxdop-controlling/ba-p/1505968</link>
      <description>The Max Degree of Parallelism, or MAXDOP, is one of the most known settings in the SQL Database Engine. There are guidelines of how to configure it that have intricate dependencies on the type of hardware resources you’re running on, and there are several occasions where someone might need to veer o...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/194232)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server/what-is-maxdop-controlling/ba-p/1505968</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Implement Azure Serverless with Blazor WebAssembly</title>
      <link>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-azure-serverless-with-blazor-web-assembly/</link>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will learn how to implement Azure serverless with Blazor web
assembly. And to do that, we will create an app that lists out some Frequently
Asked Questions (FAQ) on Covid-19. 

Here's what we will cover:

 * We will create an Azure Cosmos DB which will act as our primary database to
   store questions and answers. 
 * We will use an Azure function app to fetch data from cosmos DB. 
 * We will deploy the function app to Azure to expose it globally via an API
   en</description>
      <author> (Ankit Sharma
        Read more posts by this author.)</author>
      <guid>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-azure-serverless-with-blazor-web-assembly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TypeScript Types Deep Dive - The Talk | Barbarian Meets Coding</title>
      <link>https://www.barbarianmeetscoding.com/blog/2020/07/07/typescript-types-deep-dive-the-talk/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A%20BarbarianMeetsCoding%20(Barbarian%20Meets%20Coding)</link>
      <description>An epic journey of discovery into the mysterious world of TypeScript's type system. This time delivered as a 50 minutes talk at the Devsum 2020 conference by yours truly.</description>
      <author> (Jaime González García)</author>
      <guid>https://www.barbarianmeetscoding.com/blog/2020/07/07/typescript-types-deep-dive-the-talk/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A%20BarbarianMeetsCoding%20(Barbarian%20Meets%20Coding)</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters Weekly 172 -  NodaTime and API Controllers</title>
      <link>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/07/monsters-weekly/ep172/</link>
      <description>In a previous episode, we talked about using Noda Time Entity Framework Core and Razor Pages. In today’s episode, we look at using Noda Time with ASP.NET Core API Controllers and the configuration nee</description>
      <author> (The Monsters)</author>
      <guid>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/07/monsters-weekly/ep172/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When data is messy</title>
      <link>https://aiweirdness.com/post/622648824384602112/when-data-is-messy</link>
      <description>There’s a story I tell in my book because it’s a great illustration of how AI gets the wrong idea about what problem we’re asking it to solve: 

Researchers at the University of Tuebingen trained a neural net to recognize images, and then had it point out which parts of the images were the most important for its decision. When they asked it to highlight the most important pixels for the category “tench” (a kind of fish), this is what it highlighted: 
  
Human fingers against a green background!

Why was it looking for human fingers when it was supposed to be looking for a fish? It turns out that most of the tench pictures the neural net had seen were of people holding the fish as a trophy. It doesn’t have any context for what a tench actually is, so it assumes the fingers are part of the fish.

The image-generating neural net in ArtBreeder (called BigGAN) was also trained on the same dataset, called ImageNet, and when you ask it to generate tenches, this is what it does:
  
The humans are much more distinct than the fish, and I’m fascinated by the highly exaggerated human fingers.

There are other categories in ImageNet that have similar problems. Here’s “microphone”.
  
It’s figured out about dramatic stage lighting and human forms, but many of its images don’t contain anything that remotely resembles a microphone. In so many of its training pictures the microphone is a tiny part of the image, easy to overlook. There are similar problems with small instruments like “flute” and “oboe”.

In other cases, there might be evidence of pictures being mislabeled. In these generated images of “football helmet”, some of them are clearly of people NOT wearing helmets, and a few even look suspiciously like baseball helmets.
  
ImageNet is a really messy dataset. It has a category for agama, but none for giraffe. Rather than horse as a category, it has sorrel (a specific color of horse). “Bicycle built for two” is a category, but not skateboard.
  
A huge reason for ImageNet’s messiness is that it was automatically scraped from images on the internet.  The images were supposed to have been filtered by the crowdsourced workers who labeled them, but plenty of weirdness slipped through. And horribleness - many images and labels that definitely shouldn’t have appeared in a general-purpose research dataset, and images that looked like they had gotten there without the consent of the people pictured. After several years of widespread use by the AI community, the ImageNet team has reportedly been removing some of that content. Other problematic datasets - like those scraped from online images without permission, or from surveillance footage - have been removed recently. (Others, like Clearview AI’s, are still in use.)

This week Vinay Prabhu and Abeba Birhane pointed out major problems with another dataset, 80 Million Tiny Images, which scraped images and automatically assigned tags to them with the help of another neural net trained on internet text. The internet text, you may be shocked to hear, had some pretty offensive stuff in it.  MIT CSAIL removed that dataset permanently rather than manually filter all 80 million images.

This is not just a problem with bad data, but with a system where major research groups can release datasets with such huge issues with offensive language and lack of consent. As tech ethicist Shannon Vallor put it, ”For any institution that does machine learning today, ‘we didn’t know’ isn’t an excuse, it’s a confession”. Like the algorithm that upscaled Obama into a white man, ImageNet is the product of a machine learning community where there’s a huge lack of diversity. (Did you notice that most of the generated humans in this blog post are white? If you didn’t notice, that might be because so much of Western culture treats white as default). 

It takes a lot of work to create a better dataset - and to be more aware of which datasets should never be created. But it’s work worth doing.

Bonus material this week: a few of my favorite BigGAN image categories. Enter your email here for a gallery!

My book on AI is out, and, you can now get it any of these several ways!  Amazon - Barnes &amp; Noble - Indiebound - Tattered Cover - Powell’s﻿ - Boulder Bookstore</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aiweirdness.com/post/622648824384602112/when-data-is-messy</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shawn Wildermuth's Blog</title>
      <link>http://wildermuth.com/2020/07/07/NET-Foundation-Board-Candidate!</link>
      <description>.NET Foundation Board Candidate! - Shawn Wildermuth</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://wildermuth.com/2020/07/07/NET-Foundation-Board-Candidate!</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Training for Your Team on Redgate University: Learn DevOps and SQL Server for Free - Redgate Software</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/new-training-for-your-team-on-redgate-university-learn-devops-and-sql-server-for-free</link>
      <description>I'm excited to give you a run down of fresh new online training, open to all on Redgate University. We've got a great mix of courses on how to up your</description>
      <author> (Red Gate Software Ltd)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/new-training-for-your-team-on-redgate-university-learn-devops-and-sql-server-for-free</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Users with ASP.NET Core – ASP.NET Core Identity</title>
      <link>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2020/07/07/aspnetcoreroles/</link>
      <description>Authentication and authorization is a built-in feature of ASP.NET Core. Creating an application, you can select to authenticate with the Azure Active Directory or the Azure Active Directory B2C, or…</description>
      <author> (Published by
	Christian Nagel)</author>
      <guid>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2020/07/07/aspnetcoreroles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Core vulnerability lets attackers evade malware detection</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/net-core-vulnerability-lets-attackers-evade-malware-detection/</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the .NET Core library allows malicious programs to be launched while evading detection by security software.</description>
      <author> (Ax Sharma)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/net-core-vulnerability-lets-attackers-evade-malware-detection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Latest</title>
      <link>https://www.ams.org/news?news_id=6244</link>
      <description>Advancing research. Creating connections.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ams.org/news?news_id=6244</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 06:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solutions for EVERY GATE Theory of Computation Question! [Exam Question Monday] #gateconcept</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g_ZdcHSFGv0&amp;t=10s</link>
      <description>In which we solve EVERY exam problem offered from GATE theory exams until 2020. There are 247 questions in this list, and we tackle (most of) them, and try not to lose our minds! Thank you all for supporting this channel - hopefully this is a good Memorial Day's viewing.

#easytheory #nfa #dfa #gate #gateconcept #theoryofcomputing #turingmachine #nfatoregex #cfg #pda #undecidable #ricestheorem

Questions came from: https://pyq.ravindrababuravula.com/subject/?cs=Theory-of-Computation

00:00:00 GATE 2019
00:07:12 GATE 2020 
00:14:36 GATE 2018
00:22:29 GATE 2017 (Set 1)
00:33:37 GATE 2017 (Set 2)
00:40:55 GATE 2016 (Set 1)
00:49:18 GATE 2016 (Set 2)
00:54:51 GATE 2015 (Set 1)
01:03:12 GATE 2015 (Set 2)
01:08:30 GATE 2015 (Set 3)
01:11:30 GATE 2014 (Set 1)
01:12:35 GATE 2014 (Set 2)
01:19:19 GATE 2014 (Set 3)
01:24:52 GATE 2013 
01:28:16 GATE 2012
01:31:21 GATE 2011 
01:33:43 GATE 2010
01:38:43 GATE 2009
01:44:18 GATE 2008
01:59:17 GATE 2008 (IT)
02:08:25  GATE 2007
02:11:20 GATE 2007 (IT)
02:22:19 GATE 2006
02:28:33 GATE 2006 (IT)
02:38:00 GATE 2005
02:42:30 GATE 2005 (IT)
02:55:50 GATE 2004
02:57:58 GATE 2004 (IT)
03:02:57 GATE 2003
03:11:42 GATE 2002
03:42:39 GATE 2001
03:14:32 GATE 2000
03:17:39 GATE 1999
03:20:42 GATE 1998
03:27:31 GATE 1997
03:29:34 GATE 1996
03:35:00 GATE 1995
03:38:13 GATE 1994
03:39:40 GATE 1992
03:47:22 GATE 1991

Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/easytheory
Twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/easytheory
Mixer: https://mixer.com/easytheory
Discord: https://discord.gg/SD4U3hs
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/easytheory/
Twitter: https://twitter.com/EasyTheory
Teespring: https://teespring.com/pumping-lemma-for-regular-lang

If you like this content, please consider subscribing to my channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC3VY6RTXegnoSD_q446oBdg?sub_confirmation=1

▶SEND ME THEORY QUESTIONS◀
ryan.e.dougherty@icloud.com

▶ABOUT ME◀
I am a professor of Computer Science, and am passionate about CS theory. I have taught over 12 courses at Arizona State University, as well as Colgate University, including several sections of undergraduate theory.

▶ABOUT THIS CHANNEL◀
The theory of computation is perhaps the fundamental theory of computer science. It sets out to define, mathematically, what exactly computation is, what is feasible to solve using a computer, and also what is not possible to solve using a computer. The main objective is to define a computer mathematically, without the reliance on real-world computers, hardware or software, or the plethora of programming languages we have in use today. The notion of a Turing machine serves this purpose and defines what we believe is the crux of all computable functions.

This channel is also about weaker forms of computation, concentrating on two classes: regular languages and context-free languages. These two models help understand what we can do with restricted means of computation, and offer a rich theory using which you can hone your mathematical skills in reasoning with simple machines and the languages they define. 

However, they are not simply there as a weak form of computation--the most attractive aspect of them is that problems formulated on them are tractable, i.e. we can build efficient algorithms to reason with objects such as finite automata, context-free grammars and pushdown automata. For example, we can model a piece of hardware (a circuit) as a finite-state system and solve whether the circuit satisfies a property (like whether it performs addition of 16-bit registers correctly). We can model the syntax of a programming language using a grammar, and build algorithms that check if a string parses according to this grammar.

On the other hand, most problems that ask properties about Turing machines are undecidable. This Youtube channel will help you see and prove that several tasks involving Turing machines are unsolvable---i.e., no computer, no software, can solve it. For example, you will see that there is no software that can check whether a  C program will halt on a particular input. To prove something is possible is, of course, challenging. But to show something is impossible is rare in computer science, and very humbling.</description>
      <author> (Easy Theory)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g_ZdcHSFGv0&amp;t=10s</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 05:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xamarin/MobileBlazorBindings</title>
      <link>https://github.com/xamarin/MobileBlazorBindings</link>
      <description>Experimental Mobile Blazor Bindings - Build native mobile apps with Blazor - xamarin/MobileBlazorBindings</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/xamarin/MobileBlazorBindings</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 05:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Work by Gary Larson | TheFarSide.com</title>
      <link>https://www.thefarside.com/new-stuff</link>
      <description>Get an exclusive look at brand new cartoons and artwork from cartoonist Gary Larson, creator of the iconic comic strip The Far Side®.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.thefarside.com/new-stuff</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 04:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahmaud Arbery will not be erased</title>
      <link>https://www.atlantamagazine.com/great-reads/ahmaud-arbery-will-not-be-erased/</link>
      <description>But will his death finally force America to see the truth?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.atlantamagazine.com/great-reads/ahmaud-arbery-will-not-be-erased/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 03:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release ILSpy 6.0 · icsharpcode/ILSpy</title>
      <link>https://github.com/icsharpcode/ILSpy/releases/tag/v6.0</link>
      <description>Major Changes of Note

ILSpy 6.0 sports a multi-tab docking interface
ILSpy 6.0 comes with a new Metadata Explorer
ILSpy 6.0 has new icons for high-DPI support
ILSpy 6.0 requires at least .NET 4.7....</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/icsharpcode/ILSpy/releases/tag/v6.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 03:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It started to wrap around me': Driver fought off snake at 100km/h</title>
      <link>https://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/national/queensland/it-started-to-wrap-around-me-driver-fought-off-snake-at-100km-h-20200707-p559ts.html</link>
      <description>Footage of the June 15 ordeal shows a visibly shaken "Jimmy" trying to explain the situation to initially wary police before they find the eastern brown in his ute tray.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/mattdennien)</author>
      <guid>https://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/national/queensland/it-started-to-wrap-around-me-driver-fought-off-snake-at-100km-h-20200707-p559ts.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 02:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RickStrahl/Westwind.AspnetCore.LiveReload</title>
      <link>https://github.com/RickStrahl/Westwind.AspnetCore.LiveReload</link>
      <description>ASP.NET Core Live Reload Middleware that monitors file changes in your project and automatically reloads the browser's active page - RickStrahl/Westwind.AspnetCore.LiveReload</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/RickStrahl/Westwind.AspnetCore.LiveReload</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 02:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HDMI Capture Comparison - OneDrive</title>
      <link>https://onedrive.live.com/?cid=7230a11e3a3e316b&amp;id=7230A11E3A3E316B!2470806&amp;authkey=!AOBt2oT7LxDf-OM</link>
      <description>USB HDMI capture card, mp4 File, New, Modified 34m ago, Can view, 50.8 MB, PrivateUSB HDMI capture card.mp40:2334m ago</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://onedrive.live.com/?cid=7230a11e3a3e316b&amp;id=7230A11E3A3E316B!2470806&amp;authkey=!AOBt2oT7LxDf-OM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 02:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help message for shell scripts — samizdat</title>
      <link>https://samizdat.dev/help-message-for-shell-scripts/</link>
      <description>Samizdat blog by Egor Kovetskiy</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://samizdat.dev/help-message-for-shell-scripts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 01:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pulsar vs Kafka - Comparison and Myths Explored - Kai Waehner</title>
      <link>https://www.kai-waehner.de/blog/2020/06/09/apache-kafka-versus-apache-pulsar-event-streaming-comparison-features-myths-explored/</link>
      <description>Apache Kafka versus Apache Pulsar - which one to choose? Pros and cons, popular myths, and non-technical criteria explained to solve your business problem.</description>
      <author> (Kai Waehner)</author>
      <guid>https://www.kai-waehner.de/blog/2020/06/09/apache-kafka-versus-apache-pulsar-event-streaming-comparison-features-myths-explored/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of YouTube Trending Videos of 2019 (US)</title>
      <link>https://ammar-alyousfi.com/2020/youtube-trending-videos-analysis-2019-us</link>
      <description>The personal website of Ammar Alyousfi which contains a blog about data science, data analysis, data visualization, machine learning, Python, and more.</description>
      <author> (Ammar Alyousfi)</author>
      <guid>https://ammar-alyousfi.com/2020/youtube-trending-videos-analysis-2019-us</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area Twitter Sentiment During a Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://cameronmalloy.github.io/ba-sentiment.html</link>
      <description>What is the overall sentiment of the bay area? What is the distribution of this sentiment? What are people happy or sad about in a given...</description>
      <author> (/author/cameron-malloy.html)</author>
      <guid>https://cameronmalloy.github.io/ba-sentiment.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No pain, no gain: Tracktions' story</title>
      <link>https://crecotun.com/tracktions-story/</link>
      <description>I thought working on a side-project would be easy and profitable…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://crecotun.com/tracktions-story/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you living in a kettle?</title>
      <link>https://farez.me/are-you-living-in-a-kettle/</link>
      <description>Living in a city is like living inside a kettle. You don’t realise it but slowly over the years limescale accumulates on you.</description>
      <author> (Farez Rahman)</author>
      <guid>https://farez.me/are-you-living-in-a-kettle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most valuable developer linux notebooks in 2020</title>
      <link>https://cri.dev/posts/2020-06-20-Most-valuable-developer-linux-notebooks-in-2020/</link>
      <description>Recently I got into Linux again after a long hiatus  I fell in love with Pop!_OS by System76  Ubuntu 20 04 also looks gorgeous and made me want to go back to the Linux side  So I started looking for a worthy laptop for the job, with excellent support for Linux, and these are my findings</description>
      <author> (Christian Fei)</author>
      <guid>https://cri.dev/posts/2020-06-20-Most-valuable-developer-linux-notebooks-in-2020/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mmhmm - Clear, compelling communication for everyone</title>
      <link>https://www.mmhmm.app/</link>
      <description>A new way to communicate via video — both in real-time and asynchronously. Perfect for our new remote reality, add polish and creativity to every presentation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mmhmm.app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saadat Qadri</title>
      <link>https://saadatqadri.com/posts/how-to-be-present.html</link>
      <description>Saadat Qadri - Founder/Principal at Modern, a data science advisory</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://saadatqadri.com/posts/how-to-be-present.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Cheap VPS hosts for Tor Bridges</title>
      <link>https://worldofmatthew.com/post/webhosting-for-tor-bridge/</link>
      <description>EAs of the 5th July 2020, there are 1357 Tor bridges available for users in countries who censor the Tor network to use. Having just over 1,000 IP addresses is not a lot for such a big privacy network as Tor is, especially considering that the number of Tor Bridges peaked at 4,227 on the 4th January 2015. That means since then the network has lost more than two-thirds of its bridges.</description>
      <author> (About Matthew Christopher Morgan)</author>
      <guid>https://worldofmatthew.com/post/webhosting-for-tor-bridge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Team</title>
      <link>https://vas3k.com/blog/team/</link>
      <description>
                                                How to build awesome teams without bullshit
                                             </description>
      <author> (https://vas3k.com)</author>
      <guid>https://vas3k.com/blog/team/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disrupting Enterprise Search</title>
      <link>https://www.bargava.com/blog/disrupt-enterprise-search/</link>
      <description>We, human beings, are quite good at processing new information, but are terrible in storing them in long-term memory(LTM). LTM is finite and very limited. Many centuries ago, the printing press took a giant step in alleviating this problem. And then, distribution boomed. The number of printed content exploded.
Humans are a sucker for information. How do you find if the information you are searching for exist in that book?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bargava.com/blog/disrupt-enterprise-search/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core Series: Route To Code</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j-33Uz32hG0</link>
      <description>ASP.NET Core is a cross-platform, high-performance, open-source framework for building modern, cloud ready, connected applications

In this episode, Ryan Nowak shows us a feature in ASP.NET Core called route to code that allows us to quickly create HTTP endpoints with some of the additional work that comes along with controllers.

[00:57] - Where would you use route to rode?
[02:49] - Getting started Demo
[05:47] - Using the service provider 
[08:58] - Additional JSON methods for HTTP client 
[12:18] - Choosing to use route to code

Routing in ASP.NET Core
https://docs.microsoft.com/aspnet/core/fundamentals/routing?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli

ASP.NET Core documentation
https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/aspnet/core?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli

Create a Web API with ASP.NET Core 
https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/build-web-api-net-core?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli

#aspnetcore #dotnet #webdev</description>
      <author> (dotNET)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j-33Uz32hG0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 23:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buypass European Certificate Authority (CA)</title>
      <link>https://www.buypass.com/ssl</link>
      <description>SSL certificates - Norwegian Trustware from Buypass CA, Buy single cert, EV, Wildcard, UC, Multi,  Secure unlimited servers with up to 2048 bits encryption, Order now.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.buypass.com/ssl</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 23:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sheetui.com/</link>
      <description>Turn Your Google Spreadsheets Into A Beautiful, Responsive Web Page in 3 simple steps.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sheetui.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving from data science to machine learning engineering</title>
      <link>https://towardsdatascience.com/moving-from-data-science-to-machine-learning-engineering-68916173eaf3?gi=5a0f382dc00</link>
      <description>The world of machine learning — and software — is changing</description>
      <author> (https://towardsdatascience.com/@calebkaiser)</author>
      <guid>https://towardsdatascience.com/moving-from-data-science-to-machine-learning-engineering-68916173eaf3?gi=5a0f382dc00</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 22:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The adaptive interface system for modern web experiences</title>
      <link>https://www.fast.design/</link>
      <description>Interfaces built with FAST adapt to your design system and can be used with any modern UI Framework by leveraging industry standard Web Components.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.fast.design/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 20:41:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>microsoft/fast</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/fast</link>
      <description>The adaptive interface system  for modern web experiences. - microsoft/fast</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/fast</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 20:41:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sayedihashimi/myproposals</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sayedihashimi/myproposals/blob/master/css-media-query-updates-in-vs.pdf</link>
      <description>Contribute to sayedihashimi/myproposals development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (sayedihashimi)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sayedihashimi/myproposals/blob/master/css-media-query-updates-in-vs.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 20:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVP Perks</title>
      <link>https://store.west-wind.com/mvpperks.aspx</link>
      <description>We provide Microsoft Most Valuable Professionals, ASP.NET Insiders and Microsoft Employees 
            with complimentary licenses to Markdown Monster and West Wind Web Surge.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://store.west-wind.com/mvpperks.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 20:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPP Loan Data</title>
      <link>https://pppreport.org/</link>
      <description>A searchable database of federal 2020 Paycheck Protection Program loans.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pppreport.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 20:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concurrent Reference Counting and Resource Management in Wait-free Constant Time</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2002.07053</link>
      <description>A common problem when implementing concurrent programs is efficiently
protecting against unsafe races between processes reading and then using a
resource (e.g., memory blocks, file descriptors, or network connections) and
other processes that are concurrently overwriting and then destructing the same
resource. Such read-destruct races can be protected with locks, or with
lock-free solutions such as hazard-pointers or read-copy-update (RCU).
  In this paper we describe a method for protecting read-destruct races with
expected constant time overhead, $O(P^2)$ space and $O(P^2)$ delayed destructs,
and with just single word atomic memory operations (reads, writes, and CAS). It
is based on an interface with four primitives, an acquire-release pair to
protect accesses, and a retire-eject pair to delay the destruct until it is
safe. We refer to this as the acquire-retire interface. Using the
acquire-retire interface, we develop simple implementations for three common
use cases: (1) memory reclamation with applications to stacks and queues, (2)
reference counted objects, and (3) objects manage by ownership with moves,
copies, and destructs. The first two results significantly improve on previous
results, and the third application is original. Importantly, all operations
have expected constant time overhead.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 17 Feb 2020 (v1), last revised 29 Feb 2020 (this version, v2)])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2002.07053</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 19:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flatter wait-free hazard pointers - Paul Khuong: some Lisp</title>
      <link>https://pvk.ca/Blog/2020/07/07/flatter-wait-free-hazard-pointers/</link>
      <description>Paul Khuong's personal blog. Some Lisp, some optimisation, mathematical or computer.</description>
      <author> (Paul Khuong)</author>
      <guid>https://pvk.ca/Blog/2020/07/07/flatter-wait-free-hazard-pointers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 19:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - July 7, 2020 - FAST Framework</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sYTH_xYH3iA&amp;feature=youtu.be</link>
      <description>Join members from the ASP.NET teams for our community standup covering great community contributions for ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, and more.

Community links for this week: https://www.theurlist.com/aspnet-standup-2020-07-07</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sYTH_xYH3iA&amp;feature=youtu.be</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 18:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://walkingdre.am/</link>
      <description>Are you looking for a VR RPG game with lots of strategic depth?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://walkingdre.am/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 17:37:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>braver-browser/braver-browser</title>
      <link>https://github.com/braver-browser/braver-browser</link>
      <description>Next generation Brave browser for macOS, Windows, Linux, Android. - braver-browser/braver-browser</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/braver-browser/braver-browser</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 17:21:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solutions for EVERY GATE Theory of Computation Question! [Exam Question Monday] #gateconcept</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/g_ZdcHSFGv0</link>
      <description>In which we solve EVERY exam problem offered from GATE theory exams until 2020. There are 247 questions in this list, and we tackle (most of) them, and try not to lose our minds! Thank you all for supporting this channel - hopefully this is a good Memorial Day's viewing.

#easytheory #nfa #dfa #gate #gateconcept #theoryofcomputing #turingmachine #nfatoregex #cfg #pda #undecidable #ricestheorem

Questions came from: https://pyq.ravindrababuravula.com/subject/?cs=Theory-of-Computation

00:00:00 GATE 2019
00:07:12 GATE 2020 
00:14:36 GATE 2018
00:22:29 GATE 2017 (Set 1)
00:33:37 GATE 2017 (Set 2)
00:40:55 GATE 2016 (Set 1)
00:49:18 GATE 2016 (Set 2)
00:54:51 GATE 2015 (Set 1)
01:03:12 GATE 2015 (Set 2)
01:08:30 GATE 2015 (Set 3)
01:11:30 GATE 2014 (Set 1)
01:12:35 GATE 2014 (Set 2)
01:19:19 GATE 2014 (Set 3)
01:24:52 GATE 2013 
01:28:16 GATE 2012
01:31:21 GATE 2011 
01:33:43 GATE 2010
01:38:43 GATE 2009
01:44:18 GATE 2008
01:59:17 GATE 2008 (IT)
02:08:25  GATE 2007
02:11:20 GATE 2007 (IT)
02:22:19 GATE 2006
02:28:33 GATE 2006 (IT)
02:38:00 GATE 2005
02:42:30 GATE 2005 (IT)
02:55:50 GATE 2004
02:57:58 GATE 2004 (IT)
03:02:57 GATE 2003
03:11:42 GATE 2002
03:42:39 GATE 2001
03:14:32 GATE 2000
03:17:39 GATE 1999
03:20:42 GATE 1998
03:27:31 GATE 1997
03:29:34 GATE 1996
03:35:00 GATE 1995
03:38:13 GATE 1994
03:39:40 GATE 1992
03:47:22 GATE 1991

Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/easytheory
Twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/easytheory
Mixer: https://mixer.com/easytheory
Discord: https://discord.gg/SD4U3hs
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/easytheory/
Twitter: https://twitter.com/EasyTheory
Teespring: https://teespring.com/pumping-lemma-for-regular-lang

If you like this content, please consider subscribing to my channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC3VY6RTXegnoSD_q446oBdg?sub_confirmation=1

▶SEND ME THEORY QUESTIONS◀
ryan.e.dougherty@icloud.com

▶ABOUT ME◀
I am a professor of Computer Science, and am passionate about CS theory. I have taught over 12 courses at Arizona State University, as well as Colgate University, including several sections of undergraduate theory.

▶ABOUT THIS CHANNEL◀
The theory of computation is perhaps the fundamental theory of computer science. It sets out to define, mathematically, what exactly computation is, what is feasible to solve using a computer, and also what is not possible to solve using a computer. The main objective is to define a computer mathematically, without the reliance on real-world computers, hardware or software, or the plethora of programming languages we have in use today. The notion of a Turing machine serves this purpose and defines what we believe is the crux of all computable functions.

This channel is also about weaker forms of computation, concentrating on two classes: regular languages and context-free languages. These two models help understand what we can do with restricted means of computation, and offer a rich theory using which you can hone your mathematical skills in reasoning with simple machines and the languages they define. 

However, they are not simply there as a weak form of computation--the most attractive aspect of them is that problems formulated on them are tractable, i.e. we can build efficient algorithms to reason with objects such as finite automata, context-free grammars and pushdown automata. For example, we can model a piece of hardware (a circuit) as a finite-state system and solve whether the circuit satisfies a property (like whether it performs addition of 16-bit registers correctly). We can model the syntax of a programming language using a grammar, and build algorithms that check if a string parses according to this grammar.

On the other hand, most problems that ask properties about Turing machines are undecidable. This Youtube channel will help you see and prove that several tasks involving Turing machines are unsolvable---i.e., no computer, no software, can solve it. For example, you will see that there is no software that can check whether a  C program will halt on a particular input. To prove something is possible is, of course, challenging. But to show something is impossible is rare in computer science, and very humbling.</description>
      <author> (Easy Theory)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/g_ZdcHSFGv0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 17:06:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show &amp; tell: a steampunk desktop background radiation monitor</title>
      <link>https://www.balena.io/blog/show-tell-a-steampunk-desktop-background-radiation-monitor/</link>
      <description>Here's how to turn a Geiger counter into a desktop radiation monitor powered by a Raspberry Pi. Take a look at this steampunk-inspired project up close.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.balena.io/blog/show-tell-a-steampunk-desktop-background-radiation-monitor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 17:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Patterns after the GDPR: Scraping Consent Pop-ups and Demonstrating their Influence</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2001.02479</link>
      <description>New consent management platforms (CMPs) have been introduced to the web to
conform with the EU's General Data Protection Regulation, particularly its
requirements for consent when companies collect and process users' personal
data. This work analyses how the most prevalent CMP designs affect people's
consent choices. We scraped the designs of the five most popular CMPs on the
top 10,000 websites in the UK (n=680). We found that dark patterns and implied
consent are ubiquitous; only 11.8% meet the minimal requirements that we set
based on European law. Second, we conducted a field experiment with 40
participants to investigate how the eight most common designs affect consent
choices. We found that notification style (banner or barrier) has no effect;
removing the opt-out button from the first page increases consent by 22--23
percentage points; and providing more granular controls on the first page
decreases consent by 8--20 percentage points. This study provides an empirical
basis for the necessary regulatory action to enforce the GDPR, in particular
the possibility of focusing on the centralised, third-party CMP services as an
effective way to increase compliance.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 8 Jan 2020])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2001.02479</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 17:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding an endpoint graph to your ASP.NET Core application: Visualizing ASP.NET Core 3.0 endpoints using GraphvizOnline - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/adding-an-endpoint-graph-to-your-aspnetcore-application/</link>
      <description>In this post I show how the endpoint routes in an ASP.NET Core 3.0 application can be visualized as a directed graph, and explore the information it</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/adding-an-endpoint-graph-to-your-aspnetcore-application/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 17:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invite Rick</title>
      <link>https://inviterick.com/</link>
      <description>Drop your meeting invite link below and you'll be added to the queue. When it's your turn get ready to roll!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://inviterick.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 16:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign Statements</title>
      <link>https://dotnetfoundation.org/about/election/candidates</link>
      <description>This is your .NET Foundation!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetfoundation.org/about/election/candidates</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 16:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youtube DELETED Jordan Pier's Electronics Repair Channel!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W0mMOHrftgU</link>
      <description>Youtube have deleted Jordan Pier's (JPdylon) Youtube electronics repair channel.
This is getting ridiculous. Every creator need to be on alternative platforms like Library and Bitchute.
http://www.repairaudio.com/index-old.html
https://www.facebook.com/classicaudiorepairinc/

Subscribe to Dave on:
Library: https://lbry.tv/@eevblog:7
Bitchute: https://www.bitchute.com/eevblog/
Vimeo: https://vimeo.com/eevblog

Forum: https://www.eevblog.com/forum/blog/youtube-deleted-jordan-piers-electronics-repair-channel/

#Youtube #DeletedChannel

EEVblog Main Web Site: http://www.eevblog.com
The 2nd EEVblog Channel: http://www.youtube.com/EEVblog2

Support the EEVblog through Patreon!
http://www.patreon.com/eevblog

AliExpress Affiliate: http://s.click.aliexpress.com/e/c2LRpe8g
Buy anything through that link and Dave gets a commission at no cost to you.

Donate With Bitcoin &amp; Other Crypto Currencies!
https://www.eevblog.com/crypto-currency/

T-Shirts: http://teespring.com/stores/eevblog</description>
      <author> (EEVblog)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W0mMOHrftgU</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 16:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kicking off the 2020 .NET Foundation Director Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://dotnetfoundation.org/blog/2020/07/07/kicking-off-campaign-2020</link>
      <description>This is your .NET Foundation!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetfoundation.org/blog/2020/07/07/kicking-off-campaign-2020</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 16:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>yourduskquibbles/webannoyances</title>
      <link>https://github.com/yourduskquibbles/webannoyances</link>
      <description>Fix and remove annoying web elements such as sticky headers, floating boxes, floating videos, dickbars, social share bars and other distracting elements. - yourduskquibbles/webannoyances</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/yourduskquibbles/webannoyances</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 15:38:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#144 Bill Wagner, .Net 5 and Unifying .NET</title>
      <link>https://nodogmapodcast.bryanhogan.net/144-bill-wagner-net-5-and-unifying-net/</link>
      <description>Summary
Bill Wagner of Microsoft talks about the goal of one .NET.</description>
      <author> (by Bryan)</author>
      <guid>https://nodogmapodcast.bryanhogan.net/144-bill-wagner-net-5-and-unifying-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 14:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAMstack Crash Course - Build a Full Stack Application</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=73b1ZbmB96I</link>
      <description>Learn about the JAMstack, the new hotness in Web Development!! In this JAMstack crash course, you'll learn how to build a Full Stack application using some amazing technologies like FaunaDB, Netlify, and React. We'll use Netlify Serverless Functions for the backend and FaunaDB for the database.

Source Code - https://github.com/jamesqquick/JAMstack-Crash-Course-Build-a-Fullstack-App-with-React-Serverless-and-FaunaDB
Deployed Example - https://brave-neumann-362d90.netlify.app/

Netlify Functions Cheat Sheet - https://learn.jamesqquick.com/netlify-serverless-functions-cheat-sheet
React and Serverless Course - https://learn.jamesqquick.com/react-and-serverless-fullstack-web-development

_____________________________________________

Newsletter 🗞
Interested in exclusive content and discounts? 🤯 Sign up for the newsletter!
https://www.jamesqquick.com
_____________________________________________

Connect with me 😀
Live streams on Twitch - https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
Follow me on Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Join the 💬 Discord Server 💬 - https://discord.gg/vM2bagU
_____________________________________________

Courses  💻
Learn how to build Fullstack apps with React and Serverless Functions - https://www.jamesqquick.com/courses/react-and-serverless-fullstack-developmnent
Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code - https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/
Build a Quiz App  - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=73b1ZbmB96I</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 14:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Terrible, Horrible, No-Good, Very Bad Day at Slack</title>
      <link>https://slack.engineering/a-terrible-horrible-no-good-very-bad-day-at-slack-dfe05b485f82?gi=f9cab416681b</link>
      <description>On May 12, 2020, Slack had our first significant outage in a long time. This is a detailed look into the technical issues that caused it.</description>
      <author> (https://slack.engineering/@lnolan_54766)</author>
      <guid>https://slack.engineering/a-terrible-horrible-no-good-very-bad-day-at-slack-dfe05b485f82?gi=f9cab416681b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 14:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 9% of visitors give GDPR consent to be tracked</title>
      <link>https://markosaric.com/gdpr-consent/</link>
      <description>Privacy regulations such as the GDPR say that you need to seek permission from your website visitors before tracking them. Most GDPR consent banner implementations are deliberately engineered to be difficult to use and are full of dark patterns that are illegal according to the law. I wanted to find out how many visitors would […]</description>
      <author> (By Marko Saric)</author>
      <guid>https://markosaric.com/gdpr-consent/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 13:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Day I Met Ron Graham — Brady Haran</title>
      <link>https://www.bradyharanblog.com/blog/the-day-i-met-ron-graham</link>
      <description>RON GRAHAM 1935-2020    I know the exact date I met Ron Graham - it was the 16th of May, 2014.  That’s because it’s immortalised on my office wall, alongside his signature.</description>
      <author> (by Brady Haran)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bradyharanblog.com/blog/the-day-i-met-ron-graham</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 11:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>