<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>A Free Hyperlegible Typeface from the Braille Institute</title>
      <link>https://kottke.org/20/10/a-free-hyperlegible-typeface-from-the-braille-institute</link>
      <description>

Atkinson Hyperlegible is a free typeface developed by the Braille Institute and Applied Design Works that makes text more readab</description>
      <author> (posted by Jason Kottke &amp;#160; Oct 15, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://kottke.org/20/10/a-free-hyperlegible-typeface-from-the-braille-institute</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 09:07:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How hackers are finding creative ways to steal gift cards using artificial intelligence.</title>
      <link>https://deceptive.medium.com/how-hackers-are-finding-creative-ways-to-steal-gift-cards-using-artificial-intelligence-8a0544a54c6f</link>
      <description>Hackers are finding extraordinary ways to obtain gift cards for stores of high demand using artificial intelligence and phone providers.</description>
      <author> (https://deceptive.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://deceptive.medium.com/how-hackers-are-finding-creative-ways-to-steal-gift-cards-using-artificial-intelligence-8a0544a54c6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 09:07:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-02-05</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/02/app-developer-links-2021-02-05/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/02/app-developer-links-2021-02-05/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 09:06:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 229</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-229/</link>
      <description>This week&amp;#39;s update comes to you amongst the noisy backdrop of the garden being literally chopped up by high pressure hose (which I think my beautiful Rhode Broadcaster mic successfully excluded). As I say in the intro, it appears the horticulture industry is a little like the software one where</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-229/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 08:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helium Scraper - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/211/helium-scraper</link>
      <description>This is the third version of Helium Scraper, a web scraper that now uses CefSharp as a built in browser and can run many parallel off-screen browsers and uses a minimalist language, as well as ready-to-go wizards to configure extraction agents. It has a 10 day trial.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/211/helium-scraper</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 08:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to hire senior developers: Give them more autonomy</title>
      <link>https://hiringengineersbook.com/post/autonomy/</link>
      <description>Let me ask you a question: How much value do you think your source code has?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hiringengineersbook.com/post/autonomy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 08:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compiling DirectShow.Net for use in .NET 5</title>
      <link>https://weblogs.asp.net/rweigelt/compiling-directshow-net-for-use-in-net-5</link>
      <description>In a previous blog post, I wrote about how to access webcam properties from C# using DirectShow.Net. The last release of the library is version 2.1 from February 2010, with project files for Visual&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#8230;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://weblogs.asp.net/rweigelt/compiling-directshow-net-for-use-in-net-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 06:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here, I made a thing to save time building all projects in a solution</title>
      <link>https://www.mrlacey.com/2021/02/here-i-made-thing-to-save-time-building.html</link>
      <description>Compilers are complicated. They don&amp;#39;t always behave the way you&amp;#39;d expect. For instance, if you have a resource that has the Copy to Output D...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mrlacey.com/2021/02/here-i-made-thing-to-save-time-building.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 06:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the first six months of health care professionals replacing police officers, no one they encountered was arrested</title>
      <link>https://denverite.com/2021/02/02/in-the-first-six-months-of-health-care-professionals-replacing-police-officers-no-one-they-encountered-was-arrested/</link>
      <description>DPD Chief Pazen, who is fond of the STAR program, says it frees up officers to do their jobs: fight crime.</description>
      <author> (By  David Sachs)</author>
      <guid>https://denverite.com/2021/02/02/in-the-first-six-months-of-health-care-professionals-replacing-police-officers-no-one-they-encountered-was-arrested/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening an Admin Windows Terminal from Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2021/Feb/04/Opening-an-Admin-Windows-Terminal-from-Visual-Studio</link>
      <description>Opening Windows Terminal from another application is a bit of a pain. In particular I wanted to open Windows Terminal as an External Tool from Visual Studio and found it wasn&amp;#39;t as easy as referencing the `wt.exe` executable. Opening as an Administrator adds additional complexity. In this post I&amp;#39;ll talk about the use case of an External Tools and the settings to launch both a regular and admin Windows Terminal instance from External Tools.</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/rickstrahl)</author>
      <guid>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2021/Feb/04/Opening-an-Admin-Windows-Terminal-from-Visual-Studio</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConcurrentDictionaryExtensions.cs</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/davidfowl/3dac8f7b3d141ae87abf770d5781feed</link>
      <description>GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/davidfowl/3dac8f7b3d141ae87abf770d5781feed</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Critic - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/217/fantasy-critic</link>
      <description>Fantasy Critic is essentially fantasy football, for video games. A group of people form a league, and then create their own virtual video game “Publishers”. Each player then will assemble a roster of the games they believe will review the best. Similar to fantasy football, the players will alternat…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/217/fantasy-critic</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Profiling - Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/performance-profiling-introduction</link>
      <description>If you are not sure what to do once you start experiencing performance issues ...</description>
      <author> (Mark Downie)</author>
      <guid>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/performance-profiling-introduction</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rust-analyzer/rust-analyzer</title>
      <link>https://github.com/rust-analyzer/rust-analyzer/blob/master/docs/dev/architecture.md</link>
      <description>An experimental Rust compiler front-end for IDEs. Contribute to rust-analyzer/rust-analyzer development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (rust-analyzer)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/rust-analyzer/rust-analyzer/blob/master/docs/dev/architecture.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s Dunant subsea cable is now ready for service | Google Cloud Blog</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/infrastructure/googles-dunant-subsea-cable-is-now-ready-for-service</link>
      <description>The Dunant submarine cable system, crossing the Atlantic Ocean between Virginia Beach in the U.S. and Saint-Hilaire-de-Riez on the French Atlantic coast, has been deployed and tested and is now ready for service.</description>
      <author> (Chris Ciauri  President, EMEA, Google Cloud)</author>
      <guid>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/infrastructure/googles-dunant-subsea-cable-is-now-ready-for-service</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 03:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with SSL Certificate in Azure App Service</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/working-with-ssl-certificate-azure-app-service/</link>
      <description>This article shows you how to work with SSL certificates in Azure App Service. Last year I wrote a blog post on how to use Azure App Service managed certificates. If you’re using App service managed certificates, you don’t need to worry about the expiry, it will get renewed automatically by Azure. If you’re using custom domain names for Azure App service you will be able to configure SSL certificates to the custom domain name. To create custom TLS/SSL bindings for your App Service app, your App Service plan must be in the Basic, Standard, Premium, or Isolated tier.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/working-with-ssl-certificate-azure-app-service/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 03:05:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Templated Controls are Awesome | The Xamarin Show</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/Templated-Controls-are-Awesome--The-Xamarin-Show</link>
      <description>This week, James is joined again by Javier Su&amp;#225;rez, Developer on Xamarin.Forms, who explains what control templates are, why they are awesome, and how you can create amazing things with them. You don&amp;#39;t</description>
      <author> (by James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/Templated-Controls-are-Awesome--The-Xamarin-Show</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Suspender gets flagged for malware by Google Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.windowscentral.com/great-suspender-gets-pulled-chrome-web-store</link>
      <description>Users of The Great Suspender extension now see a message that flags it for containing malware. The popular extension was sold to new ownership last year and has been accused of adding malware in the past.</description>
      <author> (Sean Endicott)</author>
      <guid>https://www.windowscentral.com/great-suspender-gets-pulled-chrome-web-store</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxfam Australia investigating suspected data incident | Media Oxfam Australia</title>
      <link>https://media.oxfam.org.au/2021/02/oxfam-australia-investigating-suspected-data-incident/</link>
      <description>Late last week, Oxfam Australia was alerted to a suspected data incident. Oxfam immediately launched an investigation and engaged market leading experts to assist in identifying whether data may have</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://media.oxfam.org.au/2021/02/oxfam-australia-investigating-suspected-data-incident/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ideas That Created the Future</title>
      <link>https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/ideas-created-future?hss_channel=tw-20774514</link>
      <description>Classic papers by thinkers ranging from Aristotle and Leibniz to Norbert Wiener and Gordon Moore that chart the evolution of computer science.
                
                    Ideas That Created the Future collects forty-six classic papers in computer science that map the evolution of the field. It covers all aspects of computer science: theory and practice, architectures and algorithms, and logic and software systems, with an emphasis on the period of 1936–1980 but also including important earlier work. Offering papers by thinkers ranging from Aristotle and Leibniz to Alan Turing and Nobert Wiener, the book documents the discoveries and inventions that created today&amp;#39;s digital world. A brief essay by volume editor Harry Lewis, offering historical and intellectual context, accompanies each paper.Readers will learn that we owe to Aristotle the realization that fixed rules of logic can apply to different phenomena—that logic provides a general framework for reasoning—and that Leibniz recognized the merits of binary notation. They can read Ada Lovelace&amp;#39;s notes on L. F. Menabrea&amp;#39;s sketch of an analytical engine, George Boole&amp;#39;s attempt to capture the rules of reason in mathematical form, David Hilbert&amp;#39;s famous 1900 address, “Mathematical Problems,” and Alan Turing&amp;#39;s illumination of a metamathematical world. Later papers document the “Cambrian era” of 1950s computer design, Maurice Wilkes&amp;#39;s invention of microcode, Grace Hopper&amp;#39;s vision of a computer&amp;#39;s “education,” Ivan Sutherland&amp;#39;s invention of computer graphics at MIT, Whitfield Diffie and Martin Hellman&amp;#39;s pioneering work on encryption, and much more. Lewis&amp;#39;s guided tour of a burgeoning field is especially welcome at a time when computer education is increasingly specialized.</description>
      <author> (Edited by Harry R. Lewis)</author>
      <guid>https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/ideas-created-future?hss_channel=tw-20774514</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Knowledge Online</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Sharing-Knowledge-Online</link>
      <description>Want to share your knowledge and experiences with others online? David Giard, host of the Technology and Friends and GCast channels on YouTube, shows you how to get started.  Check out David&amp;#39;s videos </description>
      <author> (by Robert Green)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Sharing-Knowledge-Online</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity Framework Community Standup - Introducing MSBuild.Sdk.SqlProj</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lmHU1zD2mvA</link>
      <description>MSBuild.Sdk.SqlProj is a new open source project that allows you to build SQL Server Database Projects (.sqlproj) using the new SDK-style projects cross-plat...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lmHU1zD2mvA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safia Abdalla &amp;#183; The ReadME Project</title>
      <link>https://github.com/readme/safia-abdalla</link>
      <description>&amp;#128075; I’m Safia, also known online as [@captainsafia](https://github.com/captainsafia). I’m a full-time software engineer at Microsoft, a writer, and an [open source maintainer](https://github.blog/201...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/readme/safia-abdalla</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple and Succinct Zero Knowledge Proof</title>
      <link>https://decentralizedthoughts.github.io/2020-12-08-a-simple-and-succinct-zero-knowledge-proof/</link>
      <description>Many people have popularized the idea that succinct proofs and zero-knowledge proofs are a type of moon math. In this post, our goal is to present a simple proof system that can provide an introduction and intuition to this space. Perhaps surprisingly, the only tool we will use is the...</description>
      <author> (Decentralized Thinkers)</author>
      <guid>https://decentralizedthoughts.github.io/2020-12-08-a-simple-and-succinct-zero-knowledge-proof/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Finally Started Getting Programming</title>
      <link>https://savo.rocks/posts/i-finally-started-getting-programming/</link>
      <description>For a few last years I’ve been learning programming in various languages, on and off, with more or less success. Some languages that I’ve tried include Python, Java, Haskell and even JavaScript. And of course Clojure. But it has been going slowly, not because those languages (or programming in general) are hard. It’s because I lacked consistency in doing things on regular basis due to lack of time and energy; I’ve often been mentally exhausted at my regular IT work. Here’s how I finally managed to organize myself and actually started getting it!</description>
      <author> (Savo Djuric)</author>
      <guid>https://savo.rocks/posts/i-finally-started-getting-programming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The spectrum of synchronousness - The Engineering Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.theengineeringmanager.com/remote-working/the-spectrum-of-synchronousness/</link>
      <description>Communicating correctly is key for remote working. We look at sync and async communication on the spectrum of synchronousness.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.theengineeringmanager.com/remote-working/the-spectrum-of-synchronousness/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can networking be simple? with Tailscale&amp;#39;s Avery Pennarun | Hanselminutes with Scott Hanselman</title>
      <link>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/can-networking-be-simple-with-tailscales-avery-pennarun-ZmoBl_BN</link>
      <description>Double NAT? Triple NAT? Opening Ports, punching holes in firewalls, it&amp;#39;s all so complex, right? Does it have to be? Scott talks to Tailscale&amp;#39;s Avery Pennarun and asks &amp;quot;can networking be simple?&amp;quot; Avery and his team believes it can with a new take on networking. Personal mesh-style VPNs with tech like WireGuard over a faster, leaner, cleaner, and simpler way to share your network with your team.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/can-networking-be-simple-with-tailscales-avery-pennarun-ZmoBl_BN</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inline caching: quickening</title>
      <link>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/inline-caching-quickening/</link>
      <description>Further optimizing bytecode interpreters by removing branches and indirection</description>
      <author> (Max Bernstein)</author>
      <guid>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/inline-caching-quickening/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequencing DNA in our Extra Bedroom &amp;#171; Andrew J. Barry</title>
      <link>https://abarry.org/dna-sequencing-in-our-extra-bedroom/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://abarry.org/dna-sequencing-in-our-extra-bedroom/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh sorry, I was on mute!</title>
      <link>https://neil.computer/notes/oh-sorry-i-was-on-mute/</link>
      <description>I ranted on HN the other day about Google Meet&amp;#39;s user interface gore. Aside: Imagine you’re driving down the road and you need to make a right turn. Well, for some reason the steering wheel is stowed away and disappeared! You need to hover your hand around the center</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://neil.computer/notes/oh-sorry-i-was-on-mute/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with large .NET 5 solutions in Visual Studio 2019 16.8 | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/working-with-large-net-5-solutions-in-visual-studio-2019-16-8/</link>
      <description>With the release of .NET 5, migration of solutions from .NET Framework has increased. In particular, we have started to see very large solutions being moved. To ensure this experience is as good as possible, we have been working on optimizing Visual Studio to handle solutions that contain large numbers of .NET 5 and .NET Core projects.</description>
      <author> (Paul Vick Principal Software Engineer, Visual Studio Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/working-with-large-net-5-solutions-in-visual-studio-2019-16-8/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working inside a Docker container using Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://asp.net-hacker.rocks/2021/02/04/remote-docker.html</link>
      <description>Have you ever tried to develop inside the Docker container? I had to try it out and was impressed about how easy it is using Visual Studio Code. This tutorial shows you how to connect to a Docker container and how develop inside the Docker container.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/juergen.gutsch)</author>
      <guid>https://asp.net-hacker.rocks/2021/02/04/remote-docker.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art of Starting Things (or How to Start Doing Things That You&amp;#39;ve Been Delaying Forever) – Unstructed.tech</title>
      <link>https://unstructed.tech/2021/02/04/art-of-starting-things/</link>
      <description>Starting anything new is HARD. Doubly so if you&amp;#39;re a professional procrastinator like I am. Best way to beat procrastination is to understand it and then attack it with the battle tested tools of trade that we have. This is what this article is all about.</description>
      <author> (By Mihailo Joksimovic)</author>
      <guid>https://unstructed.tech/2021/02/04/art-of-starting-things/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enforcing work-life balance with bash scripting, or targeted ways to kill Linux programs – prem.moe</title>
      <link>https://prem.moe/2021/02/04/Enforcing-work-life-balance-with-bash/</link>
      <description>In the days of the pandemic (let it be damned) we more often than ever work from home
and, somewhat naturally, use one device both for work and out of it — for relax, hobbies, whatever.</description>
      <author> (Przemysław Buczkowski)</author>
      <guid>https://prem.moe/2021/02/04/Enforcing-work-life-balance-with-bash/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Problem with Young Internet Entrepreneurs - Clayton Horning</title>
      <link>https://claytonhorning.com/entrepreneurship/the-problem-with-young-internet-entrepreneurs/</link>
      <description>The internet has created a problem with young internet entrepreneurs - others feel down or jealous about others seemingly instant success.</description>
      <author> (By Clayton)</author>
      <guid>https://claytonhorning.com/entrepreneurship/the-problem-with-young-internet-entrepreneurs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:05:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locating Humans with DNS</title>
      <link>https://landshark.io/2021/02/04/dns-for-humans.html</link>
      <description>I recently lost access to a free email account I’ve had since before I can remember (though only temporarily, thank the lord). When it happened, I instantly became effectively uncontactable by a large portion of humanity. My own temporary disappearance from reality started me to thinking about how we can reuse existing infrastructure to store contact information in a durable and highly available way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://landshark.io/2021/02/04/dns-for-humans.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:05:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A short post on Nibby, URL shorteners and the dangers of machine translation</title>
      <link>https://thecrow.uk/on-link-shorteners-and%20the-dangers-of-google-translate/</link>
      <description>Twenty years ago, URL shorteners were a godsend. A complicated, hierarchical, 300 character address could be compressed down to a dozen characters - or fewer. So this is my new effort. nib.by. Nibby. Likened to the nib of a pen. Nibby. It kind of rolls of the tongue, and despite containing more letters than I originally sought, I’m pretty happy.</description>
      <author> (The Crow)</author>
      <guid>https://thecrow.uk/on-link-shorteners-and%20the-dangers-of-google-translate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Software, the Best Software</title>
      <link>https://craigmod.com/essays/fast_software/</link>
      <description>Essay on the benefits of speedy software, and how it affects user perception of engineering quality and overall usability</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://craigmod.com/essays/fast_software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:05:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Lose Money With 25 Years of Failed Businesses</title>
      <link>https://joeldare.com/how-to-lose-money-with-25-years-of-failed-businesses</link>
      <description>1. Close your business while it’s working</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joeldare.com/how-to-lose-money-with-25-years-of-failed-businesses</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 23:05:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>progrium/macdriver</title>
      <link>https://github.com/progrium/macdriver</link>
      <description>Native Mac APIs for Go. Contribute to progrium/macdriver development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (progrium)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/progrium/macdriver</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 22:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUKE - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/221/nuke</link>
      <description>Founded in April 2017, NUKE is a free, open-source build automation system for C#/.NET that runs cross-platform on .NET Core, .NET Framework, and Mono. While builds are bootstrapped with conventional Bash or PowerShell scripts, their actual implementation resides in simple C# console applications. …</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/221/nuke</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 22:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waiting for PostgreSQL 14 – SEARCH and CYCLE clauses – select * from depesz;</title>
      <link>https://www.depesz.com/2021/02/04/waiting-for-postgresql-14-search-and-cycle-clauses/</link>
      <description>Just as message suggests this change is related to recursive queries.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.depesz.com/2021/02/04/waiting-for-postgresql-14-search-and-cycle-clauses/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 22:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 363 - Streaming telemetry for NVAs</title>
      <link>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-363-Streaming-telemetry-for-NVAs</link>
      <description>The Azure Podcast</description>
      <author> (Sujit D&amp;#39;Mello)</author>
      <guid>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-363-Streaming-telemetry-for-NVAs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Discoverable HTTP APIs with ASP.NET Core 5 Web API | ASP.NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/creating-discoverable-http-apis-with-asp-net-core-5-web-api/</link>
      <description>Learn how to fine tune your HTTP APIs to make them more discoverable, consumable, and just plain enjoyable to use - with just a few lines of code.</description>
      <author> (Brady Gaster)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/creating-discoverable-http-apis-with-asp-net-core-5-web-api/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Architecture Design Walkthrough - Global Lifts Scenario - CodeWithStu</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xd_TElOedew</link>
      <description>Ever wondered how to answer the architecture design questions in interviews? If so, this video is for you. I take a sample of what I often receive as an arch...</description>
      <author> (freeCodeCamp.org
  
  
    

    
      
    freeCodeCamp.org
  
    



  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xd_TElOedew</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuring and extending a service</title>
      <link>https://blog.lhotka.net/2021/02/03/Configuring-and-extending-a-service</link>
      <description>CSLA has been around for over 23 years now, with the first CSLA .NET version released concurrently with .NET Framework 1.0. Over the years it has changed to take advantage of, or allow developers to take advantage of, new and exciting features of .NET, such as generics, async/await, dependency injection, and more.</description>
      <author> (Rockford Lhotka)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.lhotka.net/2021/02/03/Configuring-and-extending-a-service</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JltNo-NKTlQ</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io/</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
    

    
      
    .NET Foundation
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JltNo-NKTlQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling an API in Power Apps Portals using JavaScript | Developer Support</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/calling-an-api-in-power-apps-portals-using-javascript/</link>
      <description>Bryan Soltis demonstrates how to call an API in Power Apps Portals using JavaScript. As a developer, Power Apps are a very interesting, yet nostalgic, concept. The platform reminds me of a lot of “game changing and exciting” systems of the past that allowed users to create complex,</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/MicrosoftDeveloperSupport/)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/calling-an-api-in-power-apps-portals-using-javascript/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Security Bootcamp: Get CompTIA Certified and Land Your First Role</title>
      <link>https://www.springboard.com/courses/cyber-security-career-track/</link>
      <description>Springboard&amp;#39;s Cyber Security Bootcamp will train students on cybersecurity analysis skills, including the core mindset, tools, best practices, and more. Start now!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.springboard.com/courses/cyber-security-career-track/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chefs and Cooks</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2021/02/04/chefs-and-cooks/</link>
      <description>I’m pretty good at cooking, if I do say so myself. That may be because I only cook a handful of dishes, or that may be because I’m extra attentive to the ingredients, the taste, and am …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2021/02/04/chefs-and-cooks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s the Most Popular Component in the .NET/C# Tech Stack? -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/04/devskiller-2021.aspx</link>
      <description>A new development skills report from DevSkiller reveals the most popular components in the .NET/C# tech stack. Think web.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel02/04/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/04/devskiller-2021.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://cqi.inf.usi.ch/publications/telegram_vs_signal.pdf</title>
      <link>https://cqi.inf.usi.ch/publications/telegram_vs_signal.pdf</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cqi.inf.usi.ch/publications/telegram_vs_signal.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing App Cloud Readiness for Failover Resiliency with SQL Managed Instance</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Data-Exposed/Testing-Cloud-Readiness-Applications-with-Failover-Resiliency-for-SQL-Managed-Instance</link>
      <description>In this episode with Dani Ljepava, we will show you how to manually trigger a planned failover on SQL Managed Instance to test your applications for fault tolerance and will talk about best practices </description>
      <author> (by Marisa Brasile)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Data-Exposed/Testing-Cloud-Readiness-Applications-with-Failover-Resiliency-for-SQL-Managed-Instance</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:05:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help users in Iran reconnect to Signal</title>
      <link>https://signal.org/blog/help-iran-reconnect/</link>
      <description>Just over a week ago, we announced that Iranian censors had started blocking all Signal traffic in the country. As an interim solution to help people in Iran get connected again, we’ve added support in Signal for a simple TLS proxy that is easy to set up, can be used to bypass the network block, ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://signal.org/blog/help-iran-reconnect/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:05:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the SAN field</title>
      <link>https://www.ietf.org/archive/id/draft-rsalz-use-san-00.html</link>
      <description>In the decade since   was published, the subjectAltName
extension, as defined in   has become ubiquitous.  This document
updates   to specify that the fall-back techniques of
using commonName attribute to identify the service MUST NOT be used.</description>
      <author> (Rich Salz)</author>
      <guid>https://www.ietf.org/archive/id/draft-rsalz-use-san-00.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding approval workflow to your GitHub Action</title>
      <link>https://www.timheuer.com/blog/add-approval-workflow-to-github-actions/</link>
      <description>Want to add an approval workflow to your GitHub Action deployment easily?  With new capabilities now you can!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.timheuer.com/blog/add-approval-workflow-to-github-actions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks! vNext</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1725</link>
      <description>.NET Rocks! is a weekly talk show for anyone interested in programming on the Microsoft .NET platform. The shows range from introductory information to hardcore geekiness.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1725</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asynchronous Messaging, Part 5: Miscellaneous Considerations</title>
      <link>https://blog.stephencleary.com/2021/02/asynchronous-messaging-5-miscellaneous-considerations.html</link>
      <description>Final remarks on considerations for using asynchronous messaging with request-exogenous code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.stephencleary.com/2021/02/asynchronous-messaging-5-miscellaneous-considerations.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t use functions as callbacks unless they&amp;#39;re designed for it</title>
      <link>https://jakearchibald.com/2021/function-callback-risks/</link>
      <description>…same goes for option objects.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jakearchibald.com/2021/function-callback-risks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 18:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Viva: Empowering every employee for the new digital age - Microsoft 365 Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/blog/2021/02/04/microsoft-viva-empowering-every-employee-for-the-new-digital-age/</link>
      <description>Even before COVID-19 turned our lives upside down, a new generation of digital tools was opening up new possibilities for the future of work. What we didn’t expect was that this future would arrive almost overnight last March, as millions of businesses around the world responded to the pandemic by moving to remote and hybrid…</description>
      <author> (By Jared Spataro, Corporate Vice President for Microsoft 365)</author>
      <guid>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/blog/2021/02/04/microsoft-viva-empowering-every-employee-for-the-new-digital-age/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 17:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lottie animations for WPF - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/223/lottie-animations-for-wpf</link>
      <description>Inspired by Lottie for Android, iOS, React Native, and Web,
this library allows a WPF application to load and run Adobe After Effects animations exported as json with Bodymovin.
There are many free animations at https://www.lottiefiles.com/</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/223/lottie-animations-for-wpf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 17:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Distributed applications with ZeroMQ</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jIT8r2r5kV8</link>
      <description>ZeroMQ is a high-performance asynchronous messaging library, aimed at use in distributed or concurrent applications. NetMQ is a 100% native C# port of the li...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jIT8r2r5kV8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 16:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Usage patterns for winrt::unbox_value_or | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210204-00/?p=104795</link>
      <description>C++/WinRT’s unbox_value_or template function takes an IInspectable (which represents an arbitrary object) and tries to unbox it to a specified target type. If unable, it returns a provided default value. The most explicit way of using it is to specialize the type,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210204-00/?p=104795</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 15:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Product Intelligence Platform with Cloudflare Workers</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-product-intelligence-platform-with-cloudflare-workers/</link>
      <description>This blogpost talks about the technical challenges of building an analytics platform with Cloudflare Workers that helps us to A/B test the experiences we build in Cloudflare’s dashboard every day.</description>
      <author> (Robert Cepa)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-product-intelligence-platform-with-cloudflare-workers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 15:05:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 5 and .NET 6 with Scott Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/nopCommerce-Global-Meetup/events/275569812/?hss_channel=tw-2384354214</link>
      <description>Tue, Feb 16, 2021, 10:00 AM: Check your time zone.https://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/fixedtime.html?msg=nopCommerce+Global+Meetup+-+February&amp;amp;iso=20210216T10&amp;amp;p1=605&amp;amp;ah=2You may want to join and ins</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/nopCommerce-Global-Meetup/events/275569812/?hss_channel=tw-2384354214</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 15:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a social media platform without going bankrupt: Part IX–Dealing with the past</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/193061-A/building-a-social-media-platform-without-going-bankrupt-part-ix-dealing-with-the-past?Key=1e50fc85-8fba-42d7-9db8-3236e5f396fc</link>
      <description>A social media platform has to deal with the concept of now and its history. For the most part, most users are interacting with the current state of the syst...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/193061-A/building-a-social-media-platform-without-going-bankrupt-part-ix-dealing-with-the-past?Key=1e50fc85-8fba-42d7-9db8-3236e5f396fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 15:05:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HuffPost is now a part of Verizon Media</title>
      <link>https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/grant-shapps-uk-border-australia_uk_601a78c0c5b668b8db3d3a74</link>
      <description>HuffPost  is part of Verizon Media. We and our partners will store and/or access information on your device through the use of cookies and similar technologies, to display personalised ads and content, for ad and content measurement, audience insights and product development.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/grant-shapps-uk-border-australia_uk_601a78c0c5b668b8db3d3a74</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 14:06:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Event: Matt Parker - Events</title>
      <link>https://www.harvard.com/event/virtual_event_matt_parker/</link>
      <description>presenting</description>
      <author> (by Matt Parker)</author>
      <guid>https://www.harvard.com/event/virtual_event_matt_parker/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 12:05:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudpress - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/226/cloudpress</link>
      <description>Cloudpress allows you to write and collaborate in Google Docs and then publish your content to various Content Management Systems such as WordPress, Contentful and others.

No more hassles with incorrectly formatted content or wasting time uploading images separately. Cloudpress preserves text fo…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/226/cloudpress</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 12:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humble Pi: When Math Goes Wrong in the Real World - Harvard Book Store</title>
      <link>https://www.harvard.com/book/9780593084694_humble_pi/</link>
      <description>Type New
                                            Format Paperback
                                            ISBN 9780593084694</description>
      <author> (by Matt Parker)</author>
      <guid>https://www.harvard.com/book/9780593084694_humble_pi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 12:05:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET GC Internals - 04. Plan phase</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n4WHEW4tKUI</link>
      <description>The fourth episode of the .NET GC Internals series explaining a real in-depth knowledge how .NET GC works. This episode is about the Plan phase, which is the...</description>
      <author> (Dotnetos
  
  
    

    
      
    Dotnetos
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n4WHEW4tKUI</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 10:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ianhan/BitmapFonts</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ianhan/BitmapFonts</link>
      <description>My collection of bitmap fonts pulled from various demoscene archives over the years - ianhan/BitmapFonts</description>
      <author> (ianhan)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ianhan/BitmapFonts</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 10:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My product is my garden</title>
      <link>https://herman.bearblog.dev/my-product-is-my-garden/</link>
      <description>I’ve been part of the internet startup scene for a while. There are so many different camps: the bootstrappers, the VC-backed tech-bros, the crypto “investors”,</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://herman.bearblog.dev/my-product-is-my-garden/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 10:05:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>