<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Why and How to Execute GraphQL Queries in .NET - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/why-and-how-to-execute-graph-ql-queries-in-dotnet/</link>
      <description>This post shows how to query a GraphQL API in .NET using Strawberry Shake from a console application</description>
      <author> (Frank Boucher)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/why-and-how-to-execute-graph-ql-queries-in-dotnet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 19:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL&amp;#183;E</title>
      <link>https://typesetinthefuture.com/2018/12/04/walle/</link>
      <description>From a trash-filled Earth to the futuristic Axiom and back again, WALL&amp;#183;E is a finely crafted balance between consumerist dystopia and sixties space-race optimism. Please join me, then, for a detail…</description>
      <author> (by Dave Addey)</author>
      <guid>https://typesetinthefuture.com/2018/12/04/walle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Received Microsoft MVP Award in Developer Technologies</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/07/received-microsoft-mvp-award-in.html</link>
      <description>.NET, .NET Core, ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <author> (Posted by
Jaliya Udagedara)</author>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/07/received-microsoft-mvp-award-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AR and VR MAUI Apps | .NET MAUI Community Standup with Ed Charbeneau</title>
      <link>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/07/11/dotnet-maui-community-standup-july-2024-mixed-reality/</link>
      <description>This month’s .NET MAUI community standup focuses on Mixed Reality, specifically on building MAUI apps for AR and VR devices, featuring Ed Charbeneau, well-known in the Blazor community. His a…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/07/11/dotnet-maui-community-standup-july-2024-mixed-reality/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dut</title>
      <link>https://codeberg.org/201984/dut</link>
      <description>A disk usage calculator for Linux</description>
      <author> (201984)</author>
      <guid>https://codeberg.org/201984/dut</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating an already-completed asynchronous activity in C++/WinRT, part 3 - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240711-00/?p=109965</link>
      <description>Generalizing to the four kinds of Windows Runtime asynchronous activities.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240711-00/?p=109965</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing SSMS 20.2 ... and getting feedback for SSMS 21</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server-blog/announcing-ssms-20-2-and-getting-feedback-for-ssms-21/ba-p/4187034</link>
      <description>The SSMS team is happy to announce the release of SSMS 20.2, and we are also looking for user feedback to help shape the next major release, SSMS 21.</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/1317131)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server-blog/announcing-ssms-20-2-and-getting-feedback-for-ssms-21/ba-p/4187034</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Microservices to Modular Monoliths</title>
      <link>https://ardalis.com/from-microservices-to-modular-monoliths/</link>
      <description>What do you do when you find yourself in microservice hell? How do you keep the gains you (hopefully) made in breaking up your legacy ball of mud, without having to constantly contend with a massively distributed system? Migrate to a modular monolith.</description>
      <author> (Ardalis)</author>
      <guid>https://ardalis.com/from-microservices-to-modular-monoliths/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does code rot over time?</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/201377-A/does-code-rot-over-time?Key=b0af4b59-91db-482f-852e-b0de3b65c1a8</link>
      <description>&amp;amp;ldquo;This is Old Code&amp;amp;rdquo; is a programmer&amp;amp;rsquo;s idiom meaning &amp;amp;ldquo;There Be Dragons&amp;amp;rdquo;. &amp;amp;nbsp;The term &amp;amp;ldquo;Legacy Code&amp;amp;rdquo; is a nice way t...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/201377-A/does-code-rot-over-time?Key=b0af4b59-91db-482f-852e-b0de3b65c1a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loading aggregates with EF Core</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/07/loading-aggregates-with-ef-core.html</link>
      <description>In Domain-Driven Design (DDD), an aggregate is a cluster of domain objects that are treated as a single unit for the purpose of data changes...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/07/loading-aggregates-with-ef-core.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLMs are Blind</title>
      <link>https://vlmsareblind.github.io/</link>
      <description>Research showing that vision language models (VLMs) fail on simple visual tasks that are easy for humans.</description>
      <author> (Pooyan Rahmanzadehgervi1,*,)</author>
      <guid>https://vlmsareblind.github.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Friction</title>
      <link>https://5x9s.svix.com/p/adding-friction</link>
      <description>Today, we&amp;#39;re diving into an interesting topic: friction in development processes. I recently had a conversation with Tom about this, and it brought some new perspectives to light. An Initial Confusion During a call with our engineering team, our CEO Tom suggested adding a bit of friction to our processes. This was strange because I always want to remove friction to make things smoother and faster. Velocity is crucial for us— Tom harps on how we want to move quickly and efficiently. So, why would we want to add friction?</description>
      <author> (The Five 9&amp;#39;s Newsletter)</author>
      <guid>https://5x9s.svix.com/p/adding-friction</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fun with Positron | Andrew Heiss</title>
      <link>https://www.andrewheiss.com/blog/2024/07/08/fun-with-positron/</link>
      <description>Combine the best of RStudio and Visual Studio Code in Posit’s new Positron IDE</description>
      <author> (Andrew Heiss)</author>
      <guid>https://www.andrewheiss.com/blog/2024/07/08/fun-with-positron/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healing Broken Bone at Anatomy and Art</title>
      <link>http://anatomyandart.com/blog/?p=3358</link>
      <description>a blog by Sara Egner</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://anatomyandart.com/blog/?p=3358</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading my electric meter with RTLSDR • pdx.su</title>
      <link>https://pdx.su/blog/2024-03-17-reading-my-electric-meter-with-rtlsdr/</link>
      <description>The personal blog of software engineer Jeff Sandberg</description>
      <author> (Jeff Sandberg)</author>
      <guid>https://pdx.su/blog/2024-03-17-reading-my-electric-meter-with-rtlsdr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fat Tony’s Under Water: My Dream Startup Incubator</title>
      <link>https://sebs.website/blog/fat-tonys-under-water-my-dream-startup-incubator</link>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 1946 George Orwell wrote his short essay ‘The Moon Under Water’, describing what his dream pub would look like. Heavily influenced by this (in fact, some paragraphs are nearly identical), I have decided to write a modern version of Orwell’s essay, describing my dream startup incubator.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>
      <author> (Sebastian David Lees)</author>
      <guid>https://sebs.website/blog/fat-tonys-under-water-my-dream-startup-incubator</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG Trick: Embeddings are Spheres</title>
      <link>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2024/07/10/spheres</link>
      <description>Wed July 10, 2024</description>
      <author> (Tim Kellogg)</author>
      <guid>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2024/07/10/spheres</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I manage my KDE email</title>
      <link>https://pointieststick.com/2024/07/09/how-i-manage-my-kde-email/</link>
      <description>Every once in a while people ask me about my email routine, so I thought I’d write about it here. Everything I do starts with the philosophy that work and project email is a task queue. There…</description>
      <author> (Nate)</author>
      <guid>https://pointieststick.com/2024/07/09/how-i-manage-my-kde-email/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRL HTML Is the Place For Your Most Hand-Written Websites</title>
      <link>https://www.patrickweaver.net/blog/irl-html-is-the-place-for-your-most-hand-written-websites/</link>
      <description>Patrick Weaver’s Website</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.patrickweaver.net/blog/irl-html-is-the-place-for-your-most-hand-written-websites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Markets Act, Google, Chrome extensions - case study</title>
      <link>https://blog.lukaszolejnik.com/digital-markets-act-google-chrome-extensions-case-study/</link>
      <description>The Digital Markets Act is one of the least understood EU technology laws, yet it has tangible impacts—both positive and negative—on the technology landscape. We’ll use the opportunity to study an interesting and real-world case. It concerns the practice of Chrome preloading its web browser extension so</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.lukaszolejnik.com/digital-markets-act-google-chrome-extensions-case-study/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Programmable Web</title>
      <link>https://www.mattwensing.com/the-programmable-web/</link>
      <description>Today’s app development ecosystems resemble the creative contexts for writers and photographers pre-web and pre-iPhone.</description>
      <author> (Matthew Wensing)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mattwensing.com/the-programmable-web/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 5 Stages of Posthuman Grief - “Acceptance” Makes Progress Possible - Dan Faggella</title>
      <link>https://danfaggella.com/acceptance/</link>
      <description>The 5 Stages of Grief Model isn’t perfect - but it also seems to overlap well with the experiences of grieving people. The psychological model itself needn’t</description>
      <author> (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://danfaggella.com/acceptance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evict Your Darlings: Banish dotfiles from your home directory</title>
      <link>https://r.je/evict-your-darlings</link>
      <description>Erase Your Darlings is a great approach but what if we could banish dotfiles from our home directory entirely?</description>
      <author> (Dr. Tom Butler)</author>
      <guid>https://r.je/evict-your-darlings</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HCI Is the Bottleneck</title>
      <link>https://joshmpollock.com/blog/hci-bottleneck/</link>
      <description>HCI Is the Bottleneck in a World with Strong AI  As model capabilities advance, we are rapidly gaining the ability to generate images, videos, and audio from simple text prompts that are indistinguishable from human-generated content.  Yet, even if we discount existing flaws with models, there’s still a huge gap between model capabilities and systems that are effective in practice. I argue this gap is caused primarily by HCI problems and not model capabilities, and the gap will only continue to increase as model capabilities improve.  Is this gap due to failings of HCI? Not entirely. I think it’s also due to the mental model of AI that persists despite growing problems with integrating AI solutions.  AI is typically thought of in the following way:  input -&amp;gt; model -&amp;gt; output  The goal of core machine learning is to create the model that optimizes the output given the input, e.g., producing an output image that most faithfully represents an input text prompt. The central limitation of this model is that it ignores where inputs come from and where outputs go to. The picture looks a little more like this:  human -input-&amp;gt; model -output-&amp;gt; human  Even if we assume a perfect model that optimizes the input-output correlation, the model is still fundamentally limited by the information contained in the input, and the usefulness of the output is still fundamentally limited by a human’s ability to interpret and use it.  Improving input and output interfaces is the bottleneck as models get more capable. It can be viewed as an information-theoretic problem. How do you get more bits of information into the input stream? How do you allow humans to interpret more bits of information from the output stream? Now, solutions to these problems aren’t simply algorithmic, but also require existing context to understand. That is, it’s not as simple as cramming in more information, but also in doing so in a way that allows humans to create and understand that information.  What’s the role of HCI with imperfect models?  HCI still has a profound role, possibly a more important role, even with imperfect models. We can think of an imperfect model as a perfect model with some additional (possibly/probably biased) noise. The HCI problems with imperfect models are thus the same as with perfect models but with the added difficultly of allowing humans to understand and handle “noise” in the model output.  Won’t strong AI solve the HCI problem?  Even as models get better at producing interfaces, their capabilities are still limited to the human&amp;lt;-&amp;gt;model feedback loop. This loop can probably be used to design these interfaces (and this is already starting to happen with things like Copilot and Figma AI, for example), but it doesn’t let us sidestep this problem completely.  Aren’t’ UIs just going to be ephemerally generated all the time?  Complex interfaces like the Blenders and Photoshops of the world are still likely to be semi-stable interfaces rather than ones that are generated on the fly, because of how difficult it is to learn such interfaces and the benefits humans have when using tools they have deep knowledge/skill/practice/craft around. So these interfaces are still subject to the feedback loop problem.  How do we improve input and output fidelity?  I think I’ll save this for another time.</description>
      <author> (Josh Pollock)</author>
      <guid>https://joshmpollock.com/blog/hci-bottleneck/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Code Reviews: Align your team and ship better code</title>
      <link>https://faingezicht.com/articles/2024/07/10/pull-requests/?src=hn</link>
      <description>The pull request review process introduces a lot of friction in the development cycle but serves multiple purposes, including knowledge sharing, code quality, and team alignment. It is a worthwhile investment. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://faingezicht.com/articles/2024/07/10/pull-requests/?src=hn</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Commitment to Art and Dogs</title>
      <link>https://samwho.dev/dogs/</link>
      <description>Introducing a new design for the samwho.dev dogs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://samwho.dev/dogs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updating Prism Template to .NET 8</title>
      <link>https://checox.com/updating-prism-template-to-net-8/</link>
      <description>Have you notice that now when create a MAUI project using the new Prism Template Pack for MAUI, you are not able to select the .NET version of your project? well, in this post I will show you how to update it.</description>
      <author> (steven.checo.19)</author>
      <guid>https://checox.com/updating-prism-template-to-net-8/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Crossword Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2957/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2957/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zed on Linux is here!</title>
      <link>https://zed.dev/linux</link>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ve stabilized our Linux build, download it today!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zed.dev/linux</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>