<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot &amp;#183; Your AI pair programmer</title>
      <link>https://github.com/features/copilot</link>
      <description>GitHub Copilot works alongside you directly in your editor, suggesting whole lines or entire functions for you.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/features/copilot</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 15:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Containerized Build Agents with Azure DevOps Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/create-containerized-build-agents-with-azure-devops-pipelines</link>
      <description>This post is about how to create containerized build agents with azure devops pipeline. Few days back I wrote a blog post on creating Azure Virtual Machine as Azure DevOps pipeline build agent. In this post we will be discussing about how to use Docker container as build agent. We can use this build agents for .NET Core and .NET Framework or any other languages / platforms. For this demo I am creating a build agent for a ASP.NET Core project.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/create-containerized-build-agents-with-azure-devops-pipelines</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 11:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - d07RiV/diabloweb: Diablo 1 for web browsers</title>
      <link>https://github.com/d07RiV/diabloweb</link>
      <description>Diablo 1 for web browsers. Contribute to d07RiV/diabloweb development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (d07RiV)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/d07RiV/diabloweb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 11:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Store doesn&amp;#39;t accept </title>
      <link>https://notes.alinpanaitiu.com/Dealing%20with%20App%20Store%20rejections</link>
      <description>Alin Panaitiu&amp;#39;s notes and ramblings: short-form content on macOS apps, music and computers in general</description>
      <author> (Alin Panaitiu)</author>
      <guid>https://notes.alinpanaitiu.com/Dealing%20with%20App%20Store%20rejections</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - karanpratapsingh/system-design: Learn how to design systems at scale and prepare for system design interviews</title>
      <link>https://github.com/karanpratapsingh/system-design</link>
      <description>Learn how to design systems at scale and prepare for system design interviews - GitHub - karanpratapsingh/system-design: Learn how to design systems at scale and prepare for system design interviews</description>
      <author> (karanpratapsingh)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/karanpratapsingh/system-design</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journey to Lumen</title>
      <link>https://knarkowicz.wordpress.com/2022/08/18/journey-to-lumen/</link>
      <description>Real-time GI has always been a holy grail of computer graphics. Over the years there were multiple approaches to this problem. Usually constraining problem domain by leveraging certain assumptions …</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://knarkowicz.wordpress.com/2022/08/18/journey-to-lumen/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpropagation From Scratch</title>
      <link>https://marcospereira.me/2022/08/18/backpropagation-from-scratch/</link>
      <description>Making NPCs alive</description>
      <author> (Marcos Pereira)</author>
      <guid>https://marcospereira.me/2022/08/18/backpropagation-from-scratch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electron-Based App Vulnerabilities Hit VS Code, Microsoft Teams -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/08/19/electron-bugs.aspx</link>
      <description>  A team of researchers recently presented data about vulnerabilities in apps built on the open source Electron framework for creating desktop apps with JavaScript, HTML and CSS.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel08/19/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/08/19/electron-bugs.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Everyone Who Asks For ‘Just A Little’ Of Your Time: Here’s What It Costs To Say Yes - RyanHoliday.net</title>
      <link>https://ryanholiday.net/to-everyone-who-asks-for-just-a-little-of-your-time-heres-what-it-costs-to-say-yes/</link>
      <description>To the person who emailed me this morning with a perfectly nice request, I’m sorry to say the answer is no. You didn’t do anything wrong. You were perfectly respectful and within your rights to ask about arranging a time for a meeting (or was it for a phone call or about setting a date for that project we discussed, I don’t recall). The problem isn’t you. There is something wrong with me. I have a form of anorexia. Don’t be alarmed. It’s not serious, though I take it quite seriously. Because it’s probably the only form that’s healthy. In fact, I think it’s the secret to my success. I have calendar anorexia. I want as absolutely little in my calendar as possible. I’m meticulous about it. Whatever the least amount possible I can have in my calendar without killing my career—that’s what I want. To be clear, this isn’t some nonsense about not putting things in the calendar, like someone who says they’re on a diet but eats a lot. This is about committing to and scheduling next to nothing on a daily and weekly basis. Want to set up a quick call to chat? Should we have coffee next week? Let’s get together to discuss? Nope, nope, nope. I could, but I just can’t. Even if they are serious opportunities, even if it will only take 15 minutes, even if it’s something that everyone else does, I’d like to avoid it. Of course, I’m not perfect at this. I succumb, like everyone else in the modern world (so if you think I’m being a hypocrite, I am…and that’s why I really have to say no this time). There’s&amp;#160;stuff I have to do&amp;#160;and that stuff has to be scheduled. There are requirements for work and for basic civility. But even then… When I pull up my phone, click the day’s date and see too many little boxes of time blocked off, I get very nervous. What is all this? Where did all my time go? What about my day? Why did I agree to any of this again? (The answer is usually because it was really far away and I thought it would magically work itself out.) And then the most fearful question: How will I be able to write? I want two or three things in there at most. The rest is for me. The rest is not allowed to be scheduled. And if it is scheduled, it better be because I’m getting paid or I really, really wanted to do it. Everything else is for suckers. Paul Graham has a famous essay&amp;#160;about managers vs makers. There are two ways to run your life, he says. Managers know that their day is divided up in pieces for meetings, calls, and administrative tasks. Makers, on the other hand, need to have&amp;#160;large blocks of uninterrupted, unscheduled time&amp;#160;to do what they do. To create and think. When people ask how I manage to&amp;#160;get so much writing done, my anorexia is the answer. Same goes for how I’ve managed to keep a&amp;#160;healthy relationship&amp;#160;and how I manage to&amp;#160;exercise and read. I keep a maker’s schedule because I believe that anything else is anathema to deep work or creativity. Early in one’s creative career, this is relatively easy. Mostly because no one really wants much of your time. But as you achieve any measure of success in your field, this changes. It’s not a malicious thing. It’s actually an enormous compliment and a validation of your hard work. But the result is that you have more opportunities and responsibilities that can reasonably be accommodated. And how you choose to respond to this determines the course of your career (and in my opinion, your personal sanity and happiness). In&amp;#160;Ego is the Enemy, I tell a story about George Marshall. While he was cabinet member in the Truman administration, he was asked to sit for an official portrait. Though I’m sure he did what he could to get out of it, for whatever reason, Marshall was unable to. So he went, on several days, to sit for the artist, spending who knows how many hours still as…well…a portrait. On the final day, the artist informed Marshall that the portrait was complete. Marshall quickly got up, thanked him and began to walk out the door. The artist was surprised. He’d just spent all this time sitting, didn’t he want to at least see the painting? The answer was no. Marshall didn’t want to spend one second more than he had to. He definitely didn’t care what he looked like in some picture. I always thought it was strange to hear actors complain about the two weeks of media they had to do to promote their movies. Who doesn’t like publicity? Isn’t that the whole perk of being famous? But then, over the last few years, I started to understand.&amp;#160;These interviews were a major time and energy suck. It’s disrupting their life—a life where the rest of the time, they make their own schedule. Worse, it’s to do something repetitive and unfulfilling, answering the same questions over and over again, asked by people who usually haven’t even seen their work. When I&amp;#160;ranted about podcasts last year, it was in part, my own realization of the same idea. The podcast is fun for the person making it. For the person agreeing to be on it,&amp;#160;that’s an hour of their time they’re giving up. Both sides seem to fundamentally miss the magnitude of that imposition. But one is selfish if they point it out, or refuse to play along, except on their own terms. And so most don’t. Seneca&amp;#160;writes that if all the geniuses in history were to get together, none would be able explain our baffling relationship with time. He says, No person would give up even an inch of their estate, and the slightest dispute with a neighbor can mean hell to pay; yet we easily let others encroach on our lives—worse, we often pave the way [...]</description>
      <author> (by Ryan Holiday)</author>
      <guid>https://ryanholiday.net/to-everyone-who-asks-for-just-a-little-of-your-time-heres-what-it-costs-to-say-yes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Like a State, Progress and Poverty, and Owning Land – Loukidelis.com</title>
      <link>http://www.loukidelis.com/on-land-ownership.html</link>
      <description>August 19, 2022</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.loukidelis.com/on-land-ownership.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On being busy</title>
      <link>https://blog.aadilali.com/posts/busy.html</link>
      <description>People who:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.aadilali.com/posts/busy.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Went to a “Dangerous Alt-Right Rally” | The Blog of Dr. Josh C. Simmons</title>
      <link>https://www.joshcsimmons.com/posts/i-went-to-a-dangerous-alt-right-rally</link>
      <description>The Blog of Dr. Josh C. Simmons</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.joshcsimmons.com/posts/i-went-to-a-dangerous-alt-right-rally</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding latency: one step, two step, oops</title>
      <link>https://blog.lawrencejones.dev/latency/</link>
      <description>When it comes to complex systems, you can only go so far with synthetic experiments before you need to try something for real, and test in production. There&amp;#39;s no substitute for it, and you&amp;#39;re likely making the wrong decision if you avoid it. But I can say from experience it&amp;#39;s not without risks, and this post shares an example of where we got as much as possible from that prework and testing, even if it was a bit of a bumpy ride.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.lawrencejones.dev/latency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How not to build a bike shed</title>
      <link>https://lucasfcosta.com/2022/08/19/bikeshedding.html</link>
      <description>No matter how realistic this story may seem, it’s just fiction.</description>
      <author> (Lucas Fernandes da Costa at London, United Kingdom)</author>
      <guid>https://lucasfcosta.com/2022/08/19/bikeshedding.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should I learn X?</title>
      <link>https://kinduff.com/2022/08/19/should-i-learn-x/</link>
      <description>Some thoughts regarding gurus that recommended learning X instead of Y.</description>
      <author> (Alejandro AR)</author>
      <guid>https://kinduff.com/2022/08/19/should-i-learn-x/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolving an unusual wifi issue</title>
      <link>https://blog.ando.fyi/posts/diagnosing-an-unsual-wifi-issue/</link>
      <description>Resolving an intermittent wifi issue that I’ve been having for months, with an unusual conclusion.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ando.fyi/posts/diagnosing-an-unsual-wifi-issue/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foils Have Hooks</title>
      <link>https://rdrn.dev/foils-have-hooks/</link>
      <description>Foils are pretty easy to ignore, ask me. I managed for nearly 8 years. I managed to miss the barbed hooks and swim on. Surfing, bouldering, drones, wave pools, offshore sailing for a seasick summer, you name it. This is a story about how you need patience to let the barbs catch.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rdrn.dev/foils-have-hooks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age Milestone Privileges</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2661/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2661/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shazam turns 20</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2022/08/shazam-turns-20/</link>
      <description>Shazam — one of the most beloved and popular music discovery platforms in the world — turns 20 today.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2022/08/shazam-turns-20/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 22:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code Dev Intros Open Source Markdown Language Server -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/08/19/markdown-language-server.aspx</link>
      <description>A maintainer of JavaScript/TypeScript for the VS Code team has completely changed the way Markdown works in the editor, replacing (and adding to) functionality that was previously baked in and augmented by extensions.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel08/19/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/08/19/markdown-language-server.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 19:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf Focus on MAUI - That&amp;#39;s a wrap!</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-conf-focus-on-maui-recap/</link>
      <description>August 9th we hosted our .NET Conf Focus on MAUI event to announce and share the latest tools and updates for .NET MAUI. With 25 sessions hosted and recorded, we recap the event and get you connected with all of the content from our event.</description>
      <author> (Jeffrey Fritz)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-conf-focus-on-maui-recap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 19:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Twipped/InterviewThis: An open source list of developer questions to ask prospective employers</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Twipped/InterviewThis</link>
      <description>An open source list of developer questions to ask prospective employers - GitHub - Twipped/InterviewThis: An open source list of developer questions to ask prospective employers</description>
      <author> (Twipped)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Twipped/InterviewThis</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 16:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>