<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking your work-life balance to take over the world --- !topic</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/twilio</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> (Twilio)</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/twilio</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 14:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pumping up your internet speeds with the Unifi Security Gateway and 4G/5G</title>
      <link>https://scotthelme.co.uk/pumping-up-your-internet-speeds/</link>
      <description>I've worked from home for quite some time and having both fast and reliable internet access has of course always been a huge concern for me. In order to increase both the speed and reliability of my internet connection, I recently made an upgrade.  My Ubiquiti Home NetworkRegular readers will</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/scott.helme)</author>
      <guid>https://scotthelme.co.uk/pumping-up-your-internet-speeds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 13:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics Notes</title>
      <link>https://landgreen.github.io/physics/index.html</link>
      <description>Interactive notes for algebra based physics.</description>
      <author> (Ross Landgreen)</author>
      <guid>https://landgreen.github.io/physics/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 13:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source bug bonanza: Vulnerabilities up almost 50 per cent thanks to people actually looking for them</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.co.uk/2020/03/13/open_source_bugs/</link>
      <description>Can't fix flaws if you don't look for them</description>
      <author> (13 Mar 2020 at 07:05)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.co.uk/2020/03/13/open_source_bugs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 12:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numberphile is creating Videos | Patreon</title>
      <link>https://www.patreon.com/numberphile</link>
      <description>Become a patron of Numberphile today:
            Read 613 posts by Numberphile and get access to exclusive
            content and experiences on the world’s largest membership
            platform for artists and creators.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.patreon.com/numberphile</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 11:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding, Cloud &amp; Technology | [Unity - Introduction for the business developer Series</title>
      <link>https://blogs.siliconorchid.com/post/newbie-coder/unity-intro-for-business-developer/pt1-intro/</link>
      <description>This is part one of a beginner-level series about Unity,  aimed at existing .NET business developers, who are interested in dipping a toe into something different.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.siliconorchid.com/post/newbie-coder/unity-intro-for-business-developer/pt1-intro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 10:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fireiron: A Scheduling Language for High-Performance Linear Algebra on GPUs</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2003.06324</link>
      <description>Achieving high-performance GPU kernels requires optimizing algorithm
implementations to the targeted GPU architecture. It is of utmost importance to
fully use the compute and memory hierarchy, as well as available specialised
hardware. Currently, vendor libraries like cuBLAS and cuDNN provide the best
performing implementations of GPU algorithms. However the task of the library
programmer is incredibly challenging: for each provided algorithm,
high-performance implementations have to be developed for all commonly used
architectures, input sizes, and different storage formats. These
implementations are generally provided as optimized assembly code because
performance-critical architectural features are only exposed at this level.
This prevents reuse between different implementations of even the same
algorithm, as simple differences can have major effects on low-level
implementation details. In this paper we introduce Fireiron, a DSL and compiler
which allows the specification of high-performance GPU implementations as
compositions of simple and reusable building blocks. We show how to use
Fireiron to optimize matrix multiplication implementations, achieving
performance matching hand-coded CUDA kernels, even when using specialised
hardware such as NIVIDA Tensor Cores, and outperforming state-of-the-art
implementations provided by cuBLAS by more than 2x.</description>
      <author> (Authors:Bastian Hagedorn, Archibald Samuel Elliott, Henrik Barthels, Rastislav Bodik, Vinod Grover)</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2003.06324</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 10:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AzUpdate: CosmosDB Free tier, ASR Update Rollup, Azure Hybrid Virtual Event, and DIY Acoustic Panels</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/itops-talk-blog/azupdate-cosmosdb-free-tier-asr-update-rollup-azure-hybrid/ba-p/1224371</link>
      <description>Another week comes to an end and with it comes another AzUpdate.  Let's explore some of the news that happened in the Azure world this week.     Azure CosmosDB Free tier     This week saw the launch of a free tier within Azure CosmosDB, which can be used to run development or test environment on or ...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/347158)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/itops-talk-blog/azupdate-cosmosdb-free-tier-asr-update-rollup-azure-hybrid/ba-p/1224371</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unit Testing Entry and Entry Points — Roy Osherove</title>
      <link>https://osherove.com/blog/2020/3/12/unit-testing-entry-points-and-exit-points</link>
      <description>Let’s talk about the word “unit” in unit testing. &amp;nbsp;To me, a  unit  stands for “unit of work” or a “use case” inside the system. A unit of work has a beginning and an end. I call these  entry points  and  exit points . A simple example of a unit of work, as we’ll soon see, is a function that</description>
      <author> (Roy Osherove)</author>
      <guid>https://osherove.com/blog/2020/3/12/unit-testing-entry-points-and-exit-points</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Different ways to Check for Null – Thomas Claudius Huber</title>
      <link>https://www.thomasclaudiushuber.com/2020/03/12/c-different-ways-to-check-for-null/</link>
      <description>What is the classic way to check if for example a parameter value is null? If you've developed with C# since a while, you might be familiar with this classic syntax: public static int CountNumberOfSInName(string name) { if (name == null) { throw new ArgumentNullException(nameof(name)); } return name...</description>
      <author> (By Thomas Claudius Huber)</author>
      <guid>https://www.thomasclaudiushuber.com/2020/03/12/c-different-ways-to-check-for-null/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to uninstall old versions of .NET Core</title>
      <link>http://codeclimber.net.nz/archive/2020/03/12/how-to-uninstall-old-versions-of-net-core/</link>
      <description>Uninstalling old versions of .NET Core used to be a tedious process, so much that I still had previews of 2.0 installed. But now it's super easy thanks to the newly released .NET Core Uninstall Tool. Have a look at how it works</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://codeclimber.net.nz/archive/2020/03/12/how-to-uninstall-old-versions-of-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Clippit, get your slides out of PPTX.</title>
      <link>https://sergeytihon.com/2020/03/15/introducing-clippit/</link>
      <description>Clippit is .NETStandard 2.0 library that allow you easily and efficiently extract all slides from PPTX presentation into one-slide presentations or compose slides back together into one presentatio…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sergeytihon.com/2020/03/15/introducing-clippit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to Basics: Rewriting a URL in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2020/Mar/13/Back-to-Basics-Rewriting-a-URL-in-ASPNET-Core</link>
      <description>Sometimes in an application you need to take over the routing process with some custom processing that acts on an incoming URL and actually has to go to another URL. This can be a simple relinking task from old content to new, or it can be more complex where you access a specific URL on the public site that actually needs to be processed by another URL altogether.</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/rickstrahl)</author>
      <guid>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2020/Mar/13/Back-to-Basics-Rewriting-a-URL-in-ASPNET-Core</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tip 255 - What's Azure Private Link and how can I get started?</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/blog/tip255.html</link>
      <description>It is very important to secure all aspects of your application, including your data communications. This can be difficult as services in the cloud are often exposed to the public internet. Azure Private Link can help to secure traffic between Azure services and other applications. You can use Azure Private Link to secure Azure services and also your own services, that are behind an Azure Load Balancer. Consumers of services that are protected with Private Link, can simply use the Private Link and communicate with the protected services directly, over the Azure backbone, instead of over the public internet.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/blog/tip255.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Akka.NET v1.4 is Available on .NET Standard 2.0</title>
      <link>https://petabridge.com/blog/akkdotnet-v14-netstandard/</link>
      <description>As of this week, Akka.NET v1.4 is now fully available for users to use. We’ve published a detailed article on the Akka.NET website that describes what’s new in Akka.NET v1.4, but we wanted to capture some of the highlights here.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://petabridge.com/blog/akkdotnet-v14-netstandard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ploeh blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/</link>
      <description>Danish software design</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSI: The case of the missing WAV audio files on the FAT32 SD Card</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/CSITheCaseOfTheMissingWAVAudioFilesOnTheFAT32SDCard.aspx</link>
      <description>Buckle up kids, as this is a tale. As you may know, I have a lovely podcast at https://hanselminutes.com. You should ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/CSITheCaseOfTheMissingWAVAudioFilesOnTheFAT32SDCard.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inslee statement on statewide shutdown of restaurants, bars and</title>
      <link>https://www.governor.wa.gov/news-media/inslee-statement-statewide-shutdown-restaurants-bars-and-limits-size-gatherings-expanded</link>
      <description>Gov. Jay Inslee released a statement tonight that further expands protections against COVID-19.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.governor.wa.gov/news-media/inslee-statement-statewide-shutdown-restaurants-bars-and-limits-size-gatherings-expanded</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 05:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showing Off Some New Shiny STuff</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/allancritchie</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> (allancritchie)</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/allancritchie</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 04:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC recommends no gatherings of 50 or more for 8 weeks</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/public-health/2020/03/16/cdc-recommends-no-gatherings-of-50-or-more-for-8-weeks/</link>
      <description>Officials across the country curtailed many elements of American life to fight the coronavirus outbreak on Sunday, with health officials recommending that...</description>
      <author> (By The Associated Press5:45 PM on Mar 15, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/public-health/2020/03/16/cdc-recommends-no-gatherings-of-50-or-more-for-8-weeks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 04:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Xamarin Newsletter - The best Xamarin development links, every Friday</title>
      <link>http://weeklyxamarin.com/</link>
      <description>Subscribe to a hand-picked round up of the best Xamarin development links every week. Published every Friday. Free.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://weeklyxamarin.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 04:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KymPhillpotts - Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/kymphillpotts</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> (KymPhillpotts)</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/kymphillpotts</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 04:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US OPM - DC area Federal Government Operating Status : OPEN WITH MAXIMUM TELEWORK FLEXIBILITIES TO ALL CURRENT TELEWORK ELIGIBLE EMPLOYEES, PURSUANT TO DIRECTION FROM AGENCY HEADS</title>
      <link>https://www.opm.gov/policy-data-oversight/snow-dismissal-procedures/current-status/</link>
      <description>The following message applies only to March 16, 2020
Federal offices in the Washington, DC area are OPEN.  Please contact your supervisor to confirm telework schedule and to receive further direction from your agency head.
If you are not telework eligible or do not have access to telework equipment, please contact your supervisor to discuss next steps.
Please refer to OMB Guidance M-20-15 (https://www.whitehouse.gov/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/M20-15-Telework-Guidance-OMB.pdf) for full details. AGENCIES remain OPEN to serve the American people and conduct mission critical functions. Each EMPLOYEE should refer to their own agency for communications and guidance on telework or leave status.
Note:  If you are a customer or member of the public planning to visit a Federal building, please confirm building/facility status before visiting.  Some agency buildings and locations may have select hours, reduced in-person services, or visitor restrictions in place.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.opm.gov/policy-data-oversight/snow-dismissal-procedures/current-status/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 02:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRE keeps digging to prevent problems | Google Cloud Blog</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/management-tools/sre-keeps-digging-to-prevent-problems</link>
      <description>See a real-world example of how Google’s SRE practices can identify and help fix issues, even at the bottom of the hardware stack.</description>
      <author> (Steve McGhee  Solutions Architect, Google Cloud)</author>
      <guid>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/management-tools/sre-keeps-digging-to-prevent-problems</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 02:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Yourself First Workshops in Australia, Denmark and Portugal (Virtually, of Course)</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/hack-yourself-first-workshops-in-australia-denmark-and-portugal-virtually-of-course/</link>
      <description>Of course it's virtual because let's face it, nobody is going anywhere at the moment. Plenty of you aren't even going into an office any more let alone fronting up to a conference with hundreds or even thousands of people. That sucks for you because you end up both missing</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/hack-yourself-first-workshops-in-australia-denmark-and-portugal-virtually-of-course/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with shaders: signed distance functions!</title>
      <link>https://jvns.ca/blog/2020/03/15/writing-shaders-with-signed-distance-functions/</link>
      <description>Getting started with shaders: signed distance functions!</description>
      <author> (Julia Evans)</author>
      <guid>https://jvns.ca/blog/2020/03/15/writing-shaders-with-signed-distance-functions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ethical Source Movement: Open Source, Evolved.</title>
      <link>https://ethicalsource.dev/apply/</link>
      <description>The Ethical Source working group is a community for open source maintainers and contributors, tech ethicists and advocates, licensing experts, and more to come together to strategize about ways to incorporate ethics into our open source work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ethicalsource.dev/apply/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immutable types in C# with Roslyn</title>
      <link>https://cezarypiatek.github.io/post/immutable-types-with-roslyn/</link>
      <description>How to create immutable types without writing large amount of boilerplate code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cezarypiatek.github.io/post/immutable-types-with-roslyn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 23:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the Recovery Act</title>
      <link>https://obamawhitehouse.archives.gov/recovery/about</link>
      <description>Welcome to WhiteHouse.gov/Recovery – the place to follow America’s recovery story. On February 17th, 2009, the President signed The American Recovery and Reinvestment Act, or Recovery Act, into law.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://obamawhitehouse.archives.gov/recovery/about</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 23:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metropolitan Opera to Offer Up 'Nightly Met Opera Streams' - Opera Wire</title>
      <link>https://operawire.com/metropolitan-opera-to-offer-up-nightly-met-opera-streams/</link>
      <description>In an effort to continue providing opera to its audience members, the Met Opera will host “Nightly Met Opera Streams” on its official website to audiences worldwide. These free streams will present encores of past performances from its famed Live in HD series. The encore presentations will begin at 7:30 p.m. EST each night on the company’s official website and {…}</description>
      <author> (By David Salazar)</author>
      <guid>https://operawire.com/metropolitan-opera-to-offer-up-nightly-met-opera-streams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 23:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wiener Staatsoper</title>
      <link>https://www.staatsoperlive.com/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Performance of Jan 10, 2016)</author>
      <guid>https://www.staatsoperlive.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 23:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EarthCam - Webcam Network</title>
      <link>https://www.earthcam.com/</link>
      <description>EarthCam is the leading network of live streaming webcams for tourism and entertainment. Explore unique and interesting locations around the world with 4K streaming technology. EarthCam provides complete infrastructure services to manage, host and maintain live streaming video solutions for its consumers and corporate clients. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.earthcam.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 19:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tracelight.net – enlights your software</title>
      <link>https://www.tracelight.net/</link>
      <description>Eager to stay up to date?  Follow us on twitter and subscribe the blog feed.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tracelight.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 19:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>planetgeek.ch – Your source of geek knowledge</title>
      <link>https://www.planetgeek.ch/</link>
      <description>Explains receiving a message from a queue, for more posts in this series go to Contents. In the previous post I showed the basic bits to send a message into a queue. But how can we get it out again? The good news is that the SDK makes it pretty simple to fetch a message from a queue. We can register a message handler delegate on the queue client. The delegate is automatically called when a message arrives in the queue we are listening to. client.RegisterMessageHandler( async (message, token)...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.planetgeek.ch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 19:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TUHS] The most surprising Unix programs</title>
      <link>https://minnie.tuhs.org/pipermail/tuhs/2020-March/020664.html</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://minnie.tuhs.org/pipermail/tuhs/2020-March/020664.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 17:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee Scheduling  |  OR-Tools  |  Google Developers</title>
      <link>https://developers.google.com/optimization/scheduling/employee_scheduling</link>
      <description>Organizations whose employees work multiple shifts need to
schedule sufficient workers for each daily shift. Typically, the schedules will have
constraints, such as "no employee should work two shifts in a row". Finding a schedule
that satisfies all constraints can be computationally difficult.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developers.google.com/optimization/scheduling/employee_scheduling</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 17:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mesolabe Compass and Square Roots - Numberphile</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9VVPBS_flOI</link>
      <description>Johnny Ball on the "often missed" Hippocrates of Chios.
Check out Brilliant (get 20% off their premium service): https://brilliant.org/numberphile (sponsor)
More links &amp; stuff in full description below ↓↓↓

More on Johnny Ball, including his books and live shows: https://www.johnnyball.co.uk

See Johnny discuss Russian multiplication: https://youtu.be/HJ_PP5rqLg0

Numberphile is supported by the Mathematical Sciences Research Institute (MSRI): http://bit.ly/MSRINumberphile

We are also supported by Science Sandbox, a Simons Foundation initiative dedicated to engaging everyone with the process of science. https://www.simonsfoundation.org/outreach/science-sandbox/

And support from Math For America - https://www.mathforamerica.org/

NUMBERPHILE
Website: http://www.numberphile.com/
Numberphile on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/numberphile
Numberphile tweets: https://twitter.com/numberphile
Subscribe: http://bit.ly/Numberphile_Sub

Videos by Brady Haran

Patreon: http://www.patreon.com/numberphile

Numberphile T-Shirts and Merch: https://teespring.com/stores/numberphile

Brady's videos subreddit: http://www.reddit.com/r/BradyHaran/

Brady's latest videos across all channels: http://www.bradyharanblog.com/

Sign up for (occasional) emails: http://eepurl.com/YdjL9</description>
      <author> (Numberphile)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9VVPBS_flOI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 17:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>