<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Kagi Assistant is now available to all users!</title>
      <link>https://blog.kagi.com/assistant-for-all</link>
      <description>At Kagi, our mission is simple: to humanise the web.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.kagi.com/assistant-for-all</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(All) Databases Are Just Files. Postgres Too</title>
      <link>https://tselai.com/all-databases-are-just-files</link>
      <description>If you invest a little time understanding how the components of your database system fit together—not even the internals, just the externals—you’ll be able to move faster, debug better, and build cleaner workflows with more confidence. It only needs some upfront investment of learning the basics and confidence that you can build along the way.</description>
      <guid>https://tselai.com/all-databases-are-just-files</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 10:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Gemini in .NET: The Ultimate Guide with Jochen Kirstaetter</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2MzCfhX6aUo</link>
      <description>RJJ Software's Software Development Service This episode of The Modern .NET Show is supported, in part, by RJJ Software's Software Development Services, whether your company is looking to elevate its UK operations or reshape its US strategy, we can provide tailored solutions that exceed expectations.

 Show Notes "So on my side it was actually, the interesting experience was that I kind of used it one way, because it was mainly about reading the Python code, the JavaScript code, and, let’s say like, the Go implementations, trying to understand what are the concepts, what are the ways about how it has been implemented by the different teams. And then, you know, switching mentally into the other direction of writing than the code in C#."— Jochen Kirstaetter

 Welcome friends to The Modern .NET Show; the premier .NET podcast, focusing entirely on the knowledge, tools, and frameworks that all .NET developers should have in their toolbox. We are the go-to podcast for .NET developers worldwide, and I am your host: Jamie “GaProgMan” Taylor.

 In this episode, Jochen Kirstaetter joined us to talk about his .NET SDK for interacting with Google’s Gemini suite of LLMs. Jochen tells us that he started his journey by looking at the existing .NET SDK, which didn’t seem right to him, and wrote his own using the HttpClient and HttpClientFactory classes and REST.

 "I provide a test project with a lot of tests. And when you look at the simplest one, is that you get your instance of the Generative AI type, which you pass in either your API key, if you want to use it against Google AI, or you pass in your project ID and location if you want to use it against Vertex AI. Then you specify which model that you like to use, and you specify the prompt, and the method that you call is then GenerateContent and you get the response back. So effectively with four lines of code you have a full integration of Gemini into your .NET application."— Jochen Kirstaetter

 Along the way, we discuss the fact that Jochen had to look into the Python, JavaScript, and even Go SDKs to get a better understanding of how his .NET SDK should work. We discuss the “Pythonistic .NET” and “.NETy Python” code that developers can accidentally end up writing, if they’re not careful when moving from .NET to Python and back. And we also talk about Jochen’s use of tests as documentation for his SDK.

 Anyway, without further ado, let's sit back, open up a terminal, type in `dotnet new podcast` and we'll dive into the core of Modern .NET.

 Supporting the Show If you find this episode useful in any way, please consider supporting the show by either leaving a review (check our review page for ways to do that), sharing the episode with a friend or colleague, buying the host a coffee, or considering becoming a Patron of the show.

 Full Show Notes The full show notes, including links to some of the things we discussed and a full transcription of this episode, can be found at:  https://dotnetcore.show/season-7/google-gemini-in-net-the-ultimate-guide-with-jochen-kirstaetter/

 Jason's Links:   JoKi's MVP Profile JoKi's Google Developer Expert Profile JoKi's website  Other Links:   Generative AI for .NET Developers with Amit Bahree curl Noda Time with Jon Skeet Google Cloud samples repo on GitHub Google's Gemini SDK for Python Google's Gemini SDK for JavaScript Google's Gemini SDK for Go Vertex AI JoKi's base NuGet package: Mscc.GenerativeAI JoKi's NuGet package: Mscc.GenerativeAI.Google System.Text.Json gcloud CLI  .NET Preprocessor directives .NET Target Framework Monikers QUIC protocol  IAsyncEnumerable Microsoft.Extensions.AI  Supporting the show:  Leave a rating or review Buy the show a coffee Become a patron  Getting in Touch:  Via the contact page Joining the Discord  Remember to rate and review the show on  Apple Podcasts, Podchaser, or wherever you find your podcasts, this will help the show's audience grow. Or you can just share the show with a friend.

 And don't forget to reach out via our Contact page. We're very interested in your opinion of the show, so please get in touch.

 You can support the show by making a monthly donation on the show's Patreon page at: https://www.patreon.com/TheDotNetCorePodcast.

 Music created by Mono Memory Music, licensed to RJJ Software for use in The Modern .NET Show</description>
      <author> (Jamie Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2MzCfhX6aUo</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 09:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux - News: Valkey to replace Redis in the [extra] Repository</title>
      <link>https://archlinux.org/news/valkey-to-replace-redis-in-the-extra-repository/</link>
      <description>Valkey, a high-performance key/value datastore, will be replacing redis in the [extra] repository. This change is due to Redis modifying its license from BSD-3-Clause to RSALv2 and SSPLv1 on March 20th, 2024.</description>
      <guid>https://archlinux.org/news/valkey-to-replace-redis-in-the-extra-repository/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 03:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 14.0: Introducing Extension Members and Null-Conditional Assignment</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2025/04/c-140-introducing-extension-members-and.html</link>
      <description>.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Azure, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2025/04/c-140-introducing-extension-members-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 00:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffering as a seed for change - how to turn limitations into strength</title>
      <link>https://trojanczyk.eu/suffering-as-a-seed-for-change/</link>
      <description>Discover how personal suffering can become a catalyst for positive change. The story of a leader with haemophilia shows how consciously overcoming difficulties builds empathetic leadership and discipline based on growth and innovation.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/adam.trojanczyk)</author>
      <guid>https://trojanczyk.eu/suffering-as-a-seed-for-change/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenBSD IO benchmarking: How Many Jobs Are Worth It?</title>
      <link>https://rsadowski.de/posts/2025/fio_simple_benckmarking/</link>
      <description>Rafael Sadowski</description>
      <guid>https://rsadowski.de/posts/2025/fio_simple_benckmarking/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Software Is Confusing</title>
      <link>https://www.jakeworth.com/posts/your-software-is-confusing/</link>
      <description>If something in your software is confusing to a customer, it is confusing.</description>
      <guid>https://www.jakeworth.com/posts/your-software-is-confusing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Zen of Task Management with Org</title>
      <link>https://bzg.fr/en/the-zen-of-task-management-with-org/</link>
      <description>I don't use Org Mode to be more productive, but to achieve a kind of "ataraxia" (i.e. a "lucid state of robust equanimity" according to Wikipedia) about the things I have to do: pay my bills on time and enjoy concentrating on my work.
After more than 15 years of refining my Org configuration, I can't say it's perfect, but it's stable and comfortable enough that I think it might be useful to others.</description>
      <guid>https://bzg.fr/en/the-zen-of-task-management-with-org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How LLMs Are Changing Programming · TomAF</title>
      <link>https://afiodorov.github.io/2025/04/17/personalized-software/</link>
      <description>Today, I want to talk about the role of LLMs in the software industry.First, let me start by saying that the magic of...</description>
      <guid>https://afiodorov.github.io/2025/04/17/personalized-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collatz's Ant and similarity of collatz sequences</title>
      <link>https://gbragafibra.github.io/2025/01/08/collatz_ant2.html</link>
      <description>This is a brief continuation of a previous post (Repo), which introduced such visualization for collatz sequences based on Langton’s Ant.</description>
      <guid>https://gbragafibra.github.io/2025/01/08/collatz_ant2.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landscape of Debuggability in Machine Learning for Systems</title>
      <link>https://varungohil.github.io/blog/2025/mlsys-debuggability/</link>
      <description>Connecting diffused research on debuggability of ML-assisted systems into an intuitive framework.</description>
      <guid>https://varungohil.github.io/blog/2025/mlsys-debuggability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding X Posts in Fumadocs | rjv.im</title>
      <link>https://rjv.im/blog/solution/embed-x-post-in-fuma-docs</link>
      <description>A guide to embed X posts in your Fumadocs site</description>
      <guid>https://rjv.im/blog/solution/embed-x-post-in-fuma-docs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What MCP is Missing: UI Components</title>
      <link>https://www.maximepeabody.com/blog/mcp-missing-ui</link>
      <description>A blog post on MCP Missing UI</description>
      <guid>https://www.maximepeabody.com/blog/mcp-missing-ui</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLite Transactions and Virtual Tables</title>
      <link>https://misfra.me/2025/sqlite-transactions-and-virtual-tables/</link>
      <description>In my previous post I introduced SQL virtual tables and how to use them in Go—registering modules per connection, defining schemas, and querying external sources as regular tables.</description>
      <guid>https://misfra.me/2025/sqlite-transactions-and-virtual-tables/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Millions to Hundreds: The Evolution of Chatbot Development</title>
      <link>https://ziriusai.xyz/how-chatbot-development-changed.html</link>
      <description>Discover how chatbot development has transformed from complex, expensive projects to accessible solutions anyone can build. Learn about the evolution of AI technology and its impact on business automation.</description>
      <guid>https://ziriusai.xyz/how-chatbot-development-changed.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start building with Gemini 2.5 Flash- Google Developers Blog</title>
      <link>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/start-building-with-gemini-25-flash/</link>
      <description>Gemini 2.5 Flash,  is now in preview, offering improved reasoning while prioritizing speed and cost efficiency for developers.</description>
      <guid>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/start-building-with-gemini-25-flash/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Intro to DeepSeek's Distributed File System</title>
      <link>https://maknee.github.io/blog/2025/3FS-Performance-Journal-1/</link>
      <description>Personal website for some random tidbits I work on</description>
      <guid>https://maknee.github.io/blog/2025/3FS-Performance-Journal-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preview 2 of the .NET AI Template Now Available - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-ai-template-preview2/</link>
      <description>Preview 2 of the .NET AI Chat Web App template introduces support for .NET Aspire and Qdrant vector database integration, making it easier to create cloud-native AI-powered chat applications with custom data.</description>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-ai-template-preview2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core Azure Deployment Crash Course For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dLuUJcxFcxU</link>
      <description>💻Get the full source code (free): https://go.dotnetacademy.io/aspnet-core-azure-deploy
🔥Become a .NET Cloud Developer: https://dotnetacademy.io/bootcamp

Learn the simplest way to deploy an ASP.NET Core full stack application to the Microsoft Azure cloud, step by step.

⭐️ Topics ⭐️
00:00 Welcome!
01:32 How does App Service work?
03:21 Running the ASP.NET Core API locally
06:10 Creating an App Service Web App
17:02 ASP.NET Core API deployment
23:25 Understanding the Web App deployment
30:39 Blazor frontend deployment
35:44 Troubleshooting via App Service logs
41:15 Using environment variables
44:36 Next steps

🌐Build the ASP.NET Core API: https://youtu.be/AhAxLiGC7Pc
🌐Build the Blazor frontend: https://youtu.be/RBVIclt4sOo

🆓How to get Free Azure Credits: https://juliocasal.com/blog/4-ways-to-get-free-azure-credits

🗺️Free .NET Developer Roadmap: https://juliocasal.com/roadmap

My website: https://juliocasal.com
Follow me on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/juliocasal
Follow me on X: https://twitter.com/julioc

#aspnetcore #azure</description>
      <author> (Julio Casal)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dLuUJcxFcxU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Back RSS Feeds to Browsers</title>
      <link>https://jetgirl.art/bring-back-rss-feeds-to-browsers/</link>
      <description>

I'm currently using Thunderbird to get/read RSS feeds. Outlook used to support them but it seems that's gone now too. 

I miss when the feeds were avai...</description>
      <guid>https://jetgirl.art/bring-back-rss-feeds-to-browsers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Redis With HybridCache to Cache Your EF Core Data!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=A4iEVoYpgnk</link>
      <description>In earlier videos in the series, we saw how we could convert our Entity Framework Core data access from IMemoryCache to HybridCache!

But... there was one big problem:

It was still just a memory cache behind the scenes!

Let's see how we can get Redis wired up to our HybridCache!

----
Real-World Web Development With .NET 9:
https://amzn.to/4lCy3wk
----
Timestamps:

0:00 - Intro
1:07 - Dependencies
2:11 - Dependency Injection
3:18 - Add Services
5:21 - Ad
6:18 - Docker for Redis
6:40 - Cache Expiration Config
8:17 - Demo Setup
9:30 - Demo
11:54 - Summary
----
🔑 Membership &amp; Subscriptions:
- 📨 Weekly Newsletter: https://weekly.devleader.ca
- 🏘️ Private Discord Community: https://sidestack.io/devleader

🧠 Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Get Promoted As A Software Engineer: https://dometrain.com/course/career-getting-promoted-as-a-software-engineer/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?ref=nick-cosentino
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

🗣️ Social Media &amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs:  @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp; Products/Services That I Love:
- @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper Opus Clip: https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----

#softwareengineering #softwaredeveloper #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=A4iEVoYpgnk</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 14:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>