<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>DO NOT BUY HISENSE TV&amp;#39;S LOL (Or at least keep them offline)</title>
      <link>https://cohost.org/ghoulnoise/post/5286766-do-not-buy-hisense-t</link>
      <description>holy fucking shit!!!!!!!!!!

I&amp;#39;ve had this in my drafts to finish writing up for a few weeks but today I made another discovery that has pushed me to finally write it up lol.

My PC had a few hiccups over the past couple of years. Nothing so serious that I was truly concerned (at first) but, annoyances, to be sure. (&amp;quot;PC? Weren&amp;#39;t you talking about a TV??&amp;quot; you might be thinking to yourself. Yes. I&amp;#39;ll get there. Oh, will I ever get there.)

For a long time, the most serious hiccup with my PC was being unable to open Display Settings on my PC. I had to use Nvidia control panel to make adjustments. Whatever. Didn&amp;#39;t affect my ability to work or anything. I had just updated to Windows 11 so I thought maybe something went wrong in the update. So I did another install (which meant I had to re-install a ton of music plugin stuff on my computer which takes ages given all the stuff I use.)

The fresh install still didn&amp;#39;t fix it. So I simply ignored it for the better part of 2 years.

Over time, so slowly I didn&amp;#39;t really clock them as being related, other things started to fail.

I have a Komplete Kontrol S88 midi Keyboard that interfaces with Kontakt and Komplete Kontrol in my DAW. I can use the keyboard to adjust settings or select instruments without having to look at my computer screen. At some point last year this stopped working. I could still use it to input midi, and I was afraid I&amp;#39;d have to do a fresh install of all the Native Instruments stuff I use, so I kept putting off trying to fix it until I had less going on with work. It worked, just not as well as it should!

Then, Task manager started to hang in weird ways. It wouldn&amp;#39;t close unless I forced it closed with ProcExp. Whatever! Computers are weird!

I had trouble getting video capture cards to connect when I considered streaming Splatoon. Whatever! I&amp;#39;m not a streamer, I should probably use that energy on something else.

But then, in March, I had some things fail that, turns out, are pretty necessary to using the computer.

I was trying to get remote desktop to work on my tablet so I could work in the living room closer to my cat, Grendel, who was still very much in mourning for his best friend (&amp;lt;3 Guts). Grendel is at his happiest when he&amp;#39;s napping on the couch next to a human. So I thought, hey, I could do some stuff in remote desktop mode! It wasn&amp;#39;t something I used very often because it doesn&amp;#39;t play super nice with audio, it&amp;#39;d been probably over a year since I last used it, but I knew it had worked and had been easy to set up.

Well. It refused to connect despite appearing as an option on my tablet. And as I was trying to troubleshoot this problem...

My task bars on my PC disappeared! If I moused over the spot they should have been I got the loading circle. And my monitors would jitter!

System settings were nowhere to be found. To navigate I had to open Task Manager (which if you recall was already acting strange and sluggish for the past year) in order to open the command panel, which I&amp;#39;d then use to launch programs. Or, attempt to. If I tried to open the system settings, my PC spat out &amp;quot;Uhhh what&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;Settings&amp;quot;? We ain&amp;#39;t got settings&amp;quot; (in command I got &amp;quot;C:\Windows\System32&amp;gt;start ms-settings: Access is denied.&amp;quot; despite being in admin mode)

SO I started to panic a wee bit. It&amp;#39;s not a great time for me to possibly need a new PC! Plus, it works great when it works.

I manually backed up everything important from my main PC drive (as I could not access the windows backup program because it lived in settings!!!!!!!!) and downloaded the Windows 11 installer to a drive in case I needed to completely wipe my computer and start fresh.

In a last ditch effort, I tried updating my Nvidia GeForce graphics driver and restarted.

Lo and behold, my taskbars came back and I could access settings again! Huzzah!

This lasted for 6 days. And then the taskbars disappeared AGAIN along with Settings.

At least by now I&amp;#39;d become somewhat comfortable using command to get around, so I was less panicked than I was in round 1. I at least knew the computer wouldn&amp;#39;t crash and delete all my shit suddenly (plus I had my backups that were up-to-date).

I asked my friends if they&amp;#39;d ever heard of anything like this, and Cohost&amp;#39;s own @vogon helped me poke around some additional graphics driver stuff in case updating to the new Nvidia program that&amp;#39;s in beta would solve my issue. This felt super promising when I went into safe mode and saw taskbars. So, I did the update, and, as before, when I updated, the taskbars came back! But there were gone again almost immediately. My screen literally started flickering and they vanished. It was so fucking bizarre.

I turned to google once more, hoping that somehow, as useless as google is these days, maybe I&amp;#39;d find what I needed to fix my damn computer!

Somehow, against all odds, I found it. I happened to use the exact right string in my search to pull up some reddit threads. The first one didn&amp;#39;t have anything useful, but a few results down I spotted &amp;quot;no taskbar and task manager freezes&amp;quot; holy moly!!!

At first glance however, there wasn&amp;#39;t anything useful. But then I spotted some collapsed comments at the bottom of the thread. I knew more than likely they just had comments like &amp;quot;sucks bro&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;this is why i use linux :/&amp;quot; But I expanded them and inside was a link to a Microsoft forum post. I kept my expectations in check and clicked on the link. What I saw had my nearly vibrating in my seat.

Screenshots showing the path from my google search to reddit to a minimized comment that contained a link to a microsoft forum post with the solution to my several year long problem - caused by our TV [https://staging.cohostcdn.org/attachment/d9f5719e-fe05-4247-9c27-39c3381f0648/screenshot%20collage.png?width=675&amp;amp;#x26;auto=webp&amp;amp;#x26;dpr=1]

This was the solution. [https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/answers/questions/1339707/help-with-figuring-out-what-is-causing-waitchain-d]

Narayan B
Nov 16, 2023, 12:20 AM

So I finally solved it!

Source of the problem: an Android TV (HiSense model) connected to my network. Yes. A TV caused this issue.

HISENSE? LIKE THE SAME BRAND OF TV I HAVE HAD SINCE 2020???

I followed the instructions. I deleted keys generated by our TV for 5 straight minutes. 5 Minutes of like 200BPM clicking. I restarted. Everything worked again. I laughed so hard I cried. I felt like I&amp;#39;d solved a murder. The main suspect was the PC but the culprit was the TV in the other room. And he almost got away with it!!! If I had spent a few days carrying out a clean install and re-installing all my work stuff, my problem would have come back. If I had taken the PC out back and shot it and replaced it with a fancy new computer, the problem would have come back.

Because the problem was never the PC. The Problem was my Hisense TV in the next room.

Once I carried this out, I was able to open display settings for the first time (outside of safe mode) in 2 years. When I deleted the keys, my Task Manager started behaving normally again. I turned around and saw that my keyboard was once again displaying the VST controls on its screen. The fancy midi keyboard was back at full functionality. I was able to connect my CRT as a display again using the HDMI -&amp;gt; RCA converters I&amp;#39;d assumed had stopped working (nope! they still worked, they always worked!)

Which brings me to today. Almost a month later everything still works. So, I decided to see if remote desktop would magically work again. The answer is: Yes. Yes, in fact, my TV was the reason my remote desktop connection had failed the month before.

So here I am, sitting on my couch with my tablet and bluetooth keeb and mouse, writing this post in remote desktop mode so I could attach screenshots of this saga to my post without sitting at my PC. Grendel is snoring beside me as I write.

As a treat for reading this far, please enjoy two screenshots of my friends reacting to the solution of my great mystery.

friends reacting in discord, the overall sentiment: what the fuck that is so cursed [https://staging.cohostcdn.org/attachment/a23624ba-f7bc-4b5b-aa53-68b1e16bfd2e/cursed%20TV%20PC%20reactions.png] friends reacting in discord, the overall sentiment: what the fuck that is so cursed [https://staging.cohostcdn.org/attachment/b9d4234d-4a60-4bb0-b2a9-92b898e75fba/cursed%20TV%20PC%20reactions2.png]

adding: the TV in question, in case you&amp;#39;re curious: Hisense 50Q8G- 50&amp;quot; Smart 4K ULED™ Android TV with Quantum Dot Technology (Canada Model)</description>
      <author> (https://cohost.org/ghoulnoise)</author>
      <guid>https://cohost.org/ghoulnoise/post/5286766-do-not-buy-hisense-t</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 23:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doomscroller</title>
      <link>https://doomscroller.xyz/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://doomscroller.xyz/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 22:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI isn&amp;#39;t useless. But is it worth it?</title>
      <link>https://www.citationneeded.news/ai-isnt-useless/</link>
      <description>AI can be kind of useful, but I&amp;#39;m not sure that a &amp;quot;kind of useful&amp;quot; tool justifies the harm.</description>
      <author> (Molly White)</author>
      <guid>https://www.citationneeded.news/ai-isnt-useless/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Everything is Becoming a Game</title>
      <link>https://www.gurwinder.blog/p/why-everything-is-becoming-a-game</link>
      <description>All the easier to control you</description>
      <author> (Gurwinder)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gurwinder.blog/p/why-everything-is-becoming-a-game</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faith, Deconstructed or Reconstructed - Philip Yancey</title>
      <link>https://philipyancey.com/faith-deconstructed-or-reconstructed</link>
      <description>This blog reproduces an exchange of emails I had with Bart Campolo about faith, either deconstructed or reconstructed, prompted by my memoir.</description>
      <author> (Philip Yancey)</author>
      <guid>https://philipyancey.com/faith-deconstructed-or-reconstructed</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagine</title>
      <link>https://blog.lwoleksii.com/p/imagine</link>
      <description>The future where humans fuel machines, but not in a physical sense</description>
      <author> (Oleksii)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.lwoleksii.com/p/imagine</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Female Space Marines Make No Sense</title>
      <link>https://warfantasy.wordpress.com/2024/02/04/why-female-space-marines-make-no-sense/</link>
      <description>Recently, there has been push for more “female representation” in Warhammer 40.000. This includes female guardsmen as well as female Space Marines. But neither makes much sense, and especially the …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://warfantasy.wordpress.com/2024/02/04/why-female-space-marines-make-no-sense/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lean Scala</title>
      <link>https://odersky.github.io/blog/2024-04-11-post.html</link>
      <description>Program code is for communicating between humans, not just for instructing computers. So we strive for code to be lean. Lean code is simple and understandable. It is as concise as possible without losing clarity. It avoids lingo, over-abstraction, and obscure features. It does not mislead, that is, it expresses the meaning of a program clearly and without fault. All these properties are desirable for code just as they are desirable for technical prose.</description>
      <author> (Martin Odersky)</author>
      <guid>https://odersky.github.io/blog/2024-04-11-post.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poisson designs and Minimum Detectable Effects</title>
      <link>https://andrewpwheeler.com/2024/03/18/poisson-designs-and-minimum-detectable-effects/</link>
      <description>Ian Adam’s posted a working paper the other day on power analysis for analyzing counts, Power Simulations of Rare Event Counts and Introduction to the ‘Power Lift’ Metric (Adams, 2024). I have a fe…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewpwheeler.com/2024/03/18/poisson-designs-and-minimum-detectable-effects/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positional Encoding for Self Attention</title>
      <link>https://swe-to-mle.pages.dev/posts/positional-encoding-for-self-attention/</link>
      <description>Positional Encoding for Self Attention</description>
      <author> (peluche)</author>
      <guid>https://swe-to-mle.pages.dev/posts/positional-encoding-for-self-attention/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10x Engineers vs -10x Burdens</title>
      <link>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/10x-engineers/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been reflecting on our engineers’ diverse impact on our projects and the true meaning behind labels like &amp;quot;10x engineer&amp;quot;. Over the years, many</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/vadim.kravcenko.dev)</author>
      <guid>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/10x-engineers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoFetch: Will people ever learn?</title>
      <link>https://microkerneldude.org/2024/04/18/gofetch-will-people-ever-learn/</link>
      <description>Last month researchers reported that the data memory-dependent prefetcher (DMP) on Apple M1 chips can be used to break encryption. (And there are indications that similar attacks might be possible …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://microkerneldude.org/2024/04/18/gofetch-will-people-ever-learn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Naming: Human vs. GPT-4</title>
      <link>https://beklein.com/posts/color-naming/</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s ask ChatGPT to tell us what color it sees and compare it to human color naming in a small scale experiment.</description>
      <author> (Bernd Klein)</author>
      <guid>https://beklein.com/posts/color-naming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Suck at Marketing</title>
      <link>https://cra.mr/you-suck-at-marketing/</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t worry, we all do. So how can we get better? Let me give you the lens of someone who&amp;#39;s built a business, someone with strong beliefs around what does and doesn&amp;#39;t work, but otherwise has no clue what they&amp;#39;re talking about.  This is all grounded in what I&amp;#39;ve seen at Sentry over the years, so let me take you through our go-to-market journey a little bit.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cra.mr/you-suck-at-marketing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop going to the cloud and getting scammed. $200 infra to serve your startup till 100k monthly users in 15 minutes. Self-hosted Postgres, caddyserver and docker-compose FTW.</title>
      <link>https://grski.pl/self-host</link>
      <description>An example of how you can save money, simplify your architecture and speed up the development by going back to the basics and ditching the cloud, kubernetes and whatnot.</description>
      <author> (Olaf G&amp;#243;rski)</author>
      <guid>https://grski.pl/self-host</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 20:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating API Gateways in Zuplo – Dev Leader Weekly 40</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/04/20/creating-api-gateways-in-zuplo-dev-leader-weekly-40/</link>
      <description>Welcome to another issue of Dev Leader Weekly! In this issue sponsored by Zuplo, I share how I&amp;#39;m putting an API gateway in front of my ASCII art API!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/04/20/creating-api-gateways-in-zuplo-dev-leader-weekly-40/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Printing Log</title>
      <link>https://madebynathan.com/logs/3d-printing/</link>
      <description>I bought a Bambu Lab X1-Carbon 3D printer in March 2023.

I&amp;#39;m extremely happy with this 3D printer and highly recommend it! It&amp;#39;s more expensive than entry-level printers, but it&amp;#39;s a very high quality machine and is very reliable. I can focus on designing and making things instead of spending</description>
      <author> (Nathan Broadbent)</author>
      <guid>https://madebynathan.com/logs/3d-printing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Microsoft developer says Windows 11&amp;#39;s performance is &amp;quot;comically bad,&amp;quot; even with monster PC</title>
      <link>https://www.blobstreaming.org/former-microsoft-developer-says-windows-11s-performance-is-comically-bad-even-with-monster-pc/</link>
      <description>Microsoft Windows 11 performance has noticeably deteriorated, a former Microsoft senior software engineer has pointed out. Some prominent user interface (UI) elements were &amp;quot;comically bad,&amp;quot; while others took almost a full second to load, he noted.


Important user interface elements cannot be loaded for unknown reasons

Microsoft recently reminded Windows</description>
      <author> (Mohamed Aboelez)</author>
      <guid>https://www.blobstreaming.org/former-microsoft-developer-says-windows-11s-performance-is-comically-bad-even-with-monster-pc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear is a Trainable Animal</title>
      <link>https://www.bendingpinksteel.com/p/fear</link>
      <description>Forget being fearless. This is better.</description>
      <author> (David Ramos)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bendingpinksteel.com/p/fear</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphics offload revisited – GTK Development Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.gtk.org/2024/04/17/graphics-offload-revisited/</link>
      <description>We first introduced support for dmabufs and graphics offload last fall, and it is included in GTK 4.14. Since then, some improvements have happened, so it is time for an update.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.gtk.org/2024/04/17/graphics-offload-revisited/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Msty</title>
      <link>https://msty.app/blog/llama3-vs-gpt-4-vs-gemini-pro</link>
      <description>Msty is simplest way to use local and online LLMs. Its chat interface packed with powerful features make it easy to use LLMs. Run Ollama models such as Mixtral, Llama2, Qwen, or online models such as GPT-3, GPT-4, Mistral, Gemini, Groq, Claude, and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://msty.app/blog/llama3-vs-gpt-4-vs-gemini-pro</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Dolphin Isn&amp;#39;t Coming to the App Store - oatmealdome.me</title>
      <link>https://oatmealdome.me/blog/why-dolphin-isnt-coming-to-the-app-store/</link>
      <description>Two weeks ago, Apple modified their App Store guidelines to allow retro game emulators in the App Store. This week, Delta, a multi-system emulator that was previously only available via AltStore, was released on the App Store. Since these events happened, we&amp;#39;ve been asked many times if we will submit…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://oatmealdome.me/blog/why-dolphin-isnt-coming-to-the-app-store/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stopping a badly behaved bot the wrong way. - Lemmy</title>
      <link>https://lemmy.ml/post/14612626</link>
      <description>I host a few small low-traffic websites for local interests. I do this for free
- and some of them are for a friend who died last year but didn’t want all his
work to vanish. They don’t get so many views, so I was surprised when I happened
to glance at munin and saw my bandwidth usage had gone up a lot. I spent a
couple of hours working to solve this and did everything wrong. But it was a
useful learning experience and I thought it might be worth sharing in case
anyone else encounters similar. My setup is: Cloudflare DNS -&amp;gt; Cloudflare Tunnel
(Because my residential isp uses CGNAT) -&amp;gt; Haproxy (I like Haproxy and amongst
other things, alerts me when a site is down) -&amp;gt; Separate Docker containers for
each website. On a Debian server living in my garage. From Haproxy’s stats page,
I was able to see which website was gathering attention. It’s one running PhpBB
for a little forum. Tailing apache’s logs in that container quickly identified
the pattern and made it easy to see what was happening. It was seeing a lot of
404 errors for URLs all coming from the same user-agent “claudebot”. I know what
you’re thinking - it’s an exploit scanning bot, but a closer look showed it was
trying to fetch normal forum posts, some which had been deleted months
previously, and also robots.txt. That site doesn’t have a robots.txt so that was
failing. What was weird is that the it was requesting at a rate of up to 20 urls
a second, from multiple AWS IPs - and every other request was for robots.txt.
You’d think it would take the hint after a million times of asking. Googling
that UA turns up that other PhpBB users have encountered this quite recently -
it seems to be fascinated by web forums and absolutely hammers them with the
same behaviour I found. So - clearly a broken and stupid bot, right? Rather than
being specifically malicious. I think so, but I host these sites on a rural
consumer line and it was affecting both system load and bandwidth. What I did
wrong: 1. In docker, I tried quite a few things to block the user agent, the
country (US based AWS, and this is a UK regional site), various IPs. It took me
far too long to realise why my changes to .htaccess were failing - the phpbb
docker image I use mounts the root directory to the website internally, ignoring
my mounted vol. (My own fault, it was too long since I set it up to remember
only certain sub-dirs were mounted in)
2. Figuring that out, I shelled into the container and edited that .htaccess,
but wouldn’t have survived restarting/rebuilding the container so wasn’t a real
solution. Whilst I was in there, I created a robots.txt file. Not surprisingly,
claudebot doesn’t actually honour whats in there, and still continues to request
it ten times a second. 3. Thinking there must be another way, I switched to
Haproxy. This was much easier - the documentation is very good. And it actually
worked - blocking by Useragent (and yep, I’m lucky this wasn’t changing) worked
perfectly. I then had to leave for a while and the graphs show it’s working.
(Yellow above the line is requests coming into haproxy, below the line are
responses).
[https://lemmy.ml/pictrs/image/2bc99426-0356-4010-a0e5-f7b8dbfeb14a.png] Great -
except I’m still seeing half of the traffic, and that’s affecting my latency.
(Some of you might doubt this, and I can tell you that you’re spoiled by an
excess of bandwidth…) 4. That’s when the penny dropped and the obvious occured.
I use cloudflare, so use their firewall, right? No excuses - I should have gone
there first. In fact, I did, but I got distracted by the many options and
focused on their bot fighting tools, which didn’t work for me. (This bot is
somehow getting through the captcha challenge even when bot fight mode is
enabled) But, their firewall has an option for user agent. The actual fix was
simply to add this in WAF for that domain.
[https://lemmy.ml/pictrs/image/98041b82-de04-4cdc-bfb1-05f4e5656903.png] And
voila - no more traffic through the tunnel for this very rude and stupid bot.
After 24 hours, Cloudflare has blocked almost a quarter of a million requests by
claudebot to my little phpbb forum which barely gets a single post every three
months.
[https://lemmy.ml/pictrs/image/f3170d6c-fec1-4820-9fbb-b54b14db46f8.png] Moral
for myself: Stand back and think for a minute before rushing in and trying to
fix something in the wrong way. I’ve also taken this as an opportunity to
improve haproxy’s rate limiting internally. Like most website hosts, most of my
traffic is outbound, and slowing things down when it gets busy really does help.
This obviously isn’t a perfect solution - all claudebot has to do is change its
UA, and by coming from AWS it’s pretty hard to block otherwise. One hopes it
isn’t truly malicious. It would be quite a lot more work to integrate Fail2ban
for more bots, but it might yet come to that. Also, if you write any kind of web
bot, please consider that not everyone who hosts a website has a lot of
bandwidth, and at least have enough pride to write software good enough to not
keep doing the same thing every second. And, y’know, keep an eye on what your
stuff is doing out on the internet - not least for your own benefit. Hopefully
AWS really shaft claudebot’s owners with some big bandwidth charges… EDIT: It
came back the next day with a new UA, and an email address linking it to
anthropic.com [http://anthropic.com] - the Claude3 AI bot, so it looks like a
particularly badly written scraper for AI learning.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lemmy.ml/post/14612626</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIFs are a flat circle</title>
      <link>https://rhizome.org/editorial/GIFs-are-a-flat-circle/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (by 
Kayla Drzewicki,)</author>
      <guid>https://rhizome.org/editorial/GIFs-are-a-flat-circle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stateful Migrations using Mutations</title>
      <link>https://stack.convex.dev/migrating-data-with-mutations</link>
      <description>Online migrations in Convex using mutations. Including a helper to track migration state!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stack.convex.dev/migrating-data-with-mutations</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS Certification - I should be exempt</title>
      <link>https://cestlaz.github.io/post/i-should-be-exempt/</link>
      <description>Over the past few years, a number of states have acknowledged Computer Science as an academic area of study and have created pathways for certification. The actual requirements vary from state to state and indeed, even within a given state, there&amp;#39;s a lot of variation. Here in New York, for instance there are some strong programs that will truly prepare a candidate to teach CS in K12 but too many others that are just &amp;quot;certificate mills&amp;quot; and the state doesn&amp;#39;t seem to care.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cestlaz.github.io/post/i-should-be-exempt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Ordinary Blogs Usually Suck</title>
      <link>https://www.sungho.blog/p/why-ordinary-blogs-usually-suck</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Sungho Yahng)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sungho.blog/p/why-ordinary-blogs-usually-suck</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Optimal Workspace</title>
      <link>https://elijahpotter.dev/articles/the_optimal_workspace</link>
      <description>How I intend on living better.</description>
      <author> (Elijah Potter)</author>
      <guid>https://elijahpotter.dev/articles/the_optimal_workspace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>do tiny projects expecting them to fail</title>
      <link>https://gueejla.com/do-tiny-projects-expecting-them-to-fail/</link>
      <description>My goal

I will do tiny projects expecting them to fail.

I will post updates (sometimes here, sometimes on my youtube) on what I did, how it failed, and what I learned.

Rinse and repeat.

If you find this framing helpful or have suggestions, feel free to comment or reach</description>
      <author> (Greg)</author>
      <guid>https://gueejla.com/do-tiny-projects-expecting-them-to-fail/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iDOS 3 waiting for review</title>
      <link>https://litchie.com/2024/04/new-hope#disqus_thread?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</link>
      <description>April 14, 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://litchie.com/2024/04/new-hope#disqus_thread?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLVM is Smarter Than Me</title>
      <link>https://blog.sulami.xyz/posts/llvm-is-smarter-than-me/</link>
      <description>Weak Opinions, Strongly Held</description>
      <author> (Robin Schroer)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sulami.xyz/posts/llvm-is-smarter-than-me/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do electronic passports work? | Burak Can&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.burakcankus.com/2024/04/18/how-do-electronic-passports-work.html</link>
      <description>I explain how electronic passports (eMRTDs) work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.burakcankus.com/2024/04/18/how-do-electronic-passports-work.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Terry A. Davis</title>
      <link>https://schizophrenic.io/blog/on-terry-a-davis</link>
      <description>As someone formally diagnosed with schizophrenia who happens to be a
programmer, I often get questions such as,</description>
      <author> (Daniel Jaouen)</author>
      <guid>https://schizophrenic.io/blog/on-terry-a-davis</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quill - Your powerful rich text editor</title>
      <link>https://quilljs.com/</link>
      <description>Quill is a free, open source WYSIWYG editor built for the modern web. Completely customize it for any need with its modular architecture and expressive API.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://quilljs.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 03:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Distributed Tracing With OpenTelemetry in .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/introduction-to-distributed-tracing-with-opentelemetry-in-dotnet</link>
      <description>Distributed systems offer flexibility but introduce complexity, making troubleshooting a headache. Understanding how requests flow through your system is crucial for debugging and performance optimization. OpenTelemetry is an open-source observability framework that makes this possible.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/introduction-to-distributed-tracing-with-opentelemetry-in-dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 01:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>