<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Distributed ETL Pipeline Using Bacalhau and MongoDB Atlas</title>
      <link>https://blog.bacalhau.org/p/building-a-distributed-etl-pipeline</link>
      <description>(1:35)</description>
      <author> (Sean M. Tracey)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.bacalhau.org/p/building-a-distributed-etl-pipeline</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Essence of Lagrange Multipliers</title>
      <link>https://alexkritchevsky.com/2024/06/10/lagrange-multipliers.html</link>
      <description>In which we attempt to better understand the classic multivariable calculus optimization problem.</description>
      <author> (Alex Kritchevsky)</author>
      <guid>https://alexkritchevsky.com/2024/06/10/lagrange-multipliers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neatnik Notes &amp;#183; Gotta block ’em all</title>
      <link>https://notes.neatnik.net/2024/06/gotta-block-em-all</link>
      <description>Neatnik Notes</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.neatnik.net/2024/06/gotta-block-em-all</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Crimes at Lambda School</title>
      <link>https://www.sandofsky.com/lambda-school/</link>
      <description>Two days after his company&amp;#39;s downfall, Austen Allred wrote:

I wish people could see how ugly it is to be envious, and how obvious it is to those around you when that&amp;#39;s what&amp;#39;s happening.

There&amp;#39;s no much uglier than trying to tear someone down because they achieved what you wish</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sandofsky.com/lambda-school/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Introduction to Metathics</title>
      <link>https://www.ahalbert.com/reviews/2024/05/20/metaethics.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ahalbert.com/reviews/2024/05/20/metaethics.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>April is the Cruelest Month</title>
      <link>https://kmalexander.com/2024/06/17/april-is-the-cruelest-month/</link>
      <description>This has been a difficult post to write. I’ve written and rewritten it over the last few weeks, but I never liked how it came out. This is an attempt to correct that. It is always challenging…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kmalexander.com/2024/06/17/april-is-the-cruelest-month/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managers Should Focus More On Setting Expectations</title>
      <link>https://shamun.dev/posts/setting-expectations</link>
      <description>My tales as a technical founder, manager, and software engineer.</description>
      <author> (Ido Shamun)</author>
      <guid>https://shamun.dev/posts/setting-expectations</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&amp;#39;s OK to repeat yourself on the internet</title>
      <link>https://www.markozivanovic.com/its-ok-to-repeat-yourself-on-the-internet/</link>
      <description>I was talking recently with two fellow engineers who are actively writing on their blogs and occasionally on social media.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.markozivanovic.com/its-ok-to-repeat-yourself-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>wtb: Progressive SPAs</title>
      <link>https://cra.mr/wtb-progressive-spas/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been using React a long time at this point, and it&amp;#39;s by far my favorite approach to building a UI - interactive or not. Most of that time has been spent at Sentry, but whenever I start a new project, I still reach for React. I want to talk a little about what I&amp;#39;d love to see the React ecosystem adopt, and where I see some of the gaps with approaches today, particularly around the slow evolution of Single Page Applications.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cra.mr/wtb-progressive-spas/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lemmy and my Switch to PieFed; Threadyverse software alternatives</title>
      <link>https://jeena.net/lemmy-switch-to-piefed</link>
      <description>The main reason was Lemmy hogging server resources</description>
      <author> (Jeena)</author>
      <guid>https://jeena.net/lemmy-switch-to-piefed</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac external displays for designers and developers, part 2</title>
      <link>https://bjango.com/articles/macexternaldisplays2/</link>
      <description>Since writing about Mac external displays in 2016, not much has changed. LG, Dell, Samsung, and other display makers have either never catered for the specs many Mac designers and developers want, or they’ve reluctantly produced products that have been short-lived or compromised.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bjango.com/articles/macexternaldisplays2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>listening to your friends&amp;#39; jams with last.fm</title>
      <link>https://rjbs.cloud/blog/2024/06/lastfm-friendo/</link>
      <description>Quite a while ago, I wrote some Spotify code that would find places when my Discover Weekly playlist would intersect with those of my friends and coworkers. This was fun. Every once in a while, I talked about other things that might be fun, along those lines. I tend not to do too much with those ideas, because the Spotify API is often missing exactly the method I want, and I can work around it, but it becomes too much of a pain. Also, I’m a little lazy when the project will need other people to be interested, unless I’m sure they will be. Who wants to launch a flop to their friends?</description>
      <author> (Ricardo Signes)</author>
      <guid>https://rjbs.cloud/blog/2024/06/lastfm-friendo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comments on Scripting, CGI, and FastCGI</title>
      <link>https://www.oilshell.org/blog/2024/06/cgi.html</link>
      <description>|
blog | oilshell.org</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.oilshell.org/blog/2024/06/cgi.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grow a Pair</title>
      <link>https://codingcraftsman.wordpress.com/2024/06/17/grow-a-pair/</link>
      <description>I recently needed to merge a code change. I wasn’t a code owner of the specific repo, so I put my merge request in front of the code owners. It was a small lexical change, based on the curren…</description>
      <author> (ashleyfrieze)</author>
      <guid>https://codingcraftsman.wordpress.com/2024/06/17/grow-a-pair/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimize all windows on Mac OS
</title>
      <link>https://hartenfeller.dev/blog/mac-minimize-all-windows</link>
      <description>AppleScript to quickly minimize every window on my macOS. This is not hiding the windows, but minimizing them on the dock.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hartenfeller.dev/blog/mac-minimize-all-windows</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack the Hacker - How to Setup an SSH Honeypot</title>
      <link>https://blog.sofiane.cc/setup_ssh_honeypot/</link>
      <description>What’s a Honeypot :A honeypot detects and records attacks when an attacker tries to break into a system. The honeypot we will discuss here is an SSH honeypot. PrephaseThis article comes after the one</description>
      <author> (Sofiane Hamlaoui)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sofiane.cc/setup_ssh_honeypot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing A Run Book Can Be Your First Iterative Step</title>
      <link>https://shermanonsoftware.com/2024/06/17/writing-a-run-book-can-be-your-first-iterative-step/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (jeffpsherman)</author>
      <guid>https://shermanonsoftware.com/2024/06/17/writing-a-run-book-can-be-your-first-iterative-step/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Inspection</title>
      <link>https://danshiebler.com/2024-06-17-inspection-strategy/</link>
      <description>The CEO needs to increase company margins. He turns to the engineering leadership team to help. Engineering leadership puts together a sound plan. First the objective to “Increase Company Margins” is decomposed into a collection of eng-level goals like “Reduce Tier 2 Support Hours”. Each of these eng-level goals decompose...</description>
      <author> (Dan Shiebler)</author>
      <guid>https://danshiebler.com/2024-06-17-inspection-strategy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The case for criminalizing scientific misconduct &amp;#183; Chris Said</title>
      <link>https://chris-said.io/2024/06/17/the-case-for-criminalizing-scientific-misconduct/</link>
      <description>For a crime that could cost millions of lives, universities have failed to police themselves</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chris-said.io/2024/06/17/the-case-for-criminalizing-scientific-misconduct/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential, open source Mac apps</title>
      <link>https://ivdl.co.za/2024/06/17/essential-mac-apps/</link>
      <description>These are the apps I install on every new Mac, and this post serves as my personal reference list (as with many other posts on this blog). It&amp;#39;s likely that Rectangle will be replaced by the built-in window tiling functionality in the upcoming Sequoia release, but for now it remains indispensable. Al</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ivdl.co.za/2024/06/17/essential-mac-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There&amp;#39;s something rotten in the kingdom of Wordpress</title>
      <link>https://www.baldurbjarnason.com/2024/rotten-wordpress/</link>
      <description>Like many in web development, Wordpress has been a semi-regular feature in my professional life and, for most of it, my impression was that it suffered from the usual infighting and mismanagement you see in free or open source software, but that it was otherwise as well run as you could expect of a long-running project built on layers and layers of legacy code.</description>
      <author> (Baldur Bjarnason)</author>
      <guid>https://www.baldurbjarnason.com/2024/rotten-wordpress/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python: 10 cool tricks with the * operator</title>
      <link>https://lucasoshiro.github.io/posts-en/2024-05-11-splat-operator/</link>
      <description>Expanding args are more useful than you think!</description>
      <author> (Lucas Seiki Oshiro)</author>
      <guid>https://lucasoshiro.github.io/posts-en/2024-05-11-splat-operator/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Experience With LineageOS</title>
      <link>https://jadenarceneaux.com/posts/lineageos/</link>
      <description>Don’t take this post seriously, this is just me being goofy and having fun.
Some Background Recently, I embarked on a mini project. It started with my boss giving me her old OnePlus 8. Conveniently, the very next day the battery in my iPhone 11 Pro Max decided it wanted to see the world and pushed the screen off my phone. This meant that for the next two days, I got to become an Android user for the first time in almost 10 years.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jadenarceneaux.com/posts/lineageos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latency, Tail Latency and Response time in distributed systems</title>
      <link>https://andrewpakhomov.com/posts/latency-tail-latency-and-response-time-in-distributed-systems/</link>
      <description>Response time is a metric that shows how fast software responds. This is the time between request was sent and the time response was received.
The questions arise right from the start: a sorting of 100 000 elements naturally requires more time than of 100.
How to measure a system response time in this case?
It’s natural to agree on some standard fixed request and perform a load test: send a lot of such standards requests
and measure response time.
The distribution of the response time we receive at the end of the performance test usually resembles a Log Normal distribution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewpakhomov.com/posts/latency-tail-latency-and-response-time-in-distributed-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of Rats and Ratchets</title>
      <link>https://matklad.github.io/2024/01/03/of-rats-and-ratchets.html</link>
      <description>This is going to be related to software engineering, pinky promise!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matklad.github.io/2024/01/03/of-rats-and-ratchets.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCTS and LLMs: what&amp;#39;s the big deal?</title>
      <link>https://www.seangoedecke.com/mcts-and-llms/</link>
      <description>Why people are excited about Monte Carlo tree search and language models</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.seangoedecke.com/mcts-and-llms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Vision For Roadway Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://blog.davidsint.com/vision-for-roads/</link>
      <description>Explore the future of roadway infrastructure, envisioning smarter and safer roads as well as more efficient and pleasurable driving experiences for all.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.davidsint.com/vision-for-roads/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Friends</title>
      <link>http://talhaashraf.com/making-friends.html</link>
      <description>There&amp;#39;s a pattern for people who want to make friends but are unable to. The thing they have in common is they have unusual views on a lot of mainstream things and therefore don&amp;#39;t talk about them. The problem with having unusual views is that people think you&amp;#39;re trying to be cool. But that&amp;#39;s not it. If you say that you don&amp;#39;t like rice, it&amp;#39;s because you don&amp;#39;t like them. And any food conversation would obviously have to involve this disclosure to have some context of what you do like. 

This is one of the things that makes unusual people introverts. They often fail to relate with what people are saying and therefore find it impossible to share what they themselves are thinking.

And the unusual views make it seem like you&amp;#39;re trying to look for attention. But you&amp;#39;re not. For you, the unusual view is like saying that you have tea 3 times a day. It&amp;#39;s just something basic about you.

That&amp;#39;s also why people with unusual views tend to talk less. Because the less they talk the less likely they are to say something that would make them appear unusual.

But this has a major downside. People that have unusual views are already very unlikely to find people like themselves. And when they don&amp;#39;t even talk about their unusual views, it is almost impossible to find similar people they might make great friends with.

So to make friends or to find people like yourself, you need to do the counterintuitive thing and talk about yourself. I&amp;#39;ve been unintentionally doing this for a while and I&amp;#39;ve found people like me who&amp;#39;ve read hundreds of books, who like stupid puns, who don&amp;#39;t plan on having kids, who get extremely obsessed about things.

P.S. Ironically, after writing this down, I thought about not sharing it fearing it may seem unusual because most people don&amp;#39;t have trouble making friends.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://talhaashraf.com/making-friends.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy and security improvements in .NET modernization tooling - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-modernization-privacy-security-improvements/</link>
      <description>Learn about the latest privacy and security-related updates to Azure Migrate application and code assessment and .NET Upgrade Assistant.</description>
      <author> (Mike Rousos)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-modernization-privacy-security-improvements/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing a new RISC-V Mainboard from DeepComputing</title>
      <link>https://frame.work/blog/introducing-a-new-risc-v-mainboard-from-deepcomputing</link>
      <description>We’re excited to share a preview of a Framework Laptop 13 Mainboard with a new CPU architecture.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://frame.work/blog/introducing-a-new-risc-v-mainboard-from-deepcomputing</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The time smart quotes prevented the entire Office division from committing code - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240618-00/?p=109910</link>
      <description>Breaking your tools with your tools.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240618-00/?p=109910</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Scarecrow</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberscarecrow.com/</link>
      <description>An app for scaring away malware</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cyberscarecrow.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat Control Must Be Stopped – Now!</title>
      <link>https://threema.ch/en/blog/posts/stop-chat-control</link>
      <description>With its legislative proposal known as “Chat Control,” the EU Commission is trying to establish an unprecedented mass-surveillance apparatus of Orwellian proportions in the European Union. If EU citizens don’t stand up for privacy now, it may be too late.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://threema.ch/en/blog/posts/stop-chat-control</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat control: incompatible with fundamental rights</title>
      <link>https://freiheitsrechte.org/en/themen/digitale-grundrechte/chatkontrolle</link>
      <description>The EU Commission has presented a draft regulation that is to lay down rules for preventing and combating sexual violence against children (Chat Control Regulation). The planned regulation raises such significant fundamental rights concerns that the GFF is joining the debate while the draft is still being deliberated at EU level. The most important points of criticism at a glance.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://freiheitsrechte.org/en/themen/digitale-grundrechte/chatkontrolle</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiently Handling Stored Procedures in EFCore: Practical Solutions</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/efficiently-handling-stored-procedures-efcore-practical-solutions/</link>
      <description>Discover proven strategies and practical solutions for efficiently handling stored procedures in Entity Framework Core (EFCore) and optimize your database interactions.</description>
      <author> (Pierre Belin)</author>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/efficiently-handling-stored-procedures-efcore-practical-solutions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 09:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting 50% (SoTA) on ARC-AGI with GPT-4o</title>
      <link>https://redwoodresearch.substack.com/p/getting-50-sota-on-arc-agi-with-gpt</link>
      <description>You can just draw more samples</description>
      <author> (Ryan Greenblatt)</author>
      <guid>https://redwoodresearch.substack.com/p/getting-50-sota-on-arc-agi-with-gpt</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 09:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;Secret&amp;quot; elmah.io features #5 - Breadcrumbs leading up to errors</title>
      <link>https://blog.elmah.io/secret-elmah-io-features-5-breadcrumbs-leading-up-to-errors/</link>
      <description>This post introduces the breadcrumbs feature available on elmah.io. Get help debugging errors by seeing the history leading up to the exception.</description>
      <author> (Written by Thomas Ardal, June 18, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.elmah.io/secret-elmah-io-features-5-breadcrumbs-leading-up-to-errors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 09:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting up NGINX load balancer for .NET WebApi - Event-Driven.io</title>
      <link>https://event-driven.io/en/setting_up_nginx_with_aspnet/</link>
      <description>Event-Driven by Oskar Dudycz</description>
      <author> (Oskar Dudycz)</author>
      <guid>https://event-driven.io/en/setting_up_nginx_with_aspnet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Checks in Your OpenAPI Specs
</title>
      <link>https://wildermuth.com/2024/06/17/health-checks-in-your-open-api/</link>
      <description>Adding health checks to your ASP.NET Core projects is simple and easy, but how do you get them exposed in your OpenAPI specification? Let me show you how!
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wildermuth.com/2024/06/17/health-checks-in-your-open-api/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to achieve high HTTP scale with Azure Functions Flex Consumption</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-achieve-high-http-scale-with-azure-functions-flex/ba-p/4169736</link>
      <description>Taking Azure Functions from 0 to 32,000 RPS in 7 seconds&amp;#160;</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/342148)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/how-to-achieve-high-http-scale-with-azure-functions-flex/ba-p/4169736</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Logging Guide Part 1: Basic&amp;#160;Concepts and Importance - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/devops/containers-and-virtualization/docker-logging-guide-part-1-basic-concepts-and-importance/</link>
      <description>Docker&amp;#160;has gained popularity as a containerization platform that allows you to develop, deploy, and execute applications faster. It packages applications</description>
      <author> (Bravin Wasike)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/devops/containers-and-virtualization/docker-logging-guide-part-1-basic-concepts-and-importance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Arm development ecosystem is ready</title>
      <link>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/the-arm-development-ecosystem-is-ready</link>
      <description>I have been keeping a close eye on the Arm software and hardware ecosystem for ...</description>
      <author> (Mark Downie)</author>
      <guid>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/the-arm-development-ecosystem-is-ready</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process Monitor v4.0 and Sysmon 1.3.3 for Linux</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sysinternals-blog/process-monitor-v4-0-and-sysmon-1-3-3-for-linux/ba-p/4169957</link>
      <description>
Learn about the latest updates to Process Monitor v4.0 and Sysmon 1.3.3 for Linux
</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/776036)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sysinternals-blog/process-monitor-v4-0-and-sysmon-1-3-3-for-linux/ba-p/4169957</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Basics: Screen Recording in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/beyond-basics-screen-recording-net-maui</link>
      <description>Let’s learn how to use the ScreenRecording plugin created by Gerald Versluis in a .NET MAUI application (available for Android, iOS and macOS).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/beyond-basics-screen-recording-net-maui</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding open source LLMs</title>
      <link>https://thoughtbot.com/blog/understanding-open-source-llms</link>
      <description>Do you think you can run any Large Language Model (LLM) on your machine?</description>
      <author> (Rakesh Arunachalam

        
          June 17, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://thoughtbot.com/blog/understanding-open-source-llms</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A failed attempt at priority collection with inheritance</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/06/17/a-failed-attempt-at-priority-collection-with-inheritance/</link>
      <description>An instructive dead end.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/06/17/a-failed-attempt-at-priority-collection-with-inheritance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - nicanorflavier/spf-dkim-dmarc-simplified: Email security is a key part of internet communication. But what are SPF, DKIM, and DMARC, and how do they work? This guide will explain it all in simple terms to make these concepts clearer.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/nicanorflavier/spf-dkim-dmarc-simplified</link>
      <description>Email security is a key part of internet communication. But what are SPF, DKIM, and DMARC, and how do they work? This guide will explain it all in simple terms to make these concepts clearer. - nic...</description>
      <author> (nicanorflavier)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/nicanorflavier/spf-dkim-dmarc-simplified</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 05:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pascal&amp;#39;s Wager Triangle</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2947/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2947/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>