<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How to live an intellectually rich life</title>
      <link>https://utsavmamoria.substack.com/p/how-to-live-an-intellectually-rich</link>
      <description>.. and how living one is easier than you think</description>
      <guid>https://utsavmamoria.substack.com/p/how-to-live-an-intellectually-rich</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 17:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporation for Public Broadcasting Statement Regarding Executive Order on Public Media</title>
      <link>https://cpb.org/pressroom/Corporation-Public-Broadcasting-Statement-Regarding-Executive-Order-Public-Media</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON, D.C, (May 2, 2025) — Patricia Harrison, President and CEO of the Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB), issued the following statement today regarding the President’s Executive Order on public media: “CPB is not a federal executive agency subject to the President’s authority. Congress directly authorized and funded CPB to be a private nonprofit corporation wholly independent of the federal government.</description>
      <guid>https://cpb.org/pressroom/Corporation-Public-Broadcasting-Statement-Regarding-Executive-Order-Public-Media</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 15:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does This Senior Engineer Mobile Developer's Resume Make The Cut?!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=GOsOVchWY00</link>
      <description>This senior software engineer has a ton of experience in mobile app development! Senior engineer, team lead, and even founder!

But... Does their resume showcase all of their great work as a mobile dev?

Let's find out in this resume review!

----
Want a chance to have your resume reviewed? Submit it to resumes [at] devleader [dot] ca!
----
🔑 Membership &amp; Subscriptions:
- 📨 Weekly Newsletter: https://weekly.devleader.ca
- 🏘️ Private Discord Community: https://sidestack.io/devleader

🧠 Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Get Promoted As A Software Engineer: https://dometrain.com/course/career-getting-promoted-as-a-software-engineer/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?ref=nick-cosentino
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

🗣️ Social Media &amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs:  @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp; Products/Services That I Love:
- @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper Opus Clip: https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----

#softwareengineering #softwaredeveloper #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=GOsOVchWY00</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Fixed My Slow App Using Sentry Trace Explorer!!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=U4BkIfj_CYw</link>
      <description>Try out Sentry Tracing free for your application, and get 3 months free: https://dub.sh/sentry-milan
Get the source code for this video for FREE → https://the-dotnet-weekly.kit.com/sentry

Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt

In this video, you'll learn how to integrate Sentry with your ASP.NET Core microservices to gain full visibility into distributed systems. We'll walk through configuring the Sentry SDK using OpenTelemetry, setting up tracing, and solving real-world observability challenges like performance bottlenecks, error propagation, and black box communication between services.

📌 What you'll learn:

- How to configure Sentry in .NET using Sentry.AspNetCore and Sentry.OpenTelemetry
- How to trace requests across microservices using Sentry’s Trace Explorer
- How to debug N+1 problems and API slowdowns using distributed traces
- How to investigate exceptions and trace them across services
- How to use telemetry data to validate fixes in production

We’ll walk through a real eShop microservices system involving an order flow, product validation, and background processing. You'll see how Sentry can pinpoint issues like slow API calls and trace failures back to their root cause—even across asynchronous service boundaries.

🎯 Want to follow along?

Grab free access to Sentry and download the source code using the link in the pinned comment.

Learn more:
- Sentry with ASP.NET Core: https://docs.sentry.io/platforms/dotnet/guides/aspnetcore/?utm_source=milanjovanovic&amp;utm_medium=paid-community&amp;utm_campaign=tracing-fy26q2-traceexplorer&amp;utm_content=video-dotnettracing-learnmore
- Sentry monitoring: https://sentry.io/signup/?utm_source=milanjovanovic&amp;utm_medium=paid-community&amp;utm_campaign=tracing-fy26q2-traceexplorer&amp;utm_content=video-dotnettracing-learnmore</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=U4BkIfj_CYw</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Day Anubis Saved Our Websites From a DDoS Attack</title>
      <link>https://fabulous.systems/posts/2025/05/anubis-saved-our-websites-from-a-ddos-attack/</link>
      <description>Anubis, designed to protect your website from unwanted requests from AI crawlers, is way more powerful than you might think.</description>
      <guid>https://fabulous.systems/posts/2025/05/anubis-saved-our-websites-from-a-ddos-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABP — SaaS Module</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=6Tp2E6M159c</link>
      <description>Tired of building SaaS infrastructure from scratch? Watch our video on how the ABP SaaS module handles the core SaaS functionality for you. Save time, scale faster!

Module: https://abp.io/modules/Volo.SaaS
Website: https://abp.io

#abp #abpmodules #abpframework #saas</description>
      <author> (Volosoft)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=6Tp2E6M159c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Study: Waymo is reducing serious crashes and making streets safer for those most at risk</title>
      <link>https://waymo.com/blog/2025/05/waymo-making-streets-safer-for-vru</link>
      <description>The path to Vision Zero requires reducing severe crashes and improving the safety of those most at risk. Our latest research paper shows that the Waymo Driver is making significant strides in both areas. By reducing the most dangerous crashes and providing better protection for pedestrians, cyclists, and other vulnerable road users, Waymo is making streets safer in cities where it operates.</description>
      <guid>https://waymo.com/blog/2025/05/waymo-making-streets-safer-for-vru</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Peppers Unleashes Code Chaos: How .NET Meets the NES</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EyACUmH8AH4</link>
      <description>RJJ Software's Software Development Service This episode of The Modern .NET Show is supported, in part, by RJJ Software's Podcasting Services, whether your company is looking to elevate its UK operations or reshape its US strategy, we can provide tailored solutions that exceed expectations.

 Show Notes "When you program for the NES you deeply need to understand the hardware, right. And that's not a thing; like as a .NET developer you don't really know what a register is, or like or a bus, or like NES has a thing called a PPU"— Jonathan Peppers

 Welcome friends to The Modern .NET Show; the premier .NET podcast, focusing entirely on the knowledge, tools, and frameworks that all .NET developers should have in their toolbox. We are the go-to podcast for .NET developers worldwide, and I am your host: Jamie "GaProgMan" Taylor.

 In this episode, Jonathan Peppers joins us to talk about something which is a little out of the ordinary for us here: programming the Nintendo Entertainment System but in C#. We talk about the process behind his (some would say absurd) idea for an AOT transpiler which can convert a subset of C# over to the Assembler required to write and publish a NES game.

 "So you think about that example, what I described there on the NES side is actually very similar to what's on the IL side, is that in IL, you have a string, right? It goes and looks up in a string table, the contents of the string, and puts it on a stack, and then it calls vram_write, and then it's the runtimes job to actually like make that happen at runtime; or in the case of an AOT compiler it would emit, you know, native machine code that does the same thing."— Jonathan Peppers

 Along the way, we talk about that Ahead-of-Time compilation is, have a brief intro to what IL is (that's what your C# code is compiled to before running it), and how all of that fits in with .NES—the wonderful name for Jon's AOT NES compiler.

 Anyway, without further ado, let's sit back, open up a terminal, type in `dotnet new podcast` and we'll dive into the core of Modern .NET.

 Supporting the Show If you find this episode useful in any way, please consider supporting the show by either leaving a review (check our review page for ways to do that), sharing the episode with a friend or colleague, buying the host a coffee, or considering becoming a Patron of the show.

 Full Show Notes The full show notes, including links to some of the things we discussed and a full transcription of this episode, can be found at:  https://dotnetcore.show/season-7/jonathan-peppers-unleashes-code-chaos-how-dotnet-meets-the-nes/

 Links:   Native AOT Development  System.Reflection.Metadata 8bitworkshop.com neslib  BinaryWriter Retron5 Flight68k .NES on GitHub .NES Discord Server  Supporting the show:  Leave a rating or review Buy the show a coffee Become a patron  Getting in Touch:  Via the contact page Joining the Discord  Remember to rate and review the show on  Apple Podcasts, Podchaser, or wherever you find your podcasts, this will help the show's audience grow. Or you can just share the show with a friend.

 And don't forget to reach out via our Contact page. We're very interested in your opinion of the show, so please get in touch.

 You can support the show by making a monthly donation on the show's Patreon page at: https://www.patreon.com/TheDotNetCorePodcast.

 Music created by Mono Memory Music, licensed to RJJ Software for use in The Modern .NET Show</description>
      <author> (Jamie Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EyACUmH8AH4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Waltz Accidentally Reveals Obscure App the Government Is Using to Archive Signal Messages</title>
      <link>https://www.404media.co/mike-waltz-accidentally-reveals-obscure-app-the-government-is-using-to-archive-signal-messages/</link>
      <description>A photograph of Trump administration official Mike Waltz's phone shows him using an unofficial version of Signal designed to archive messages during a cabinet meeting.</description>
      <guid>https://www.404media.co/mike-waltz-accidentally-reveals-obscure-app-the-government-is-using-to-archive-signal-messages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third Party Cookies Must Be Removed</title>
      <link>https://w3ctag.github.io/web-without-3p-cookies/</link>
      <description>Third-party (AKA cross-site) cookies are harmful to the web, and must be removed from the web platform. This finding explains why they must be removed, and examines the challenges in removing them. We highlight some use cases that depend on third-party cookies and offer some examples of designed-for-purpose technologies that can replace them. Specification authors are expected to ensure they do not undermine the benefits of removing third-party cookies when proposing new web platform technologies.</description>
      <guid>https://w3ctag.github.io/web-without-3p-cookies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“The Gang has a Mid-Life Crisis”</title>
      <link>https://chris-martin.org/2025/the-gang-has-a-mid-life-crisis</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://chris-martin.org/2025/the-gang-has-a-mid-life-crisis</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When You Get to Be Smart Writing a Macro</title>
      <link>https://tonsky.me/blog/hashp/</link>
      <description>A story of writing Clojure’s println alternative that works inside threading-first/last macros</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/nikitonsky)</author>
      <guid>https://tonsky.me/blog/hashp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to ship 10x faster.</title>
      <link>https://benspring.com/p/how-to-ship-10x-faster</link>
      <description>For founders, leaders and PMs who want to supercharge product development</description>
      <guid>https://benspring.com/p/how-to-ship-10x-faster</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My journey from sales-led to product-led entrepreneurship</title>
      <link>https://www.dvg.blog/p/my-journey-from-sales-led-to-product</link>
      <description>... and what I wish I had known before transitioning</description>
      <guid>https://www.dvg.blog/p/my-journey-from-sales-led-to-product</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I’m getting off US tech</title>
      <link>https://www.disconnect.blog/p/why-im-getting-off-us-tech</link>
      <description>At least as much as feasibly possible</description>
      <guid>https://www.disconnect.blog/p/why-im-getting-off-us-tech</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompting != Learning ‣ Gustavo Veloso | My Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://blog.gjmveloso.dev/posts/2025/05/01/prompting-is-not-learning/</link>
      <description>gjmveloso's personal blog. The opinions expressed here are my own and do not necessarily represent those of current or past employers.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.gjmveloso.dev/posts/2025/05/01/prompting-is-not-learning/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elm test distributions</title>
      <link>https://martin.janiczek.cz/2025/05/01/elm-test-distributions.html</link>
      <description>…in which I’ll tell you how you can make sure your property based tests are testing the interesting cases.</description>
      <guid>https://martin.janiczek.cz/2025/05/01/elm-test-distributions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charity Bragging Page</title>
      <link>https://jakub.jankiewicz.org/blog/charity-bragging-page/</link>
      <description>In this article, I will show you 4 resources which will help you learn design as a web developer.</description>
      <guid>https://jakub.jankiewicz.org/blog/charity-bragging-page/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the pay-once business model saved my *aaS</title>
      <link>https://kyrylo.org/software/2025/05/01/how-the-pay-once-business-model-saved-my-aas.html</link>
      <description>Yesterday, I launched Telebugs.</description>
      <guid>https://kyrylo.org/software/2025/05/01/how-the-pay-once-business-model-saved-my-aas.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-Powered Search: o4-mini-high vs o3 vs Deep Research | alexop.dev</title>
      <link>https://alexop.dev/posts/llm-powered-search-comparison-o4-mini-high-o3-deep-research/</link>
      <description>A practical benchmark of three OpenAI models—o4-mini-high, o3, and Deep Research—for LLM-powered search. Compare their speed, depth, accuracy, citations, and cost when tackling real research questions like 'How does Vercel use Speakeasy for API testing?Ideal for developers exploring AI-assisted technical research</description>
      <guid>https://alexop.dev/posts/llm-powered-search-comparison-o4-mini-high-o3-deep-research/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making of Monkeys.zip (PART ONE)</title>
      <link>https://www.lukeschaefer.dev/posts/making-of-monkeys/</link>
      <description>How monkeys.zip was built</description>
      <author> (Luke Schaefer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.lukeschaefer.dev/posts/making-of-monkeys/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fare thee well Shopify</title>
      <link>https://lbjgruppen.com/en/posts/fare-thee-well-shopify</link>
      <description>Twice in my professional carreer, have I had the opportunity to deal with Shopify and twice I've opted to quit the platform fairly quickly.</description>
      <guid>https://lbjgruppen.com/en/posts/fare-thee-well-shopify</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing FEEN: A Simple, Canonical Notation for Board Positions</title>
      <link>https://blog.cyril.email/posts/2025-05-01/introducing-feen-notation.html</link>
      <description>FEEN: A minimalistic, rule-agnostic format for representing board positions in chess variants and other board games, designed for canonicity and flexibility.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.cyril.email/posts/2025-05-01/introducing-feen-notation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i will cheerlead the fuck out of your project for a 0.1% equity stake</title>
      <link>https://blog.greg.technology/2025/04/29/i-will-cheerlead-the-fuck-out-of-your-project-for-a-0-1-equity-stake.html</link>
      <description>if you’re trying to finish a project and need moral &amp; emotional support over text and as many calls as you need, i will cheerlead the fuck out of your project for a 0.1% equity stake.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.greg.technology/2025/04/29/i-will-cheerlead-the-fuck-out-of-your-project-for-a-0-1-equity-stake.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I've learned from jj</title>
      <link>https://zerowidth.com/2025/what-ive-learned-from-jj/</link>
      <description>How Jujutsu's flexibility and safety changed my approach to version control</description>
      <guid>https://zerowidth.com/2025/what-ive-learned-from-jj/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude can now connect to your world</title>
      <link>https://www.anthropic.com/news/integrations</link>
      <description>Today we're announcing Integrations, a new way to connect your apps and tools to Claude. We're also expanding Claude's Research capabilities with an advanced mode that searches the web, your Google Workspace, and now your Integrations too.</description>
      <guid>https://www.anthropic.com/news/integrations</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enchanted by Desire &amp; Darklite</title>
      <link>https://www.pouet.net/prod.php?which=103924</link>
      <description>256b for MS-Dos, 2nd at Revision 2025</description>
      <guid>https://www.pouet.net/prod.php?which=103924</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 9 🔥🚀 : ASP.NET Core feature flags</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=t3LZxsXIONw</link>
      <description>In this video we will discussed how we can implement feature flags into our .NET Web API

Support me on Patreon to access the source code:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand

Base App: https://youtu.be/NNiupSwiVfg

Let us connect:
🌍  My website  - https://mohamadlawand.com
📸  Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/mohamadlawand087/
🐦  Twitter - https://twitter.com/moe23
♯     Github - https://github.com/mohamadlawand087
🎫 LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/mlawand
💥 LinkTree - https://linktr.ee/mohamadlawand
Discord - https://discord.gg/KEepAhxTeu

Gear I use  (affiliate link): https://amzn.to/3EbT8Jw

Support my work:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand
https://www.buymeacoffee.com/mohamadlawand

Hire Me:
https://transactions.sendowl.com/products/78999951/625477F1/view

WHO AM I:
I'm Mohamad, a Enterprise Architect working in Manchester, UK. I make videos about web, cloud, desktop and mobile development. 

GET IN TOUCH:
If you’d like to talk, I’d love to hear from you. Tweeting @moe23 directly will be the quickest way to get a response, but if your question is very long, feel free to email me at hello@mohamadlawand.com.

#dotnet   #api   #featureflags</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=t3LZxsXIONw</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>