<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>C# Interfaces With Default Method Implementations #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=I5XHHM_yHa0</link>
      <description>&amp;#128204; Check out my Pragmatic Clean Architecture course: https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/pragmatic-clean-architecture&amp;#128640; Join 770+ engineers in my  Patreon commun...</description>
      <author> (Learnit Training
  
  
  
    Learnit Training
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=I5XHHM_yHa0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500 Byte Images: The Haiku Vector Icon Format</title>
      <link>https://blog.leahhanson.us/post/recursecenter2016/haiku_icons.html</link>
      <description>Haiku uses a custom vector image format to store icons. This is surprising both because most OSes consider bitmaps to be totally sufficient to represent icons and because there are plenty of vector graphics formats out this (e.g. SVG). The goal of the Haiku Vector Icon Format (HVIF) is to make vector icon files as small as possible. This allows Haiku to display icons as several sizes while still keeping the files small enough to fit into an inode (i.e., inside a file’s metadata). The goal of keeping the icons in the metadata is to reduce the disk reads needed to display a folder – it allows each file to only require one disk read to display.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.leahhanson.us/post/recursecenter2016/haiku_icons.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Pro Guide | Stefan Đokić</title>
      <link>https://stefandjokic.tech/</link>
      <description>Stefan Djokic, a seasoned .NET professional, shares insights, tutorials, and tips for aspiring C# and .NET developers. Subscribe for weekly content updates.</description>
      <author> (Stefan Đokić)</author>
      <guid>https://stefandjokic.tech/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 11:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Web PubSub for Socket.IO</title>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-web-pubsub/socketio-overview</link>
      <description>An overview of Web PubSub&amp;#39;s support for the open-source Socket.IO library</description>
      <author> (kevinguo-ed)</author>
      <guid>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-web-pubsub/socketio-overview</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 11:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bun v0.8.0</title>
      <link>https://bun.sh/blog/bun-v0.8.0</link>
      <description>Bun gets debugger support, fetch streaming, and `bun update`. ReadStream and WriteStream from `node:tty` are implemented, including raw mode on `process.stdin`. SvelteKit now works in Bun. Plus bug fixes and stability improvements.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bun.sh/blog/bun-v0.8.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 10:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Mark Methods as Deprecated in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-mark-methods-as-depricated/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will learn how to mark methods as deprecated in C# together with providing useful information accordingly.</description>
      <author> (Marko Hrnčić)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-mark-methods-as-depricated/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 09:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Announces Financial Results for Second Quarter Fiscal 2024</title>
      <link>https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/news/nvidia-announces-financial-results-for-second-quarter-fiscal-2024</link>
      <description>NVIDIA today reported revenue for the second quarter ended July 30, 2023, of $13.51 billion, up 101% from a year ago and up 88% from the previous quarter.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/news/nvidia-announces-financial-results-for-second-quarter-fiscal-2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 07:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Async Teaching Through PR Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/async-teaching-pr-reviews</link>
      <description>Are pull requests the key to teaching less experienced devs at work? Hear one tech lead’s success story.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/async-teaching-pr-reviews</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 06:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Builder Pattern in C#</title>
      <link>https://blog.stackademic.com/generative-builder-pattern-in-c-4717120855c7</link>
      <description>In our previous post, we discussed the power of&amp;#160;.NET source code generators and implemented one to automate the Builder pattern. This time…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@bnayae)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.stackademic.com/generative-builder-pattern-in-c-4717120855c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EI022: SQL Processing Service (Part 3)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=rhW3LxRmLuI</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Learnit Training
  
  
  
    Learnit Training
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=rhW3LxRmLuI</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 06:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demo Front-End</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/articles/demo-front-end.html</link>
      <description>A front-end application to test and explore an API</description>
      <author> (Matteo Vaccari)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/articles/demo-front-end.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks! Minimal Architecture with Jeremy Miller</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/details/1860</link>
      <description>How much architectural ceremony is enough? Carl and Richard talk to Jeremy Miller about his minimal approach to architecture when building software, including his products Wolverine and Marten. Jeremy talks about how good tooling can simplify architecture, ultimately by writing less code - so that you are writing only the code that is unique to your customer needs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/details/1860</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to sabotage your salary negotiation efforts before you even start</title>
      <link>https://interviewing.io/blog/sabotage-salary-negotiation-before-even-start</link>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ve helped hundreds of people negotiate an average of $50k more. These are the two mistakes we can&amp;#39;t undo.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://interviewing.io/blog/sabotage-salary-negotiation-before-even-start</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluent UI Insights: Accessible by default</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Xmt1wZ_r8JM</link>
      <description>Fluent UI Insights is a series that describes the design and decisions behind the Fluent UI design system. In the fifth episode, members of the Fluent UI tea...</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Developer
  
  
  
    Microsoft Developer
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Xmt1wZ_r8JM</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM taps AI to translate COBOL code to Java | TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2023/08/22/ibm-taps-ai-to-translate-cobol-code-to-java/</link>
      <description>IBM&amp;#39;s new product offering, Code Assistant for IBM Z, leverages a generative AI model to translate COBOL code to Java.</description>
      <author> (Kyle Wiggers)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2023/08/22/ibm-taps-ai-to-translate-cobol-code-to-java/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Define the Game</title>
      <link>https://anuatluru.com/blog/definethegame</link>
      <description>my working theories</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anuatluru.com/blog/definethegame</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cool Caddy config tricks for your self-hosted domain</title>
      <link>https://jarv.org/posts/cool-caddy-config-tricks/</link>
      <description>The HTML5 Herald</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jarv.org/posts/cool-caddy-config-tricks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the `setup` convention in Neovim. Is it time for a paradigm shift?</title>
      <link>https://mrcjkb.dev/posts/2023-08-22-setup.html</link>
      <description>In the ever-evolving Neovim plugin ecosystem, the usage and appropriateness of a setup function
for initializing plugins has become somewhat a hot topic.
This discussion has sparked differing opinions among plugin developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mrcjkb.dev/posts/2023-08-22-setup.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gap</title>
      <link>https://sam.jajoo.fun/notes/gap</link>
      <description>Apprenticing to expand what I can build</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sam.jajoo.fun/notes/gap</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Human Generator – Generate and Modify People Online</title>
      <link>https://generated.photos/human-generator/</link>
      <description>Use AI to generate people online that don’t exist, change clothing and modify face and body traits. Download generated people in different postures.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://generated.photos/human-generator/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETS</title>
      <link>https://themeddle.com/posts/ets</link>
      <description>Posted on Saturday, 19 August 2023, 15:46</description>
      <author> (by 
meddle)</author>
      <guid>https://themeddle.com/posts/ets</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Srikanth Vemaraju</title>
      <link>https://svemaraju.github.io/ttd-online-booking.html</link>
      <description>Building software applications that handle millions of concurrent users is hard. Designing such applications need both technical skill and some...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://svemaraju.github.io/ttd-online-booking.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to set up a development environment in Android</title>
      <link>https://matan-h.com/how-to-set-up-a-development-environment-in-android/</link>
      <description>How to set up a development environment on Android so that you can create anything from a simple script to an Android app using only your phone</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matan-h.com/how-to-set-up-a-development-environment-in-android/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on a Stanford Journey</title>
      <link>https://www.ryantolsma.com/thoughts/2023/06/05/stanford-reflection.html</link>
      <description>It’s now been almost two years since graduating from Stanford, and I wanted to carve out a post to reflect deeply on how well I spent my time there, now with the benefit of hindsight, and with the additional goal of informing my future self to bias towards activities that matter longer term. There a variety of ways to measure quality of time, but the core aspects that I’ve grown to appreciate can be broadly categorized within: social life, health, career, and academics1. Courses can be looked up here by number if you’re curious&amp;#160;↩</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ryantolsma.com/thoughts/2023/06/05/stanford-reflection.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use web components for what they’re good at</title>
      <link>https://nolanlawson.com/2023/08/23/use-web-components-for-what-theyre-good-at/</link>
      <description>Dave Rupert recently made a bit of a stir with his post “If Web Components are so great, why am I not using them?”. I’ve been working with web components for a few years now, so I…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nolanlawson.com/2023/08/23/use-web-components-for-what-theyre-good-at/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How minimal is too minimal? Brainstorming syntax for VisionScript | James&amp;#39; Coffee Blog</title>
      <link>https://jamesg.blog/2023/08/23/visionscript-syntax/</link>
      <description>Yesterday evening I was thinking about syntax for VisionScript, the programming language on which I am working. My goal is to make the syntax as intuitive as possible while retaining a clear structure. As an aside, VisionScript got to the front-page of Hacker News (HN). I was humbled, excited; indeed, elated. Thank you for being so amazing, HN community! If you haven&amp;#39;t seen it, check out the demo for the language.</description>
      <author> (James&amp;#39; Coffee Blog ☕)</author>
      <guid>https://jamesg.blog/2023/08/23/visionscript-syntax/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Task Anxiety</title>
      <link>https://shubhamjain.co/2023/08/23/task-anxiety/</link>
      <description>
The to-do list in my head is a big source of my anxiety. Sometimes, it just so happens that the number of tasks that I have to complete starts to feel impossible and begins to overwhelm me. That in turn kickstarts a negative feedback loop. I find it difficult to get started because I am anxious. I am anxious because time is flying and I am not getting started. The tasks themselves might be trivial, but once they occupy a chunk of my mental space, it becomes harder to focus on any of them, and having no progress only exacerbates the problem. 

In such situations, distractions like Netflix and social media become an easy escape. It’s absurd and ironic. Procrastinating would probably be the worst option here and yet, that’s exactly what I end up doing. Even if I do get started, the anxiety about remaining tasks is still peeping from the shadows. 

Of course, it’s not a new thing, and the solutions are aplenty: break down tasks into steps, assign a priority score, and practice time management. However, I feel they are myopic and don’t address the root cause of the problem. Over the years, I have realized that once I start thinking about everything in terms of tasks to be completed in a certain time frame, no amount of breaking down the task, or managing my time, is going to do the trick. 

On top of it, it can suck the joy out of even enjoyable things. As Anne Helen Petersen wrote in her famous essay, “[How Millennials Became The Burnout Generation](https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/annehelenpetersen/millennials-burnout-generation-debt-work)”:

&amp;gt; That’s one of the most ineffable and frustrating expressions of burnout: It takes things that should be enjoyable and flattens them into a list of tasks, intermingled with other obligations that should either be easily or dutifully completed. The end result is that everything, from wedding celebrations to registering to vote, becomes tinged with resentment and anxiety and avoidance.

So, the lack of progress isn’t the source of my anxiety, it’s merely a symptom of a time-centric mindset, when the thoughts of doing X number of things dwarves the simpler pleasure of existing in the present being in the flow. As Anne further elaborates:

&amp;gt; “The modern Millennial, for the most part, views adulthood as a series of actions, as opposed to a state of being,” an article in Elite Daily explains. “Adulting therefore becomes a verb.” “To adult” is to complete your to-do list — but everything goes on the list, and the list never ends. “I’m really struggling to find the Christmas magic this year,” one woman in a Facebook group focused on self-care recently wrote. 
&amp;gt;
&amp;gt; “I have two little kids (2 and 6 months) and, while we had fun reading Christmas books, singing songs, walking around the neighbourhood to look at lights, I mostly feel like it’s just one to-do list superimposed over my already overwhelming to-do list. I feel so burned out. Commiseration or advice?”

This perfectly articulates where my sense of overwhelm comes from. When I see life only as a never-ending list of chores, each and everything (no matter how fun), just becomes a task to check off the list. Sometimes, I don’t even know who put the task on the list. Was it me or some social media post I read while doomscrolling through Twitter? It doesn’t end there. 

Each task demands the same level of urgency as the other. Whether it’s cleaning your car, your kitchen, or your cupboard. Whether it’s strength training, meditating, or following a diet plan. Whether it’s making time for hobbies, socializing, or doing weekend trips. Time has to be made for everything. Is it a surprise that I find myself overwhelmed?

Humans were never meant to endure such a torturous way of living, of having a list of tasks and deadlines, and feeling guilt and shame when they failed.

&amp;gt; The medieval farmer simply had no reason to adopt such a bizarre idea in the first place. Workers got up with the sun and slept at dusk, the lengths of their days varying with the seasons. There was no need to think of time as something abstract and separate from life: you milked the cows when they needed milking and harvested the crops when it was harvest time, and anybody who tried to impose an external schedule on any of that—for example, by doing a month’s milking in a single day to get it out of the way, or by trying to make the harvest come sooner—would rightly have been considered a lunatic. 
&amp;gt;
&amp;gt; There was no anxious pressure to “get everything done,” either, because a farmer’s work is infinite: there will always be another milking and another harvest, forever, so there’s no sense in racing toward some hypothetical moment of completion.

In fact, in the rural world, it’s curious to see how people in the rural world think about time and their tasks. 

&amp;gt; Tea or chai is a staple drink of the Afghan people and the tea house—the chai shop—is a favorite meeting place. 
&amp;gt; 
&amp;gt; Throughout the day, you will find groups of men sitting around drinking tea and talking, and this is an important and integral part of their social life.
&amp;gt; 
&amp;gt; In general, the Afghan has time for himself and others. He’s not tied to a 9-5 routine as most people in the West are. Here time has quite a different meaning and it’s one thing that even the poorest man is a master of.
&amp;gt;
&amp;gt; — From the documentary, [Afghanistan Before the Russian Invasion (Documentary, 1979)](https://youtu.be/fHPrU7R8L2Y?t=2163) 

I am probably arriving at the same boring truth, of being in the present. But maybe the root of all problems is the failure to abide by a simple principle. In the modern world, cultivating such a sense requires constant effort. 

## Containing the Overwhelm
I don’t believe I am lazy, I am just burdened by expectations—self-imposed or otherwise—about my time. I am overwhelmed because of the sheer number of things I have self-assigned myself to do. Undoing those expectations, and trying to focus on what&amp;#39;s important is a gradual process. I haven’t figured it all out myself, but I know “being in the moment” matters and there are a few things that help. 

1. **Waste time mindfully**: I feel every one of us should waste some part of the day, but “mindfully”. Not reading, not watching, not scrolling, not doing anything that engages the mind. This could include taking a walk, just sitting in the park, or back-floating in the water. It achieves two things: a) It gives the mind time to breathe. It’s no wonder how [some of the greatest ideas](https://everwalk.com/walk-the-big-idea-how-walking-has-changed-our-world/) have been conceived while walking. b) It convinces us that we don’t need infinite control over our time. That not every moment needs to be spent doing something. 

2. **Do things the slow, long-winded way**: The habit of rushing and finishing things off pervades everything we do. The best example is reading. I often find myself more worried about finishing off the book than actually enjoying it at my own pace. Sometimes, I catch myself reading while my mind is daydreaming elsewhere. Isn’t it foolish? What’s the point of reading if you’re not focused on the book?

I advocate doing things leisurely, truly trying to savor the moment. Read books as slowly as possible. After a shower, take time to relax and moisturize your body. Listen to slow music. 

3. **Practice gentle discipline**: Being carefree and relaxed is a wonderful attitude. However, I feel it’s also important to nudge yourself to do things. That’s especially important for a person like me, who has a tendency to fall into a rut of lazy entertainment that makes me miserable. At the same time, you must also avoid being too hard on yourself.

I call it “gentle discipline.” It involves urging myself to do something—reading, writing, or coding, but also listening to my mind, and realizing when I am not liking it. 

4. **Practice gentle routine**: Routines provide predictability and a sense of control. When individuals know what to expect from their day, their mind is less anxious and chaotic. It should be gentle, however. Something like a walk and a shower in the morning, to begin your day. Meals at predictable times. And an evening ritual to call it a day, and head to bed. 

5. **Disrupt your life**: I have noticed that disrupting your life can affect a positive change in life just by virtue of being disruptive. Challenging or novel experiences disturb our set patterns and thoughts. They help us give a fresh perspective. This can include travel, retreats, or a short-to-long-term break from work. 

6. **Focus only on what you want to do in the day**: We all plan our time and there are various ways to do it. It can be done in terms of a decade, a year, a month, a week, a day, or even an hour. The last one is funny and majorly comes from productivity gurus, who think that each day has to be planned in advance down to the hour. I abhor this concept of leaving yourself little-to-no flexibility.

I have come to the conclusion that it’s wise to focus only on one major thing you want to complete in the day. When you start thinking in terms of a week and beyond, there’s an urge to fill the time bucket with more and more tasks because you feel it’s big enough. You won’t think that you can make a trip, complete your tax return, and clean your kitchen, in a single day, but it’s not difficult to believe it can be done in a week. Naturally, a feeling of being overwhelmed with work will follow, leading to the paralysis I talked about.

I also think that when the time bucket is larger, we tend to fill it up with inconsequential tasks. When it’s smaller, we care about the more important stuff. Although I have convinced myself of the immediacy of every task, most of them _can_ be delayed. 

An added benefit of focusing on a single major thing is that it builds momentum to do other tasks as well. It&amp;#39;s surprising how much I can do in a single day when I have had a good, productive start.

--------

Most of us don&amp;#39;t realize that our thought patterns have been shaped, to a large extent, by the society we live in and the stories we have consumed. Having a travel wishlist, or being ambitious, is not inherently wrong. At some point, though, we overwhelm our life with too many things we wish to do, often not because we genuinely want it, but because we think it&amp;#39;s expected. This cycle needs to be broken. That task on your list can wait. But &amp;quot;living life&amp;quot; can&amp;#39;t.

</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shubhamjain.co/2023/08/23/task-anxiety/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ergaster - Syncing Notes with Obsidian</title>
      <link>https://ergaster.org/posts/2023/08/23-syncing-notes-with-obsidian/</link>
      <description>I often braindump in bed, before picking up the ideas and fleshing them out on a computer the next day. This means I need to synchronise Obsidian between my computers and phone.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ergaster.org/posts/2023/08/23-syncing-notes-with-obsidian/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accounting systems before TigerBeetle</title>
      <link>https://aivarsk.com/2023/08/23/accounting-before-tigerbeetle/</link>
      <description>TigerBeetle is an interesting project to follow. It links to interesting papers, it challenges assumptions, algorithms, and architecture of past systems. It satisfies my cravings for low-level programming.</description>
      <author> (Aivars Kalvāns)</author>
      <guid>https://aivarsk.com/2023/08/23/accounting-before-tigerbeetle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lewis Carson</title>
      <link>https://lewiscarson.com/chess</link>
      <description>In this article I&amp;#39;ll give a brief introduction to programming for computer chess. I&amp;#39;ll assume some knowledge about chess and how a chess engine operates under the hood. I&amp;#39;m by no means an expert on the topic, but I recently created a chess engine and wanted to prevent others from making some of the mistakes I did.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lewiscarson.com/chess</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Laravel’s Illuminate Database Query Builder With WordPress</title>
      <link>https://oddevan.com/2023/08/21/use-laravels-illuminate.html</link>
      <description>I’ve been working on Smolblog, a social web blogging app. To help me get to a minimally viable product sooner, I’ve been building it on top of WordPress. However, WordPress is built exclusively for the MySQL database, and I eventually want Smolblog to work with many different databases, especially SQLite. This means, for my own code, I need to abstract the database away.
The first pass I had at this was to simply have Query objects and services to handle those.</description>
      <author> (Evan Hildreth)</author>
      <guid>https://oddevan.com/2023/08/21/use-laravels-illuminate.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Excruciatingly Detailed Guide To SSH (But Only The Things I Actually Find Useful)  &amp;#183; Graham Helton</title>
      <link>https://grahamhelton.com/blog/ssh-cheatsheet/</link>
      <description>Welcome We&amp;amp;amp;rsquo;ve all seen these great diagrams of how SSH port forwarding works but if your brain is anything like mine, these diagrams leave you with a lot of unanswered questions. If you&amp;amp;amp;rsquo;re on a red team, understanding how to traverse a network better than the people who designed it gives you immense power to do evil things. SSH is such a powerful tool but sometimes the syntax and other concepts can get in the way of us accomplishing our goals.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://grahamhelton.com/blog/ssh-cheatsheet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>String Poaster</title>
      <link>https://ja3k.com/blog/stringpoaster</link>
      <description>I made a tool to cross post my tweets to X, bluesky, threads, mastodon and farcaster.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ja3k.com/blog/stringpoaster</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Code Between Different Hardware/Prototypes with Meadow IoT</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Q-CPMpvf2q8</link>
      <description>James is joined by Adrian Stevens who shows us how easy it is to share code when building IoT solutions with Meadow when working with different hardware and ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Q-CPMpvf2q8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Previews &amp;#39;Python in Excel&amp;#39; -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/08/23/python-excel.aspx</link>
      <description>Integrating the data science darling programming language with the super-popular spreadsheet program means analysts will no longer have to jump through so many workaround hoops or use third-party add-ins.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel08/23/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/08/23/python-excel.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 470 - News Roundup</title>
      <link>https://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-470-News-Roundup</link>
      <description>Episode 76 - BUILD and Ignite NewsWe talk about the latest Azure announcements from //BUILD and Ignite.

Media file: http://azpodcas...Episode 359 - 2020 RoundupCynthia, Cale, Evan and Sujit reminisce about the year that was 2020. They share their highlights, l...Episode 379 - Azure for OperatorsThe team is joined by Shawn Hakl, VP of Program Management for Azure for Operators to learn more abo...</description>
      <author> (Sujit D&amp;#39;Mello)</author>
      <guid>https://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-470-News-Roundup</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tales from the .NET Migration Trenches - Cataloging</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmybogard.com/tales-from-the-net-migration-trenches-catalog/</link>
      <description>Posts in this series:


 * Intro
 * Cataloging


When I talk with folks about modernization, inevitably the question comes up &amp;quot;OK but how much is it going to cost?&amp;quot; This is never an easy question but first we need to understand what exactly our target state is. That&amp;#39;s also context-dependent, but for</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Bogard
                
                    Aug 23, 2023
                        • 5 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jimmybogard.com/tales-from-the-net-migration-trenches-catalog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Framework August 2023 Cumulative Update Preview - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-framework-august-2023-cumulative-update-preview/</link>
      <description>August 2023 Cumulative Update Preview Updates for .NET Framework</description>
      <author> (Salini Agarwal)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-framework-august-2023-cumulative-update-preview/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a pretty console logger using Go&amp;#39;s slog package</title>
      <link>https://dusted.codes/creating-a-pretty-console-logger-using-gos-slog-package</link>
      <description>Programming Adventures</description>
      <author> (Dustin Moris Gorski)</author>
      <guid>https://dusted.codes/creating-a-pretty-console-logger-using-gos-slog-package</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pronunciation</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2819/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2819/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Video: &amp;#39;await&amp;#39; Return Types</title>
      <link>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2023/08/new-video-await-return-types.html</link>
      <description>   A new video is available on my YouTube channel:&amp;#160; Why do you have to return a Task when you use &amp;quot;await&amp;quot; in a C# method? . The video is a q...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2023/08/new-video-await-return-types.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 17:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot &amp;#183; Your AI pair programmer</title>
      <link>https://github.com/features/copilot#does-github-copilot-write-perfect-code/?WT.mc_id=onedevquestion-c9-githubcopilot</link>
      <description>GitHub Copilot works alongside you directly in your editor, suggesting whole lines or entire functions for you.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/features/copilot#does-github-copilot-write-perfect-code/?WT.mc_id=onedevquestion-c9-githubcopilot</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 17:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safely use secrets in HTTP requests in Visual Studio 2022 - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/safely-use-secrets-in-http-requests-in-visual-studio-2022/</link>
      <description>In the 17.8 Preview 1 version of Visual Studio 2022 we have updated the HTTP file editor in to enable you to externalize variables to make testing your Web APIs across different environments easier. This update also includes support to handle secrets in a secure fashion.</description>
      <author> (Sayed Ibrahim Hashimi)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/safely-use-secrets-in-http-requests-in-visual-studio-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 17:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welk bedrag mag ik maximaal contant betalen?</title>
      <link>https://www.rijksoverheid.nl/onderwerpen/geldzaken/vraag-en-antwoord/grote-aankopen-met-contant-geld</link>
      <description>Op dit moment mag u alle aankopen contant betalen. Bij contante aankopen boven de € 10.000 moet de verkoper een cli&amp;#235;ntenonderzoek doen. Maar niet alle verkopers accepteren contant geld. Het kabinet werkt aan een wetsvoorstel om contante betalingen vanaf € 3.000 te verbieden.&amp;#160;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.rijksoverheid.nl/onderwerpen/geldzaken/vraag-en-antwoord/grote-aankopen-met-contant-geld</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 16:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On writing loops in PPL and continuation-passing style, part 2 - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230823-00/?p=108640</link>
      <description>Recursion comes back.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230823-00/?p=108640</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 15:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EF Core 8.0 Preview: Raw SQL Queries for Unmapped Types</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2023/08/ef-core-80-preview-raw-sql-queries-for.html</link>
      <description>.NET, .NET Core, ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2023/08/ef-core-80-preview-raw-sql-queries-for.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE telecast of Chandrayaan-3 Soft-landing</title>
      <link>https://www.isro.gov.in/LIVE_telecast_of_Soft_landing.html</link>
      <description>ISRO Headquarters, Antariksh Bhavan, New BEL Road 
                    Bengaluru-560 094</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.isro.gov.in/LIVE_telecast_of_Soft_landing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>