<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Sejil - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/115/sejil</link>
      <description>Sejil is a library that enables you to capture, view and filter your ASP.net core app&amp;#39;s log events right from your app using a custom url. It supports structured logging, querying as well as saving log event queries.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/115/sejil</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:06:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azeroth Status - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/185/azeroth-status</link>
      <description>An app to track World of Warcraft realms and token prices per region. This app was made for the developers pure enjoyment, but is also useful to the Warcraft community at the same time. 

Next app I want to build a SaaS offering for service owners. </description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/185/azeroth-status</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:06:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caledos Runner for Android - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/119/caledos-runner-for-android</link>
      <description>If you want to start running or want to improve your performance, this app offers you the right motivation to do so. We&amp;#39;ll help you reach your goals by tracking your progress and by helping you analyse results. Millions have already done so - start now and have fun with us!

Track and analyze you…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/119/caledos-runner-for-android</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:06:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solcast API - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/126/solcast-api</link>
      <description>The Solcast API estimates and forecasts solar PV power and solar radiation globally. Clouds across the world are tracked and updated every 10-15 minutes using data from the latest generation geostationary weather satellites. Data crunching is performed by non .NET platforms but all data is exposed …</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/126/solcast-api</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:06:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memstate - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/120/memstate</link>
      <description>Platform for building event-sourced, ACID transactional, in-memory data applications. Great for complex OLTP workloads. Cloud and docker ready. Millions of transactions per second. 

Your data fits in RAM. Moving bits and pieces back and forth between disk and memory is slow, difficult to maintai…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/120/memstate</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice in a Can - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/184/voice-in-a-can</link>
      <description>I wanted Alexa on my Apple Watch so I built it. Also working on iPhone, Android, Mac and Tizen, because ... Xamarin.

Delightful to be able to share core tested functionality (Alexa Voice Service client implementation) across all the platforms, and UI where appropriate using Xamarin Forms.

Pub…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/184/voice-in-a-can</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ObjectStore OR Mapper - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/114/or-mapper-that-is-automatically-derifing-from-abstract</link>
      <description>Its an ORMapper where you define entity types as abstract classes and the Library implements those classes and implement INotifyPropertyChanged. It also gives you IQueryables with INotifyCollectionChanged implemented, which gets updated when an Entity is created or has changed so that it meets the …</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/114/or-mapper-that-is-automatically-derifing-from-abstract</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RemarkFS Markdown slides - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/124/remarkfs</link>
      <description>RemarkFS is an Markdown slide creation tool based on Remark built with FSharp. Using tools and libraries like FAKE, Fue and FSharp.Formatting, RemarkFS utilizes scripts to generate Remark HTML presentations from Markdown documents. </description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/124/remarkfs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:06:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tube Mate Underground planner - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/131/tube-mate</link>
      <description>Tube Mate is a simple Xamarin.Forms app which helps you to get around London Underground services. Provides route planner, live departures and realtime disruptions. The app provides the features above by communicating with a REST api from Transport for London (TFL OpenData) which is free to use for…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/131/tube-mate</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wexflow - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/180/wexflow</link>
      <description>Wexflow is an open source extensible workflow engine with a cross-platform manager and designer. The goal of Wexflow is to automate recurring tasks without user intervention. Wexflow aims to make automations, workflow processes, long-running processes and interactions between systems, applications …</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/180/wexflow</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core2D - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/116/core2d</link>
      <description>Core2D is a multi-platform application for making data driven 2D diagrams. The application has built-in wyswig vector graphics editor where you can bind data to shapes, share data across multiple documents, edit documents using layers. It also supports exporting documents to many popular file forma…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/116/core2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Function Flow - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/122/function-flow</link>
      <description>Function Flow is a library that takes a set of algorithms and wires them together in to a single composite algorithm. 

Without Function Flow, one might right. 

public Enchilada MakeEnchilada(Oil oil, Spices spices, Flour flour, Broth broth, Tortillas tortillas, Cheese cheese, Onion onion){
 …</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/122/function-flow</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exalt Training - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/187/exalt-training</link>
      <description>Exalt Training is the first sport tracking solution for racehorse trainers developed by Souffl and Sharpnado for the Paris-Turf group. It is an innovative solution that allows to understand and analyze objectively the level of performance of a horse to improve his training. The solution is based on…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/187/exalt-training</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weapsy CMS - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/186/weapsy-cms</link>
      <description>Weapsy CMS is an ASP.NET Core open source Content Management System based on DDD, CQRS and Event Sourcing. Data providers already available are SQL Server, MySQL, SQLite and PostgreSQL. CosmosDB SQL and MongoDB will be included in future releases.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/186/weapsy-cms</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Graham &amp;amp; Brown AR App - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/129/the-graham-brown-ar-app</link>
      <description>Often the hardest part of choosing a wallpaper is visualising what it will look like in your own home, but our app lets you visualise YOUR walls with YOUR wallpaper choices in seconds using ARKit.

Interior design has never been easier.

The Graham &amp;amp; Brown app uses augmented reality to make it …</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/129/the-graham-brown-ar-app</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Envoice - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/117/envoice</link>
      <description>The simplest app for doing business online. Sell online, send invoices, track invoice activities, automate with our API and get fast credit card payment with Paypal, Payoneer, Stripe and many other supported payment gateways.

Envoice is a product developed fully in .NET. The technical characterist…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/117/envoice</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoloLens object recognition - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/130/hololens-object-recognition</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m a fan of Terminator movies. This project is about doing Terminator Vision in Hololens.

What it does
Do Object Detection and analysis using Microsoft Cognitive Services Vision API. The user would say &amp;#39;Scan Image&amp;#39;, hololens will snapshot the scene, A Box Assistant will respond to the request …</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/130/hololens-object-recognition</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spoons - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/127/spoons</link>
      <description>Spoons is a side project I whipped up for Android (iOS not yet released) in Xamarin Forms 3.1 using a local SQLite DB for a friend of mine who suffers with chronic pain.

I had some very limited Xamarin experience, and come from  UWP background.

They already use the &amp;quot;spoon&amp;quot; method to budget th…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/127/spoons</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ombi Mobile - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/10/ombi-mobile</link>
      <description>Ombi is a self-hosted web application that automatically gives your shared Plex or Emby users the ability to request content by themselves! Ombi can be linked to multiple TV Show and Movie DVR tools to create a seamless end-to-end experience for your users. </description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/10/ombi-mobile</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 06:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baking with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://sararobinson.dev/2020/04/30/baking-machine-learning.html</link>
      <description>Like many people, I’ve been entertaining myself at home by baking a ton. I’ve gotten pretty good at following recipes, but I decided I wanted to take things one step further and understand the science behind what differentiates a cake from a bread or a cookie. I also like machine learning so I thought: what if I could combine it with baking??!</description>
      <author> (Sara Robinson)</author>
      <guid>https://sararobinson.dev/2020/04/30/baking-machine-learning.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 04:39:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Maze Weekly #62 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-62/</link>
      <description>This week we bring you a new batch of interesting articles to read during the weekend. Continuous improvement is important for any software developer and this is the best place to start honing your skills and keeping up-to-date. So, take a short break from whatever you do and pick one article you think can improve […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-62/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 01:05:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving 11M IOPS &amp;amp; 66 GB/s IO on a Single ThreadRipper Workstation - Tanel Poder Consulting</title>
      <link>https://tanelpoder.com/posts/11m-iops-with-10-ssds-on-amd-threadripper-pro-workstation/</link>
      <description>TL;DR Modern disks are so fast that system performance bottleneck shifts to RAM access and CPU. With up to 64 cores, PCIe 4.0 and 8 memory channels, even a single-socket AMD ThreadRipper Pro workstation makes a hell of a powerful machine - if you do it right!
 Introduction In this post I&amp;amp;rsquo;ll explain how I configured my AMD ThreadRipper Pro workstation with 10 PCIe 4.0 SSDs to achieve 11M IOPS with 4kB random reads and 66 GiB/s throughput with larger IOs - and what bottlenecks &amp;amp;amp; issues I fixed to get there. - Linux, Oracle, SQL performance tuning and troubleshooting - consulting &amp;amp; training.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tanelpoder.com/posts/11m-iops-with-10-ssds-on-amd-threadripper-pro-workstation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 01:05:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code with Fire! Top VS Code Tips -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/01/29/vs-code-tips.aspx</link>
      <description>Imagine typing Blazor code while orange flames blaze from your cursor. What could be better than that for your developer quality of life?</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel01/29/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/01/29/vs-code-tips.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 01:05:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover - Pony</title>
      <link>https://www.ponylang.io/discover/</link>
      <description>Pony - High Performance Actor Programming</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ponylang.io/discover/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:11:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyO3/pyo3</title>
      <link>https://github.com/PyO3/pyo3</link>
      <description>Rust bindings for the Python interpreter. Contribute to PyO3/pyo3 development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (PyO3)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/PyO3/pyo3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Subtle Hazards of Real-World Cryptography</title>
      <link>https://soatok.blog/2020/11/27/the-subtle-hazards-of-real-world-cryptography/</link>
      <description>Imagine you’re a software developer, and you need to authenticate users based on a username and password. If you’re well-read on the industry standard best practices, you’ll proba…</description>
      <author> (By Soatok)</author>
      <guid>https://soatok.blog/2020/11/27/the-subtle-hazards-of-real-world-cryptography/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I didn&amp;#39;t install Signal for privacy</title>
      <link>https://chrispanag.com/posts/i-didnt-install-signal-for-privacy/</link>
      <description>Why your right to choice is more important than your right to privacy.</description>
      <author> (Christos Panagiotakopoulos)</author>
      <guid>https://chrispanag.com/posts/i-didnt-install-signal-for-privacy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why we walked away from a $1.5 million seed round and shut down our company</title>
      <link>https://mikkeldengsoe.com/why-we-walked-away-from-a-million</link>
      <description>Why we walked away from a $1.5 million seed round and shut down our company</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mikkeldengsoe.com/why-we-walked-away-from-a-million</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>khalidabuhakmeh/monorepo_build</title>
      <link>https://github.com/khalidabuhakmeh/monorepo_build/blob/main/.github/workflows/build.yml</link>
      <description>An example of building a mono repo based on files changes - khalidabuhakmeh/monorepo_build</description>
      <author> (khalidabuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/khalidabuhakmeh/monorepo_build/blob/main/.github/workflows/build.yml</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zone to Zone Disaster Recovery with Azure Site Recovery | Azure Friday</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Zone-to-Zone-Disaster-Recovery-with-Azure-Site-Recovery</link>
      <description>Siddharth Deekshit joins Scott Hanselman to show how you can now protect your Azure VMs by replicating them from one availability zone to another within the same region.</description>
      <author> (by Scott Hanselman, Rob Caron)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Zone-to-Zone-Disaster-Recovery-with-Azure-Site-Recovery</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Psychology of Stock Bubbles</title>
      <link>https://halldorbjarni.github.io/the-psychology-of-stock-bubbles/</link>
      <description>The recent 800% rally in the stock of brick-and-mortar video game store GameStop over the span of a couple of days, in the middle of a pandemic, seems to defy all laws of financial theory. Surely new information didn’t come forward so that the value of the business could suddenly grow 22 billions in just over 5 days. However, it is hardly the first time such bubbles have happened in individual stock issues. For example, Qualcomm rose a whopping 2,619% in the middle of the dot-com bubble before cratering when the bubble popped in 2000. And keep in mind that bubbles have been occurring long before the advent of technology and globalization. Back in the 18th century the Mississippi Company, a French trading company, rose 3,000% before losing more than 50% of its value the next year1. But what causes these bubbles to happen in the first place?&amp;#160;                 The Mississippi Bubble, or How the French Eliminated All Their Government Debt (So Why Can’t Bernanke?), 2013&amp;#160;↩</description>
      <author> (Halldor Thorhallsson)</author>
      <guid>https://halldorbjarni.github.io/the-psychology-of-stock-bubbles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Launched my side project on Product Hunt, here is what I learned.</title>
      <link>https://blog.rutikwankhade.dev/i-launched-my-side-project-on-product-hunt-here-is-what-i-learned?guid=none</link>
      <description>Every time I used to visit Product Hunt, I would end up discovering a few awesome tools and products that make me say, wow! This is so cool. I want to build something like that. But the thing is I had no idea what to do. But I so wanted to build a pr...</description>
      <author> (Rutik WankhadePublished on Jan 28, 202110 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.rutikwankhade.dev/i-launched-my-side-project-on-product-hunt-here-is-what-i-learned?guid=none</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020-2021 Solarwinds hack explained in details by a software engineer. - Lav Patel | Lead Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://lavpatel.com/solarwinds-hack-explained-by-engineer/</link>
      <description>What is Solarwinds hack? Explanation why so many government and private institutions got affected? What are the best security practices ?</description>
      <author> (by Lav Patel)</author>
      <guid>https://lavpatel.com/solarwinds-hack-explained-by-engineer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hedge Fund Citadel Does Not Buy Robinhood Data, Citadel Securities is a Different Company, and Other Misconceptions</title>
      <link>https://stu2b50.dev/posts/the-hedge-fund747c5</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s been a wild week, and if there&amp;#39;s anything I&amp;#39;ve learned, it&amp;#39;s that no one knows what a Hedge Fund is and what a Market Maker is.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stu2b50.dev/posts/the-hedge-fund747c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Hired College Students to Run My Business (&amp;lt;span class=&amp;quot;caps&amp;quot;&amp;gt;PK&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;amp;C WINternship 2020&amp;#160;Report)</title>
      <link>https://philipkiely.com/essays/winterns_2020.html</link>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;December 2020 marked the first winter after I graduated from college. I wanted to build the winter break internship that I wish I’d been able to experience myself and offer it to current Grinnell&amp;#160;students.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://philipkiely.com/essays/winterns_2020.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whiteboarding software and hardware</title>
      <link>https://www.justingarrison.com/blog/2021-02-02-remote-whiteboarding/</link>
      <description>Personal site and blog of Justin Garrison</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.justingarrison.com/blog/2021-02-02-remote-whiteboarding/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily links from Cory Doctorow</title>
      <link>https://pluralistic.net/2021/01/28/payment-for-order-flow/#knowledge-is-power?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pluralistic.net/2021/01/28/payment-for-order-flow/#knowledge-is-power?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For once, not DNS: Huawei Modem ARP spoofing</title>
      <link>https://notbobthebuilder.github.io/arp-spoofing</link>
      <description>A couple of days ago I noticed my Ring Chime was disconnected in the Ring app. After a couple of years happily connected it was time to fulfil the ultimate purpose of both software and hardware: annoy humans.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notbobthebuilder.github.io/arp-spoofing</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 23:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t write unit tests for their own sake</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2021/01/29/dont-write-unit-tests-for-their-own-sake/</link>
      <description>One problem I often hear about is that TDD is hard; and so teams come away with the idea that if they ignore TDD, and just write Unit Tests, they’ll get the value of TDD without the hard part…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2021/01/29/dont-write-unit-tests-for-their-own-sake/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 21:07:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event Video: &amp;quot;Witches of Agnesi&amp;quot; Play Performance and Panel ⋆ National Math Festival</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalmathfestival.org/2021/event-video-witches-of-agnesi-play-performance-and-panel/</link>
      <description>You can now view the January 27, 2021 NMF Live Performance Series event featuring a pre-recorded performance of the play&amp;#160;Witches of Agnesi&amp;#160;followed by a panel of four women mathematicians, including playwright Dr. Susan Gerofsky. Check it out below, along with... Learn more →</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nationalmathfestival.org/2021/event-video-witches-of-agnesi-play-performance-and-panel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 21:07:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenWrt Forum</title>
      <link>https://forum.openwrt.org/</link>
      <description>OpenWrt - Wireless Freedom</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://forum.openwrt.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 21:07:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Directory</title>
      <link>https://dotnetfoundation.org/community/speakers?hss_channel=tw-2384354214</link>
      <description>This is your .NET Foundation!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetfoundation.org/community/speakers?hss_channel=tw-2384354214</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 20:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Of Mordor And Shadow Of War&amp;#39;s Nemesis System Hasn&amp;#39;t Appeared In More Games Because WB Patented The System - PlayStation Universe</title>
      <link>https://www.psu.com/news/shadow-of-mordor-and-shadow-of-wars-nemesis-system-hasnt-appeared-in-more-games-because-wb-patented-the-system/</link>
      <description>Shadow Of Mordor And Shadow Of War&amp;#39;s Nemesis System was patented by WB, which is why we haven&amp;#39;t seen it crop up in more games.</description>
      <author> (Joe Apsey / January 29, 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://www.psu.com/news/shadow-of-mordor-and-shadow-of-wars-nemesis-system-hasnt-appeared-in-more-games-because-wb-patented-the-system/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 19:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‎iCircuit 3D</title>
      <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/icircuit-3d/id1539977373</link>
      <description>‎iCircuit 3D gives you an endless virtual workbench upon which to design and test your electronics projects. It combines the robust electronics simulation engine of the original iCircuit with the latest rendering and 3D physics technology of iOS.

Don’t let the physical availability of parts be a con…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/icircuit-3d/id1539977373</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 19:06:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate a GitHub Actions workflow with Visual Studio or the dotnet CLI | Azure DevOps Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/generate-a-github-actions-workflow-with-visual-studio-or-the-dotnet-cli/</link>
      <description>It can feel like a lot to get started with GitHub Actions or Azure Pipelines – it’s a whole new skillset. Because the alternatives for deployment are so easy (right-click publish for example), teams sometimes question whether implementing a pipeline is worth the effort.</description>
      <author> (Damian Brady Senior Cloud Advocate, Cloud DevOps Advocacy Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/generate-a-github-actions-workflow-with-visual-studio-or-the-dotnet-cli/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 19:06:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#150 Luke Hoban, Pulumi - Infrastructure as Software | no dogma podcast</title>
      <link>https://no-dogma-podcast-301aeb97.simplecast.com/episodes/150-luke-hoban-pulumi-infrastructure-as-software-qYOI2rax</link>
      <description>discussions on topics connected with software development; privacy, security, management, tools, techniques, skills, training, business</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://no-dogma-podcast-301aeb97.simplecast.com/episodes/150-luke-hoban-pulumi-infrastructure-as-software-qYOI2rax</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 19:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>microsoft/vscode-edge-devtools</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/vscode-edge-devtools#setting-up-your-project-to-show-live-changes-in-the-extension</link>
      <description>A VSCode extension that allows you to use browser devtools from within the editor. The devtools will connect to an instance of Microsoft Edge giving you the ability to alter CSS styling, perform di...</description>
      <author> (microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/vscode-edge-devtools#setting-up-your-project-to-show-live-changes-in-the-extension</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 18:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Facts #364 - 1.1 stable | Factorio</title>
      <link>https://factorio.com/blog/post/fff-364</link>
      <description>Hello, we have a stable version! 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
When we were releasing the 1.0 FFF-360, we actually stated that there were &amp;quot;around 150 bugs on the forums and around 80 internal tasks to be solved&amp;quot;. These were obviously minor issues, things hard to reproduce or very rare problems. In other words, it was quite reasonably stable, which normally goes without saying when it comes to Factorio stable versions. But it proved to be a mistake wording it this way, since some media picked up on it and presented it as a &amp;quot;fairly bugged release&amp;quot;. 
 
 
 
So I&amp;#39;m pretty thrilled to finally get to the point, where we actually have 0 known issues and 0 active bug reports on the forums. Its like cleaning the kitchen properly, so you can start cooking something fresh....</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://factorio.com/blog/post/fff-364</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statement of Acting Chair Lee and Commissioners Peirce, Roisman, and Crenshaw Regarding Recent Market Volatility</title>
      <link>https://www.sec.gov/news/public-statement/joint-statement-market-volatility-2021-01-29</link>
      <description>Statement of Acting Chair Lee and Commissioners Peirce, Roisman, and Crenshaw Regarding Recent Market Volatility

January 29, 2021</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sec.gov/news/public-statement/joint-statement-market-volatility-2021-01-29</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Named a ‘Best Place to Work for LGBTQ Equality’</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-named-a-best-place-to-work-for-lgbtq-equality/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare receives a perfect score of 100 on the Human Rights Campaign’s 2021 Corporate Equality Index.</description>
      <author> (Chase Robinson)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-named-a-best-place-to-work-for-lgbtq-equality/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET R&amp;amp;D Digest (January, 2021)</title>
      <link>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2021/01/29/net-rd-digest-january-2021/</link>
      <description>This issues contains bits of .NET, .NET Internals, Windows, Debugging, Diagnostics and C#!</description>
      <author> (Oleg Karasik)</author>
      <guid>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2021/01/29/net-rd-digest-january-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 16:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoscrolling on drag, part 5: Adding wiggle-to-scroll to escape velocity | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210129-00/?p=104773</link>
      <description>Last time, we implemented autoscroll speed based on the mouse’s velocity. But our implementation didn’t support the popular bug-that-is-now-a-feature where wiggling the mouse makes the window scroll faster. Let’s bring that back. void OnMouseMove(HWND hwnd, int x, int y, UINT keyFlags) {   if (g_fDragging) {     if (g_dyAutoScroll == 0) {       int direction = DetectAutoScroll({ x,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210129-00/?p=104773</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 15:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com: AUKEY USB C Power Bank, 20000mAh Portable Charger USB C, Slimline Type C Battery Pack with 3 Input &amp;amp; 4 Output Compatible with iPhone&amp;#160;11/11&amp;#160;Pro/XS Max/8, Nintendo Switch, Samsung Galaxy Note8, Pixel</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/AUKEY-20000mAh-External-Compatible-Nintendo/dp/B0759TDR3H/?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202101</link>
      <description>Amazon.com: AUKEY USB C Power Bank, 20000mAh Portable Charger USB C, Slimline Type C Battery Pack with 3 Input &amp;amp; 4 Output Compatible with iPhone&amp;#160;11/11&amp;#160;Pro/XS Max/8, Nintendo Switch, Samsung Galaxy Note8, Pixel</description>
      <author> (AUKEY Direct)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/AUKEY-20000mAh-External-Compatible-Nintendo/dp/B0759TDR3H/?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202101</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t grow.</title>
      <link>https://joanwestenberg.medium.com/dont-grow-d7f87faeaf56</link>
      <description>When you walk down any street with a touch of history, you’ll see storefronts marked with dates. Est. 1856. Est. 1912.</description>
      <author> (https://joanwestenberg.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://joanwestenberg.medium.com/dont-grow-d7f87faeaf56</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 14:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a social media platform without going bankrupt: Part V–Handling the timeline</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/193057-A/building-a-social-media-platform-without-going-bankrupt-part-v-handling-the-timeline?Key=f24ec06d-5d24-49ba-9a90-2809f6b55c3f</link>
      <description>In the series of posts so far, when discussing reads, I punted the part where we know what to read. I mentioned that we get a whole batch of post ids from so...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/193057-A/building-a-social-media-platform-without-going-bankrupt-part-v-handling-the-timeline?Key=f24ec06d-5d24-49ba-9a90-2809f6b55c3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 13:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting a new job in the middle of a pandemic</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/starting-a-new-job-in-the-middle-of-a-pandemic/</link>
      <description>When 2020 started, it was not in my plans to change jobs and start working at a new company, completely remote, without ever meeting my colleagues in person or visiting the office. However, that is exactly what happened, and I am so glad I did.</description>
      <author> (Daniela Rodrigues)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/starting-a-new-job-in-the-middle-of-a-pandemic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 12:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open MCT - Open Source Mission Control Software — Open MCT</title>
      <link>https://nasa.github.io/openmct/</link>
      <description>1Clone the source code</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nasa.github.io/openmct/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 12:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebook Reader for web</title>
      <link>https://www.loudreader.com/</link>
      <description>Web&amp;#39;s only  usable ebook reader inside a browser. It could replace your desktop ebook reader!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.loudreader.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 12:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-01-29</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/01/app-developer-links-2021-01-29/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/01/app-developer-links-2021-01-29/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 09:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Look at iMessage in iOS 14</title>
      <link>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2021/01/a-look-at-imessage-in-ios-14.html</link>
      <description>Posted By Samuel Gro&amp;#223;, Project Zero On December 20, Citizenlab published “ The Great iPwn ”, detailing how “Journalists [were] Hacked with S...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2021/01/a-look-at-imessage-in-ios-14.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 09:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Hunt: &amp;#39;De Adobe-breach kwam precies goed uit voor Have I been Pwned&amp;#39;</title>
      <link>https://tweakers.net/reviews/8620/troy-hunt-de-adobe-breach-kwam-precies-goed-uit-voor-have-i-been-pwned.html</link>
      <description>Troy Hunt is oprichter en enige beheerder van Have I Been Pwned, met miljarden records en tienduizenden bezoekers per dag. Hoe onderhoud je zoiets naast je werk?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tweakers.net/reviews/8620/troy-hunt-de-adobe-breach-kwam-precies-goed-uit-voor-have-i-been-pwned.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 08:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 228</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-228/</link>
      <description>Well, it kinda feels like we&amp;#39;re back to the new normal that is 2021. I&amp;#39;m home, the kids are back at school and we&amp;#39;re all still getting breached. We&amp;#39;re breached so much that even when we&amp;#39;re not breached but someone says we&amp;#39;re breached, it genuinely looks like we&amp;#39;re breached. Ok,</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-228/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 08:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>