<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How To Create Compound Efficiencies In Engineering</title>
      <link>https://devinterrupted.substack.com/p/how-to-create-compound-efficiencies</link>
      <description>Improvements in your engineering team&amp;#39;s workflow don&amp;#39;t occur independent of each other.</description>
      <author> (Dev Interrupted)</author>
      <guid>https://devinterrupted.substack.com/p/how-to-create-compound-efficiencies</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I made a keyboard stand for bicycle adventures</title>
      <link>https://undercoverlocal.wordpress.com/2023/07/10/i-made-a-keyboard-stand-for-bicycle-adventures/</link>
      <description>So since this discovery, brought on by extensive exploration into what keyboard stands I could find to fit my purpose, I decided to make my own. But do you need to have a keyboard stand for bicycle…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://undercoverlocal.wordpress.com/2023/07/10/i-made-a-keyboard-stand-for-bicycle-adventures/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do we save water: Stop growing alfalfa in Imperial County</title>
      <link>https://www.desertsun.com/story/opinion/contributors/valley-voice/2023/02/05/growing-alfalfa-in-imperial-county-and-california-wastes-water/69860506007/</link>
      <description>Is the California desert the right place to grow alfalfa? It needs a considerable water to sustain this crop for a year.</description>
      <author> (Gerald McKenna
&amp;#160;|&amp;#160; Special to The Desert Sun)</author>
      <guid>https://www.desertsun.com/story/opinion/contributors/valley-voice/2023/02/05/growing-alfalfa-in-imperial-county-and-california-wastes-water/69860506007/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity 4D #2: Extending Unity to 4D - Alan Zucconi</title>
      <link>https://www.alanzucconi.com/2023/07/06/unity-3d-to-4d/</link>
      <description>Follow @AlanZucconi This article will show how to extend Unity to support four-dimensional geometry. This is the second article in a series of four, and the first one which will probably start discussing the Mathematics and the C# code necessary to store and manipulate 4D objects in Unity. You can find all the articles in […]</description>
      <author> (Alan Zucconi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.alanzucconi.com/2023/07/06/unity-3d-to-4d/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
    The lost generation of young founders
</title>
      <link>https://www.jdilla.xyz/post/52</link>
      <description>
    In the most recent [conversations with Tyler](https://conversationswithtyler.com/episodes/paul-graham/), Paul Graham and Tyler Cowen discuss the question: &amp;quot;Why are there so few great founders in their..
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jdilla.xyz/post/52</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to DIY home security</title>
      <link>https://vedard.com/blog/how-to-diy-home-security/</link>
      <description>How to DIY home security? It is easy to buy an IP camera and place it in the living room and remote monitor your home. But it is not enough to secure your home. To completely secure your home and prevent any intrusion, you need to know how to choose the detectors, where to install the detectors and how to set up the home security system. We will analyze the actual case of home security solution. We hope that can help you understanding home anti-theft and monitoring systems.
Step1:Determine the scope of prevention according to the home situation

From Figure 1, we can see that the 2 balconies and doors are in the most vulnerable areas. The second one is the kitchen and the study room windows (because the study room and kitchen are usually unoccupied, especially at night, they are usually vacant, which can easily become the entrance of thieves). The third is the master bedroom ①, children’s room ② and bathroom ③. So we firstly determined the areas that need to be protected. Then we need to determine the priority of the prevention area (the intrusion position is indicated by the priority of the prevention in the figure)
Step 2:Determine the defense area and the prevention method and equipment of each defense
After the location and area that are vulnerable to intrusion are determined, we need to determine the prevention method and equipment for each defense area.  It is better to have all areas protected. But if the environment situation and community security is good, you can only have the main entrance areas protected.

1)Basic home security solution
This security solution only set defense areas of gate, both balconies, kitchen, and study room. Wireless door contacts are used for protection of gate, kitchen and study room. PIR motion sensors are used for protection of living room and bed room.
When the gate or study room, kitchen room door or windows are open, or body motion detected in living room and bed room, the detector will trigger alarm panel and loud sound siren strobe goes alarm, at the same time, alarm signal will be sent to mobile phone or security service center.
The shortage: When using door contact, the windows should be closed even in summer. Bathroom and children room is not protected and with security hazard.
2)Complete home security solution

On the basis of basic home security solution, one added infrared detector is installed in children’s room, living room and study room, and one door magnetic detector is installed in the window of the bathroom. In this way, we have completed a basic family anti-theft system, and at the same time, double detection equipment is installed in the key defense area (gate and study room)
When the gate or the study room, kitchen, bathroom window is opened, or have human body movement detected in balcony, children room, study room, the alarm will go off. At the same time, double defend of different types sensors installed in gate and study room to ensure the defense of the main entrance.
The shortage: although all the indoor scope has been in the protection, but the passive infrared detector can only active after the invasion. The perimeter protection of the balcony and the window is not very effective with door contact.
3)Improved home security solution

In order to solve the problem that the balcony and windows intruders can not be prevented at first time. We installed infrared barriers on the balcony and windows, and remove some indoor infrared detectors.
So, the infrared barriers outside the balcony and windows can promptly alarm when someone approaches the balcony and the window. Keep the intruder outside, prevent the intruder from entering the room. The improved home security solution can better protect the personal and property safety.
Shortages:&amp;#160;No video monitoring function and linkage equipment, and unable to use technical means to retain evidence while alarming

Step3: Optional equipment to enhance the prevention function
Based on the above setting, we can choose smart detectors or microwave detectors to replace the above ordinary infrared detectors; add harmful gas detectors in the kitchen, Add linkage lighting control equipment in the living room (when someone approaches the window, the lights in the living room will automatically turn on when the alarm is issued); the door is equipped with a digital anti-theft lock; the glass is equipped with a vibration detector to further enhance the prevention ability.&amp;#160;One thing to note is that, while focusing on new technologies and new products, security products should also focus on stable and mature conventional and reliable ability.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vedard.com/blog/how-to-diy-home-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Sabbaticals, Sunsetting Retirement Age</title>
      <link>https://jacek.migdal.pl/2023/08/16/sabbaticals.html</link>
      <description>Debug, simplify and execute.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jacek.migdal.pl/2023/08/16/sabbaticals.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Assistant compatible desk fan (120mm) – Tristam</title>
      <link>https://tristam.ie/2023/663/</link>
      <description>Frustrated by the lack of fans that integrate with Home Assistant, I decided to modify this 120mm fan stand  to include a compartment for a Wemos D1 mini and a buck converter. This allows us to run ESPHome on a Wemos D1 mini which outputs a 25khz PWM signal to control the speed of an off the shelf 120mm computer fan. The whole setup is powered from a single micro USB port and with this fan, draws a max of 0.3A at 5v so it’ll run off a power bank for hours.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tristam.ie/2023/663/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Stanley - Designing a Bangle.js commute timer</title>
      <link>https://incoherency.co.uk/blog/stories/banglejs-commute-timer.html</link>
      <description>Wed 16 August 2023
Tagged: banglejs</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://incoherency.co.uk/blog/stories/banglejs-commute-timer.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I just made my first $1 on the internet!</title>
      <link>https://www.murilopereira.com/i-just-made-my-first-1-on-the-internet/</link>
      <description>In 2020 I wanted to create annotated charts showing events influencing the COVID-19 numbers. I looked around and didn’t find great ways to do it, so of course, as a software engineer, I started building a thing: contextualize.ai.
Fast forward many weekends, and lots and lots of hours around my 9-5s, I get the project to a level where I’m not absolutely embarrassed by around a month ago and start building and sharing charts with it.</description>
      <author> (Murilo Pereira)</author>
      <guid>https://www.murilopereira.com/i-just-made-my-first-1-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How accurate is the birthday’s paradox formula?</title>
      <link>https://lemire.me/blog/2023/08/15/how-accurate-is-the-birthdays-paradox-formula/</link>
      <description>Given a set of r random values from a large set (of size N), I have been using the formula 1-exp(-r**2/(2N)) to approximate the probability of a collision. It assumes that r is much smaller than N. The formula suggests that if you have hundreds of millions of random 64-bit numbers, you will start getting … Continue reading How accurate is the birthday’s paradox formula?</description>
      <author> (Published by)</author>
      <guid>https://lemire.me/blog/2023/08/15/how-accurate-is-the-birthdays-paradox-formula/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Match LLM Patterns to Problems</title>
      <link>https://eugeneyan.com/writing/llm-problems/</link>
      <description>Distinguishing problems with external vs. internal LLMs, and data vs non-data patterns</description>
      <author> (https://eugeneyan.com/about/)</author>
      <guid>https://eugeneyan.com/writing/llm-problems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep Your Vue Apps Fresh v2</title>
      <link>https://paltman.com/keep-your-vue-apps-fresh-v2/</link>
      <description>SPA frontends can remain open on a user&amp;#39;s browser for a long time.  This article describes how to update the frontend with the latest version of the code.</description>
      <author> (Patrick Altman)</author>
      <guid>https://paltman.com/keep-your-vue-apps-fresh-v2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>part 1 — blog documentation</title>
      <link>https://oscarbenjamin.github.io/blog/czi/post1.html</link>
      <description>This is the first part of a series of posts on big changes for SymPy with
particular focus on speed. What I am going to describe in these posts are:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://oscarbenjamin.github.io/blog/czi/post1.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My bug finding chronicles (and how to earn money through vulnerability research)</title>
      <link>https://mijailovic.net/2023/08/16/bug-finding-chronicles/</link>
      <description>At least one person has asked me about my thought process when searching for denial-of-service
vulnerabilities: how do I choose the target libraries, what specifically I look for in them, etc.
“At least one person” meaning “exactly one person”, and that one person happens to be my wife, but
I decided to write a whole post on this topic anyway! In this half-memoir,
half-tutorial post, I’ll show you the most interesting bugs I’ve found so far and the methods I
used to find them. I wouldn’t say I have any advanced bug finding skills, but I do know a few useful
techniques, so I hope you will learn something new today.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mijailovic.net/2023/08/16/bug-finding-chronicles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Types of Solar Eclipse</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2816/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2816/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You don&amp;#39;t hate JIRA, you hate your manager</title>
      <link>https://jarvispowered.com/you-dont-hate-jira-you-hate-your-manager/</link>
      <description>It seems like it has become popular to hate on JIRA. In fact, a good friend of mine sent me this, which is what triggered this post: (if you&amp;#39;re the owner of the image, reach out to me and I&amp;#39;ll attribute it properly) I&amp;#39;m usually…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jarvispowered.com/you-dont-hate-jira-you-hate-your-manager/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Power of Visual Studio 2022 for C++ Game Development - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/unleashing-the-power-of-visual-studio-2022-for-c-game-development/</link>
      <description>We are excited to bring you a multitude of performance tune-ups, productivity enhancements, and Unreal Engine integrations for C++ game development.</description>
      <author> (David Li)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/unleashing-the-power-of-visual-studio-2022-for-c-game-development/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tales from the .NET Migration Trenches - Intro</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmybogard.com/tales-from-the-net-migration-trenches/</link>
      <description>Over the past year or so I&amp;#39;ve been part of a large-ish modernization effort, both migrating from .NET 4.8 to .NET 6 (the latest LTS at the time) and from an on-premise deployment to Azure. While these two workstreams were largely independent (luckily), we did have some dependencies between</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Bogard
                
                    Aug 16, 2023
                        • 3 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jimmybogard.com/tales-from-the-net-migration-trenches/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How They Tried to Kill Me | Elena Kostyuchenko</title>
      <link>https://www.nplusonemag.com/online-only/online-only/how-they-tried-to-kill-me/</link>
      <description>I didn’t want to write this for a long time. I feel disgusted, afraid, ashamed. I can’t write about everything I know because I have to protect the people who’ve saved my life. On February 24, 2022, my country attacked Ukraine.</description>
      <author> (https://www.nplusonemag.com/author/mark-krotovgmail-com/)</author>
      <guid>https://www.nplusonemag.com/online-only/online-only/how-they-tried-to-kill-me/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 16:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core in .NET 8 Preview 7: Blazor, Native AOT, Antiforgery and More </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/08/aspnet-core-8-preview-7/</link>
      <description>The latest release of .NET 8 Preview 7 brings significant additions and changes to ASP.NET Core. The most notable enhancements for this release of ASP.NET Core are related to the Blazor alongside the updates regarding the Native AOT, Identity, new SPA Visual Studio templates, Antiforgery middleware&amp;#160;additions and many more.</description>
      <author> (Almir Vuk)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/08/aspnet-core-8-preview-7/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside STL: The shared_ptr constructor and enable_shared_from_this - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230816-00/?p=108608</link>
      <description>Working together through a secret signal.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230816-00/?p=108608</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core 8.0 Preview: All New Identity Endpoints</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2023/08/aspnet-core-80-preview-all-new-identity.html</link>
      <description>.NET, .NET Core, ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2023/08/aspnet-core-80-preview-all-new-identity.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 14:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;lt;/&amp;gt; htmx ~ htmx is part of the GitHub Accelerator!</title>
      <link>https://htmx.org/posts/2023-06-06-htmx-github-accelerator/</link>
      <description>We are excited to announce that htmx has been accepted into the first class of the 
GitHub Open Source Accelerator!  This is a tremendous opportunity to work with and
learn from some of the most successful open source developers and projects, and a great chance to get the message
out about hypermedia and htmx.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://htmx.org/posts/2023-06-06-htmx-github-accelerator/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Use Named HttpClients In .NET #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=xyGi4wsVi_I</link>
      <description>&amp;#128204; Check out my Pragmatic Clean Architecture course: https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/pragmatic-clean-architecture&amp;#128640; Join 770+ engineers in my  Patreon commun...</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=xyGi4wsVi_I</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern CSV 2 is now available.</title>
      <link>https://www.moderncsv.com/modern-csv-2-is-now-available/</link>
      <description>And I think you’ll love it. I focused on several areas: Improved UI and user experience Faster performance Useful features Updated documentation For Mac users, Native Apple Silicon (ARM – M1, M2) compatibility If that’s all you need to know, you can buy a license here. Or if you already have a version 1 license, you can upgrade here. For those that need more details, here you go. Improved UI and User Experience There are two areas of the user interface that I aimed to improve for usability: Preferences and File Metadata. I also added several new themes and a […]</description>
      <author> (evan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.moderncsv.com/modern-csv-2-is-now-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft .NET Code Analysis: Simplify the New Expression for C#</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/08/16/microsoft-net-code-analysis-simplify-the-new-expression-for-c/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the introduction of a simplified new expression syntax in .NET 5, which allows for more concise and readable object initialization. The new syntax offers advantages such as re…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave
		

		
			I live in San Diego, Ca USA			
				View all posts by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/08/16/microsoft-net-code-analysis-simplify-the-new-expression-for-c/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Generate a Stream From a String? - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/dotnet-generate-stream-from-string/</link>
      <description>Generating a stream from a string is a common operation when building applications. This article will discuss how to do it in .NET.</description>
      <author> (Januarius Njoku)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/dotnet-generate-stream-from-string/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Circuit Breaker Design Pattern? #shorts #microservices</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Rr3nhxWwQGs</link>
      <description>What is Circuit Breaker Design Pattern? #shortsSupport me on Patreon to access the source code:https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawandLet us connect:&amp;#127757;  My web...</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand
  
  
  
    Mohamad Lawand
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Rr3nhxWwQGs</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Videos In Blazor Server  #dotnet #csharp #blazor #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=4rpHtCAFNAM</link>
      <description>How can we play and stream videos in Blazor Server? Well, it&amp;#39;s fairly easy and you&amp;#39;re about to find out in less than a minute!Join this channel to get source...</description>
      <author> (Security Now
  
  
  
    Security Now
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=4rpHtCAFNAM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Weasel for Database Development</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/08/15/introducing-weasel-for-database-development/</link>
      <description>An unheralded, but vital foundational piece of the “Critter Stack” is the Weasel family of libraries that both Marten and Wolverine use quite heavily for a range of database development…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/08/15/introducing-weasel-for-database-development/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How is LLaMa.cpp possible?</title>
      <link>https://finbarr.ca/how-is-llama-cpp-possible/</link>
      <description>If you want to read more of my writing, I have a Substack. Articles will be posted simultaneously to both places.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://finbarr.ca/how-is-llama-cpp-possible/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>