<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Host Your MySQL Blog Database On Azure In Only Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HMNNoSxtIs8</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s continue on the Blazor blog tutorial! Next stop:

Hosting your database in the cloud!

The reality is that for most folks you&amp;#39;re probably fine to run with the base SQLite settings.
- SQLite is plenty performant (billions of instances it across the world running on our phones)
- Low effort. Low setup.
- Just works.

But if you&amp;#39;re interested in learning how to set up and run a database in Azure for your blog, this is for you!

----
- Steven&amp;#39;s blog: https://steven-giesel.com/
- Repository: https://github.com/linkdotnet/Blog

----
&amp;#128273; Membership &amp;amp; Subscriptions:
- &amp;#128232; Weekly Newsletter: https://weekly.devleader.ca
- &amp;#127960;️ Private Discord Community: https://sidestack.io/devleader

&amp;#129504; Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Get Promoted As A Software Engineer: https://dometrain.com/course/career-getting-promoted-as-a-software-engineer/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?ref=nick-cosentino
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

&amp;#128483;️ Social Media &amp;amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs:  @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp;amp; Products/Services That I Love:
- @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper Opus Clip: https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----

#softwareengineering #softwaredeveloper #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HMNNoSxtIs8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 14:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Anti-Patterns in C# Development</title>
      <link>https://blog.stackademic.com/how-to-avoid-anti-patterns-in-c-development-822dbb010778?source=rss-c77187421577------2</link>
      <description>Avoiding Common Pitfalls: Best Practices for Clean and Efficient C# Development</description>
      <author> (https://malshikay.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.stackademic.com/how-to-avoid-anti-patterns-in-c-development-822dbb010778?source=rss-c77187421577------2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can use C-Reduce for any language</title>
      <link>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/creduce/</link>
      <description>C-Reduce is a tool by Regehr and friends for minimizing C compiler bug reproducers. Imagine if you had a 10,000 line long C file that triggered a Clang bug. You don’t want to send a massive blob to the compiler developers because that’s unhelpful, but you also don’t want to cut it down to size by hand. The good news is that C-Reduce can do that for you. The bad news is that everyone thinks it only works for C.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/creduce/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 02:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surviving a Week Without Power:  Ultimate Home Backup Solution!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XBrUI3PRTeo</link>
      <description>Dave describes the various stages of emergency power backup, from small Costco generators to large industrial standby units, and compares their capabilities.  Free Sample of my Book on the Spectrum: https://amzn.to/3zBinWM

Dave&amp;#39;s Attic - Friday 4PM Podcast - https://www.youtube.com/@UCtb6a_CnmGbSns9G8W2Ny0w 

Follow me for updates!  
Twitter:   @davepl1968 davepl1968
Facebook: fb.com/davepl</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XBrUI3PRTeo</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 02:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Reality of an Employer’s Market</title>
      <link>https://yusufaytas.com/the-reality-of-an-employers-market/</link>
      <description>Learn how to navigate the current employer’s market in tech, where employers hold the leverage. Tips for job seekers to stay proactive and resilient.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/yusufaytas)</author>
      <guid>https://yusufaytas.com/the-reality-of-an-employers-market/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we got to 10,000 stars (+ why you should be launching as often as you can)</title>
      <link>https://blog.skyvern.com/how-we-got-to-10-000-stars-why-you-should-be-launching-as-often-as-you-can/</link>
      <description>Why does YC keep talking about &amp;quot;launch early, launch often&amp;quot;?

By default.. people don&amp;#39;t know that you exist. It&amp;#39;s your job to be the squeaky wheel, and let people know &amp;quot;HEY I EXIST&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;HEY I CAN SOLVE YOUR PROBLEM&amp;quot;

You may have seen my many posts talking about Skyvern hitting</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.skyvern.com/how-we-got-to-10-000-stars-why-you-should-be-launching-as-often-as-you-can/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why BlueSky is better than Twitter</title>
      <link>https://vpon.me/articles/blue-sky-vs-twitter</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vpon.me/articles/blue-sky-vs-twitter</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why PostgreSQL major version upgrades are hard</title>
      <link>http://peter.eisentraut.org/blog/2024/11/26/why-postgresql-major-version-upgrades-are-hard</link>
      <description>Upgrades between PostgreSQL major versions are famously annoying. You can’t just install the server binaries and restart, because the format of the data directory is incompatible. Why is that? Why can’t we just keep the data format compatible?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://peter.eisentraut.org/blog/2024/11/26/why-postgresql-major-version-upgrades-are-hard</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examining Meta-Analysis – R Works</title>
      <link>https://rworks.dev/posts/meta-analysis/</link>
      <description>In this post we would like to review the idea of meta-analysis and compare a traditional, frequentist style, random effects meta-analysis to Bayesian methods.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rworks.dev/posts/meta-analysis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice Activity Detection in Elixir and Membrane</title>
      <link>https://underjord.io/voice-activity-detection-elixir-membrane.html</link>
      <description>I hacked on something quite useful in the last few weeks, off and on. Voice Activity Detection in Elixir with Silero VAD through ONNX. I&amp;#39;ll show what I did and try to give an idea of what it is and why it is useful.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://underjord.io/voice-activity-detection-elixir-membrane.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I smash burgers</title>
      <link>https://lmno.lol/alvaro/how-i-smash-burgers</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m neither a burger expert nor a connoisseur of any kind, yet I sure have a lot of fun smashing burgers at home. Needless to say, I shamelessly enjoy gobbling them too!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lmno.lol/alvaro/how-i-smash-burgers</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving my frontend to Astro / Cory Dransfeldt</title>
      <link>https://coryd.dev/posts/2024/moving-my-frontend-to-astro/</link>
      <description>This site has an

absurd

number of pages for a personal site. Every artist, book, movie, show, genre and post get their own page. My sitemap has

4812

pages.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://coryd.dev/posts/2024/moving-my-frontend-to-astro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Storytelling: Lessons from The Dragon and The City</title>
      <link>https://blog.temaki.ai/storytelling-dragon-and-the-city/</link>
      <description>The ‘Dragon and the City’ is a storytelling framework where a city, representing our everyday world, faces a threat—a dragon—that disrupts the status quo. The dragon, while terrifying, often sits upon a treasure, symbolizing the reward of overcoming the obstacles. This bold narrative structure mirrors the challenges and opportunities present in any impactful project. Whether […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.temaki.ai/storytelling-dragon-and-the-city/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI is Fast - Yoav Anaki</title>
      <link>https://yoav.us/The+Future/AI+is+Fast</link>
      <description>AI is Fast - Yoav Anaki</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yoav.us/The+Future/AI+is+Fast</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Useful things I&amp;#39;ve 3D printed</title>
      <link>https://nathanfriend.com/2024/11/25/useful-things-ive-3d-printed.html</link>
      <description>3D printers are ridiculously cool. There’s something about seeing a digital object slowly manifest in the real world that is pure magic. But they’re also useful. Being able to custom manufacture replacement parts can save otherwise perfectly-working equipment from the landfill. I’ve written before about some of the things I’ve 3D printed, including my Zoom light and my weird keyboard; here are some other useful things I’ve printed: Monitor arm adapter My main monitor - a Samsung U28E590D - has a terrible design flaw. Its VESA mount is at the very top of the monitor! This means that when connected to my monitor arms, it sits much too low, even with the arm at its maximum height. While searching for solutions, I ran across this adapter, which effectively moves the VESA connection near the bottom of the monitor. Sadly, I couldn’t find a way to purchase it in Canada. So I decided to design and print my own! I originally printed the adapter in PETG, as PETG is strong and flexible and usually a better choice for functional prints. However, it was a little too flexible - it caused my monitor to bounce around in a sickening way whenever I bumped my desk. I printed another in PLA (unfortunately the only color I had in enough quantity was a bright blue), which is much stiffer and has mostly eliminated the wobble. The adapter, printed in blue PLA Attached to the monitor and arm My workspace post-adapter. The monitor now sits comfortably at eye-level. Thingiverse link: https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:6845708 SodaStream bottle stabilizer I drink way too much carbonated water, usually straight from the SodaStream bottle. The bottles look cool, but their tiny bases resulted in many a messy spill. The very stylish and tippable SodaStream bottle I modeled a base using the exact curvature of the bottle’s bottom, resulting in a nearly untippable receptacle. The curvature exactly matches the shape of the SodaStream bottle 100% less tippage As silly as it sounds, this simple print might be the most-used 3D printed object in my house. Thingiverse link: https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:5422282 Conduit cover When we finished our basement, I installed a conduit in the wall with the idea that maybe someday I’d set up a ceiling-mounted projector and need a clean way to route the cables. The conduit in the wall, before drywall was installed This left some unseemly holes in our wall once the drywall was in place: The opening of the conduit in the ceiling I modeled and printed covers for each end of the conduit: The cover in place The floor version They weren’t the cleanest prints, but it’s a huge improvement over the previous look! Thingiverse link: https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:6847090 Dryer lint filter handle One of my earliest functional prints was a new lint filter handle for my in-laws’ ancient dryer. The original handle had snapped off years ago and they had been using pliers to pull it out since then! The broken lint filter All fixed! Thingiverse link: https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:6847164 TV wall mount conduit When I wall-mounted our TV, I wanted a clean look without any visible cables. This involved cutting two holes through the wall behind the TV so that the cables could be run into the storage room behind the wall and then back to the cabinet underneath the TV: I let my son help me drill the holes the drywall; I think it was the highlight of his year To make this tidier, I printed two conduits that exactly matched the depth of the wall. A conduit and end cap This made running the cables much easier and cleaner. The conduit installed in the wall The end result is a floating TV that seemingly requires no power source or video cables! The end result (You might also notice the LED backlighting; this is an ambient lighting setup I installed that is powered by Hyperion, which could be the subject of a blog post of its own!) 3D printer enclosure I built my own 3D printer enclosure to help stabilize the ambient temperature during prints (especially for plastic prone to warping, like PETG). My printer enclosure While the structure itself was mainly built from wood scraps, most of the joints, hinges, and other interesting pieces were 3D printed in white PETG. A &amp;quot;print-in-place&amp;quot; hinge (which I did not design) Some other various pieces (which I did design) Printables link for the hinge: https://www.printables.com/model/120766-print-in-place-geared-hinge Laptop stand A friend needed a laptop stand, so I printed him one! The stand The stand, in action Unlike most of these other models, I didn’t design this one myself; I found it here. Thingiverse link: https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:3708825 Yeti adapter Another friend had a Yeti can insulator that was designed for 16 oz cans and was therefore too long for standard 12 oz cans. I printed a spacer so that the insulator could work with either. Appropriately branded, of course Clamping mitre box I wanted a large mitre box to help me make straight wood cuts: Mitre box While it was fun to model and print, it was ultimately a failure as it broke within the first five minutes of usage. Thingiverse link: https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:5380012 Desiccant containers 3D printer filament needs to be kept dry; it naturally absorbs humidity from the air which can negatively impact print quality. I printed some desiccant containers that I keep alongside my filament spools in a sealed plastic tub. Container for desiccant beads Although, to be honest, I don’t think they are doing much good; the desiccant beads are supposed to be recharged in the oven or microwave every few months, and ain’t nobody got time for that. Instead, I now dry individual filament spools using a food dehydrator like this. Poster frame I got this funky poster as part of a swag package from Stripe. I modeled some matching low-poly poster holders that clamp together with magnets to display in my home office. To be honest, I&amp;#39;m not really sure what it&amp;#39;s portraying? But it looks cool. Thingiverse link: https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:6848192 Smoke alarm cover Our smoke and carbon monoxide detectors expired, so I replaced the individual units with a single, combined detector. This left an empty hole in the ceiling of each room, so I printed a simple cover that snapped into the existing bracket. The cover When installed in the old detector&amp;#39;s bracket Thingiverse link: https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:6449765 Cabinet legs We bought an IKEA BEST&amp;#197; TV cabinet, but discovered the doors got caught in our shag area rug. I printed some simple legs to elevate the cabinet just enough to allow the doors to operate unobstructed. TV cabinet with legs Thingiverse link: https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:6848214 And more to come! I plan on treating this post as an evergreen log of the functional things I’ve printed. Be sure to revisit! </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nathanfriend.com/2024/11/25/useful-things-ive-3d-printed.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance archaeology: OLTP</title>
      <link>https://vondra.me/posts/postgres-performance-archaeology-oltp/</link>
      <description>History of Postgres performance improvements for OLTP workloads.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vondra.me/posts/postgres-performance-archaeology-oltp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny, Untyped Monads</title>
      <link>https://text.marvinborner.de/2024-11-18-00.html</link>
      <description>Implementing monads in untyped languages</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://text.marvinborner.de/2024-11-18-00.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You have built an Erlang</title>
      <link>https://vereis.com/posts/you_built_an_erlang</link>
      <description>Approx. 3 minutes</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vereis.com/posts/you_built_an_erlang</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 3 Years, I Failed. Here&amp;#39;s All My Startup&amp;#39;s Code. | Dylan Huang</title>
      <link>https://dylanhuang.com/blog/closing-my-startup/</link>
      <description>And by &amp;quot;all,&amp;quot; I mean everything: core product, failed pivots, miscellaneous</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dylanhuang.com/blog/closing-my-startup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonas Hietala: The current Cybershard layout</title>
      <link>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2024/11/26/the_current_cybershard_layout/</link>
      <description>Published: 



  November 26, 
  2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2024/11/26/the_current_cybershard_layout/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 01:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - xairy/lights-out: Tools for controlling webcam LED on ThinkPad X230</title>
      <link>https://github.com/xairy/lights-out</link>
      <description>Tools for controlling webcam LED on ThinkPad X230. Contribute to xairy/lights-out development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/xairy/lights-out</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neutrino Modem</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3017/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3017/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET AI Community Standup - Get started with AI in your .NET apps with the AI Dev Gallery</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5H9TxzCQfNo</link>
      <description>The AI Dev Gallery is a Windows app for developers to discover AI scenarios and how to implement them in their own apps. Meet the team behind the Gallery to learn why and how it was created, and how you can help the team make the app better for you.

Don&amp;#39;t miss this chance to contribute your ideas and help shape the Gallery for developers like you!

Community Links: https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/collections/07j6hyg872o744

Featuring: Bruno (@elbruno), Nikola (@metulev), Alexandre (@AlexandreChohfi)

#dotnet #AI #CSharp #OpenSource #AIinDev #Microsoft #AIApps</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5H9TxzCQfNo</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Ignite Announcements</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=s7ibcTqv8Y4</link>
      <description>In this edition of #tech on ice, I go over the #microsoft #ignite announcements and the ones that might be interesting for developers. #technology #programming #developer #coldplunge</description>
      <author> (Isaac Levin)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=s7ibcTqv8Y4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 19:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dramatically faster package restores with .NET 9&amp;#39;s new NuGet resolver - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-9-nuget-resolver/</link>
      <description>.NET 9 introduces a new NuGet dependency graph resolver that dramatically improves package restore performance for large repositories. Learn how this reimagined approach reduces restore times from 30 minutes to just 2 minutes by creating a more efficient dependency graph with fewer nodes.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-9-nuget-resolver/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to disable iOS 18 tab transition animation with .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://msicc.net/how-to-disable-ios18-tab-transition-animation-with-net-maui/</link>
      <description>In this post, I will show you how to deactivate the new tab transition animation Apple introduced with iOS 18 in your .NET MAUI app.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://msicc.net/how-to-disable-ios18-tab-transition-animation-with-net-maui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>