<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>10 Essential Tips Every Developer Should Try</title>
      <link>https://malshikay.medium.com/10-essential-tips-every-developer-should-try-0276384c0cb2</link>
      <description>Essential Steps to Elevate Your Development Journey</description>
      <author> (https://malshikay.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://malshikay.medium.com/10-essential-tips-every-developer-should-try-0276384c0cb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To: Formatting the Ancient Hard Drive in a PDP-11</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FOONsywfj-w</link>
      <description>Dave takes you on a trip down Hard Drive memory lane as he shows you how to replace and format the drive in a PDP-11 minicomputer, including getting the drive mounted on RT-11 and RSX-11M.  Free Sample of my Book on the Spectrum: https://amzn.to/3zBinWM

Dave&amp;#39;s Attic - Friday 4PM Podcast - https://www.youtube.com/@UCtb6a_CnmGbSns9G8W2Ny0w 

Follow me for updates!  
Twitter:   @davepl1968 davepl1968
Facebook: fb.com/davepl</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FOONsywfj-w</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform 5.5 - Automated App Packaging, .NET 9 RC2, OpenGL, WebView2 and more</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/5-5/</link>
      <description>Pixel-Perfect Multi-Platform Applications with C# and WinUI for Windows, WebAssembly, iOS, macOS, Android and Linux</description>
      <author> (Uno Platform Team)</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/5-5/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loading State for Images in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/vhugogarcia/loading-state-for-images-in-net-maui-28ng</link>
      <description>Handling the loading state for images can significantly enhance the user experience in any...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/vhugogarcia/loading-state-for-images-in-net-maui-28ng</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Power of GitHub Models in .NET with Semantic Kernel - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/github-ai-models-dotnet-semantic-kernel/</link>
      <description>Explore how to integrate GitHub&amp;#39;s AI models, like GPT, Llama and Phi, into your .NET apps using Microsoft&amp;#39;s Semantic Kernel for intelligent applications</description>
      <author> (Bruno Capuano)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/github-ai-models-dotnet-semantic-kernel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 19:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ref and Out in C#</title>
      <link>https://malshikay.medium.com/ref-and-out-in-c-423c3969eb24</link>
      <description>Understanding the difference between ref and out keywords in C#</description>
      <author> (https://malshikay.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://malshikay.medium.com/ref-and-out-in-c-423c3969eb24</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How One Line of Code Led to Catastrophe:  The Mars Polar Lander</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=9p1amOAn38M</link>
      <description>In December 1999, NASA&amp;#39;s Mars Polar Lander was on a pioneering mission to explore Mars&amp;#39; south pole, aiming to unlock secrets about the planet&amp;#39;s climate and the possibility of water ice beneath its surface. Equipped with cutting-edge technology and years of meticulous planning, the spacecraft represented a significant leap forward in planetary exploration.

But as the lander approached the Martian atmosphere, an unseen flaw lurked within its software—a tiny error buried deep in the code controlling its descent and landing sequence. This subtle glitch caused the lander to misinterpret vibrations from its leg deployment as a confirmation of touchdown while it was still high above the Martian surface. Acting on this false signal, the onboard computer prematurely shut down the descent engines.

With its engines off and no parachute to slow its fall, the Mars Polar Lander plummeted silently to the Red Planet, disappearing without a trace. Back on Earth, engineers and scientists were left in stunned silence, their hopes for groundbreaking discoveries dashed by a single overlooked line of code.

This documentary delves into the intricate world of spacecraft engineering and software development, unraveling how a minor software oversight led to the loss of a $165 million mission. Through expert interviews and detailed analysis, we explore the challenges of designing autonomous systems for space exploration, the critical importance of rigorous testing, and the lessons learned from this poignant failure.

Join us as we journey into the heart of the Mars Polar Lander&amp;#39;s story—a compelling tale of human ambition, technological complexity, and the razor-thin line between triumph and catastrophe in the quest to explore the cosmos.

Free Sample of my Book on the Spectrum: https://amzn.to/3zBinWM

Dave&amp;#39;s Attic - Friday 4PM Podcast - https://www.youtube.com/@UCtb6a_CnmGbSns9G8W2Ny0w 

Follow me for updates!  
Twitter:   @davepl1968 davepl1968
Facebook: fb.com/davepl</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=9p1amOAn38M</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time application with .NET SignalR and Angular #dotnet #csharp #coding #angular</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XCrfa6Kxv74</link>
      <description>We dive into SignalR in .NET 8 combined with Angular to create a real-time shopping list application. I’ll guide you through adding users to SignalR groups and sending notifications for real-time communication between the backend and Angular frontend. Watch as we build seamless, live updates to enhance user experience, allowing instant communication and collaboration within the app.

Perfect for developers looking to integrate real-time functionality into their projects using SignalR!</description>
      <author> (Remigiusz Zalewski)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XCrfa6Kxv74</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind Your Step (by Step): Chain-of-Thought can Reduce Performance on Tasks where Thinking Makes Humans Worse</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2410.21333</link>
      <description>Chain-of-thought (CoT) prompting has become a widely used strategy for working with large language and multimodal models. While CoT has been shown to improve performance across many tasks, determining the settings in which it is effective remains an ongoing effort. In particular, it is still an open question in what settings CoT systematically reduces model performance. In this paper, we seek to identify the characteristics of tasks where CoT reduces performance by drawing inspiration from cognitive psychology, looking at cases where (i) verbal thinking or deliberation hurts performance in humans, and (ii) the constraints governing human performance generalize to language models. Three such cases are implicit statistical learning, visual recognition, and classifying with patterns containing exceptions. In extensive experiments across all three settings, we find that a diverse collection of state-of-the-art models exhibit significant drop-offs in performance (e.g., up to 36.3% absolute accuracy for OpenAI o1-preview compared to GPT-4o) when using inference-time reasoning compared to zero-shot counterparts. We also identify three tasks that satisfy condition (i) but not (ii), and find that while verbal thinking reduces human performance in these tasks, CoT retains or increases model performance. Overall, our results show that while there is not an exact parallel between the cognitive processes of models and those of humans, considering cases where thinking has negative consequences for human performance can help us identify settings where it negatively impacts models. By connecting the literature on human deliberation with evaluations of CoT, we offer a new tool that can be used in understanding the impact of prompt choices and inference-time reasoning.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 27 Oct 2024])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2410.21333</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Use Case of Action #dotnet</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=uagqOqjt7YY</link>
      <description>Here&amp;#39;s a practical use case of the Action class in #csharp</description>
      <author> (Codewrinkles)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=uagqOqjt7YY</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Pizza 2022</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ASMgd-sVw0s</link>
      <description>It was a freudian slip... but now, its a thing #shorts

https://www.twitch.tv/csharpfritz</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ASMgd-sVw0s</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 03:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 JetBrains Rider Secrets You Should Know - Plus a Special Giveaway!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=TzzR51b4bPY</link>
      <description>&amp;#127873; Win a 1-year JetBrains dotUltimate license for FREE: https://guiferreira.kit.com/6dc25d19ef

⏲️ CHAPTERS
00:00 Intro
00:25 Feature 1
03:42 Feature 2
06:05 Feature 3
09:08 Feature 4
10:24 Feature 5
12:24 Feature 6
14:14 Feature 7
18:26 Feature 8
20:10 Feature 9

#dotnet #jetbrains</description>
      <author> (Gui Ferreira)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=TzzR51b4bPY</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 01:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House of Nettles • A Non-Technical Intro to Webmentions</title>
      <link>https://nex-3.com/blog/a-non-technical-intro-to-webmentions/</link>
      <description>I keep bringing up &amp;quot;Webmentions&amp;quot; in the context of discussing the sociable web and advocating for more people to adopt more social technologies on their websites, but I always run into a wall: there&amp;#39;s no good place to link people to so they can understand more about what that means. All the existing explanations I&amp;#39;ve found are deep in the weeds of how Webmentions work on a technical level, which isn&amp;#39;t a very helpful place to start for people who just want to post.

I want to fill that gap with this post, and give people who don&amp;#39;t know the ins and outs of HTTP a working understanding of what Webmentions do and how to get them up and running for your site. To that end:

Webmentions are a way to let a website know that you linked to it.

That&amp;#39;s it! At it&amp;#39;s core, it&amp;#39;s just that simple. If…</description>
      <author> (Natalie)</author>
      <guid>https://nex-3.com/blog/a-non-technical-intro-to-webmentions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lorentz app</title>
      <link>https://lorentz.app/blog-item.html?id=service-isolation</link>
      <description>The personal website of Lorentz Kinde, a Cloud Engineer.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lorentz.app/blog-item.html?id=service-isolation</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using CTID Based Pagination for Data Cleanups in PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://www.shayon.dev/post/2024/303/using-ctid-based-pagination-for-data-cleanups-in-postgresql/</link>
      <description>When dealing with very large PostgreSQL tables (we&amp;#39;re talking 15TB+), sometimes routine maintenance like archiving very old data can become surprisingly challenging</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.shayon.dev/post/2024/303/using-ctid-based-pagination-for-data-cleanups-in-postgresql/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratising publishing</title>
      <link>https://john.onolan.org/democratising-publishing/</link>
      <description>Thoughts on open source governance and how to create trust within technology, communities, and media.</description>
      <author> (Harvard Medical School)</author>
      <guid>https://john.onolan.org/democratising-publishing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone is wrong about that Slack flowchart – Sophie Alpert</title>
      <link>https://sophiebits.com/2024/10/30/everyone-is-wrong-about-that-slack-flowchart</link>
      <description>Building software is hard. Oftentimes things that seem like they should be simple end up being way more complicated when you get into the details. (OK, maybe this isn’t specific to software.)</description>
      <author> (Sophie Alpert)</author>
      <guid>https://sophiebits.com/2024/10/30/everyone-is-wrong-about-that-slack-flowchart</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EN]  How I upgraded my pet project from Rails 7 to Rails 8 in 30 minutes</title>
      <link>https://bpohoriletz.github.io/2024/10/30/how-i-upgraded-my-pet-project-from-rails-7-to-rails-8-in-30-minutes.html</link>
      <description>Time: 10-15 min Level: Intermediate Code: Application Revision: Oct 30, 24</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bpohoriletz.github.io/2024/10/30/how-i-upgraded-my-pet-project-from-rails-7-to-rails-8-in-30-minutes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When does the TDD approach make sense? - Luka Peharda - PHP and JS developer</title>
      <link>https://lukapeharda.com/article/when-does-the-tdd-approach-make-sense/</link>
      <description>To do TDD or not to do TDD? That is the question. Personally I never bought into TDD practices. But I always use TDD when I need to develop a feature that will require me to test a lot of different variants and edge cases.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lukapeharda.com/article/when-does-the-tdd-approach-make-sense/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authenticating People With Certificate Chains</title>
      <link>https://blog.tealok.tech/authenticating-with-certificate-chains/</link>
      <description>written by
    
      Eli Ribble
    
    on 2024-10-29</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.tealok.tech/authenticating-with-certificate-chains/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating OpenAI Whisper&amp;#39;s Hallucinations on Different Silences</title>
      <link>https://www.sabrina.dev/p/evaluating-openai-whisper-s-hallucinations-on-different-silences</link>
      <description>Fascinating experiment to see how &amp;quot;silence&amp;quot; is transcribed by OpenAI&amp;#39;s speech-to-text model, Whisper</description>
      <author> (Sabrina Ramonov)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sabrina.dev/p/evaluating-openai-whisper-s-hallucinations-on-different-silences</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the death of the architect</title>
      <link>https://explaining.software/archive/the-death-of-the-architect/</link>
      <description>Once upon a time, every project began with the creation of a canonical design document. This was called the system architecture, because it &amp;quot;rightly...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://explaining.software/archive/the-death-of-the-architect/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Breakdown: Estimating Full Projects</title>
      <link>https://shermanonsoftware.com/2024/10/30/collaborative-breakdown-estimating-full-projects/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (jeffpsherman)</author>
      <guid>https://shermanonsoftware.com/2024/10/30/collaborative-breakdown-estimating-full-projects/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to Open-Source Embedding Models</title>
      <link>https://www.bentoml.com/blog/a-guide-to-open-source-embedding-models</link>
      <description>Explore the top open-source embedding models and find answers to some FAQs about them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bentoml.com/blog/a-guide-to-open-source-embedding-models</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Karma connection in Chrome Web Store</title>
      <link>https://palant.info/2024/10/30/the-karma-connection-in-chrome-web-store/</link>
      <description>A bunch of malicious extensions in Chrome Web Store have hidden affiliate fraud functionality, collect users’ browsing profiles, or both. These extensions appear to be connected to the Karma shopping assistant, developed by Karma Shopping Ltd. which is not a small company.</description>
      <author> (Wladimir Palant)</author>
      <guid>https://palant.info/2024/10/30/the-karma-connection-in-chrome-web-store/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hetzner Considered Hostile: A PSA - Ten Forward&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://tenforward.blog/hetzner-considered-hostile-a-psa/</link>
      <description>On 8 October 2024 I received an email from Hetzner. This was a forwarded abuse report. As is standard practice in the web hosting business Hetzner forwarded this to me so I could take action on it. This was no ordinary abuse report. This was targeted harassment from a threat actor that has been harassing me and my friends for a long time. Now they have started targeting Ten Forward itself in an attempt to cause disruption in the day to day operations of Ten Forward.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tenforward.blog/hetzner-considered-hostile-a-psa/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recursion, Tidy Stars, and Water Lilies</title>
      <link>https://planktonvalhalla.com/20241030-recursion-tidy-stars-and-water-lilies/</link>
      <description>Feedback is why there are things to talk about.</description>
      <author> (Marco Giancotti)</author>
      <guid>https://planktonvalhalla.com/20241030-recursion-tidy-stars-and-water-lilies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marcus&amp;#39; Blog</title>
      <link>https://mbuffett.com/posts/optimizing-datahand-layout</link>
      <description>Ever seen this keyboard? This was called the Datahand, it was a radical new approach to keyboards that mostly only existed within a small community of RSI sufferers. It cost $2,000 in 1993, which is north of $4,000 today, so you really had to need this thing to justify the price. Even now there&amp;amp;rsquo;s a small community that continues to use these.
For a long time after Datahand shut down production, there was no real replacement.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mbuffett.com/posts/optimizing-datahand-layout</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side Effects // Richard Mavis dot info</title>
      <link>http://richardmavis.info/side-effects</link>
      <description>What it do?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://richardmavis.info/side-effects</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to export OPML from Omnivore</title>
      <link>https://sethmlarson.dev/how-to-export-opml-from-omnivore</link>
      <description>Omnivore recently announced they were bought by ElevenLabs, which is an AI company funded by Trump-supporting VC firm Andreessen Horowitz.
As a part of this deal, they are shuttering the service on...</description>
      <author> (Seth Michael Larson)</author>
      <guid>https://sethmlarson.dev/how-to-export-opml-from-omnivore</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrum doesn&amp;#39;t have to suck</title>
      <link>https://blog.raed.dev/posts/scrum_doesnt_have_to_suck</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t let dogma ruin Scrum for you !</description>
      <author> (Raed Chammam)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.raed.dev/posts/scrum_doesnt_have_to_suck</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic at the SPA! | hai.haus</title>
      <link>https://www.hai.haus/post/panic-at-the-spa/</link>
      <description>Browse high-quality photographs and read articles about computers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hai.haus/post/panic-at-the-spa/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam games will now need to fully disclose kernel-level anti-cheat on store pages</title>
      <link>https://www.gamingonlinux.com/2024/10/steam-games-will-now-need-to-fully-disclose-kernel-level-anti-cheat-on-store-pages/</link>
      <description>Valve announced a change for Steam today that will make things a lot clearer for everyone, as developers will now need to clearly list the kernel-level anti-cheat used on Steam store pages.</description>
      <author> (Liam Dawe)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gamingonlinux.com/2024/10/steam-games-will-now-need-to-fully-disclose-kernel-level-anti-cheat-on-store-pages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 23:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disposal</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3005/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3005/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 23:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>