<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Building Blazor applications on a Mac</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nS_eNFFNE1A&amp;list=PLReL099Y5nRf3mOUXCVZsfoDBSpvu8G-Q&amp;index=2</link>
      <description>Download Visual Studio: https://aka.ms/VS4MacDownload

Blazor lets you build interactive web UIs using C# instead of JavaScript, with rich web UI components implemented using C#, HTML, and CSS. Both client and server code are written in C#, allowing you to share code and libraries. Visual Studio 2019 for Mac includes support for building Blazor Server applications, and in this session, Daniel Roth and Kendra Havens are going to show you how to get started!</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Visual Studio)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nS_eNFFNE1A&amp;list=PLReL099Y5nRf3mOUXCVZsfoDBSpvu8G-Q&amp;index=2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 23:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel x86 Root of Trust: loss of trust </title>
      <link>http://blog.ptsecurity.com/2020/03/intelx86-root-of-trust-loss-of-trust.html</link>
      <description>   The scenario that Intel system architects, engineers, and security specialists perhaps feared most is now a reality. A vulnerability has ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://blog.ptsecurity.com/2020/03/intelx86-root-of-trust-loss-of-trust.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 22:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the f*** were they thinking?! Crazy website biases exposed by naughty words lists (the NSFW version)</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/what-f-were-they-thinking-crazy-website/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#x2019;ve long held the view that passwords should consist of as many crazy things as the owner deems fit. If I want to create a password that looks like a dog just ate the keyboard and threw up all the keys, then good for me. (Chances are that</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/what-f-were-they-thinking-crazy-website/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Incident Information | Help &amp;amp; Advice</title>
      <link>https://www.virginmedia.com/help/data-incident/important-information</link>
      <description>Some personal information, stored on one of our databases, has been accessed without permission. Here is the most important information you need to know</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.virginmedia.com/help/data-incident/important-information</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fancy Dress Costumes for all Occasions | Smiffys</title>
      <link>https://www.smiffys.com/</link>
      <description>Smiffys are the fancy dress experts. With over 5000 fancy dress costumes and accessories to choose from you can guarantee you will find the perfect outfit. Free delivery available.</description>
      <author> (Smiffys)</author>
      <guid>https://www.smiffys.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Sam compensates you for data leaks (yeah, right)</title>
      <link>https://www.kaspersky.com/blog/data-leak-compensation-scam/32057/</link>
      <description>Under the pretext of compensation for data leaks, fraudsters are selling "temporary U.S. social security numbers."</description>
      <author> (Tatyana Sidorina)</author>
      <guid>https://www.kaspersky.com/blog/data-leak-compensation-scam/32057/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 20:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiooooo.com - The Musical Time Machine</title>
      <link>http://radiooooo.com/</link>
      <description>Pick a decade, pick a country, and let yourself get carried away by the most beautiful musical collection in the world!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://radiooooo.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 18:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NuGet Gallery | Blazored</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/profiles/Blazored</link>
      <description>Blazored.LocalStorage

                    


                    
                        by:
                            Blazored</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/profiles/Blazored</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 18:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The History of the URL</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-history-of-the-url/</link>
      <description>On the 11th of January 1982 twenty-two computer scientists met to discuss an issue with ‘computer mail’ (now known as email).</description>
      <author> (Zack Bloom)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-history-of-the-url/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 17:41:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal notice| Aberdeen Standard Investments</title>
      <link>https://www.aberdeenstandard.com/en-us/us/investor/legal-notice#socialMedia</link>
      <description>Legal information for Aberdeen Standard Investments</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.aberdeenstandard.com/en-us/us/investor/legal-notice#socialMedia</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 16:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Yourself Into a Learning Machine</title>
      <link>https://superorganizers.substack.com/p/how-to-build-a-learning-machine###</link>
      <description>Shopify’s Director of Production Engineering explains how reading broadly helps him get to the bottom of things</description>
      <author> (Dan Shipper)</author>
      <guid>https://superorganizers.substack.com/p/how-to-build-a-learning-machine###</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 16:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Malware Analysis and Reverse Engineering</title>
      <link>https://class.malware.re/</link>
      <description>Introduction to Malware Analysis and Reverse Engineering</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://class.malware.re/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 12:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love and Math: The Heart of Hidden Reality: Edward Frenkel: 8601419969265: Amazon.com: Books</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/Love-Math-Heart-Hidden-Reality/dp/0465064957?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202003</link>
      <description>Buy Love and Math: The Heart of Hidden Reality on Amazon.com ✓ FREE SHIPPING on qualified orders</description>
      <author> (Follow the Author)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/Love-Math-Heart-Hidden-Reality/dp/0465064957?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202003</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 10:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clemens Vasters @clemensv</title>
      <link>https://www.pscp.tv/w/cS9mwzU1MzY0NXwxQmR4WVFERG1ZQXhYMAILrxXTXzPU5t7rPYdEl1ijPTsrkeUgQgAjp5cUkrg=</link>
      <description>I’m the Principal PM Architect for Messaging in the Microsoft #Azure Cloud and related standards. Come ask me questions.</description>
      <author> (Twitter Inc)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pscp.tv/w/cS9mwzU1MzY0NXwxQmR4WVFERG1ZQXhYMAILrxXTXzPU5t7rPYdEl1ijPTsrkeUgQgAjp5cUkrg=</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 10:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Levandowski ordered to pay $179 million to Google – TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2020/03/04/anthony-levandowski-ordered-to-pay-179-million-to-google/</link>
      <description>Anthony Levandowski, the engineer and autonomous vehicle startup founder who was at the center of a trade secrets lawsuit between Uber and Waymo, has been ordered to pay $179 million to end a contract dispute over his departure from Google. Reuters was the first to report the court order. An arbitr…</description>
      <author> (Kirsten Korosec@kirstenkorosec / 4:49 pm PST • March 4, 2020comment Comment)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2020/03/04/anthony-levandowski-ordered-to-pay-179-million-to-google/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 07:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landmark Computer Science Proof Cascades Through Physics and Math | Quanta Magazine</title>
      <link>https://www.quantamagazine.org/landmark-computer-science-proof-cascades-through-physics-and-math-20200304/</link>
      <description>Computer scientists established a new boundary on computationally verifiable knowledge. In doing so, they solved major open problems in quantum mechanics and</description>
      <author> (By Kevin HartnettMarch 4, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://www.quantamagazine.org/landmark-computer-science-proof-cascades-through-physics-and-math-20200304/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 07:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tyranny of I/O and the rise of distributed systems</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/190209-C/the-tyranny-of-i-o-and-the-rise-of-distributed-systems?Key=35588803-7158-41b6-86b2-a2ae15063843</link>
      <description>A system that runs on a single machine is an order of magnitude simpler than one that reside on multiple machines. The complexity involved in maintaining con...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/190209-C/the-tyranny-of-i-o-and-the-rise-of-distributed-systems?Key=35588803-7158-41b6-86b2-a2ae15063843</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 06:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor WASM Debugging Planned for Visual Studio -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/03/03/vs-roadmap.aspx</link>
      <description>  Microsoft has updated the Spring 2020 roadmap for Visual Studio, which shows several items planned to improve the debugging experience for Blazor, the company's ASP.NET Core project that uses WebAssembly (WASM) to allow C# to be used in web development instead of JavaScript.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel03/03/2020)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/03/03/vs-roadmap.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 06:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating storage accounts and blob containers using Azure fluent API-s</title>
      <link>https://gunnarpeipman.com/azure-storage-fluent-api/</link>
      <description>Using new Azure fluent API-s to create Azure storage accounts and blob containers in code is easy, resulting in flexible and readable code.</description>
      <author> (Gunnar Peipman)</author>
      <guid>https://gunnarpeipman.com/azure-storage-fluent-api/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 06:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scoping in JavaScript: The Basics</title>
      <link>https://hackernoon.com/scoping-in-javascript-the-basics-k73j32fv?source=rss</link>
      <description>Let's start with an example. You have the following code and like every good developer, your instinct cries out to remove the duplication. We should only call processVar in one spot. While having it twice might not be the end of the world, imagine additional functions need to be called while passing in x. You'd end up with a lot of duplication. Not very DRY of you. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hackernoon.com/scoping-in-javascript-the-basics-k73j32fv?source=rss</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 06:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Encrypt to revoke 3,048,289 certificates</title>
      <link>https://scotthelme.co.uk/lets-encrypt-to-revoke/</link>
      <description>Yesterday it was announced that Let's Encrypt are to revoke a large number of certificates after identifying a bug in their CA software, Boulder. This blog is here to keep a record of details related to this event and help those affected.  What happenedLet's Encrypt found a bug in their</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/scott.helme)</author>
      <guid>https://scotthelme.co.uk/lets-encrypt-to-revoke/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 06:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Encrypt discovers CAA bug, must revoke customer certificates</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2020/03/lets-encrypt-revoking-https-certs-due-to-certificate-authority-bug/</link>
      <description>Let's Encrypt users will need to manually force-renew once to avoid downtime.</description>
      <author> (Jim Salter
    -  3/3/2020, 8:42 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2020/03/lets-encrypt-revoking-https-certs-due-to-certificate-authority-bug/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 06:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WTF :: WTF - the terminal dashboard</title>
      <link>https://wtfutil.com/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wtfutil.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 04:28:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please stop recommending Git Flow! – George Stocker</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2020/03/04/please-stop-recommending-git-flow/</link>
      <description>Git-flow is a branching and merging methodology popularized by this blog post, entitled “A Successful Git branching model”.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2020/03/04/please-stop-recommending-git-flow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 04:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo Via – Waymo</title>
      <link>https://waymo.com/waymo-via/</link>
      <description>Since 2017, the Waymo Driver has been learning to drive large Class 8 trucks in much the same way a human driver would, after years of driving passenger cars. Many of the principles are the same, but things like braking, turning, and checking for blind spots are quite different with a fully-loaded truck and trailer.  We’re currently testing our fleet of trucks in California and Arizona, and we’ll soon expand to Texas and New Mexico in the near future.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://waymo.com/waymo-via/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 03:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured concurrency - Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Structured_concurrency</link>
      <description>Structured concurrency is a programming paradigm aimed at improving the clarity, quality, and development time of a computer program by using a structured approach to concurrent programming. The core concept is the encapsulation of concurrent threads of execution (here encompassing kernel and userland threads and processes) by way of control flow constructs that have clear entry and exit points and that ensure all spawned threads have completed before exit.  The concept is analogous to structured programming, which introduced control flow constructs that encapsulated sequential statements and subroutines.  Such encapsulation allows errors in concurrent threads to be propagated to the control structure's parent scope and managed by the native error handling mechanisms of each particular computer language.  It allows control flow to remain readily evident by the structure of the source code despite the presence of concurrency. To be effective, this model must be applied consistently throughout all levels of the program-- otherwise concurrent threads may leak out, become orphaned, or fail to have runtime errors correctly propagated.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Structured_concurrency</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 03:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor Tutorial : Event Handling - EP23</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wxU6wWTT4mQ</link>
      <description>Happy Coding!!

Like our page - https://www.facebook.com/curiousdrive/
Follow us on - https://twitter.com/curious_drive</description>
      <author> (Curious Drive)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wxU6wWTT4mQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 03:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing PowerShell 7.0 | PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/announcing-powershell-7-0/</link>
      <description>Today, we’re happy to announce the Generally Available (GA) release of PowerShell 7.0! Before anything else, we’d like to thank our many, many open-source contributors for making this release possible by submitting code, tests, documentation, and issue feedback. PowerShell 7 would not have been possible without your help.</description>
      <author> (Joey AielloFollow Joey)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/announcing-powershell-7-0/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 02:33:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoror — Unified monitoring wallboard</title>
      <link>https://monitoror.com/</link>
      <description>Monitoror is a wallboard monitoring app to monitor server status; monitor CI builds progress or even display critical values</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://monitoror.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 01:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Let’s use Kubernetes!” Now you have 8 problems</title>
      <link>https://pythonspeed.com/articles/dont-need-kubernetes/</link>
      <description>If you’re using Docker, the next natural step seems to be Kubernetes, aka K8s: that’s how you run things in production, right? Well, maybe. Solutions designed for 500 software engineers working on the same application are quite different than solutions for 50 software engineers. And both will be different from solutions designed for a team of 5. If you’re part of a small team, Kubernetes probably isn’t for you: it’s a lot of pain with very little benefits. Let’s see why.</description>
      <author> (Itamar Turner-Trauring)</author>
      <guid>https://pythonspeed.com/articles/dont-need-kubernetes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 01:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Explaining Copyright Broke the YouTube Copyright System</title>
      <link>https://www.law.nyu.edu/centers/engelberg/news/2020-03-04-youtube-takedown</link>
      <description>This is a story about how the most sophisticated copyright filter in the world prevented us from explaining copyright law. It doesn’t involve TikTok dance moves or nuanced 90s remixes featuring AOC. No, it involves a debate at a law school conference over how and when one song can infringe the copyright of another and how exactly one proves in a courtroom if the accused song is “substantially similar” enough to be deemed illegal.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.law.nyu.edu/centers/engelberg/news/2020-03-04-youtube-takedown</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 01:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police raid tech support scam centre who had their CCTV hacked by vigilantes</title>
      <link>https://www.grahamcluley.com/police-raid-tech-support-scam-centre/</link>
      <description>An indepth investigation by online vigilantes has exposed the activities of an Indian tech support scam centre. Extraordinarily, fraudsters had the tables turned on them as YouTuber Jim Browning was able to hack into the call centre and access recordings of scam phone calls and even watch live CCTV footage exposing the criminals at work.</description>
      <author> (Graham Cluley  12:26 pm, March 4, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://www.grahamcluley.com/police-raid-tech-support-scam-centre/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dapr - Visual Studio Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=ms-azuretools.vscode-dapr</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=ms-azuretools.vscode-dapr</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>is it canceled yet?</title>
      <link>https://www.isitcanceledyet.com/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.isitcanceledyet.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boots halts Advantage Card payments</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-51742079</link>
      <description>Attackers using stolen passwords have tried to access Boots accounts, the company says.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/bbcnews)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-51742079</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy Past Cure for Xbox One - Microsoft Store</title>
      <link>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/p/past-cure-for-xbox-one/9032m8cx3bqv</link>
      <description>U&amp;I Entertainment Past Cure Xbox One</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/p/past-cure-for-xbox-one/9032m8cx3bqv</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>