<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Power of Windows Development with Peter Bull</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ubJEOLkQ9pg</link>
      <description>The Definition of Done This episode of The Modern .NET Show is supported, in part, by &amp;quot;The Definition of Done and Other Tall Tales&amp;quot;.   The Definition of Done...</description>
      <author> (Paths of Illumination
  
  
  
    Paths of Illumination
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ubJEOLkQ9pg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 09:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S6E04 - From Silverlight to Windows App SDK: Unleashing the Power of Windows Development with Peter Bull</title>
      <link>https://dotnetcore.show/season-6/from-silverlight-to-windows-app-sdk-unleashing-the-power-of-windows-development-with-peter-bull/</link>
      <description>Seasoned developer Peter Bull joins host Jamie Taylor to dive deep into the Windows App SDK, a powerful tool for modern Windows application development. They explore the combination of Win32 and UWP frameworks, the benefits of writing tutorials to solidify knowledge, and how to get started with the Windows App SDK. They also discuss the flexibility and third-party controls available, as well as considerations when choosing between the Windows App SDK and other frameworks. This podcast is a must-listen for developers looking to create rich, native Windows applications and stay up-to-date with the latest developments in Windows application development.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetcore.show/season-6/from-silverlight-to-windows-app-sdk-unleashing-the-power-of-windows-development-with-peter-bull/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 09:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nota: A Document Language for the Browser</title>
      <link>https://nota-lang.org/#def-nota</link>
      <description>Making a world where you never have to use LaTeX again.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nota-lang.org/#def-nota</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just paying Figma $15/month because nothing else fucking works</title>
      <link>https://fasterthanli.me/articles/just-paying-figma-15-dollars</link>
      <description>My family wasn&amp;#39;t poor by any stretch of the imagination, but I was raised to
avoid spending money whenever possible. I was also taught &amp;amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s a poor craftsman that blames th...</description>
      <author> (Amos Wenger)</author>
      <guid>https://fasterthanli.me/articles/just-paying-figma-15-dollars</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please Pay For a Year of Nothing</title>
      <link>https://joe-steel.com/2023-10-19-Please-Pay-For-a-Year-of-Nothing.html</link>
      <description>This morning, two emails came in from Apple. The first was about the upcoming renewal of my yearly subscription to Disney+ and the second email was about the price increase of my Disney+ subscription from $79.99 to $109.99. It took me all of 10 seconds to think about it, but I canceled my subscription. It’s not really about the $30 price increase, which is outrageous, but mostly because there won’t be 12 months of TV show and movies to watch, in no small part thanks to the actions of Disney’s CEO.
I’m affected by the ongoing strikes, where the studios have once again walked away from the negotiating table. Almost all entertainment production has ground to a halt. The recent resolution of the WGA strike was celebrated, but it was a long, and painful process. All of our hopes, as workers in this industry, were pinned on the SAG-AFTRA dispute coming to a close. Instead, the studios decided to do what they did months ago in the WGA strike and take their case to the Hollywood trade publications owned by Penske Media in the hopes that they could gin up dissent in the union to push the union negotiators. It didn’t work with the WGA membership, and I don’t think anyone other than studio brass expects it to work on SAG-AFTRA either. There can be no resolution external to negotiation, so this just delays everything.
Films and shows that were slated to come out this year have been spread out, some pushing to next year. You can only spread things out so far, and that is particularly true of all the studio streamers that got into this game late.
When Disney+ first premiered it was criticized for only having The Mandalorian and WandaVision which were both over in the blink of an eye. Marvel, for me, has had diminishing returns since then, and I would not subscribe to Disney+ to exclusively watch anything from Marvel at this point.
Star Wars, unfortunately, is also on the bubble with several disappointments, including the most recent Star Wars: Ahsoka where I watched 50 minutes of space whales doing space whale stuff. Stretching Star Wars: Skeleton Key and Star Wars: The Acolyte out into next year, with both unlikely to be as inspired as Star Wars: Andor doesn’t convince me that $109.99 needs to leave my bank account right this very minute. If anything I can always dip in if it’s good, or wait until it’s over and binge. A year of, basically nothing, isn’t a year I need to pay for.
How Did We Get Here?
Disney, and everyone else, sold streaming licensing rights to Netflix for many years. It was like selling the broadcast rights for a film to appear on an old-fashioned TV channel. Audiences were trained to expect streaming media. Bob Iger, infamously, compared this to arms dealing, in a metaphor that no one really thought he should be making. Then Disney’s contract with Netflix ended and they went direct to consumer with Disney+.
I still remember the live-streamed shareholder meeting where Disney+ was first announced and Christine McCarthy (former CFO) outlined how the company’s low introductory price, and small number of territories, meant that it would be unprofitable for many, many years. Disney expected the stock market to treat Disney like they treated Netflix, which at the time was operating on a growth model. Everything was upended by the pandemic halting production, starving new services of new entertainment, and then by the Netflix Correction, where interest rates were up and shareholders wanted to see revenue off those subscribers, not just growth. That was not something Disney was prepared for, at any level of the company.
Bob Iger’s plans for Disney+ had blown up spectacularly and his hand-picked successor was ousted, by himself, so he could fix his own plans. Unfortunately, he’s been one of the people chiefly responsible for the WGA and SAG-AFTRA issues this year. A lot of the assumptions based on the finances of streaming have to do with taking advantage of labor contracts that didn’t cover streaming well. The AI likeness issue is a huge deal for Disney, not just the money, and they would very much like to treat actors like ageless property that can be applied to their sprawling connected universes.
Not a Boycott
Neither the writers, nor the actors, called for boycotts of the streaming services. They want to work, and they want to be paid, which means people need to pay the studios. That’s the how the system is supposed to work.
Hell, I have absolutely nothing to gain by people canceling their subscriptions. The only way I get paid is by the studios hiring VFX houses. Actors and writers don’t pay me.
Having said that, I absolutely do not need to pay studios a yearly subscription for 2024. They haven’t earned that from me on a personal level. Also none of these streaming price hikes translate into any benefit for me, the pressure is still on cutting costs in producing content.
What services every person choses to pay for are deeply personal, based on all kinds of factors, so there will be people for whom Disney+ is still essential, even without new content. Or they might be willing to step down to an ad-supported plan (I’m not). Disney+ does have an extensive library.
Same goes for Warner Brothers Discovery’s Max, which has been rightfully criticized along the way because of David Zaslav’s bumbling, and attempts to stuff the service with lower-cost unscripted fare from Discovery.
Smaller streamers are faced with these same problems, because they did what the big studios did, but they don’t have the libraries, IP, cash, or really anything to compete with the big studios. That’s why they’re small studios. It’s not that hard to understand, but it’s why Paramount+ following along has really hurt Paramount Global. While Comcast is huge, the part that’s a studio, isn’t (NBCUniversal).
Outside Money
However, things get a little more interesting with Netflix and Prime Video. My opinion of these services is not especially high. In the past month, Prime Video announced it was going to include ads in its previously ad-free entertainment, which was already intermingled with FreeVee ad-supported content. An extra recurring subscription can be paid to watch without ads. Amazon keeps tacking on all these fees onto a product that was supposed to be an all-inclusive affair. Like, that’s supposed to be their whole thing, you know? Their shows are generally expensive, and seemingly don’t do much to motivate any meaningful internal metrics for Amazon. It still pays to license some high quality TV shows and movies from others. That’s really its core value, that I’m not sure Amazon entirely understands.
Netflix’s mediocre filler piles up more and more every day. Like a machine that only knows how to spit out half-packaged products. It’s biggest asset is its size. I wouldn’t say it’s too big to fail, but it’s too ubiquitous to ever fail quickly. Which is why they can continue to generally fuck up a lot, and do stupid shit. Shareholders have calmed down since The Netflix Correction, and they’re generally content. There are no concerns about Netflix ever ratcheting up it’s fees too high, the concerns are about the slow growth of their ad-supported tier to bring in more price-conscious consumers.
The most recent stumble for Netflix has been in kid-focused animated entertainment. Their history was mostly with buying up stuff from outside companies (Mitchells vs the Machines is frequently cited as a Netflix film, but it’s a Sony Pictures Animation film that Sony sold off in the pandemic), until they started their own internal division. Then last week they announced they were killing projects and cutting staff. Then this week they announced they were going to be taking over Apple’s end of their deal with Skydance Animation. The animation company owned by nepo baby David Ellison, and headed up by the disgraced John Lasseter. David proved to the world that it was worth it to hire John by releasing Luck, a film that at best, was fine but not a critical or financial success for Apple.
Netflix’s flailing with making their own films and TV shows kind of doesn’t matter because they’re so big that they can turn licensed library material into a phenomenon. The most recent example being the craze over Suits which originally aired on USA Network, owned by Comcast Universal. Comcast Universal can’t turn anything into a success because it entered the market late with Peacock, and no one could think of a reason to subscribe to it if they weren’t already a Comcast customer.
This ability to turn something that could be a small success, and large financial loss, into a big hit by virtue of its ubiquity is what Netflix does best. To circle back to animation, this is also why the plug was pulled on the Paramount+ and Nickelodeon show Star Trek: Prodigy and it found a home on Netflix. Paramount Global will get money for something that wasn’t working for them, because Paramount+ isn’t ubiquitous.
Netlfix has also licensed a bunch of HBO shows, which is hugely damaging to Max, because it trains customers to expect HBO shows eventually coming to Netflix, but does help Netflix with their quality problem.
So Netflix increasing their prices to nearly cable-package prices? It’s not something I like at all, but it’s working for them because they’re basically a cable package of licensed stuff again, like they were before the studios panicked and tried to start their own streamers.
They can weather anything 2024 throws at them because there will always be studios desperate enough to sell shows to them, even if that excludes Disney. The SAG-AFTRA dispute could go on for another year and they’d buy their way through it. As repulsive as that thought is, it’s true.
The Lost Year
There is, unfortunately, the very real possibility that nothing gets resolved before the winter holidays — or even if it does, productions won’t start ramping up until next January or February. When it resumes, it’s not like turning on a light switch. The entertainment industry works with overlapping schedules. This production starts while this one wraps, this is shooting while this is in post. You just can’t do everything in parallel all at the same time. That means we’re also going to get a trickle of finished TV shows and films. Even lowering the standards, and “putting a rush” on it doesn’t bypass everyone else doing exactly the same thing.
That means that even if people aren’t anticipating the drop in stuff to watch, they will eventually realize that there’s not much new. It’s going to be much harder to get those people to resubscribe, at high prices, than it was to get them to subscribe the first time.
I’m not sure what’s going to get me to reactivate Disney+, maybe it’ll be whenever the second season of Andor comes out towards the end of 2024 or early 2025, but it’ll just be the two months the show runs, and then I’m out again like the Falcon leaving the Death Star. Disney has lost yearly subscription rights in this household. A brand is a promise and the only promise I’m interested in from Disney is a single TV show, on a calendar far, far away.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joe-steel.com/2023-10-19-Please-Pay-For-a-Year-of-Nothing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Server-side rendering (SSR) for Blazor in .NET 8</title>
      <link>https://www.roundthecode.com/dotnet-tutorials/server-side-rendering-ssr-blazor-dotnet-8</link>
      <description>Server-side rendering (SSR) is a render mode which has become a new Blazor feature for .NET 8, working in a similar way to ASP.NET Core MVC.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.roundthecode.com/dotnet-tutorials/server-side-rendering-ssr-blazor-dotnet-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple’s use of Swift and SwiftUI in iOS 17</title>
      <link>https://blog.timac.org/2023/1019-state-of-swift-and-swiftui-ios17/</link>
      <description>Now that iOS 17 is available, let’s analyze its built-in apps to answer a few questions: How many binaries are in iOS 17? Which programming languages are used to develop these apps? How many apps are written with Swift? What is the percentage of apps using SwiftUI versus UIKit?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.timac.org/2023/1019-state-of-swift-and-swiftui-ios17/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor Basics: Blazor Routing and Navigation Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/blazor-basics-blazor-routing-navigation-fundamentals</link>
      <description>Routing is a key feature of any single-page application. It allows the developer to arrange the website and the user to navigate different pages.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/blazor-basics-blazor-routing-navigation-fundamentals</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 06:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved DynamoDB Initialization Patterns for the AWS SDK for .NET | Amazon Web Services</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/improved-dynamodb-initialization-patterns-for-the-aws-sdk-for-net/</link>
      <description>The&amp;#160;AWS SDK for .NET includes the&amp;#160;Document and Object Persistence programming models, which provide an idiomatic .NET experience for working with&amp;#160;Amazon DynamoDB. Beginning in&amp;#160;AWSSDK.DynamoDBv2 3.7.203, there are new ways to initialize the document and object persistence models which can improve your application’s performance by reducing thread contention and throttling issues during the first call to DynamoDB. […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/improved-dynamodb-initialization-patterns-for-the-aws-sdk-for-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 06:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 6 - Parallel.ForEachAsync</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/10/net-6-parallelforeachasync.html</link>
      <description>You maybe used Parallel.ForEach()  before. It allows to iterate over a collection in a parallel way. It works similar to a Parallel.For  loo...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/10/net-6-parallelforeachasync.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 06:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Million Users Exposed in Educational Robot Company Data Breach</title>
      <link>https://www.safetydetectives.com/news/sphero-leak-report/</link>
      <description>A hacker allegedly stole and exposed the data of users from Sphero’s database, affecting an estimated 1 million educators and students.
SafetyDetectives’ cybers</description>
      <author> (SafetyDetectives Cybersecurity Team)</author>
      <guid>https://www.safetydetectives.com/news/sphero-leak-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 06:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Premature Infrastructure is the Root of All Evil</title>
      <link>https://michaelscodingspot.com/premature-infrastructure-is-evil/</link>
      <description>Premature infrastructure is a peculiar behavior pattern that I witnessed in every single tech company I worked for. It is the habit of creating infrastructure code before it is actually needed. The development team is predicting future requirements and preparing ahead of time. That might be preparation for a future feature, extension capabilities that aren’t needed yet, or customization that may or may not be wanted.
I believe that creating premature infrastructures is one of the biggest problems in software development.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://michaelscodingspot.com/premature-infrastructure-is-evil/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 06:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of WebAssembly 2023</title>
      <link>https://blog.scottlogic.com/2023/10/18/the-state-of-webassembly-2023.html</link>
      <description>This blog posts shares the results of the third annual State of WebAssembly survey, where we found that Rust and JavaScript usage continues to increase, but there is a growing desire for Zig and Kotlin. The use of wasm as a plugin environment continues to climb,  with developers hoping it will deliver of the “write once and run anywhere” promise.</description>
      <author> (Colin Eberhardt)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.scottlogic.com/2023/10/18/the-state-of-webassembly-2023.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 06:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagining the Ideal GraphQL Integration for Marten</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/10/19/imagining-the-ideal-graphql-integration-for-marten/</link>
      <description>I’m seeing an increasing amount of interest in exposing Marten data behind GraphQL endpoints from folks in the Critter Stack Discord channels and from current JasperFx Software clients. After…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/10/19/imagining-the-ideal-graphql-integration-for-marten/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 23:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 370</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=fvXY-Sti9Ok</link>
      <description>Twitter and the $1 Fee: Comparable Precedents, Verified Bots, Whistleblowers, Abusive Spouses, Stolen &amp;amp; Burner Cards, Elon is a Poo Poo Head</description>
      <author> (Deep Dive with Ali Abdaal 
  
  
  
    Deep Dive with Ali Abdaal 
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=fvXY-Sti9Ok</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 23:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serializing and Deserializing JSON in C# with System.Text.Json</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=isdfIIYGH-E</link>
      <description>In this short video, I walk through how you can use the System.Text.Json package in C# to easily serialize and deserialize JSON using different configuration...</description>
      <author> (AI Anytime
  
  
  
    AI Anytime
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=isdfIIYGH-E</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 23:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 reasons to delay adopting .NET 8 and 10 to do it ASAP</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/3-reasons-to-delay-adopting-net-8-and-10-to-do-it-asap/</link>
      <description>Pixel-Perfect Multi-Platform Applications with C# and WinUI for Windows, WebAssembly, iOS, macOS, Android and Linux</description>
      <author> (Uno Platform Team)</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/3-reasons-to-delay-adopting-net-8-and-10-to-do-it-asap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hampton Blog</title>
      <link>https://joinhampton.com/blog/mae-karwowski-obviously</link>
      <description>A private and highly vetted network for high-growth founders and CEOs.</description>
      <author> (BY Ethan Brooks)</author>
      <guid>https://joinhampton.com/blog/mae-karwowski-obviously</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I turned down $16M for my startup. Here’s why...</title>
      <link>https://www.groovehq.com/helpdesk-software/imperfect-startup/startup-acquisition-offer</link>
      <description>It was a tempting offer, but when it came down to signing on the dotted line, there were five reasons that convinced me to decline an acquisition offer and bet on growth for Groove.</description>
      <author> (Alex Turnbull)</author>
      <guid>https://www.groovehq.com/helpdesk-software/imperfect-startup/startup-acquisition-offer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking notes for effective learning</title>
      <link>https://hcrypt.net/2023/10/19/notes/</link>
      <description>I have been learning a lot of cool things lately and it was becoming a bit difficult to retain all the information that I had learnt.</description>
      <author> (Hcrypt)</author>
      <guid>https://hcrypt.net/2023/10/19/notes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Me To Search: A Complete Guide on Adding Yourself to Google People Card</title>
      <link>https://acodez.in/add-me-to-search-a-complete-guide-on-adding-yourself-to-google-people-card/</link>
      <description>In this article, we examine the benefits and steps to adding yourself to a Google People Card, but first, let us understand the essence of &amp;quot;Add Me To Search&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/farhan.srambiyan)</author>
      <guid>https://acodez.in/add-me-to-search-a-complete-guide-on-adding-yourself-to-google-people-card/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stream Deck for Developers</title>
      <link>https://adam.ac/blog/stream-deck-for-developers/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve always been keen on creating shortcuts and macros for everything and this is how I&amp;#39;m using a Stream Deck XL to make things even easier.</description>
      <author> (Adam Cooke)</author>
      <guid>https://adam.ac/blog/stream-deck-for-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the machine reads a letter about LLMs</title>
      <link>https://shragafeivel.com/2023/10/19/the-machine-reads-a-letter-about-llms/</link>
      <description>We asked the machine to read a recent post: Presumably the more orthodox style of the LLM-generated tone will be more friendly to the new reader. The forwarded message you’ve provided covers …</description>
      <author> (powera)</author>
      <guid>https://shragafeivel.com/2023/10/19/the-machine-reads-a-letter-about-llms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Web Is For User Agency</title>
      <link>https://berjon.com/user-agency/</link>
      <description>We take the Web for granted as that thing that&amp;#39;s there and we talk of things being good or bad for the Web, but we don&amp;#39;t ever sit down and really say what the Web is for. I take a look at this question with an eye towards understanding what it is we need to do to build a Web that&amp;#39;s actually better.</description>
      <author> (Robin Berjon)</author>
      <guid>https://berjon.com/user-agency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full-Stack Something</title>
      <link>https://anuatluru.com/blog/fullstacksomething</link>
      <description>my working theories</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anuatluru.com/blog/fullstacksomething</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advice on early-stage fundraising</title>
      <link>https://philippzentner.com/advice-on-early-stage-fundraising.html</link>
      <description>More in-depth advice on how to execute a fundraise within an early stage startup. Mentallity, preparation and execution.</description>
      <author> (Philipp Zentner)</author>
      <guid>https://philippzentner.com/advice-on-early-stage-fundraising.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networking as an introvert CTO</title>
      <link>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/networking-introvert-cto/</link>
      <description>There I was, standing in the middle of a buzzing tech event that our company organized, feeling like a fish out of water. The room was filled with</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/vadim.kravcenko.dev)</author>
      <guid>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/networking-introvert-cto/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On automating unit tests with LLMs.</title>
      <link>https://jakobs.dev/on-automating-unit-tests-with-llms/</link>
      <description>Using LLMs for auto-generating unit tests aids rapid development in building Python libraries, but while beneficial, it&amp;#39;s no substitute for deliberate test-writing and might create a false safety net</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jakobs.dev/on-automating-unit-tests-with-llms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AppSec loves Agile</title>
      <link>https://beny23.github.io/posts/appsec_loves_agile/</link>
      <description>I describe myself as an Agile Fundamentalist because I really like the ideas of the Agile manifesto, and I also confidently state that I am an AppSec snooper, because in my day job I tend to look at other people’s code, logs and systems and break them. I happen to think that agile and application security go together rather well!
I had two different Slack conversations recently. One was on the UK cross-governmental #security Slack channel and the other one was on the Equal Experts #securit-ee Slack channel (yes I’m a consultant, and our Slack channels have hilariously got ee in their names).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://beny23.github.io/posts/appsec_loves_agile/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debugging a kdump kernel crash</title>
      <link>https://rustylife.github.io/2023/10/19/veeamsnap-kernel-crash.html</link>
      <description>Debugging a kernel bug could be a challenging task.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rustylife.github.io/2023/10/19/veeamsnap-kernel-crash.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 22:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering asynchronous code, threading and parallelism workshop and .NET DeveloperDays 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233928-mastering-asynchronous-code-threading-and-parallelism-workshop-and-net-developerdays-2023</link>
      <description>19 Oct 2023
	
	 2 mins
	
	 Presentations &amp;amp; Speaking</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233928-mastering-asynchronous-code-threading-and-parallelism-workshop-and-net-developerdays-2023</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 21:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Thoughts 15 years into Software Engineering</title>
      <link>https://roughlywritten.substack.com/p/random-thoughts-15-years-into-software</link>
      <description>I’m coming up on 15 years of professional software engineering. I’ve worked at companies from unknown startups to large FAANG-like silicon valley companies and everywhere in between. In no particular order, sharing some things I’ve learned that others may find helpful.</description>
      <author> (Ryan O&amp;#39;Neill)</author>
      <guid>https://roughlywritten.substack.com/p/random-thoughts-15-years-into-software</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 18:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google-hosted malvertising leads to fake Keepass site that looks genuine</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2023/10/google-hosted-malvertising-leads-to-fake-keepass-site-that-looks-genuine/</link>
      <description>Google-verified advertiser + legit-looking URL + valid TLS cert = convincing look-alike.</description>
      <author> (Dan Goodin
    -    10/18/2023, 9:50 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/security/2023/10/google-hosted-malvertising-leads-to-fake-keepass-site-that-looks-genuine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Software Pro&amp;#39;s Best Kept Secret.</title>
      <link>https://app.codecrafters.io/courses/bittorrent/overview</link>
      <description>Real-world proficiency projects designed for experienced engineers. Develop software craftsmanship by recreating popular devtools from scratch.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://app.codecrafters.io/courses/bittorrent/overview</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRM-Free e-Books Are Now Available. Here’s Why That’s a Big Deal</title>
      <link>https://www.libraryjournal.com/story/drm-free-e-books-are-now-available-heres-why-thats-a-big-deal</link>
      <description>Since e-books first emerged as a way for readers to consume content digitally, publishers and authors have required content aggregators to apply Digital Rights Management (DRM) technology to the e-books they sell to libraries to prevent the unauthorized use, copying, and redistribution of these materials. While this practice has given publishers and authors peace of mind that sales won’t be lost to piracy or other unauthorized sharing, it has placed undue restrictions on readers who rely on institutional access to e-books.</description>
      <author> (EBSCO)</author>
      <guid>https://www.libraryjournal.com/story/drm-free-e-books-are-now-available-heres-why-thats-a-big-deal</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 14:04:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s the difference between setting a page&amp;#39;s protection to PAGE_NOACCESS and freeing it? - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231019-00/?p=108907</link>
      <description>Nobody can access it, but it&amp;#39;s still there.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20231019-00/?p=108907</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 14:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events are an API. Treat them that way!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=qf-BSAhbrWw</link>
      <description>Events are an API. Treat them that way. Often events are thought of as either domain events or integration events. But there&amp;#39;s more of a distinction to be ma...</description>
      <author> (CodeOpinion
  
  
  
    CodeOpinion
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=qf-BSAhbrWw</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 13:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Implement the Facade Pattern in C# for Simplified Code and Increased Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/10/19/how-to-implement-the-facade-pattern-in-c-for-simplified-code-and-increased-efficiency/</link>
      <description>Want to simplify complex subsystems in your C# project? Learn about the Facade Pattern in C#. Explore an implementation and real-world examples in this article!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/10/19/how-to-implement-the-facade-pattern-in-c-for-simplified-code-and-increased-efficiency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 13:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks: Data Sharding with Oren Eini</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/200257-A/net-rocks-data-sharding-with-oren-eini?Key=2f029000-e491-4ad5-b1bc-0cee8f61ddc2</link>
      <description>You can listen to me talk to Carl &amp;amp;amp; Richard on RavenDB Sharding here.What is data sharding, and why do you need it? Carl and Richard talk to Oren Eini ab...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/200257-A/net-rocks-data-sharding-with-oren-eini?Key=2f029000-e491-4ad5-b1bc-0cee8f61ddc2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 13:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - localsend/localsend: An open source cross-platform alternative to AirDrop</title>
      <link>https://github.com/localsend/localsend</link>
      <description>An open source cross-platform alternative to AirDrop - GitHub - localsend/localsend: An open source cross-platform alternative to AirDrop</description>
      <author> (localsend)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/localsend/localsend</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 12:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>