<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>MassTransit Bus Stop - SQL Transport Update</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=F0lQUYSvSh8</link>
      <description>So much progress on the SQL transport since it was first announced. The SQL Database Transport for MassTransit is a game-changing addition that will transfor...</description>
      <author> (Chris Patterson
  
  
  
    Chris Patterson
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=F0lQUYSvSh8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to IoT with .NET and Meadow</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=0eUQcD295tY</link>
      <description>James is joined Bryan from Wilderness Labs to talk about what products and frameworks they offer for .NET developers to build IoT solutions with .NET. Bryan ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=0eUQcD295tY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insidious implicit statistical assumptions | Andrey Akinshin</title>
      <link>https://aakinshin.net/posts/insidious-assumptions/</link>
      <description>Recently, I was rereading &amp;amp;ldquo;Robust Statistics: The Approach Based on Influence Functions&amp;amp;rdquo; by Frank Hampel et al. and I found this quote about the difference between robust and nonparametric statistics (page 9):
Robust statistics considers the eff...</description>
      <author> (Andrey Akinshin)</author>
      <guid>https://aakinshin.net/posts/insidious-assumptions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nim v2.0 released</title>
      <link>https://nim-lang.org/blog/2023/08/01/nim-v20-released.html</link>
      <description>The Nim team is proud and happy to announce Nim version 2.0.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nim-lang.org/blog/2023/08/01/nim-v20-released.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Giorgi Dalakishvili: Beyond Relational Data with Entity Framework - Episode 255</title>
      <link>http://feed.azuredevops.show/giorgi-dalakishvili-beyond-relational-data-with-entity-framework-episode-255</link>
      <description>Giorgi Dalakishvili is a software developer with more than a decade of experience. He works mainly with C#,  MVC/ Core, REST, WCF, Xamarin, Android, iOS, Entity Framework, Azure, SQL Server, and Oracle. &amp;amp;nbsp; Giorgi is an open-source author and contributor on GitHub and a member of the .NET Foundation and InfoQ Editor. &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [3:33] Giorgi has worked with all the frameworks and libraries that Microsoft has come out with over the past 10‒15 years. He discusses using Entity Framework and starting his small speaking engagements. [5:12]  is a website where you can put out some different topics that you’d be willing to speak on, and just reach out to different user groups to take the plunge and do some public speaking for the first time. [6:03] Other types of data with Entity Framework beyond relational data, such as hierarchical data type from SQL Server. [8:49] How it simplifies your life. [9:28] What about JSON? Are there any limitations on the back-end database? [13:00] Is the support in EF Core 7.0 good enough to give a try if you’re going against SQL Server? [14:09] What other types of data are interesting to work with with Entity Framework? [14:36] Using geospatial data. What does it even look like? [18:30] Full text search, and how it’s different from a regular text search. [23:20] There are a lot of features to uncover in relational databases that we aren’t even aware of yet. [26:22] There are some problems and some tasks that are better solved with non-relational databases, but the majority can overlap between the two systems. &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episodes:     — New Video Podcast! Email us   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!  — Follow to stay informed about future events!  — Video podcast!    &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://feed.azuredevops.show/giorgi-dalakishvili-beyond-relational-data-with-entity-framework-episode-255</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside STL: The pair and the compressed pair - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230801-00/?p=108509</link>
      <description>Two fields in one object, how hard can it be?</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230801-00/?p=108509</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 14:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Integration Tests for .NET 7 API with WebApplicationFactory and NUnit</title>
      <link>https://www.code4it.dev/blog/advanced-integration-tests-webapplicationfactory/</link>
      <description>Integration Tests are incredibly useful: a few Integration Tests are often more useful than lots of Unit Tests. Let’s learn some advanced capabilities of WebApplicationFactory.</description>
      <author> (Davide Bellone)</author>
      <guid>https://www.code4it.dev/blog/advanced-integration-tests-webapplicationfactory/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Form Validation and More with Data Triggers - .NET MAUI 101</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=K9jDlt0_5Us</link>
      <description>Using data binding and no code at all, you can still disable controls and change their appearance! That is exactly what we&amp;#39;ll see in this video! Curious abou...</description>
      <author> (Devs School
  
  
  
    Devs School
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=K9jDlt0_5Us</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The BEST Design Pattern for Maintainable Tests</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pwj_sw31mfw</link>
      <description>What is the Builder Design Pattern and how to use it to build better and maintainable tests?&amp;#128142; Be a Patreon to get the source code: https://patreon.com/gsfer...</description>
      <author> (LambdaTest
  
  
  
    LambdaTest
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pwj_sw31mfw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Worst API Ever Made</title>
      <link>https://caseymuratori.com/blog_0025</link>
      <description>A call-by-call look at context switch logging with the Event Tracing for Windows API.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://caseymuratori.com/blog_0025</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where To Place Your Validation Code In Clean Architecture</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=OhQA4PDdp0Q</link>
      <description>&amp;#128640; Support me on Patreon to access the source code: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovicValidation is critical for a secure and maintainable application. S...</description>
      <author> (Codewrinkles
  
  
  
    Codewrinkles
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=OhQA4PDdp0Q</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Practices for Azure Infrastructure - Continuous Operations &amp;amp; Continuous Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://www.tpeczek.com/2023/08/devops-practices-for-azure.html</link>
      <description>This the last post in my series on implementing DevOps practices for Azure infrastructure where I complete the operations side of the loop.</description>
      <author> (Tomasz Pęczek)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tpeczek.com/2023/08/devops-practices-for-azure.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superconductor Pb$_{10-x}$Cu$_x$(PO$_4$)$_{6O}$ showing levitation at room temperature and atmospheric pressure and mechanism</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2307.12037</link>
      <description>A material called LK-99, a modified-lead apatite crystal structure with the
composition Pb$_{10-x}$Cu$_x$(PO$_4$)$_{6O}$ ($0.9&amp;lt;x&amp;lt;1.1$), has been
synthesized using the solid-state method. The material exhibits the Ohmic metal
characteristic of Pb(6s1) above its superconducting critical temperature,
$T_c$, and the levitation phenomenon as Meissner effect of a superconductor at
room temperature and atmospheric pressure below $T_c$. A LK-99 sample shows
$T_c$ above 126.85$^	rc$C (400 K). We analyze that the possibility of
room-temperature superconductivity in this material is attributed to two
factors: the first being the volume contraction resulting from an
insulator-metal transition achieved by substituting Pb with Cu, and the second
being on-site repulsive Coulomb interaction enhanced by the structural
deformation in the one-dimensional(D) chain (Pb2-O$_{1/2}$-Pb2 along the
c-axis) structure owing to superconducting condensation at $T_c$. The mechanism
of the room-temperature $T_c$ is discussed by 1-D BR-BCS theory.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 22 Jul 2023 (v1), last revised 29 Jul 2023 (this version, v2)])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2307.12037</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Bicep - The Evolution of ARM Templates</title>
      <link>https://www.claudiobernasconi.ch/2023/08/01/introduction-to-bicep-the-evolution-of-arm-templates/</link>
      <description>Bicep is a transpiler that transforms domain-specific language into ARM templates. It&amp;#39;s the next generation of Microsoft&amp;#39;s infrastructure as code tooling.</description>
      <author> (Claudio Bernasconi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.claudiobernasconi.ch/2023/08/01/introduction-to-bicep-the-evolution-of-arm-templates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get ChatGPT to Stop Apologizing?</title>
      <link>https://genai.stackexchange.com/questions/177/how-to-get-chatgpt-to-stop-apologizing</link>
      <description>Is there a way to stop ChatGPT from excessively apologizing, when challenged, even when ChatGPT is correct in its reply?
ChatGPT will start apologizing and start the replies with sentences like:

I </description>
      <author> (Arbel)</author>
      <guid>https://genai.stackexchange.com/questions/177/how-to-get-chatgpt-to-stop-apologizing</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>icanhazip: How a simple IP address tool survived a deluge of users | APNIC Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.apnic.net/2021/06/17/how-a-small-free-ip-tool-survived/</link>
      <description>Major Hayden made a simple and free tool to check the public-facing IP address of infrastructure. Its popularity nearly killed it.</description>
      <author> (Major Hayden)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.apnic.net/2021/06/17/how-a-small-free-ip-tool-survived/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding Faster with dotNetTips.com Spargine 6: Aug 2023 Release</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/08/01/coding-faster-with-dotnettips-com-spargine-6-aug-2023-release/</link>
      <description>Spargine 6 (v2023.6.8.1) is now available, an open-source project offering NuGet packages for .NET 6 &amp;amp; 7 with new classes, methods, and significant speed improvements. The release introduces a …</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave
		

		
			I live in San Diego, Ca USA			
				View all posts by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/08/01/coding-faster-with-dotnettips-com-spargine-6-aug-2023-release/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 09:03:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Mocking With NSubstitute in .NET - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-effective-mocking-with-nsubstitute/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will delve into the world of mocking with NSubstitute in .NET and explore how it can help us create comprehensive tests.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-effective-mocking-with-nsubstitute/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 09:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing IDisposableOf&amp;lt;T&amp;gt;: A New Design Pattern</title>
      <link>https://itnext.io/introducing-idisposableof-t-a-new-design-pattern-e62aa4b2d7b0?source=rss-6d96c8d6335b------2</link>
      <description>In the dynamic world of software development, innovation is the name of the game. Developers constantly seek to create tools and practices…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@csharpwriter)</author>
      <guid>https://itnext.io/introducing-idisposableof-t-a-new-design-pattern-e62aa4b2d7b0?source=rss-6d96c8d6335b------2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 08:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Origin of correlated isolated flat bands in copper-substituted lead phosphate apatite</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2307.16892</link>
      <description>A recent report of room temperature superconductivity at ambient pressure in
Cu-substituted apatite (`LK99&amp;#39;) has invigorated interest in the understanding
of what materials and mechanisms can allow for high-temperature
superconductivity. Here I perform density functional theory calculations on
Cu-substituted lead phosphate apatite, identifying correlated isolated flat
bands at the Fermi level, a common signature of high transition temperatures in
already established families of superconductors. I elucidate the origins of
these isolated bands as arising from a structural distortion induced by the Cu
ions and a chiral charge density wave from the Pb lone pairs. These results
suggest that a minimal two-band model can encompass much of the low-energy
physics in this system. Finally, I discuss the implications of my results on
possible superconductivity in Cu-doped apatite</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 31 Jul 2023])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2307.16892</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 07:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semiconducting transport in Pb10-xCux(PO4)6O sintered from Pb2SO5 and Cu3P</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2307.16802</link>
      <description>The very recent claim on the discovery of ambient-pressure room-temperature
superconductivity in modified lead-apatite has immediately excited sensational
attention in the entire society, which is fabricated by sintering lanarkite
(Pb2SO5) and copper(I) phosphide (Cu3P). To verify this exciting claim, we have
successfully synthesized Pb2SO5, Cu3P, and finally the modified lead-apatite
Pb10-xCux(PO4)6O. Detailed electrical transport and magnetic properties of
these compounds were systematically analyzed. It turns out that Pb2SO5 is a
highly insulating diamagnet with a room-temperature resistivity of ~7.18x10^9
Ohm.cm and Cu3P is a paramagnetic metal with a room-temperature resistivity of
~5.22x10^-4 Ohm.cm. In contrast to the claimed superconductivity, the resulting
Pb10-xCux(PO4)6O compound sintered from Pb2SO5 and Cu3P exhibits
semiconductor-like transport behavior with a large room-temperature resistivity
of ~1.94x10^4 Ohm.cm although our compound shows greatly consistent x-ray
diffraction spectrum with the previously reported structure data. In addition,
when a pressed Pb10-xCux(PO4)6O pellet is located on top of a commercial
Nd2Fe14B magnet at room temperature, no repulsion could be felt and no magnetic
levitation was observed either. These results imply that the claim of a
room-temperature superconductor in modified lead-apatite may need more careful
re-examination, especially for the electrical transport properties.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 31 Jul 2023])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2307.16802</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 07:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help the Library of Congress Create Video Games that Improve Public Knowledge of Civics | In Custodia Legis</title>
      <link>https://blogs.loc.gov/law/2023/06/help-the-library-of-congress-create-video-games-that-improve-public-knowledge-of-civics/</link>
      <description>The Friends of the Library of Congress are sponsoring a challenge to help improve public knowledge of civics–that is, the rights and responsibilities of citizens-by asking video games developers to create fun, lightweight video games related to civics that incorporate Library of Congress resources.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.loc.gov/law/2023/06/help-the-library-of-congress-create-video-games-that-improve-public-knowledge-of-civics/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 07:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Jesper Kr&amp;#230;gp&amp;#248;th Ryder – The Future Is Here! WebAssembly for .NET Developers – Recording Available | The .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/07/31/joshua-jesper-kraegpoth-ryder-the-future-is-here-webassembly-for-dotnet-developers-recording-available/</link>
      <description>This is a recording of a live JetBrains webinar about WebAssembly explained to the .NET audience and why it&amp;#39;s important.</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2023/07/31/joshua-jesper-kraegpoth-ryder-the-future-is-here-webassembly-for-dotnet-developers-recording-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to handle transactions in Node.js reference architecture | Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/31/how-handle-transactions-nodejs-reference-architecture</link>
      <description>This installment of our Node.js reference architecture series covers integrating transactions into your application. (Part 15)</description>
      <author> (Michael Dawson)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/31/how-handle-transactions-nodejs-reference-architecture</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using C# source generation for enhanced logging - Bruno Sonnino</title>
      <link>https://blog.revolution.com.br/2023/07/29/using-c-source-generation-for-enhanced-logging/</link>
      <description>In the last article, I wrote about logging in C# and how to use log formatters to suit your needs. Once you start adding logs to your applications, you start to notice there is too much info that you must add to every message: the event id, level, scopes, besides the message (which you can</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.revolution.com.br/2023/07/29/using-c-source-generation-for-enhanced-logging/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top React Testing Libraries in 2023: A Comprehensive Review</title>
      <link>https://www.sitepoint.com/top-react-testing-libraries-in-2023/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will explore some of the top React testing libraries. We&amp;#39;ll examine their features, and look at the pros and cons.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sitepoint.com/top-react-testing-libraries-in-2023/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 06:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help! I accidently enabled HSTS–on localhost</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/07/help-i-accidently-enabled-hstson.html</link>
      <description>I ran into an issue after accidently enabling HSTS for a website on localhost. This was not an issue for the original website that was runni...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/07/help-i-accidently-enabled-hstson.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 06:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The unit test that you should try not to write</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@csharpwriter/the-unit-test-that-you-should-try-not-to-write-c68dab266903</link>
      <description>Unit testing is an essential part of software development, and it involves testing small, isolated pieces of code, known as units, to…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@csharpwriter)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@csharpwriter/the-unit-test-that-you-should-try-not-to-write-c68dab266903</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 05:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EI012: AI Processing Service (Part 6)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Qj8dBTzmb-g</link>
      <description>In this session, we will be continuing to develop validation logic for a list of inputs for AI Processing Services.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Qj8dBTzmb-g</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 05:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Python String Data Type | Pro Code Guide</title>
      <link>https://procodeguide.com/python-tutorials/understanding-python-string/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will learn about Python string data types. We will explore how to assign text or multiple-line text to a string in Python programming</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://procodeguide.com/python-tutorials/understanding-python-string/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 05:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims of Room Temperature and Ambient Pressure Superconductor</title>
      <link>https://forums.spacebattles.com/threads/claims-of-room-temperature-and-ambient-pressure-superconductor.1106083/page-11?post=94266395#post-94266395</link>
      <description>Compilation of all Claims/Reports of Replication Efforts underway that I know of (all Reliability of Claim classifications are based on my personal judgement, do not take them at face value, read the details and judge for yourself) :

Official/Professional/Institutional



Group
Country...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://forums.spacebattles.com/threads/claims-of-room-temperature-and-ambient-pressure-superconductor.1106083/page-11?post=94266395#post-94266395</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 05:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fall of Stack Overflow, Explained</title>
      <link>https://newsletter.devmoh.co/p/the-fall-of-stack-overflow-explained?r=1nwcx</link>
      <description>Stack Overflow&amp;#39;s decline is partly self-imposed, but also somewhat out if its control.</description>
      <author> (Priyam)</author>
      <guid>https://newsletter.devmoh.co/p/the-fall-of-stack-overflow-explained?r=1nwcx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 03:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bing Preview Release Notes: Dark Mode</title>
      <link>https://blogs.bing.com/search/july-2023/Bing-Preview-Release-Notes-Dark-Mode</link>
      <description>This week, browsing the web just got easier on your eyes and better for your laptop battery—we released dark mode for Bing Chat! This feature now works in both Bing Chat and Bing Chat Enterprise in your desktop browser, and it’s already available in the Bing mobile app. Dark mode also changes the appearance of the search page on Bing.com.&amp;#160;
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.bing.com/search/july-2023/Bing-Preview-Release-Notes-Dark-Mode</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shamir Secret Sharing</title>
      <link>https://max.levch.in/post/724289457144070144/shamir-secret-sharing</link>
      <description>It’s 3am. Paul, the head of PayPal database administration carefully enters his elaborate passphrase at a keyboard in a darkened cubicle of 1840 Embarcadero Road in East Palo Alto, for the fifth time....</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://max.levch.in/post/724289457144070144/shamir-secret-sharing</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Real World frontends and backends with Conduit</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DGrPQqyOpcU</link>
      <description>Does the phrase, &amp;quot;mother of all demo apps&amp;quot; get your attention? It sure grabbed ours! In this weeks episode, community MVP Matthew Groves joins us to implemen...</description>
      <author> (Bloomberg Technology
  
  
  
    Bloomberg Technology
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DGrPQqyOpcU</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binary Heap | Concurrency Deep Dives</title>
      <link>https://cmhteixeira.com/concurrency/binaryHeap.html</link>
      <description>Implementing a binary heap from scratch, so that you understand how it works internally. These are used in schedulers/timers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cmhteixeira.com/concurrency/binaryHeap.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackmagic Design SDI-HDMI converter micro USB problems, and a rant about connector receptacles in general</title>
      <link>https://www.krekr.nl/content/blackmagic-design-sdi-hdmi-converter-micro-usb-problems-and-a-rant-about-connector-receptacles-in-general/</link>
      <description>Blackmagic Design make some really awesome hardware. With some shitty flaws that means they break on lousy parts like a micro USB-connector.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.krekr.nl/content/blackmagic-design-sdi-hdmi-converter-micro-usb-problems-and-a-rant-about-connector-receptacles-in-general/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next step: PostOwl</title>
      <link>https://michaelaufreiter.com/posts/the-next-step-postowl</link>
      <description>In April, Nils and I released the proof of concept of Home, Not Alone, a social network made out of independent websites, that can talk to one another. We didn’t develop this further since, because for something like HNA to exist in the real world, we’d need to lay some foundations first. So — today, I’m happy to announce PostOwl. Together with Tom Atkins, we developed a minimalistic self-contained web app that offers you: The easiest way to blog using in-place editing (no technical skills needed) Sharing p…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://michaelaufreiter.com/posts/the-next-step-postowl</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security keys in the land of passkeys</title>
      <link>https://blog.millerti.me/2023/07/30/security-keys-in-the-land-of-passkeys/</link>
      <description>Protect your synced passkey provider accounts with the gold standard in multi-factor authenticators.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.millerti.me/2023/07/30/security-keys-in-the-land-of-passkeys/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on a Month with BBEdit and Nova — Sympolymathesy, by Chris Krycho</title>
      <link>https://v5.chriskrycho.com/journal/reflections-on-a-month-with-bbedit-and-nova/</link>
      <description>I spent a month seeing whether BBEdit could replace Sublime Text and whether Nova could replace VS Code. They absolutely did, and I am delighted.</description>
      <author> (Chris Krycho)</author>
      <guid>https://v5.chriskrycho.com/journal/reflections-on-a-month-with-bbedit-and-nova/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I switched from Plaid to Stripe.. and then back to Plaid - Balance Budget</title>
      <link>https://balancebudget.app/2023/07/29/why-i-switched-from-plaid-to-stripe-and-then-back-to-plaid/</link>
      <description>Alright, lets chat about Stripe&amp;#39;s Financial Connections &amp;#128517; Initially, Balance (a privacy first budgeting app) started off with Plaid as the financial connections provider. Plaid was the industry standard at the time, and I had some experience with them already. Unfortunately, I had to pause work on Balance due to some family reasons. Why use</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://balancebudget.app/2023/07/29/why-i-switched-from-plaid-to-stripe-and-then-back-to-plaid/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toggles suck! | Axess Lab</title>
      <link>https://axesslab.com/toggles-suck/</link>
      <description>You’ve all seen them, tiny switches that let you toggle a setting. And maybe, just like me, you sometimes pause, thinking “...Is it on or…</description>
      <author> (Published 28 July 2023, 
								by Joel Holmberg)</author>
      <guid>https://axesslab.com/toggles-suck/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LK-99: The Live Online Race for a Room-Temperature Superconductor (Summary)</title>
      <link>https://eirifu.wordpress.com/2023/07/30/lk-99-superconductor-summary/</link>
      <description>Disclaimer: I’m not a materials scientist. I may update this over time as I collate more information.Updated 2023-07-31 – Spacebattles table (11 online replication efforts)Added a perso…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://eirifu.wordpress.com/2023/07/30/lk-99-superconductor-summary/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasting Time to Waste Less Time</title>
      <link>https://www.aidanmstrong.com/blog/wasting-time-to-waste-less-time</link>
      <description>How idle games paradoxically attract players</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.aidanmstrong.com/blog/wasting-time-to-waste-less-time</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll Working</title>
      <link>https://hybras.dev/posts/2023-06-06-poll-working/</link>
      <description>Today I was a poll worker in New Jersey’s Primary election. I was the only brown person, and one of 2 people below the age of 55. The other person was middle aged. Suffice it to say, almost everyone involved in the process was basically a retiree. It was a massive culture shock for me. I felt tapped into the soul of my country for a day.
Democracy is Dead I had to show up at 6am, which felt offensive.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hybras.dev/posts/2023-06-06-poll-working/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tribal Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://daedtech.com/tribal-knowledge/</link>
      <description>In my last post, I alluded briefly to the concept of “tribal knowledge” when developing software. I’ve heard this term defined in various contexts, but for the sake of discussion here, I’m going to define this as knowledge about how to accomplish a task that is not self-evident or necessarily intuitive. So, for instance, let’s […]</description>
      <author> (By Erik Dietrich)</author>
      <guid>https://daedtech.com/tribal-knowledge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Social Network Is Bigger Than You Think! – James Ashford</title>
      <link>https://jrashford.com/2023/07/31/your-social-network-is-bigger-than-you-think/</link>
      <description>Your social network is bigger than you think!</description>
      <author> (About James Ashford)</author>
      <guid>https://jrashford.com/2023/07/31/your-social-network-is-bigger-than-you-think/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Limits of AI: Why Not Every Problem Can Be Solved with Machine Learning - Arkavian</title>
      <link>https://arkavian.com/2023/07/31/the-limits-of-ai-why-not-every-problem-can-be-solved-with-machine-learning/</link>
      <description>The Limits of AI: Why Not Every Problem Can Be Solved with Machine Learning There’s no denying that AI is a powerful tool. It has revolutionized the way we interact with technology, giving birth to intelligent virtual assistants, self-driving cars, and language processing tools. Some view it as a solution for all the world’s ailments,Continue reading &amp;quot;The Limits of AI: Why Not Every Problem Can Be Solved with Machine Learning&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> (arkavianai)</author>
      <guid>https://arkavian.com/2023/07/31/the-limits-of-ai-why-not-every-problem-can-be-solved-with-machine-learning/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cachelines and Striped Locks — ~ngp</title>
      <link>https://packetlost.dev/blog/cachelines-and-striped-locks/</link>
      <description>As part of a larger project, MehDB, I developed multiple implementations of a striped locking mechanism in both Rust and Golang (blog post on that soon?).</description>
      <author> (Published on July 30, 2023)</author>
      <guid>https://packetlost.dev/blog/cachelines-and-striped-locks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>File distribution over DNS: (ab)using DNS as a CDN (eighty-twenty news)</title>
      <link>https://eighty-twenty.org/2023/07/31/dns-as-a-cdn</link>
      <description>This is the story of a one-afternoon hack that turned into a one-weekend hack.</description>
      <author> (Tony Garnock-Jones)</author>
      <guid>https://eighty-twenty.org/2023/07/31/dns-as-a-cdn</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialized Proof of Work</title>
      <link>https://blog.erlend.sh/socialized-proof-of-work</link>
      <description>There’s an increasing obsession with “humanness” these days: https://worldcoin.org/blog/engineering/humanness-in-the-age-of-ai https://ne...</description>
      <author> (Open Indie)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.erlend.sh/socialized-proof-of-work</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So, you want to deploy on the edge?</title>
      <link>https://zknill.io/posts/edge-database/</link>
      <description>Application developers often deploy their apps into a single area, generally represented by a handful of AZs in a single region. No matter where their users make requests from, those requests get served by the region where the developers’ apps run.
If a user makes a request from Europe, and the apps run in US East, that adds an extra 100-150ms of latency just by round-tripping across the Atlantic.
Edge computing tries to solve this problem, by letting app developers deploy their applications across the globe, so that apps serve the user requests closer to the user.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zknill.io/posts/edge-database/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Paid Off $194k in Student Loans in Six Years. It Wasn’t Easy. - BJL</title>
      <link>https://benjaminlabaschin.com/194k-in-loans-in-six-years/</link>
      <description>Table of Contents Disbelief In which I accomplish a long sought after financial goal and determine the need to reflect on how it came to be. Adventures in Aliens and Castration In which I discuss a ruined scheme to bypass a formal education. &amp;quot;Deer&amp;quot;, Dear Friends In which I discuss the forces that led to</description>
      <author> (Ben Labaschin)</author>
      <guid>https://benjaminlabaschin.com/194k-in-loans-in-six-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with NGINX</title>
      <link>https://sophiazhang.com/post/start-with-nginx/</link>
      <description>Learning NGINX</description>
      <author> (Sophia Zhang)</author>
      <guid>https://sophiazhang.com/post/start-with-nginx/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabe Henriques</title>
      <link>https://gabehenriques.com/blog/space-tourism/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gabehenriques.com/blog/space-tourism/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An optimal-stopping quant riddle - Emir&amp;#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://emiruz.com/post/2023-07-30-optimal-stopping/</link>
      <description>I happened upon a post by Gwern discussing, in
some detail, various solutions to riddle #14 from Nigel Coldwell’s
list of quant riddles. I initially got
as far as the problem description in Gwern’s article and avoided reading
further so I could first solve it for myself. The problem is stated as follows:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://emiruz.com/post/2023-07-30-optimal-stopping/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A comprehensive guide to Redux for beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.tanvi.dev/blog/3-a-comprehensive-guide-to-redux-for-beginners</link>
      <description>Redux is a very popular but perceived to be hard to understand React library that is becoming increasingly popular. In this guide I explain what is the purpose of this library and how to understand it in the perspective of a new developer.</description>
      <author> (Tanvi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tanvi.dev/blog/3-a-comprehensive-guide-to-redux-for-beginners</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Diaries: Two Important Facts About Generative Prose</title>
      <link>https://www.davystevenson.com/articles/ai-diaries-two-important-facts-about-generative-prose</link>
      <description>Here, I will outline two important high-level points that anyone working with generative prose needs to keep in mind.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.davystevenson.com/articles/ai-diaries-two-important-facts-about-generative-prose</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Migrate from framework to core with System.Web.Adapters</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/l_PKg_VozFc</link>
      <description>Taylor Southwick shares some tips and tricks for incremental framework to core migrations with the System.Web adapters. He&amp;#39;ll go over some common scenarios h...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/l_PKg_VozFc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 21:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Syme Live at fsharpConf 2023</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=UVbfNyGnZa0</link>
      <description>Don Syme stops by fsharpConf 2023 to discuss the past, present, and future of F# and the F# community.Resources: https://aka.ms/fsharpconf2023fsharpConf is a...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=UVbfNyGnZa0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 21:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2809/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2809/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 20:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amanda (@Pandamoanimum@mstdn.social)</title>
      <link>https://mstdn.social/@Pandamoanimum/110808340828034444</link>
      <description>Attached: 1 video

I saw this advert from 1956 on Instagram and can’t work out how a fridge from nearly 70 years ago basically has better features than the fridge I own now.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mstdn.social/@Pandamoanimum/110808340828034444</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 19:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA mistakenly severs communication to Voyager 2</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2023/07/31/nasa_mistakenly_disconnects_voyager_2/</link>
      <description>Thankfully the probe regularly phones home to fix this sort of mess</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2023/07/31/nasa_mistakenly_disconnects_voyager_2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 19:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The proposal to enhance Go&amp;#39;s HTTP router</title>
      <link>https://benhoyt.com/writings/go-servemux-enhancements/</link>
      <description>A brief look at the proposed enhancements to the Go standard library HTTP request router, net/http.ServeMux: matching on HTTP method, and supporting wildcards in matched paths.</description>
      <author> (Ben Hoyt)</author>
      <guid>https://benhoyt.com/writings/go-servemux-enhancements/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 19:03:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>