<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Pushed Authorization Requests (PAR) in ASP.NET Core 9</title>
      <link>https://nestenius.se/uncategorized/pushed-authorization-requests-par-in-asp-net-core-9/</link>
      <description>Discover how ASP.NET Core 9 supports Pushed Authorization Requests (PAR) to improve security in OAuth and OpenID Connect.</description>
      <author> (webmaster)</author>
      <guid>https://nestenius.se/uncategorized/pushed-authorization-requests-par-in-asp-net-core-9/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 11:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Caching with Aspect-Oriented Programming and Metalama in .NET</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/simplifying-caching-with-aop-metalama/</link>
      <description>1. Introduction: Simplifying Caching with Aspect-Oriented Programming in .NET


Aspect-Oriented Programming (AOP) offers elegant solutions for handling cross-cutting concerns in our .NET applications, such as method caching. In a previous article on GoatReview &amp;#128016;, we explored using Fody to implement a caching aspect. Although powerful, this tool presents significant challenges.


Let&amp;#39;s</description>
      <author> (Cyril Canovas)</author>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/simplifying-caching-with-aop-metalama/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 10:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boost Your .NET Projects: Unleashing the Power of Spargine’s UlidGenerator</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/11/05/boost-your-net-projects-unleashing-the-power-of-spargines-ulidgenerator/</link>
      <description>Spargine is an open-source set of .NET 8 assemblies and NuGet packages created for efficient ULID generation, combining randomness with alphabetical sorting. ULIDs are compact, sortable identifiers…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/11/05/boost-your-net-projects-unleashing-the-power-of-spargines-ulidgenerator/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 10:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing secure Go code</title>
      <link>https://jarosz.dev/article/writing-secure-go-code/</link>
      <description>Security testing starts with understanding vulnerabilities. The CVE website lists known software flaws. The OWASP Top Ten highlights common weaknesses. With this knowledge, we can improve our Go development. This article shows how to put in place robust practices. They are fuzz inputs, verify dependencies, and use static analysis tools (SAST).</description>
      <author> (Jakub Jarosz)</author>
      <guid>https://jarosz.dev/article/writing-secure-go-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 09:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Forest Service Decision to Halt Prescribed Burns in California is History Repeating</title>
      <link>https://cepr.net/us-forest-service-decision-to-halt-prescribed-burns-in-california-is-history-repeating/</link>
      <description>Exploring the consequences of ending prescribed burns in California. Discover the importance of understanding the state&amp;#39;s forest management practices.</description>
      <author> (Adam Fishbein)</author>
      <guid>https://cepr.net/us-forest-service-decision-to-halt-prescribed-burns-in-california-is-history-repeating/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 08:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PostgreSQL streaming replication characteristics on UNLOGGED tables</title>
      <link>https://ivdl.co.za/2024/11/04/what-happens-if-you-enable-logging-on-an-unlogged-postgresql-table-with-streaming-replication/</link>
      <description>Photo by Timelab on Unsplash – WAL shipping in action?



This is a bit of a rabbit hole, so let me explain. In brief: streaming physical replication ships the WALs from the primary to the standby servers. The documentation states that UNLOGGED tables are not written to the WALs1, and therefore, the</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ivdl.co.za/2024/11/04/what-happens-if-you-enable-logging-on-an-unlogged-postgresql-table-with-streaming-replication/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequencing Swabs</title>
      <link>https://www.jefftk.com/p/sequencing-swabs</link>
      <description>Cross-posted from my NAO Notebook  Update 2024-02-26: due to a serious typo all the results in this post were off by a factor of 100. Sequencing from individuals still looks promising, but by less than it did before. I&amp;#39;ve updated the numbers in the post, and added notes above the charts to explain how they&amp;#39;re wrong. Thanks to Simon Grimm for catching my mistake.   While this is about an area I wor</description>
      <author> (Jeff Kaufman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jefftk.com/p/sequencing-swabs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chess Analogy or How Important is Trust?</title>
      <link>https://blog.usuf.dev/the-chess-analogy-or-how-important-is-trust</link>
      <description>As a kid, I used to play chess with my dad and later with my grandfather. Starting from third grade, I even joined chess clubs. Initially, I would lose every game to my dad, but later on, he would let me win—though I didn’t realize it then. This taug...</description>
      <author> (https://hashnode.com/@uwussimo)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.usuf.dev/the-chess-analogy-or-how-important-is-trust</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlighting Text in Links with Text Fragments</title>
      <link>https://calebhearth.com/text-fragments</link>
      <description>I’ve used URL text fragments in a few posts now and often use it outside of this blog to point someone to a particular piece of text on a page. They’re a really useful feature that allows you to...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://calebhearth.com/text-fragments</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensors and Graphs: Canonization by Search</title>
      <link>https://www.philipzucker.com/canon_search/</link>
      <description>There are many interesting syntactic and semantic objects that hold a notion of symmetry that a simple syntax tree can’t quite capture.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.philipzucker.com/canon_search/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication for team leaders - Trust</title>
      <link>https://frederickvanbrabant.com/blog/2024-10-31-communication-for-team-leaders-trust/</link>
      <description>The second part of a three-part: Communication for Team Leaders. This one is about trust, letting go and delegating. I think it&amp;#39;s the hardest one for new managers.</description>
      <author> (Frederick Vanbrabant)</author>
      <guid>https://frederickvanbrabant.com/blog/2024-10-31-communication-for-team-leaders-trust/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to serve custom maps for free with Leaflet and Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.robindevooght.be/posts/homemade_tiling/</link>
      <description>How to make an interactive map of all buildings in Belgium when you are too lazy to learn proper tools.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.robindevooght.be/posts/homemade_tiling/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tinkering with Neovim</title>
      <link>https://maskray.me/blog/2024-11-02-tinkering-with-neovim</link>
      <description>After migrating from Vim to Emacs as my primary C++ editor in 2015, I switched from Vim to Neovim for miscellaneous non-C++ tasks as it is more convenient in a terminal. Customizing the editor with a</description>
      <author> (MaskRay)</author>
      <guid>https://maskray.me/blog/2024-11-02-tinkering-with-neovim</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You don’t need a startup advisor. You just need to do 1 of these 5 things. &amp;#187; Anand Sanwal</title>
      <link>https://anandsanwal.me/startup-advice/</link>
      <description>I fired myself as CEO of CB Insights earlier this year. After announcing this, some early-stage B2B startup founders reached out to asking me to advise them or join their board. I had never done any advisory work of this type but having made every mistake in the book so why not? I did it</description>
      <author> (Anand Sanwal
					

		
			
			
							
					See Full Bio)</author>
      <guid>https://anandsanwal.me/startup-advice/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exporting iCloud passwords on Windows</title>
      <link>https://lets.re/blog/icloud-passwords-export/</link>
      <description>Unlike the iCloud passwords app on macOS, the Windows app does not have export functionality. So I extended the Chrome extension with the help of Cursor and Claude.</description>
      <author> (retsl)</author>
      <guid>https://lets.re/blog/icloud-passwords-export/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf 2024 - Day 3</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=bD3s78pfSk8</link>
      <description>Full agenda: https://dotnetconf.net/agenda

.NET Conf has been a virtual event since the beginning, and this year we’re celebrating our 14th online conference. We always strive to create a world class, engaging, virtual experience for all our attendees no matter where they are. Over the years we&amp;#39;ve expanded our content and our reach. We now draw over 100 thousand live viewers and sponsor hundreds of local events around the world.

Over the course of the three days we provide a wide selection of live sessions that feature speakers from the community and .NET team members. We have sessions streaming 24/7 between day two and three of the conference so everyone can get involved no matter what their time zone. You can ask questions live on Twitter, join the fun on Twitch, attend the virtual attendee parties where you can play trivia games and win prizes. Best of all, you can take what you learn here and be a better .NET developer.

Connect with .NET: 
Blog:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/blog
Twitter: https://aka.ms/dotnet/twitter
TikTok:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/tiktok
Mastodon:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/mastodon
LinkedIn:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/linkedin
Facebook:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/facebook
Docs: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet
Forums: https://aka.ms/dotnet/forums
&amp;#128587;‍♀️Q&amp;amp;A: https://aka.ms/dotnet-qa
&amp;#128104;‍&amp;#127891;Microsoft Learn: https://aka.ms/learndotnet

#dotnet #dotnetconf</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=bD3s78pfSk8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Functors to Monads: A Story of Shapes
</title>
      <link>https://blog.jle.im/entry/functors-to-monads-a-story-of-shapes.html</link>
      <description>For many years now I’ve been using a mental model and intuition that has guided me well for understanding and teaching and using functors, applicatives, monads, and other related Haskell abstractions, as well as for approaching learning new ones. Sometimes when teaching Haskell I talk about this concept and assume everyone already has heard it, but I realize that it’s something universal yet easy to miss depending on how you’re learning it. So, here it is: how I understand the Functor and other related abstractions and free constructions in Haskell. The crux is this: instead of thinking about what fmap changes, ask: what does fmap keep constant? This isn’t a rigorous understanding and isn’t going to explain every aspect about every Functor, and will probably only be useful if you already know a little bit about Functors in Haskell. But it’s a nice intuition trick that has yet to majorly mislead me.</description>
      <author> (Justin Le)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jle.im/entry/functors-to-monads-a-story-of-shapes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matryoshka Embeddings: Detail at Multiple Scales - Milvus Blog</title>
      <link>https://milvus.io/blog/matryoshka-embeddings-detail-at-multiple-scales</link>
      <description>Embeddings with shortened dimensions without sacrificing semantic integrity, ideal for more efficient search and storage.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://milvus.io/blog/matryoshka-embeddings-detail-at-multiple-scales</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape the Surveillance Web with Gemini</title>
      <link>https://john.soban.ski/gemini.html</link>
      <description>Intrusive advertisements, Bloated JavaScript widgets, and Artificial Intelligence (AI) generated, Search Engine Optimized (SEO) slop...</description>
      <author> (https://john.soban.ski/author/john-sobanski.html)</author>
      <guid>https://john.soban.ski/gemini.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaggregated Storage - a brief introduction - blag</title>
      <link>https://avi.im/blag/2024/disaggregated-storage/</link>
      <description>a brief introduction to disaggregated storage systems in context of database systems</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://avi.im/blag/2024/disaggregated-storage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving my website from Netlify to Caddy</title>
      <link>https://alexwlchan.net/2024/netlify-to-caddy/</link>
      <description>To avoid getting stung by Netlify&amp;#39;s bandwidth charges, I moved this site to a Linux server running Caddy as my web server. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alexwlchan.net/2024/netlify-to-caddy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRF is Not Enough</title>
      <link>https://softwaredoug.com/blog/2024/11/03/rrf-is-not-enough</link>
      <description>Reciprocal Rank Fusion, while a useful tool, doesnt magically make hybrid search relevant</description>
      <author> (Doug Turnbull)</author>
      <guid>https://softwaredoug.com/blog/2024/11/03/rrf-is-not-enough</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best CEOs Respond</title>
      <link>https://dan.bulwinkle.net/blog/the-best-ceos-respond/</link>
      <description>Vision for the company is a key role for a CEO, and engaging with customers is important to fully realize that role.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dan.bulwinkle.net/blog/the-best-ceos-respond/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The smallest (useful) HTTP responses possible</title>
      <link>https://jamesbvaughan.com/small-http/</link>
      <description>I recently did a little experiment to see how small (in bytes) I could make useful valid HTTP responses for a particular use case.
Background On my homepage, I have a little feature where I display the names of the last song I listened to and the last movie I watched. I’ve implemented that via a bit of JavaScript that fetches that information from a pair of Lambda functions that make requests to Last.</description>
      <author> (James Vaughan)</author>
      <guid>https://jamesbvaughan.com/small-http/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Podia doesn’t use review apps anymore</title>
      <link>https://jamie.ideasasylum.com/2024/10/31/why-podia-doesnt-use-review-apps-anymore</link>
      <description>It turns out the review apps are fundamentally incompatible with short-lived branches. We prefer to use feature flags.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.ideasasylum.com/2024/10/31/why-podia-doesnt-use-review-apps-anymore</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from 130 hours in a Waymo</title>
      <link>https://www.mattbell.us/what-i-learned-from-130-hours-in-a-waymo/</link>
      <description>A peek into the bright future of a world full of self-driving cars</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/thismattbell)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mattbell.us/what-i-learned-from-130-hours-in-a-waymo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federation Deathmatch</title>
      <link>https://blog.glyph.im/2024/11/the-federation-deathmatch.html</link>
      <description>It’s the weekend, and I have some Thoughts about federated social media. So, buckle up, I guess, it’s time to start some fights.</description>
      <author> (Glyph Lefkowitz)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.glyph.im/2024/11/the-federation-deathmatch.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking Past Helix&amp;#39;s Horizon | Vhyrro&amp;#39;s Digital Garden</title>
      <link>https://vhyrro.github.io/posts/ki-editor/</link>
      <description>The Ki Editor may have just one-upped the boss.</description>
      <author> (Vhyrro)</author>
      <guid>https://vhyrro.github.io/posts/ki-editor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building My Resume in HTML using Eleventy by Michael Engen</title>
      <link>https://michaelengen.com/posts/my-eleventy-resume/</link>
      <description>Like many before me, I&amp;#39;ve built and rebuilt my resume many times over the years.
I&amp;#39;ve used many different approaches, including LaTeX and visual editors, in search of something that fulfilled my aspirational criteria:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://michaelengen.com/posts/my-eleventy-resume/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Spencer</title>
      <link>https://nathancspencer.com/5months/</link>
      <description>Nov 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nathancspencer.com/5months/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We’re leaving Kubernetes - Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.gitpod.io/blog/we-are-leaving-kubernetes</link>
      <description>After six years of running our CDE on Kubernetes we&amp;#39;ve learned Kubernetes is not the right choice for us. Here&amp;#39;s why.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.gitpod.io/blog/we-are-leaving-kubernetes</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3007/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3007/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 21:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yohan Malshika: Why I love to write</title>
      <link>https://niche.sweet.pub/yohan-malshika-why-i-love-to-write-d4af0e7b2792?source=rss-c77187421577------2</link>
      <description>Always love to help each other</description>
      <author> (https://malshikay.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://niche.sweet.pub/yohan-malshika-why-i-love-to-write-d4af0e7b2792?source=rss-c77187421577------2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 20:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET  IDE &amp;#128640; &amp;#128165; - Rider is now Free &amp;#128293;&amp;#128293;&amp;#128293;</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=oVSO4V4Ni80</link>
      <description>In this video will discuss the best IDE for .NET! on Mac

https://www.dotnetconf.net
https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/aspnet/core/release-notes/aspnetcore-9.0
https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/ef/core/what-is-new/ef-core-9.0/whatsnew

Support me on Patreon to access the source code:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand

Let us connect:
&amp;#127757;  My website  - https://mohamadlawand.com
&amp;#128248;  Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/mohamadlawand087/
&amp;#128038;  Twitter - https://twitter.com/moe23
♯ Github - https://github.com/mohamadlawand087
&amp;#127915; LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/mlawand
&amp;#128165; LinkTree - https://linktr.ee/mohamadlawand

Gear I use  (affiliate link): https://amzn.to/3EbT8Jw

Support my work:
https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand
https://www.buymeacoffee.com/mohamadlawand

Hire Me:
https://transactions.sendowl.com/products/78999951/625477F1/view

WHO AM I:
I&amp;#39;m Mohamad, a Enterprise Architect working in Manchester, UK. I make videos about web, cloud, desktop and mobile development. 

GET IN TOUCH:
If you’d like to talk, I’d love to hear from you. Tweeting @moe23 directly will be the quickest way to get a response, but if your question is very long, feel free to email me at hello@mohamadlawand.com.

#dotnet  #rider    #jetbrains</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=oVSO4V4Ni80</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting a job in Tech - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=T6I3b-hrs8I</link>
      <description>In this edition of #tech on ice, we start with part 1 of a &amp;quot;Getting a job in tech&amp;quot; series that I will be doing. This part is all about picking the tech that is most interesting to you and using it as a good starting point. Follow along! #technology #programming #developer #coldplunge</description>
      <author> (Isaac Levin)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=T6I3b-hrs8I</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey Conf 2024 C4P now open!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=568JhGVOE1M</link>
      <description>Become a channel member to enjoy benefits and access more content.
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCKnuLHRlK_zhrpaTWvNOdMA/join</description>
      <author> (Javier Su&amp;#225;rez)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=568JhGVOE1M</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 16:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>