<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Python Beginner Projects 2020 - Add them to your resume!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W9nbdVWl4PA&amp;feature=youtu.be</link>
      <description>Learning Python? You should consider building some projects! They truly help you understand how all the snippets of code work together. However, you always see the same projects around and recruiters are not too excited to see always the same stuff. Be creative! In this video, I show you three projects examples that you can use to set yourself apart from the competition!

Corona Invaders: https://github.com/DavideMerlin/Corona_Invaders
Election Scraper: https://github.com/DavideMerlin/Twitter_election_scraper
Login Automation: https://github.com/DavideMerlin/Automated_login

TIMESTAMPS:
00:00 Intro
00:52 General Advice
1:29 Project 1: Corona Invader
2:55 Project 2: Election Scraper
4:31 Project 3: Login Automation
5:58 Conclusions

#Python #Projects

Social:

Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/davidemerlin97</description>
      <author> (Davide Merlin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W9nbdVWl4PA&amp;feature=youtu.be</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web apps aren't tech. They're "tech".</title>
      <link>https://questinglog.com/web-apps-arent-tech</link>
      <description>I do hear sometimes from programmers who are kind of sad that they don't have the opportunity to write game engines from scratch like I did and have it matter or make an impact...
&gt;
&gt; -John Carmack
 ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://questinglog.com/web-apps-arent-tech</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Talk about Cache - Daniel Leskosky</title>
      <link>https://www.danielleskosky.com/lets-talk-about-cache/</link>
      <description>A cache is hardware or software that is used to temporarily store data. Learn about when caches are used and how caching works.</description>
      <author> (About Daniel Leskosky)</author>
      <guid>https://www.danielleskosky.com/lets-talk-about-cache/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create change within your locus of control</title>
      <link>https://brettcvz.com/posts/131-create-change-within-your-locus-of-control</link>
      <description>When you want to change policy, show, don’t tell. Start by creating the change within your local environment, demonstrating the benefits, and encouraging others to try it. Once you’ve proven out the playbook and earned enthusiastic support, then advocate for a formal policy change.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://brettcvz.com/posts/131-create-change-within-your-locus-of-control</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Problem of Preference Falsification in Online Dating</title>
      <link>https://jayriverlong.github.io/2020/08/02/online-dating.html</link>
      <description>Online dating is as old as the internet. It has exploded in popularity in recent years: roughly 40% of straight couples now meet online. It has given women more safety and choice as they participate in the dating market, and brought down divorce rates as people date more widely and make better-informed decisions than in the past.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jayriverlong.github.io/2020/08/02/online-dating.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Should Buy ARM? - Dr. Z and Eng. L</title>
      <link>https://drz.today/2020/who-should-buy-arm/</link>
      <description>There are rumors about NVIDIA in advanced talks of buying ARM. Softbank has been in need of cash injection for some time, and ARM itself is a good asset.</description>
      <author> (YZ and L)</author>
      <guid>https://drz.today/2020/who-should-buy-arm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Market Capitalism vs Government Socialism</title>
      <link>https://joelx.com/capitalism-vs-socialism/15934/</link>
      <description>Socialism by definition involves the government directing resources. Capitalism by definition involves individuals self-directing themselves. so·cial·ism - a</description>
      <author> (Published by
	
			

	
		Joel Gross

		
			Joel Gross is the CEO of Coalition Technologies.)</author>
      <guid>https://joelx.com/capitalism-vs-socialism/15934/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honey, I Accidentally Became A Product Manager</title>
      <link>https://den.dev/blog/pm/</link>
      <description>This is the story about how I ended up following the product manager career path.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://den.dev/blog/pm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs - Raspberry Pi Documentation</title>
      <link>https://www.raspberrypi.org/documentation/faqs/#pi-performance</link>
      <description>Official documentation for the Raspberry Pi, written by the Raspberry Pi Foundation with community contributions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.raspberrypi.org/documentation/faqs/#pi-performance</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hydroxychloroquine: The Narrative That it Doesn’t Work is the Biggest Hoax in Recent Human History</title>
      <link>https://truthabouthcq.com/hcq-works/</link>
      <description>The narrative that Hydroxychloroquine doesn't work is the biggest hoax in recent human history. Here's a completely timeline of the coverup with sources.</description>
      <author> (By: Filipe RafaeliAugust 1, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://truthabouthcq.com/hcq-works/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low latency tuning guide</title>
      <link>https://rigtorp.se/low-latency-guide/</link>
      <description>This guide describes how to tune your AMD64/x86_64 hardware and Linux system for running real-time or low latency workloads.</description>
      <author> (Erik Rigtorp)</author>
      <guid>https://rigtorp.se/low-latency-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrueFire hacked - credit cards and other personal info potentially compromised</title>
      <link>https://guitar.com/news/industry-news/truefire-data-breach/</link>
      <description>Tuition website TrueFire admits a "data breach" that may have given hacker unauthorised access to personal data for over five months.</description>
      <author> (Cillian Breathnach)</author>
      <guid>https://guitar.com/news/industry-news/truefire-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 22:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home | Laws of UX</title>
      <link>https://lawsofux.com/</link>
      <description>Laws of UX is a collection of the maxims and principles that designers can consider when building user interfaces. It was created by &lt;a href='http://jonyablonski.com'&gt;Jon Yablonski&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <author> (Jon Yablonski)</author>
      <guid>https://lawsofux.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail delays are frustrating Philly residents, and a short-staffed Postal Service is struggling to keep up</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/philadelphia/usps-tracking-in-transit-late-mail-delivery-philadelphia-packages-postal-service-20200802.html</link>
      <description>“It’s just piles of our mail sitting in the post office," one Overbrook Park resident said.</description>
      <author> (Ellie Rushing)</author>
      <guid>https://www.inquirer.com/news/philadelphia/usps-tracking-in-transit-late-mail-delivery-philadelphia-packages-postal-service-20200802.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 22:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sliderulemuseum.com/SR_Course.htm</link>
      <description>Images created from Emulators designed by Derek Ross.
Initial examples based on Derek's Self Guided demo and expanded by Mike Konshak.</description>
      <author> (MK)</author>
      <guid>https://sliderulemuseum.com/SR_Course.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 20:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tines Blog / Part 1 : Breaches are inevitable and early detection is crucial</title>
      <link>https://www.tines.io/blog/breaches-are-inevitable-and-early-detection-is-crucial</link>
      <description>This is part 1 of a 3 part series on security automation for dealing with account compromise. Part 1 covers detection, part 2 looks at enrichment and case management, while part 3 tackles protection and response including prompting the user to acknowledge the incident via a side-channel.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tines.io/blog/breaches-are-inevitable-and-early-detection-is-crucial</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 20:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmetics firm Avon leaks 19 million customer records (Includes interview)</title>
      <link>http://www.digitaljournal.com/tech-and-science/technology/cosmetics-firm-avon-leaks-19-million-customer-records/article/575553</link>
      <description>The latest data breach has struck the purveyor of lower-cost cosmetics - Avon. Once a staple of door-to-door selling, the company has operated a successful online business for many years.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.digitaljournal.com/tech-and-science/technology/cosmetics-firm-avon-leaks-19-million-customer-records/article/575553</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 20:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPU.js - GPU accelerated Javascript</title>
      <link>https://gpu.rocks/</link>
      <description>GPGPU operations using pure javascript!. Accelerate javascript functions using a GPU</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gpu.rocks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 19:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram files EU antitrust complaint against Apple’s App Store</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/07/telegram-files-eu-antitrust-complaint-against-apples-app-store/</link>
      <description>Messaging company is latest company to criticize restrictions and fees.</description>
      <author> (Javier Espinoza, Financial Times
        -  7/30/2020, 6:38 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/07/telegram-files-eu-antitrust-complaint-against-apples-app-store/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 19:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>System UIcons</title>
      <link>https://systemuicons.com/</link>
      <description>A free icon set designed for systems and products. Use how you want, without attribution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://systemuicons.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 13:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Portable Air Conditioners</title>
      <link>https://pmarks.net/ac/</link>
      <description>I bought a couple EdgeStar AP14001HS portable air conditioners in April 2020, since I expect to spend most of the Summer at home.  I'm not able to use window A/Cs here, though that would be the obvious choice for efficiency because all the hot parts remain outside.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pmarks.net/ac/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The mysterious case of man who can read letters—but not numbers—exposes roots of consciousness</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/07/mysterious-case-man-who-can-read-letters-not-numbers-exposes-complex-roots</link>
      <description>With a condition that’s “too strange for words,” patient can do mental math but cannot recognize numerals</description>
      <author> (By Sam KeanJul. 29, 2020 , 12:35 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/07/mysterious-case-man-who-can-read-letters-not-numbers-exposes-complex-roots</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>andrewlock/blazor-with-source-generators-poc</title>
      <link>https://github.com/andrewlock/blazor-with-source-generators-poc</link>
      <description>Contribute to andrewlock/blazor-with-source-generators-poc development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (andrewlock)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/andrewlock/blazor-with-source-generators-poc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Astronauts Return Home in SpaceX's Crew Dragon Spacecraft</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=13OkD0C_TWU</link>
      <description>They’re coming home! 🌎

On Aug. 1, NASA astronauts Robert Behnken and Douglas Hurley will depart from the International Space Station aboard SpaceX’s Dragon “Endeavour” spacecraft after their mission aboard our orbiting laboratory. Starting at 5:15 p.m. EDT, tune in for our live coverage to see the duo undock from the station and make their return back to planet Earth.</description>
      <author> (NASA)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=13OkD0C_TWU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 09:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Wong Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://www.davidwong.fr/</link>
      <description>Check the menu on the left to see what I've been up to!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.davidwong.fr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 08:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pimp up your Blazor EditForms with Tailwind CSS!</title>
      <link>https://jonhilton.net/pimp-up-blazor-edit-forms-with-tailwind-css</link>
      <description>EditForms are a unstyled by default, so it falls to you to make your forms pop!</description>
      <author> (Jon Hilton)</author>
      <guid>https://jonhilton.net/pimp-up-blazor-edit-forms-with-tailwind-css</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 08:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2km From Home</title>
      <link>https://2kmfromhome.com/5km</link>
      <description>How far can you exercise from home during the Government restrictions?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2kmfromhome.com/5km</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 06:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber attack downs Telstra network, affecting thousands of internet users</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/national/nsw/thousands-affected-by-telstra-internet-outage-20200802-p55hq9.html</link>
      <description>A cyber attack has brought down the critical internet address books that help run Telstra's network, resulting in thousands of people across Australia reporting outages on Sunday morning.</description>
      <author> (Angus Thompson, Ben Grubb)</author>
      <guid>https://www.smh.com.au/national/nsw/thousands-affected-by-telstra-internet-outage-20200802-p55hq9.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 05:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NES Background Parallax Explained - Audiovisual Effects Pt. 03</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wt73KPS_23w</link>
      <description>How can NES games create parallax background effects if the console only supports one background layer? It's all explained right here.

LINKS
Twitter (updates): https://twitter.com/RetroGameMechEx
Patreon (support): https://www.patreon.com/rgmechex
SubscribeStar (support): https://www.subscribestar.com/rgmechex
Discord (discussion): http://discord.rgmechex.com

SUPPORTERS
Thank you to everyone who supports the channel!
Anthony Losego, Dan Salvato, F. Murmel, Jonathan Aldrich, Ange Albertini, hyperforce, Avi Drissman, Mike Gerow, Larry Koubiak, Tina Wuest, Owen Christensen, Gynvael, Buddy, Chris Margroff, Brandan Lennox, Nik, Jason Hughes, Diamond Ice, Chris Post, Cypher Signal, Rupix, Gabe S, krivx, Walter Huf, Pixy011, David Spalding, Acceleration Shark, Rory Kelly, Carl Cassler, Joe Mecca, Michael Greb, Kefen, Heptonion, leftler, Scott Beca, 19day, Michael Dragone, John Losego, Travis, Arthur Kunkle, Jordan Wright, Christopher Tramel, Alexander Paz, Stephan J Hennion, coon, Node1729, Andrea, Michael Cafarelli, Red Sona, Kodi_x86, tripper, Nebelwerfer Granitara, Sten, 333Rich333, Glenn hEADcRASH Sugden NPC, Alex Yancey, David Mazarro, Steven, null, Ryan, Corey Ogburn, Martin Trozell, Garret Kelly, Jake Hickman, Joel Kuhn, Dan Shedd, Sembiance, Xander479, 4F Panda, Max Roncace, David, A Sentient JDAM, Alec Johnson, Brian Henriquez, Travis Nellor, Zach Hugethanks, dishsoap42, Yakov, Oxygen Chen, RetroReversing.com, yuriks, Ceres, Jeremiah, Chris Roy, Chris Connett, Mark, Matthew, sapslaj, Jonathan Scott, Xkeeper, Bjoern Hansen, ers35, Daniel Bernard (ReckedCat), Lukas Kalbertodt, Vier Ladair, Bwangry, iPaq, zephyrin, Jeremy Wright, David Johnson, Brandon, Matt Shepard, Felix Freiberger, Sypwn, Niles Rogoff, Reflet, Yann Le Brech, Evan, Eugene Bulkin, Walter Weaver, Gethiox, Articate, Julien Oster, buzzert, Steve Losh, Samuel Stoddard, HattyJetty, Paige ? Hex, Yeero, Cruz Godar, Linh Pham, Noah Greenberg, Nick Rogers, Sean Nelson (audiohacked), Bryce, Andrew Yukhymchak, Sean Bryant, John Gabriel, BazBadger, Kyle, Master Knight DH, Tim Romero, Michael B., Eric Loewenthal, Adrian Haslinger, Proxy, Nolan Varani, Thoscellen, Wii2, Daniel Robinson, Hans Jorgensen, waielal, Daniel A.A. Pelsmaeker, Aaron, Max Gartung, Nicolas Dohrendorf, Eric Hoppe, Chaz Serir, derHinek, Gyiyg, Niels Peyronnel, samfu, Dominic Wehrmann, André Greubel, Anon42, Urda, Ted Berkowitz, araknofennisti, AA, Joseph Torres, serhef, Daniel, Patrick Johnston, Rodrigo Monteiro, Punchmaster, Stephen Bank, Thomas Berg, Crazed Geek, Dasterin, Matthew Yu, Alice Hartley, KieferSkunk, Tasman, &amp; Marcus N!</description>
      <author> (Retro Game Mechanics Explained)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wt73KPS_23w</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 03:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing Passwords</title>
      <link>https://textslashplain.com/2020/07/29/revealing-passwords/</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Edge browser, Edge Legacy, and Internet Explorer all offer a convenient mechanism for users to unmask their typing as they edit a password field: Clicking the little eye icon disables…</description>
      <author> (Published by ericlaw)</author>
      <guid>https://textslashplain.com/2020/07/29/revealing-passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 02:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Wong Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://davidwong.fr/index2.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidwong.fr/index2.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 02:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Wong</title>
      <link>https://davidwong.fr/</link>
      <description>site vitrine de david wong</description>
      <author> (david wong)</author>
      <guid>https://davidwong.fr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 02:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happened When I Peeked Into My Node_Modules Directory</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/s/silicon-satire/i-peeked-into-my-node-modules-directory-and-you-wont-believe-what-happened-next-b89f63d21558</link>
      <description>Just absolute madness</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@jdan)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/s/silicon-satire/i-peeked-into-my-node-modules-directory-and-you-wont-believe-what-happened-next-b89f63d21558</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 01:44:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>