<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>News Release : Sep. 19, 2024 &amp;quot;Filing Lawsuit for Infringement of Patent Rights against Pocketpair, Inc.&amp;quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.nintendo.co.jp/corporate/release/en/2024/240919.html</link>
      <description>Press release of Nintendo Co., Ltd.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nintendo.co.jp/corporate/release/en/2024/240919.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Semrush subreddit: &amp;#39;How the Keyword Magic Tool made my year hell&amp;#39;</title>
      <link>https://jackyan.com/blog/2024/09/on-the-semrush-subreddit-how-the-keyword-magic-tool-made-my-year-hell/</link>
      <description>Here’s your second notice, Semrush. Since you don’t answer emails, I’ve come here. Will you do anything about it, or will it be ignored?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jackyan.com/blog/2024/09/on-the-semrush-subreddit-how-the-keyword-magic-tool-made-my-year-hell/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoErgo Glove80 programmable ergonomic keyboard</title>
      <link>https://sunaku.github.io/moergo-glove80-keyboard.html</link>
      <description>NOTE: Check out the interactive layer map for this keyboard below!
DEMO: Watch this video of me typing and me coding on this keyboard.
DOWNLOAD: Get this keymap for your Glove80 from my Git repository.



Is that… Batman’s keyboard?! &amp;#129415;  No, but it sure makes me feel like him:
  sitting in the turquoise glow of the Batcomputer, deep within the quiet
  solitude of the Batcave, saving the world with this ergonomic marvel!</description>
      <author> (Suraj N. Kurapati)</author>
      <guid>https://sunaku.github.io/moergo-glove80-keyboard.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TLA⁺ is more than a DSL for breadth-first search</title>
      <link>https://ahelwer.ca/post/2024-09-18-tla-bfs-dsl/</link>
      <description>Although it isn’t usually taught that way, a lot of TLA⁺ newcomers develop the understanding that TLA⁺ is just a fancy domain-specific language (DSL) for breadth-first search. If you want to model all possible executions of a concurrent system - so the thinking goes - all you have to do is define:
The set of variables modeling your system The values of those variables in the initial state(s) Possible actions changing those variables to generate successor states Safety invariants you want to be true in every state The model checker will then use breadth-first search (BFS) to churn through all possible states (&amp;amp; thus execution orders) of your system, validating your invariants.</description>
      <author> (Andrew Helwer)</author>
      <guid>https://ahelwer.ca/post/2024-09-18-tla-bfs-dsl/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models Are Real-Time Game Engines</title>
      <link>https://hlfshell.ai/posts/gamengen/</link>
      <description>Your browser does not support the video tag.  Google Deepmind recently released Diffusion Models Are Real-Time Game Engines [Site] | [Paper], a fascinating paper wherein a modified Stable Diffusion model acts as the game engine for the classic game of DOOM. Player actions are fed directly into the model (which they called GameNGen), which outputs a generated image of the next frame 20 times a second. The game state and display is entirely handled by the model itself.</description>
      <author> (Keith Chester)</author>
      <guid>https://hlfshell.ai/posts/gamengen/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprising Scalability of Multitenancy - Marc&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://brooker.co.za/blog/2023/03/23/economics.html</link>
      <description>When most folks talk about the economics of cloud systems, their focus is on automatically scaling for long-term seasonality: changes on the order of days (fewer people buy things at night), weeks (fewer people visit the resort on weekdays), seasons, and holidays. Scaling for this kind of seasonality is useful and important, but there’s another factor that can be even more important and is often overlooked: short-term peak-to-average. Roughly speaking, the cost of a system scales with its (short-term1) peak traffic, but for most applications the value the system generates scales with the (long-term) average traffic.</description>
      <author> (Marc Brooker)</author>
      <guid>https://brooker.co.za/blog/2023/03/23/economics.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The self-hosted to DevOps engineer pipeline</title>
      <link>https://hiandrewquinn.github.io/til-site/posts/the-self-hosted-to-devops-engineer-pipeline/</link>
      <description>What’s the best way to get a job? Show someone with a job to do that you can do the job within their iron triangle. What’s the best way you can show someone you can handle a complicated k8s deployment, with 7 different CNCF-approved add-ons, zero-downtime rollouts and a whole bunch of YAML files? Probably by competently and publicly running your own complicated k8s infrastructure.
Self-hosters remind me a lot of the sysadmins of yore, who mostly ended up in the profession because they just couldn’t help but mess around with their underlying computing machine until they knew all kinds of weird nooks and crannies within it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hiandrewquinn.github.io/til-site/posts/the-self-hosted-to-devops-engineer-pipeline/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Text Compression Benchmark</title>
      <link>http://www.mattmahoney.net/dc/text.html</link>
      <description>Matt Mahoney
Last update: Sept 17, 2024. history</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.mattmahoney.net/dc/text.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking the CLOS — Dan&amp;#39;s Musings</title>
      <link>https://blog.djhaskin.com/blog/benchmarking-the-clos/</link>
      <description>I asked this question on the Lisp Discord recently:</description>
      <author> (Published on September 18, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.djhaskin.com/blog/benchmarking-the-clos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Displaying RTSP stream on a Kindle Paperwhite - cri.dev</title>
      <link>https://cri.dev/posts/2024-09-13-display-tapo-surveillance-camera-kindle-ffmpeg-jailbreak-root/</link>
      <description>Displaying RTSP stream on a Kindle Paperwhite using ffmpeg and eips to show local Tapo camera stream without servers, only with a scripted command running.</description>
      <author> (Christian Fei)</author>
      <guid>https://cri.dev/posts/2024-09-13-display-tapo-surveillance-camera-kindle-ffmpeg-jailbreak-root/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid search with PostgreSQL and pgvector</title>
      <link>https://jkatz05.com/post/postgres/hybrid-search-postgres-pgvector/</link>
      <description>An example of how to perform hybrid search with PostgreSQL and pgvector over vector data.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jkatz05.com/post/postgres/hybrid-search-postgres-pgvector/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Ensure Your Blog Outlives You</title>
      <link>https://sauravtom.github.io/posts/blogging-for-longevity/</link>
      <description>The Eternal Blog: A Practical Guide to Digital Longevity</description>
      <author> (sauravtom)</author>
      <guid>https://sauravtom.github.io/posts/blogging-for-longevity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I’m glad I miss the ’90s-00s internet</title>
      <link>https://tonyedwardspz.co.uk/blog/im-glad-i-miss-the-old-internet/</link>
      <description>A reply to I Wish I Didn’t Miss the ’90s-00s Internet.</description>
      <author> (Tony Edwards)</author>
      <guid>https://tonyedwardspz.co.uk/blog/im-glad-i-miss-the-old-internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Tor still safe to use? | Tor Project</title>
      <link>https://blog.torproject.org/tor-is-still-safe/</link>
      <description>This blog post is a response to an investigative news report about a large-scale law-enforcement attack that managed to de-anonymize a user of an old version of the long-retired app Ricochet. This blog post aims to provide insight into what we know so far. Nothing that the Tor Project has learned about this incident suggests that Tor Browser was attacked or exploited. Tor users can continue to use Tor Browser to access the web securely and anonymously.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.torproject.org/tor-is-still-safe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUNY First Computer System to Aid Administrative Control over Colleges at the Expense of Efficiency and Effectiveness</title>
      <link>http://pscbc.blogspot.com/2013/03/cuny-first-computer-system-to-aid.html</link>
      <description> Guest Post  &amp;#160;     Every once in a while I get a question, either privately or in a department meeting, regarding CUNYFirst. Here is what I ...</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>http://pscbc.blogspot.com/2013/03/cuny-first-computer-system-to-aid.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 23:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tectonic Surfing</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2987/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2987/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 20:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving GitHub Copilot Completions in Visual Studio for C# Developers - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/improving-github-copilot-completions-in-visual-studio-for-csharp-developers/</link>
      <description>Learn about the latest GitHub Copilot improvements for C# developers</description>
      <author> (Mika Dumont)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/improving-github-copilot-completions-in-visual-studio-for-csharp-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 19:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wonderful vi</title>
      <link>https://world.hey.com/dhh/wonderful-vi-a1d034d3</link>
      <description>The speed of change in technology often appears to be the industry&amp;#39;s defining characteristic. Nothing highlights that perception more than the recent and relentless march of AI advancements. But for as much as some things in technology change, many other things stay the same. Like vi! vi is a programming text editor that was created by...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://world.hey.com/dhh/wonderful-vi-a1d034d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 19:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>wordfreq/SUNSET.md at master &amp;#183; rspeer/wordfreq</title>
      <link>https://github.com/rspeer/wordfreq/blob/master/SUNSET.md</link>
      <description>Access a database of word frequencies, in various natural languages. - rspeer/wordfreq</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/rspeer/wordfreq/blob/master/SUNSET.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 14:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>