<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Get to know the .NET 5.0 SDK</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WmOCtlvNaTQ</link>
      <description>.NET 5 is the next version of .NET Core. The .NET SDK incudes the language compilers for C#, Visual Basic and F#. It also includes NuGet to manage packages, ...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WmOCtlvNaTQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 22:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com: Design Patterns: Elements of Reusable Object-Oriented Software eBook: Erich, Gamma, Helm Richard, Johnson Ralph, Vlissides John, Grady Booch: Kindle Store</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/Design-Patterns-Object-Oriented-Addison-Wesley-Professional-ebook/dp/B000SEIBB8?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202101</link>
      <description>Amazon.com: Design Patterns: Elements of Reusable Object-Oriented Software eBook: Erich, Gamma, Helm Richard, Johnson Ralph, Vlissides John, Grady Booch: Kindle Store</description>
      <author> (Gamma Erich







(Author),)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/Design-Patterns-Object-Oriented-Addison-Wesley-Professional-ebook/dp/B000SEIBB8?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202101</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 21:26:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3s2OAi9EbCA</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io/</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
    

    
      
    .NET Foundation
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3s2OAi9EbCA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 21:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If it will matter after today, stop talking about it in a chat room</title>
      <link>https://critter.blog/2021/01/12/if-it-matters-after-today-stop-talking-about-it-in-a-chat-room/</link>
      <description>Live chat is for things that can get lost.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://critter.blog/2021/01/12/if-it-matters-after-today-stop-talking-about-it-in-a-chat-room/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 21:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code Java Project Explorer Gets Better -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/01/12/vs-code-java-dec20.aspx</link>
      <description>The recently introduced project view for managing Java projects in Visual Studio Code received several enhancements in the latest update to Java functionality provided in Microsoft&amp;#39;s popular open source, cross-platform code editor.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel01/12/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/01/12/vs-code-java-dec20.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 21:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hacker Remotely Penetrated Bluetooth Chastity Belts, Demanding Victims Pay Ransom</title>
      <link>https://www.gizmodo.com.au/2021/01/a-hacker-remotely-penetrated-bluetooth-chastity-belts-demanding-victims-pay-ransom/</link>
      <description>A security flaw allowed a hacker to exploit users of an internet-enabled chastity belt by remotely locking them into their devices.</description>
      <author> (Lauren Rouse



 Posts




 Email)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gizmodo.com.au/2021/01/a-hacker-remotely-penetrated-bluetooth-chastity-belts-demanding-victims-pay-ransom/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 21:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jukefoxer/Signal-Android</title>
      <link>https://github.com/jukefoxer/Signal-Android/tree/feature/wa-db-import</link>
      <description>Fork from the JohanW fork of Signal, a private messenger for Android. It adds the option to import Whatsapp conversations. The purpose of this fork is to make the transition to Signal easier. It wa...</description>
      <author> (jukefoxer)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/jukefoxer/Signal-Android/tree/feature/wa-db-import</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 21:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code Day 2021 live event</title>
      <link>https://code.visualstudio.com/vscode-day</link>
      <description>Online, January 27, 2021. Join the VS Code team and community at a live event just for VS Code users. Get a glimpse of things to come and meet the team who works on VS Code every day.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code.visualstudio.com/vscode-day</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 20:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Entity Framework: A Tour of EF Core 5.0 pt 1</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p0UJdoBj-Lc</link>
      <description>#dotnet #EntityFramework #DataEF Core 5.0 includes support for many-to-many relationships and TPT mapping, two sorely missed features from EF6. Join us for a...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p0UJdoBj-Lc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 19:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dave Probert: Inside Windows 7 - User Mode Scheduler (UMS)</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/shows/Going+Deep/Dave-Probert-Inside-Windows-7-User-Mode-Scheduler-UMS/</link>
      <description>Here, we continue our exploration of the morphology of Windows 7 on Going Deep with windows kernel architect Dave Probert. You may remember him from an early
 four part episode of Going Deep where he</description>
      <author> (by Charles)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/shows/Going+Deep/Dave-Probert-Inside-Windows-7-User-Mode-Scheduler-UMS/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 19:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dave Probert: Inside Windows 7 - User Mode Scheduler (UMS)</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Going+Deep/Dave-Probert-Inside-Windows-7-User-Mode-Scheduler-UMS/player</link>
      <description>Here, we continue our exploration of the morphology of Windows 7 on Going Deep with windows kernel architect Dave Probert. You may remember him from an early
 four part episode of Going Deep where he</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Going+Deep/Dave-Probert-Inside-Windows-7-User-Mode-Scheduler-UMS/player</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 19:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I received first-ever donation on my open-source side project and it felt great!</title>
      <link>https://gourav.io/blog/first-donation-on-open-source-side-project</link>
      <description>I decided to build an extension for VSCode. That would add handy buttons for many common commands like save file, format file, show opened files etc.</description>
      <author> (Gourav Goyal)</author>
      <guid>https://gourav.io/blog/first-donation-on-open-source-side-project</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 19:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plain Text Accounting, a guide to Ledger and friends</title>
      <link>https://plaintextaccounting.org/</link>
      <description>Who&amp;#39;s using Ledger? has some stories.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://plaintextaccounting.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 19:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Silicon Valley, in a Show of Monopolistic Force, Destroyed Parler</title>
      <link>https://greenwald.substack.com/p/how-silicon-valley-in-a-show-of-monopolistic</link>
      <description>In the last three months, tech giants have censored political speech and journalism to manipulate U.S. politics, while liberals, with virtual unanimity, have cheered.</description>
      <author> (Glenn Greenwald)</author>
      <guid>https://greenwald.substack.com/p/how-silicon-valley-in-a-show-of-monopolistic</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 18:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Meet the Blazor Team</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5enEE3BBGJM</link>
      <description>Meet the people behind the code! Join us for a fun livestream with members of the Blazor team.Featuring: Safia Abdalla (@captainsafia), Jon Galloway (@jongal...</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
    

    
      
    .NET Foundation
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5enEE3BBGJM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 18:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Cake Bridge Dependency Injection</title>
      <link>https://devlead.medium.com/introducing-cake-bridge-dependency-injection-c7964f0210ed</link>
      <description>Utilize Cake abstractions and addins using Microsoft dependency injection</description>
      <author> (https://devlead.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://devlead.medium.com/introducing-cake-bridge-dependency-injection-c7964f0210ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 17:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Radar&amp;#39;s 2020 Year In Review</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-radar-2020-year-in-review/</link>
      <description>Today we are launching a dedicated Year In Review page with interactive maps and charts where you can explore what changed on the Internet in 2020. Year In Review is part of Cloudflare Radar.</description>
      <author> (John Graham-Cumming)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-radar-2020-year-in-review/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 17:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Objective-See: LuLu</title>
      <link>https://objective-see.com/products/lulu.html</link>
      <description>the free, shared-source macOS firewall</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://objective-see.com/products/lulu.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 17:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why am I receiving SHCNE_UPDATEDIR notifications that my code never generates? | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210112-00/?p=104707</link>
      <description>A customer had created a custom shell namespace, and they generated notifications for items in that namespace. Meanwhile, they also had code that listened for those notifications, and they found that sometimes the listener received SHCNE_UPDATE&amp;#173;DIR notifications, which is odd because their namespace never generates those notifications.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210112-00/?p=104707</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 16:04:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirated Academic Database Sci-Hub Is Now on the ‘Uncensorable Web’</title>
      <link>https://www.nasdaq.com/articles/pirated-academic-database-sci-hub-is-now-on-the-uncensorable-web-2021-01-11</link>
      <description>After her website faced repeated domain name revocations, Sci-Hub founder Alexandra Elbakyan has registered her website on the distributed domain names network Handshake.
The pirated database of academic papers is now accessible directly through the service’s portals as well as through NextDNS, a privacy-focused, cloud-based domain name service resolver which converts IP addresses into domain names.
“The DNS is like a phonebook for the internet. The addresses in the phonebook are the server IP addresses. DNS was created to give IP addresses human-readable names so with our platform, you’re finding the IP address through Handshake, not through a certificate authority,” Namebase CEO Tieshun Roquerre told CoinDesk.
Related: Now Is the Time to Advance the Decentralized Web
For a website that has had various domain names revoked over the years and which is now suspended from Twitter, the censorship-resistant DNS will help keep Sci-Hub accessible even as the legacy domain name system applies pressure.&amp;#160;
Sci-Hub is a worldwide database of academic publications, which pulls the research papers from under the paywalls of academic magazines and uploads them to the internet for everyone to download and read. It’s maintained by a single coder from Kazakhstan, Alexandra Elbakyan, who is raising donations via Russian payment network Yandex and bitcoin, CoinDesk wrote last year.
How does Handshake work?
Handshake is “is effectively a decentralized domain name server,” Roquerre said. Instead of using the web-standard certificate authority to authenticate user connections to a server, Handshake stores references to the IP address of the websites registered in its system. Namebase is a platform that offers users access to the Handshake network
That way, if certificate authority firms try to censor Sci-Hub’s domain name through the legacy system, then people who want to access the site still can through Handshake’s records.
Related: The Future of Cryptographic Security in the Age of Quantum
“If you get censored at the server level, you can switch servers. But if your domain name gets taken down, no one can access your site. As long as the name is intact, you can point it to any server,” he continued. Even if the band website finds a new domain, users may not know whether or not it is authentic (as an example, Roquerre said that Sci-Hub is no stranger to imposter sites).
To register a Handshake domain, anyone can propose a website name and place a bid for that website on Handshake’s marketplace with its eponymous HNS token. After a two week auction period, the highest bidder wins the domain (whose blockchain footprint acts like an NFT, Roquerre said) and the tokens are burned.
Roquerre said that Namebase does not issue tokens and that they are instead mined through Bitcoin-esque proof of work.
A total number of unique 6,818 Handshake domains are actively in use while roughly 375,000 have been registered, according to Handshake data shared with CoinDesk. The same data showed that marketplace volume has grown 60% on average month-over-month and is anticipated to top $140,000 this month.
Building the decentralized web
A decentralized domain name system like Handshake could be a significant win in the fight for the decentralized web.
The project is part of a crop of so-called Web 3.0 applications vying to create a less centralized, censorship-resistant internet. Handshake, for example, has a complementary browser to create an uncensored internet search experience.
Urbit, still another web 3.0 hopeful, is more than a decade in development and relies on Ethereum to construct a platform for decentralized personal servers.
As evidenced by Sci-Hub’s own problems, the decentralized web is being built out of fears of deplatforming. As the internet’s access points are increasingly centralized in the hands of a few actors, certain applications – most recently, Twitter-alternative Parler – have faced censorship at the hands of web server providers, app stores and DNS certificate authorities.
CORRECTION (Jan. 12, 2021, 01:15 UTC): This article originally said Namebase built Handshake. Namebase only provides offers users access to the network.
Related Stories

Building the Next Wave of Web 3.0
Web 3.0 Infrastructure Blockchain ‘The Graph’ Now Live on Ethereum</description>
      <author> (Contributor)</author>
      <guid>https://www.nasdaq.com/articles/pirated-academic-database-sci-hub-is-now-on-the-uncensorable-web-2021-01-11</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 16:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add a Parameter to a .NET Core Project Template</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Add-a-Parameter-to-a-NET-Core-Project-Template</link>
      <description>Every .NET project is based on a project template. Want to learn more about the ones that ship &amp;amp;quot;in the box&amp;amp;quot;? Want to learn how to create your own? In this multi-part series, ASP.NET PM Sayed</description>
      <author> (by Robert Green, Leslie Richardson [MSFT], Channel 9 Studio)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Add-a-Parameter-to-a-NET-Core-Project-Template</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 16:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SignalRs Crazy 8</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/signalrs-crazy-8</link>
      <description>Come join Alyssa Nicoll as she dives into the .NET world by learning SignalR. Ed Charbeneau will be co-hosting to create a week full of fun streams!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/signalrs-crazy-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 16:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP&amp;#178; quantile estimator: estimating the moving median without storing values</title>
      <link>https://aakinshin.net/posts/mp2-quantile-estimator/</link>
      <description>An algorithm that allows estimating moving quantile values without storing values</description>
      <author> (Andrey Akinshin)</author>
      <guid>https://aakinshin.net/posts/mp2-quantile-estimator/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 15:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resilient social networks</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/192898-B/resilient-social-networks?Key=3e0cf165-abe5-4e25-9c18-9544fcd78401</link>
      <description>Yesterday I posted about Parler banning and the likely impact of that, both legally and in terms of the technical details. My expectations is that new actors...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/192898-B/resilient-social-networks?Key=3e0cf165-abe5-4e25-9c18-9544fcd78401</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 15:05:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes are Coming... My Goals for 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VS0pqdKfdI8</link>
      <description>Although 2020 sucked in so many ways, I made a lot of progress in content creation. 2021 is going to be another big year for me, and I can wait to share with...</description>
      <author> (James Perkins)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VS0pqdKfdI8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 15:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theranos destroyed crucial subpoenaed SQL blood test database, can&amp;#39;t unlock backups, prosecutors say</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2021/01/12/theranos_database_loss/</link>
      <description>CEO Holmes also accused of funding extravagant lifestyle through fraud</description>
      <author> (Kieren McCarthy in San Francisco
            Tue&amp;#160;12&amp;#160;Jan&amp;#160;2021 // 03:28&amp;#160;UTC)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2021/01/12/theranos_database_loss/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 15:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moderna Provides Business Update and Announces Three New Development Programs in Infectious Disease Vaccines | Moderna, Inc.</title>
      <link>https://investors.modernatx.com/news-releases/news-release-details/moderna-provides-business-update-and-announces-three-new</link>
      <description>Seasonal flu vaccine program will cover four seasonal viruses recommended by the World Health Organization (WHO) HIV vaccine program to accelerate human validation of novel vaccination strategies Nipah vaccine program established against a virus of public health concern Moderna now has one</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://investors.modernatx.com/news-releases/news-release-details/moderna-provides-business-update-and-announces-three-new</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 14:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire Computer Science Curriculum in 1000 YouTube Videos | Laconicml</title>
      <link>https://laconicml.com/computer-science-curriculum-youtube-videos/</link>
      <description>This is The Entire Computer Science Curriculum in 1000 YouTube Videos. The curriculum is going to be organized in 40 courses in total, further organized in 4 academic years...</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/FilipProjcheski)</author>
      <guid>https://laconicml.com/computer-science-curriculum-youtube-videos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 14:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teamspeak 5 Beta Bug-Report BBcode not working, channel commander not shown</title>
      <link>https://community.teamspeak.com/t/teamspeak-5-beta-bug-report-bbcode-not-working-channel-commander-not-shown/14670/4</link>
      <description>Teamspeak 5 is based on Matrix, which uses a subset of HTML for formatting instead.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://community.teamspeak.com/t/teamspeak-5-beta-bug-report-bbcode-not-working-channel-commander-not-shown/14670/4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 14:04:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimising Blazor Applications | ConFoo.ca</title>
      <link>https://confoo.ca/en/yul2021/session/optimising-blazor-applications</link>
      <description>Conference for web developers February 22-26, 2021 in Montreal, Canada.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://confoo.ca/en/yul2021/session/optimising-blazor-applications</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 13:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An introduction to the Data Protection system in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/an-introduction-to-the-data-protection-system-in-asp-net-core/</link>
      <description>In this post I provide a primer on the ASP.NET Core data-protection system: what it is, why do we need it, and how it works at a high level</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/an-introduction-to-the-data-protection-system-in-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 13:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>theseus-os/Theseus</title>
      <link>https://github.com/theseus-os/Theseus</link>
      <description>A modern experimental OS written from scratch in Rust to explore novel OS structure and state management techniques. - theseus-os/Theseus</description>
      <author> (theseus-os)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/theseus-os/Theseus</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 12:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel Root Exploit via a ptrace() and execve() Race Condition</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/qUh507Na9nk</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s have a look at a recent kernel local privilege escalation exploit!Exploit Source: https://hxp.io/blog/79/hxp-CTF-2020-wisdom2/Kernel Developer Walkthro...</description>
      <author> (IppSec
  
  
    

    
      
    IppSec
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/qUh507Na9nk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 12:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON ECHO FLEX: MICROPHONE MUTE, REAL OR FAKE?</title>
      <link>https://electronupdate.blogspot.com/2021/01/amazon-echo-flex-microphone-mute-real.html</link>
      <description>Teardown and analysis of electronics.  Integrated circuit design analysis.</description>
      <author> (electronupdate)</author>
      <guid>https://electronupdate.blogspot.com/2021/01/amazon-echo-flex-microphone-mute-real.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 11:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Planets</title>
      <link>https://avinayak.github.io/art/2021/01/09/noise-planets.html</link>
      <description>Atul&amp;#39;s Programming Journals. A blog where I explore programming &amp;amp; Design
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://avinayak.github.io/art/2021/01/09/noise-planets.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 11:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-01-12</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/01/app-developer-links-2021-01-12/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/01/app-developer-links-2021-01-12/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 09:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go (golang) defer - Making Sure Something Gets Done</title>
      <link>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2021/01/go-golang-defer-making-sure-something.html</link>
      <description>   My primary world has been C# for a while. There are several things in Go   (golang) that I find interesting. One of those is the &amp;quot;defer&amp;quot; ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2021/01/go-golang-defer-making-sure-something.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 09:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Man at Capitol Riot Die After Accidentally Tasing Himself?</title>
      <link>https://www.snopes.com/fact-check/capitol-riot-taser-death/</link>
      <description>Four persons died in conjunction with the Capitol riot, but some reports surrounding their deaths weren’t entirely accurate.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.snopes.com/fact-check/capitol-riot-taser-death/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 08:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notification of Data Security Incident - December 23, 2020</title>
      <link>https://netgalley.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/360060979293</link>
      <description>Dear NetGalley Member,It is with great regret that we inform you that on Monday, December 21, 2020 NetGalley was the victim of a data security incident. What initially seemed like a simple defaceme...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://netgalley.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/360060979293</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 08:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECMAScript proposal: Import assertions</title>
      <link>https://2ality.com/2021/01/import-assertions.html</link>
      <description>The ECMAScript proposal “Import assertions” (by Myles Borins, Sven Sauleau, Dan Clark, and Daniel Ehrenberg) introduces syntax for associating metadata with import statements. In this blog post, we examine what that looks like and why it’s useful.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2ality.com/2021/01/import-assertions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve error message when CORS is not configured correctly by JamesNK &amp;#183; Pull Request #1171 &amp;#183; grpc/grpc-dotnet</title>
      <link>https://github.com/grpc/grpc-dotnet/pull/1171</link>
      <description>Fixes #1163
Not including required gRPC headers in CORS configuration is a common error when using gRPC client in the browser. Why the error happens with CORS, and how to fix it is non-obvious.
Upd...</description>
      <author> (grpc)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/grpc/grpc-dotnet/pull/1171</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programmatically Navigate with React Router</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/programmatically-navigate-with-react-router</link>
      <description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll look at a myriad of approaches to navigating programmatically—redirecting a user based on an action—with React Router.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/programmatically-navigate-with-react-router</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we quickly refactored with Resharper more than 23.000 calls to Debug.Assert() into more meaningful assertions - NDepend</title>
      <link>https://blog.ndepend.com/how-we-quickly-refactored-with-resharper-more-than-23-000-calls-to-debug-assert-into-more-meaningful-assertions/</link>
      <description>Case study of a major refactoring session performed in a few hours thanks to the Resharper Structural Search and Replace feature.</description>
      <author> (Patrick Smacchia)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ndepend.com/how-we-quickly-refactored-with-resharper-more-than-23-000-calls-to-debug-assert-into-more-meaningful-assertions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:05:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining .NET 5, WinUI, UWP - FullTrust, PartialTrust, WindowsAppContainer - Nick&amp;#39;s .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/trust-appcontainers/</link>
      <description>As Microsoft progresses towards the first release of WinUI3 and in parallel invests into Project Reunion, the gap between Win32 based applications (eg WinForms, WPF) and UWP applications is being eroded. In this post we’re going to look at the role of trust, identity, capabilities and the Windows App Container, and how they relate to … Continue reading &amp;quot;Combining .NET 5, WinUI, UWP – FullTrust, PartialTrust, WindowsAppContainer&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/trust-appcontainers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Minister announces online freedom of speech bill</title>
      <link>https://polandin.com/51388314/justice-minister-announces-online-freedom-of-speech-bill</link>
      <description>If a social media service doesn’t obey a ruling, a special court could subject it to a fine of up to EUR 1.8 million imposed by the Office of Electronic Communications.</description>
      <author> (Telewizja Polska S.A)</author>
      <guid>https://polandin.com/51388314/justice-minister-announces-online-freedom-of-speech-bill</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform How To Build A Single-Page Web App in XAML and C# with WebAssembly Using Uno Platform</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/how-to-build-a-single-page-web-app-in-xaml-and-c-with-webassembly-using-uno-platform/</link>
      <description>Pixel-Perfect Multi-Platform Applications with C# and WinUI for Windows, WebAssembly, iOS, macOS, Android and Linux</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/how-to-build-a-single-page-web-app-in-xaml-and-c-with-webassembly-using-uno-platform/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing decoupled code with MediatR: The Mediator Pattern</title>
      <link>https://samwalpole.com/writing-decoupled-code-with-mediatr-the-mediator-pattern?guid=none</link>
      <description>I recently wrote a blog post introducing some of my favourite NuGet packages: My Top 4 NuGet Packages for ASP.NET Core. In that post, I briefly introduced a package called MediatR. Today, I will dedicate this post to revisiting MediatR in further det...</description>
      <author> (Sam WalpolePublished on Jan 9, 20219 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://samwalpole.com/writing-decoupled-code-with-mediatr-the-mediator-pattern?guid=none</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using .env in .NET - Dusted Codes</title>
      <link>https://dusted.codes/dotenv-in-dotnet</link>
      <description>
.NET (Core) comes with a lot of bells and whistles. One of them is the sheer amount of managing app...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dusted.codes/dotenv-in-dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A practical guide to WebAssembly memory - radu&amp;#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://radu-matei.com/blog/practical-guide-to-wasm-memory/</link>
      <description>Memory in WebAssembly is one of the topics that creates confusion for newcomers, particularly for those with experience in languages with memory management features like garbage collection, such as JavaScript, Go, or Java. In this article we explore using memory in WebAssembly in various scenarios - passing JavaScript arrays to Rust and AssemblyScript modules, checking for some basic memory leaks using Valgrind, or exchanging strings between runtimes and modules using Wasmtime.</description>
      <author> (Radu M
                    @matei_radu)</author>
      <guid>https://radu-matei.com/blog/practical-guide-to-wasm-memory/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 06:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Need a New Media System</title>
      <link>https://taibbi.substack.com/p/we-need-a-new-media-system</link>
      <description>If you sell culture war all day, don’t be surprised by the real-world consequences</description>
      <author> (Matt Taibbi)</author>
      <guid>https://taibbi.substack.com/p/we-need-a-new-media-system</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 05:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>01-11-21 Boca SN9--3 - EasyZoom | Place for high-resolution images</title>
      <link>https://www.easyzoom.com/imageaccess/202ac1471a8b461e92b3903ad43e6832</link>
      <description>Share huge gigapixel high-resolution images from microscopy, photography, astronomy</description>
      <author> (by
                            Jack Beyer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.easyzoom.com/imageaccess/202ac1471a8b461e92b3903ad43e6832</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 04:16:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pakrym/jab</title>
      <link>https://github.com/pakrym/jab</link>
      <description>C# Source Generator based dependency injection container implementation. - pakrym/jab</description>
      <author> (pakrym)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/pakrym/jab</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 03:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does it mean to be really deliberate about building your space? How can we build a nest for our home office with a 4k window scene? For FREE?!</title>
      <link>https://www.tiktok.com/@shanselman/video/6916662898748165382?_d=secCgYIASAHKAESMgowSOH0R6XQO%2B9g3y27OYADxUo3RI%2FZkRYulRYrDOlqWwPfnTw4qQ%2B0qkdFOcvBKMHyGgA%3D&amp;language=en&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;sec_user_id=MS4wLjABAAAAFt5MIdypn_f0WZh40awWRF89Zw9Amdawzs3Uv8kCYseoyWirUnzj1bZawGbeNpw4&amp;share_item_id=6916662898748165382&amp;share_link_id=3BFF4AF1-4C5F-4AE1-A81F-46CC275FEA18&amp;timestamp=1610411177&amp;u_code=de1hm7ac6mg7id&amp;user_id=6860974717076014086</link>
      <description>Scott Hanselman (@shanselman) has created a short video on TikTok with music original sound. | What does it mean to be really deliberate about building your space? How can we build a nest for our home office with a 4k window scene? For FREE?!</description>
      <author> (shanselmanScott Hanselman &amp;#183; 39m ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiktok.com/@shanselman/video/6916662898748165382?_d=secCgYIASAHKAESMgowSOH0R6XQO%2B9g3y27OYADxUo3RI%2FZkRYulRYrDOlqWwPfnTw4qQ%2B0qkdFOcvBKMHyGgA%3D&amp;language=en&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;sec_user_id=MS4wLjABAAAAFt5MIdypn_f0WZh40awWRF89Zw9Amdawzs3Uv8kCYseoyWirUnzj1bZawGbeNpw4&amp;share_item_id=6916662898748165382&amp;share_link_id=3BFF4AF1-4C5F-4AE1-A81F-46CC275FEA18&amp;timestamp=1610411177&amp;u_code=de1hm7ac6mg7id&amp;user_id=6860974717076014086</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 01:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blog migrated to Statiq</title>
      <link>https://devlead.medium.com/blog-migrated-to-statiq-960da1a2504b</link>
      <description>Since 2016 I’ve been using Medium as my platform of choice, this is not a rage quit from the platform, I’ll keep posting on Medium, the…</description>
      <author> (https://devlead.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://devlead.medium.com/blog-migrated-to-statiq-960da1a2504b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 01:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updated Infragistics UI/UX Desktop Components Support .NET 5 -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/01/11/infragistics-update.aspx</link>
      <description>Infragistics announced a new update to its UI/UX components suite, declaring that the .NET-centric Windows Forms and Windows Presentation Foundation (WPF) components are compatible with .NET 5, Microsoft&amp;#39;s open source and cross-platform evolution of the old Windows-only .NET Framework.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel01/11/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/01/11/infragistics-update.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 01:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does .NET 5 Do XAML? By Decoupling It from Windows with WinUI 3, C#/WinRT and More -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/01/11/xaml-net5.aspx</link>
      <description>By lifting WinRT projections for C# out of the compiler and the runtime Microsoft is enabling the use of .NET5 with XAML applications.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel01/11/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/01/11/xaml-net5.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 01:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundred Rabbits</title>
      <link>https://100r.co/site/working_offgrid_efficiently.html</link>
      <description>Hundredrabbits create open source low-power hardware, tools and toys aboard a sailboat named Pino</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://100r.co/site/working_offgrid_efficiently.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 01:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My personal wishlist for a decentralized social network</title>
      <link>https://carter.sande.duodecima.technology/decentralized-wishlist/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;d be interested in a decentralized social network with network-layer anonymity, grassroots content delivery, and customizable moderation.</description>
      <author> (Carter Sande)</author>
      <guid>https://carter.sande.duodecima.technology/decentralized-wishlist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup ideas for 2021</title>
      <link>https://sagivo.com/startup/2021/01/11/startup-ideas.html</link>
      <description>Here are some ideas I have for 2021</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sagivo.com/startup/2021/01/11/startup-ideas.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updating system right way</title>
      <link>https://blog.bshah.in/2021/01/11/updating-system-right-way/</link>
      <description>I was arguing discussing earlier today with some community members what is best practice regarding the updating systems.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.bshah.in/2021/01/11/updating-system-right-way/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The clipboard history feature is the best thing since sliced bread  :: Martin De Wulf — </title>
      <link>https://multitasked.net/2021/01/11/the-clipboard-history.html</link>
      <description>For those who do not know, having a clipboard history is the best thing since sliced bread.
It is that little feature that allows you, after you made a few copy actions (ctrl+c on Windows or command-c on Mac), to choose any of the copied texts to paste it.
It looks like this when I use Alfred, a productivity tool on Mac, by pression option-command-c (the three buttons at once).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://multitasked.net/2021/01/11/the-clipboard-history.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Right to Pay for my Products</title>
      <link>https://paulheymann.de/essay/2021/01/08/the-right-to-pay-for-my-products.html</link>
      <description>The Right to Pay for my Products</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://paulheymann.de/essay/2021/01/08/the-right-to-pay-for-my-products.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kafka As A Database? Yes Or No – A Summary Of Both Sides</title>
      <link>https://davidxiang.com/2021/01/10/kafka-as-a-database/</link>
      <description>Should you use Kafka as a database? The popularity of stream-focused architectures has risen in popularity—is it right for your software?</description>
      <author> (by dxiang)</author>
      <guid>https://davidxiang.com/2021/01/10/kafka-as-a-database/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My ISP Is Killing My Idle SSH Sessions. Yours Might Be Too. – Title</title>
      <link>https://anderstrier.dk/2021/01/11/my-isp-is-killing-my-idle-ssh-sessions-yours-might-be-too/</link>
      <description>tl;dr: My ISP’s CGNAT session timeout is too short, meaning TCP keepalives gets dropped. Test if your own NAT, or your ISP’s CGN, violates RFC5382‘s REQ-5 using this tool: https://github.com/AndersTrier/NAT-TCP-test.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anderstrier.dk/2021/01/11/my-isp-is-killing-my-idle-ssh-sessions-yours-might-be-too/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>52 Launches in 52 Weeks</title>
      <link>https://joeldare.com/52-launches-in-52-weeks</link>
      <description>Back in 2016 I did a project where I released something of value every week for 12 weeks. I called it The Passive Income Experiment. It wasn’t financially successful, but I created a couple products that I still use regularly. I also launched 10 things that were terrible ideas.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joeldare.com/52-launches-in-52-weeks</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Beat Parkinson&amp;#39;s Law - Anthony Dik&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://antdke.co/posts/how-to-beat-parkinsons-law/</link>
      <description>This is a method I use to help me stop procrastinating on work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://antdke.co/posts/how-to-beat-parkinsons-law/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the Canadian Tech Scene Doesn’t Work</title>
      <link>https://alexdanco.com/2021/01/11/why-the-canadian-tech-scene-doesnt-work/</link>
      <description>Toronto is not the next great startup scene. Neither is Waterloo, or Vancouver, or anywhere in Canada.&amp;#160; I’m sorry that I have to write this. I really am. I want&amp;#160;it to work. But the growing cho…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alexdanco.com/2021/01/11/why-the-canadian-tech-scene-doesnt-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NetConf Virtual Event |Creating Native iOS + Android Apps in C# using Xamarin</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Redmond/events/274973022</link>
      <description>Mon, Jan 11, 2021, 4:00 PM: Do you love C# and want to create an iOS or Android app? Me too!Xamarin enables .NET developers to create native Android and iOS apps in C#.Xamarin gives C# developers acce</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Redmond/events/274973022</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Experts Real? | Fantastic Anachronism</title>
      <link>https://fantasticanachronism.com/2021/01/11/are-experts-real/</link>
      <description>Credentials, Expertise, and Feedback Loops</description>
      <author> (Alvaro de Menard)</author>
      <guid>https://fantasticanachronism.com/2021/01/11/are-experts-real/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laptops need to change</title>
      <link>https://grigorchuk.me/posts/laptops-need-to-change/</link>
      <description>They do</description>
      <author> (Sergey Grigorchuk)</author>
      <guid>https://grigorchuk.me/posts/laptops-need-to-change/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL with Maarten Louage</title>
      <link>https://developerweeklypodcast.com/19</link>
      <description>In this episode, I talk with Maarten Louage about GraphQL. I find out what GraphQL actually is, what it can do and why I should use it. I went blank into this conversation, with little knowledge about GraphQL, and I am delighted about it and will certainly try out an implementation of it (as GraphQL is not a technology, but a specification). So if you want to create easy to use APIs that are fast, listen to the episode to learn how to create those with GraphQL. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developerweeklypodcast.com/19</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 23:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Application Insights Profiler | Channel 9</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Azure-Application-Insights-Profiler/player</link>
      <description>Need to collect performance data about your Azure apps while they are running in production? DevDiv Azure Services PM Chuck Weininger shows us how to do that using the Azure Application Insights Profi</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Azure-Application-Insights-Profiler/player</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 23:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Query Strings in Blazor WebAssembly - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/query-strings-blazor-webassembly/</link>
      <description>Using query strings in Blazor WebAssembly is quite easy, and we are going to learn how to send and read them in our components.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/query-strings-blazor-webassembly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 23:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Developer Weekly podcast</title>
      <link>https://developerweeklypodcast.com/</link>
      <description>A weekly show for developers and technologists that are interested in technology, life-long learning, and the people behind the tech. This is not an ordinary technology show as it goes beyond the latest tools and frameworks and shines a spotlight on the humans that create and use it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developerweeklypodcast.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 23:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>