<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Finland bans smartphones in schools</title>
      <link>https://yle.fi/a/74-20158886</link>
      <description>Pupils will be able to use their phones in some circumstances, but they will need to get permission from teachers.</description>
      <guid>https://yle.fi/a/74-20158886</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sycophancy in GPT-4o: What happened and what we’re doing about it</title>
      <link>https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/</link>
      <description>We have rolled back last week’s GPT‑4o update in ChatGPT so people are now using an earlier version with more balanced behavior. The update we removed was overly flattering or agreeable—often described as sycophantic.</description>
      <guid>https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - freeman-jiang/beatsync: 🔊 High-precision web player for multi-device audio playback and spatial audio.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/freeman-jiang/beatsync</link>
      <description>🔊 High-precision web player for multi-device audio playback and spatial audio. - freeman-jiang/beatsync</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/freeman-jiang/beatsync</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo and Toyota Outline Strategic Partnership to Advance Autonomous Driving Deployment</title>
      <link>https://waymo.com/blog/2025/04/waymo-and-toyota-outline-strategic-partnership</link>
      <description>Toyota Motor Corporation (“Toyota”) and Waymo reached a preliminary agreement to explore a collaboration focused on accelerating the development and deployment of autonomous driving technologies.</description>
      <guid>https://waymo.com/blog/2025/04/waymo-and-toyota-outline-strategic-partnership</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Nix or Not to Nix?</title>
      <link>https://charliesabino.com/to-nix-or-not-to-nix/</link>
      <description>I've been considering hopping on the  hype train for a little while now. Its new  finally addresses its notorious documentation gap—a big deal for a system b...</description>
      <guid>https://charliesabino.com/to-nix-or-not-to-nix/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Scale Data Processing: Over Thousands of Devices With Azure Cosmos DB and Expanso</title>
      <link>https://blog.bacalhau.org/p/high-scale-data-processing-cosmosdb-bacalhau</link>
      <description>If you're dealing with data generated across thousands of devices or locations, you know the pain.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.bacalhau.org/p/high-scale-data-processing-cosmosdb-bacalhau</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons From TestCon 4</title>
      <link>https://creme332.github.io/posts/testcon4/</link>
      <description>My personal experience at TestCon 4, including key insights on AI in testing, test efficiency metrics, recommended resources, and honest critiques.</description>
      <guid>https://creme332.github.io/posts/testcon4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carl Öst Wilkens´ Blog - Remembering my friends´ faces using Flash Cards</title>
      <link>https://ostwilkens.se/blog/remember-faces-with-anki</link>
      <description>A place for me to vent about my current obsessions.</description>
      <guid>https://ostwilkens.se/blog/remember-faces-with-anki</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converting My 500+ Page Blog from Jekyll to Hugo — Nick Janetakis</title>
      <link>https://nickjanetakis.com/blog/converting-my-500-page-blog-from-jekyll-to-hugo</link>
      <description>This was a fun adventure that took less time than I thought it would have. Here's a bunch of things I learned along the way.</description>
      <guid>https://nickjanetakis.com/blog/converting-my-500-page-blog-from-jekyll-to-hugo</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using equatable() to Avoid the NavigationLink Pre-Build Pitfall</title>
      <link>https://fatbobman.com/en/posts/using-equatable-to-avoid-the-navigationlink-pre-build-pitfall/</link>
      <description>SwiftUI NavigationLink can cause performance issues by pre-building views; using equatable() on Equatable views prevents this and keeps navigation smooth.</description>
      <guid>https://fatbobman.com/en/posts/using-equatable-to-avoid-the-navigationlink-pre-build-pitfall/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good vs Great Animations</title>
      <link>https://emilkowal.ski/ui/good-vs-great-animations</link>
      <description>Practical tips on how to go from good to great animations.</description>
      <guid>https://emilkowal.ski/ui/good-vs-great-animations</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Broken OTPs and Open Endpoints Turned a Dating App Into a Stalker’s Playground</title>
      <link>https://alexschapiro.com/blog/security/vulnerability/2025/04/21/startups-need-to-take-security-seriously</link>
      <description>Startups Need to Take Security Seriously</description>
      <guid>https://alexschapiro.com/blog/security/vulnerability/2025/04/21/startups-need-to-take-security-seriously</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A love letter to LLM</title>
      <link>https://itzlambda.com/posts/a-love-letter-to-llm/</link>
      <description>Or how LLM helped me overcome perfectionism</description>
      <author> (itzlambda)</author>
      <guid>https://itzlambda.com/posts/a-love-letter-to-llm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Solved the Expression Problem</title>
      <link>https://gavinhoward.com/2025/04/how-i-solved-the-expression-problem/</link>
      <description>The Expression Problem is the biggest unsolved problem in programming languages. I solved it, and here's how.</description>
      <guid>https://gavinhoward.com/2025/04/how-i-solved-the-expression-problem/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launching BSSG - My Journey from Dynamic CMS to Bash Static Site Generator</title>
      <link>https://it-notes.dragas.net/2025/04/07/launching-bssg-my-journey-from-dynamic-cms-to-bash-static-site-generator/</link>
      <description>Announcing the public release of BSSG, a Bash Static Site Generator born from a personal journey away from complex dynamic CMS. Discover a simple, portable alternative for your blog.</description>
      <guid>https://it-notes.dragas.net/2025/04/07/launching-bssg-my-journey-from-dynamic-cms-to-bash-static-site-generator/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A PostgreSQL planner gotcha with CTEs DELETE and LIMIT</title>
      <link>https://www.shayon.dev/post/2025/119/a-postgresql-planner-gotcha-with-ctes-delete-and-limit/</link>
      <description>How a seemingly straightforward DELETE query using a CTE and LIMIT returned more rows than expected due to query planner optimization.</description>
      <guid>https://www.shayon.dev/post/2025/119/a-postgresql-planner-gotcha-with-ctes-delete-and-limit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Tsai - Blog - Revisiting ZFS for Mac</title>
      <link>https://mjtsai.com/blog/2025/04/28/revisiting-zfs-for-mac/</link>
      <description>Hacker News is highlighting Adam Leventhal’s 2016 post (2016 comments) about Apple’s Leopard-era support for ZFS:</description>
      <guid>https://mjtsai.com/blog/2025/04/28/revisiting-zfs-for-mac/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The indifference engine</title>
      <link>https://ponnekanti.net/posts/the-indifference-engine/</link>
      <description>It’s just insane that language models actually work. How is it possible. The world is enchanted. Do you still feel it? A kind of feverish awe? My computer can talk to me, it can teach me, yet it possesses no greater essence than its transistors…
Except I don’t really feel like that. Not often, certainly not constantly. I think the most beautiful thing about it all to me is how one is forced to constantly excite themselves into this state. It would be so easy to let it slip into normalcy. “OK. Guess my laptop can talk to me now and teach me anything”. Accept and move on. Kids using them to cheat on their essays. Out of nowhere, eldritch magic cast into our computers, and just like that effortlessly integrated into life. The machine is not human-shaped. The human is machine-shaped. We can accept anything, this is the rule that governs us.</description>
      <guid>https://ponnekanti.net/posts/the-indifference-engine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The weirdest HTML feature (or bug?): display your head</title>
      <link>https://lapcatsoftware.com/articles/2025/4/7.html</link>
      <description>According to the Mozilla Developer Network web docs, "The head of an HTML document is the part that is not displayed in the web browser when the page is loaded."</description>
      <guid>https://lapcatsoftware.com/articles/2025/4/7.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 23:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts: I made my AI think harder by making it argue with itself repeatedly. It works stupidly well.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts</link>
      <description>I made my AI think harder by making it argue with itself repeatedly. It works stupidly well. - PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 22:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee and Open Source Conversation - David Whitney</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FK6DdD5ke9Y</link>
      <description>David is the Director of Architecture for NewDay, and the founder of Electric Head Software. Focusing on iterative software delivery, developer mentoring and cultural change - mostly working with London-based organisations.

He speaks about software design, culture, and ethics in technology - rounded out by an assortment of talks about software that probably doesn't need to exist but makes the world a little more fun. David has previously served as the chief coding technical architect for JustGiving and helped market-leading organisations including JUST-EAT, Trainline and Vodafone improve their technical capabilities.

David is a Microsoft MVP, has been part of the OpenUK Honours list for open-source advocacy, and is a twice bestselling author of children's books about programming.

There's a chance you've seen him talk at a spread of conferences, user groups and code-dojos around the UK over the last decade or indulged in bar-room programming debates after one.

You can follow David on Social Media
https://bsky.app/profile/davidwhitney.co.uk
http://twitter.com/david_whitney
https://mastodon.social/@david_whitney
http://github.com/davidwhitney
https://threads.net/@davidwhitneycouk

PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO THE PODCAST

- Spotify: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-spotify
- Apple Podcasts: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-apple
- Google Podcasts: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-google
- RSS: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-rss

You can check out more episodes of Coffee and Open Source on https://www.coffeeandopensource.com

Coffee and Open Source is hosted by Isaac Levin (https://twitter.com/isaacrlevin)</description>
      <author> (Isaac Levin)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FK6DdD5ke9Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 19:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI is not replacing jobs or hurting wages at all</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2025/04/29/generative_ai_no_effect_jobs_wages/</link>
      <description>: 'When we look at the economic outcomes, it really has not moved the needle'</description>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2025/04/29/generative_ai_no_effect_jobs_wages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 18:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Periodic Suggestion to Try, Just Try, Switching to Kagi for Search</title>
      <link>https://daringfireball.net/2025/04/try_switching_to_kagi</link>
      <description>Paying for Kagi today feels a *lot* like paying for HBO back in the cable TV heyday.</description>
      <guid>https://daringfireball.net/2025/04/try_switching_to_kagi</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Mac Mini M4 Accessory? Pulwtop Hub &amp; Dock Hands-On Review - M.2 SSD, HDMI, &amp; USB!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dnn0Bid9C88</link>
      <description>Buy - https://amzn.to/3YgL2K5

In this video, I review the sleek Pulwtop Mac Mini M4 Hub Dock—a game-changing 9-in-1 accessory that enhances your 2024 Mac Mini M4 and M4 Pro with 4K HDMI output, multiple USB ports, card readers, and even an M.2 SSD expansion slot for supercharged storage, all wrapped in an elegant design perfect for any creative or professional workspace.

Official Page: https://pulwtop.com/products/pulwtop-mac-mini-hub-bd240a

Chapters:
00:00 - Intro &amp; Device Overview
01:12 - Unboxing &amp; SSD Install
03:13 - SSD &amp; WiFi Speed Tests
05:34 - Review &amp; Final Thoughts

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCENTmbKaTphpWV2R2evVz2A/join

👕 Buy some swag! - https://jamesmontemagno.myspreadshop.com/
☕️ Buy me a coffee - https://www.buymeacoffee.com/jamesmontemagno

Follow:
👨‍💻 GitHub: https://github.com/jamesmontemagno
🦜 X: https://x.com/jamesmontemagno
📄 Website: https://www.montemagno.com
📰 Newsletter: https://newsletter.montemagno.com/

Disclaimer: This channel, videos, and streams are created in my spare time and are a product of me... James Montemagno! They are NOT officially affiliated or endorsed by Microsoft (my employer) in any way. Opinions and views are my own.

What is on my hat? It is the CLE clothing logo because I am from Cleveland! Checkout their awesome CLE merch: https://cleclothingco.myshopify.com/

What is that art on my wall? It is an original piece from the French street artist Gregos of La Butte Montmartre: https://www.instagram.com/p/BceZ1oNHiQx/

My Setup:
📷 Canon M50 Mark II - https://amzn.to/3P8R7lp
💡 Nanoleaf Elements Lights - https://amzn.to/3umwJVW
🎙 Blue Spark Microphone - https://amzn.to/3qgtYkq
🎙 Blue Pop Filter - https://amzn.to/3jEWM3r
🤳 Rode Microphone Arm - https://amzn.to/2Z68AlE
🎧 Sony MDR7306 Headphones - https://amzn.to/372jxta
📲 Stream Deck - https://amzn.to/373Uk1n
🖱 MX Master 2S Mouse - https://amzn.to/3d7J2gj
⌨️ Tecware Phantom Keyboard - https://amzn.to/3aUP4y9

Using links I provide I may receive a commission if you buy something which helps support the channel.

#macminim4 #macmini #pulwtop</description>
      <author> (James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=dnn0Bid9C88</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>