<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Aspect — Sample Code</title>
      <link>https://sample-code.aspect.app/</link>
      <description>Copy React code from any site</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sample-code.aspect.app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 02:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Vim the Simple Way</title>
      <link>https://www.vimified.com/</link>
      <description>Vim lessons that get to the point. Build proficiency fast. Improve with detailed feedback.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.vimified.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add support for specifying a template name. by haacked &amp;#183; Pull Request #44 &amp;#183; DamianEdwards/TagHelperPack</title>
      <link>https://github.com/DamianEdwards/TagHelperPack/pull/44</link>
      <description>The Display Template HTML helpers support specifying a template name that is used to override the default display/editor template for a given type.
This adds support for that to the display and edi...</description>
      <author> (DamianEdwards)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/DamianEdwards/TagHelperPack/pull/44</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 23:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TagHelperPack 0.8.0-pre-20220709.21</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/TagHelperPack/0.8.0-pre-20220709.21</link>
      <description>A set of useful, and possibly opinionated, Tag Helpers for ASP.NET Core.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/TagHelperPack/0.8.0-pre-20220709.21</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 23:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kate Bush&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;Running Up That Hill&amp;quot; Synth Sounds | Reverb Machine</title>
      <link>https://reverbmachine.com/blog/kate-bush-running-up-that-hill-synth-sounds/</link>
      <description>Kate Bush has had an enormous impact on modern music, as a musician her adoption of the Yamaha CS-80 synth and CMI Fairlight sampler empowered her to be more creative. Bush released four albums before finally building her own studio in 1985, and subsequently released her fifth album, Hounds of Love, featuring the single Running Up That Hill. The album was an art-rock masterpiece with heavy synthpop overtones; it topped charts and is regarded as her finest album. On many of Kate Bush’s early albums, she used the Yamaha CS-80 as her main composition instrument. She seemed to favour it particularly for its touch-sensitivity, and it was one of the few synths that offered the feature at the time. Bush mainly relied on the synths presets, and utilising its touch-sensitivity allowed her to create more organic-sounding tracks, which worked for her as she would often layer the CS-80 with real acoustic instruments, such as cellos and the balalaika. The Fairlight CMI was released in 1979, and Kate Bush was an early user, utilising it on several tracks from her 1980 album Never Ever. The Fairlight soon replaced the CS-80 as her main instrument and ended up being used heavily on Hounds of Love, providing many of the album&amp;#39;s signature sounds. Arturia has created software emulations of both the Yamaha CS-80 and the Fairlight CMI, and I’ll use these throughout the article.&amp;#160;</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/reverbmachine/)</author>
      <guid>https://reverbmachine.com/blog/kate-bush-running-up-that-hill-synth-sounds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Should Pay for Tutors - Scott H Young</title>
      <link>https://www.scotthyoung.com/blog/2022/06/21/pay-for-tutors/</link>
      <description>One-on-one instruction is highly underrated. Here&amp;#39;s why you should get tutors for the skills and subjects you care about.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.scotthyoung.com/blog/2022/06/21/pay-for-tutors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nested Corner Case — Carlos Nuila</title>
      <link>https://carlosnuila.com/blog/nested-corners</link>
      <description>If you’re like me and get spooked by non-concentric corners then you’ll be happy to know that there is an easy fix!</description>
      <author> (Jun 6
            
            Written By Carlos Nuila)</author>
      <guid>https://carlosnuila.com/blog/nested-corners</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Issues in Replacing OpenSSL – Security Poodle</title>
      <link>http://www.richsalz.com/tls/issues-in-replacing-openssl/</link>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I tweeted about “what would it take to replace OpenSSL”?  You can see my tweet thread and responses here. I phrased my question poorly: I didn’t make it clear that the intent was to replace OpenSSL within an organization which already had a lot of software (including open source) that uses OpenSSL. Unfortunately, this made a lot of excellent comments, notably around using a memory-safe language, not relevant. Sorry, my fault.</description>
      <author> (admin)</author>
      <guid>http://www.richsalz.com/tls/issues-in-replacing-openssl/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printers Are Demons</title>
      <link>https://cjohanaja.com/musings/printer-demons/</link>
      <description>Printers are the bane of my existence.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cjohanaja.com/musings/printer-demons/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Need New Words for Work</title>
      <link>https://www.henryvanwagenberg.com/essays/we-need-new-definitions-of-the-word-work</link>
      <description>I’m cracking the word “work” into dozens of new words.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.henryvanwagenberg.com/essays/we-need-new-definitions-of-the-word-work</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voronoi Relaxation Under Different Distance Metrics</title>
      <link>https://natejh.com/Voronoi-Relaxation-Under-Different-Distance-Metrics</link>
      <description>07 Jul 2022 - Nate Hofmann</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://natejh.com/Voronoi-Relaxation-Under-Different-Distance-Metrics</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Downloading Academic Papers Automatically</title>
      <link>https://yannherklotz.com/ebib-papers/</link>
      <description>Ebib is a great bibliography manager that can be extended in various useful ways.  I’ll go over my procedure of how I added automatic downloading of papers to ebib bib entries.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yannherklotz.com/ebib-papers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;ve come to hate the term Best Practice | Ashlan&amp;#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://ashlan.com/blog/i-ve-come-to-hate-the-term-best-practice/</link>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;#39;m not against the concept or idea of Best Practice, but just like Communism, when its deployed in the real world, things don&amp;#39;t go as planned. Best practice, despite its innocent sounding name, doesn&amp;#39;t necessary mean its always good. Best practice simply means that everybody is following in that direction.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the software engineering department of my company, the upper management is obsessed with Best Practice. We have many meetings where it is evangelized. Its lead to a cult-like behavior where questioning anything that is labeled Best Practice is suspicious or treated as an anti-pattern. Nobody is questioning if the best practices are wrong or if they only apply in certain situations or certain designs. Maybe there are people who question it but are too afraid to be labeled as a heretic? I know a lot of times I question why we choose to do things a certain way but don&amp;#39;t want to be called out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The biggest reason why best practices in software engineering can be harmful is because not all best practices are really best practices. Some times, certain ways of doing things haven&amp;#39;t been generally accepted. Other times, individuals might think their own experience or opinion are best practice because of the community and individuals they surround themselves with. People who are preaching their best practices might actually be preaching their preferences. Take for example Hibernate in Java. Best practice suggest to use it. Does this mean we should use it in ALL scenarios? Does this mean any software not using Hibernate needs to be refactored?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Good best practices are simple and universal. Many developer best practices tackle complex issues that require nuance and context — but that nuance and context get lost as the best practice spreads. Generally speaking, most people agree that blindly accepting and following something without analyzing it is bad, but many developers operate like this. The only way out of this cult is to start questioning the merits of the best practices in question and determine yourself if its beneficial for your, your team, your company and your software.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ashlan.com/blog/i-ve-come-to-hate-the-term-best-practice/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emacs Lisp Functions for Easy BibTeX Recording</title>
      <link>https://www.erichgrunewald.com/posts/emacs-lisp-functions-for-easy-bib-te-x-insertions/</link>
      <description>Texts on philosophy, poetry, literature, history, altruism, science, programming and music.</description>
      <author> (https://www.erichgrunewald.com)</author>
      <guid>https://www.erichgrunewald.com/posts/emacs-lisp-functions-for-easy-bib-te-x-insertions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming Fonts - Test Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.programmingfonts.org/</link>
      <description>Try out the best and newest monospace fonts for code</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.programmingfonts.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 20:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proebsting&amp;#39;s Law</title>
      <link>https://proebsting.cs.arizona.edu/law.html</link>
      <description>This means that while hardware computing horsepower increases at roughly
60%/year, compiler optimizations contribute only 4%.
Basically, compiler optimization work makes only marginal contributions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://proebsting.cs.arizona.edu/law.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 20:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoRegex</title>
      <link>https://autoregex.xyz/</link>
      <description>Converting plain english to RegEx with Natural Language Processing</description>
      <author> (Aarya Gadekar)</author>
      <guid>https://autoregex.xyz/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 05:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>