<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How to See Bright, Vivid Images in Your Mind&amp;#39;s Eye</title>
      <link>https://photographyinsider.info/image-streaming-for-photographers/</link>
      <description>Learn to improve the brightness and clarity of images in your mind&amp;#39;s eye. Image Streaming is an easy technique to learn. Is it a cure for aphantasia?</description>
      <author> (James Somerset)</author>
      <guid>https://photographyinsider.info/image-streaming-for-photographers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 10:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QCon San Francisco 2023</title>
      <link>https://qconsf.com/presentation/oct2023/what-if-infrastructure-code-never-existed</link>
      <description>We rewind the clock and ask ourselves: what if Infrastructure as Code never existed? What different solutions might we have come up with to the problems we faced? We’ll leave you full of possibilities about the future.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://qconsf.com/presentation/oct2023/what-if-infrastructure-code-never-existed</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 06:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wifi without internet on a Marabu flight – marx.wtf</title>
      <link>https://marx.wtf/2023/09/30/wifi-without-internet-on-a-marabu-flight/</link>
      <description>Just as james vaughan, I spent a recent flight finding out what I could do with a connection to the flight’s wifi, but without access to the internet. After reading james‘ blogpost, I decided to share my story ‒ I found more data &amp;#128578;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marx.wtf/2023/09/30/wifi-without-internet-on-a-marabu-flight/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Importance of Goal Clarity for Delegation - Byte Tank</title>
      <link>https://lopespm.com/notes/2023/09/30/goal_clarity_in_delegation.html</link>
      <description>Clarity as one of the keys to unlock the delegation formula</description>
      <author> (Pedro Lopes)</author>
      <guid>https://lopespm.com/notes/2023/09/30/goal_clarity_in_delegation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software and Projects</title>
      <link>https://davidvujic.blogspot.com/2023/09/software-and-projects.html</link>
      <description>How can we simplify things, to add value as early as possible?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidvujic.blogspot.com/2023/09/software-and-projects.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinical update about where the cancer is, and what’s happening with treatment:</title>
      <link>https://jakeseliger.com/2023/09/29/clinical-update-about-where-the-cancer-is-and-whats-happening-with-treatment/</link>
      <description>A lot of doctors have been reading the squamous cell carcinoma saga, and they keep asking for clinical detail about what’s going on. Although they don’t literally say: “The emotio…</description>
      <author> (By  Jake Seliger)</author>
      <guid>https://jakeseliger.com/2023/09/29/clinical-update-about-where-the-cancer-is-and-whats-happening-with-treatment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chasing the Myth of Zero-Overhead Memory Safety (plus pictures of mythical birds!)</title>
      <link>https://verdagon.dev/blog/myth-zero-overhead-memory-safety</link>
      <description>In my recent article, I showed how Vale&amp;#39;s linear types can provide memory safety without a borrow checker, generations, reference counting, or tracing GC.</description>
      <author> (Evan Ovadia)</author>
      <guid>https://verdagon.dev/blog/myth-zero-overhead-memory-safety</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Soft Deletes: How and Why with Custom Prisma Client queries</title>
      <link>https://www.jeffedmondson.dev/database-soft-deletes-with-prisma/</link>
      <description>Soft deletes and hard deletes are two different approaches to deleting data from a database. In this article, we will explore soft delete write and write some custom Prisma client queries to implement soft deletes.</description>
      <author> (Jeff Edmondson)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jeffedmondson.dev/database-soft-deletes-with-prisma/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of B2B Differentiation | Lucas Vittor</title>
      <link>https://www.lucasvittor.com/the-art-of-b2b-differentiation/</link>
      <description>The place where I share my learnings.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lucasvittor.com/the-art-of-b2b-differentiation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change - Tim H&amp;#229;rek</title>
      <link>https://timharek.no/blog/change</link>
      <description>Technologist from Norway that cares about creating solutions that respects people in terms of privacy, security and user experience.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://timharek.no/blog/change</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Integration Testing with FastAPI</title>
      <link>https://alex-jacobs.com/posts/fastapitests/</link>
      <description>Integration Testing FastAPI: Harnessing the Power of Mocking Backend Services with MongoMock, MockS3, and More</description>
      <author> (Alex Jacobs)</author>
      <guid>https://alex-jacobs.com/posts/fastapitests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layoffs from the founder’s perspective</title>
      <link>https://dylancollins.com/2023/09/30/layoffs-from-the-founders-perspective/</link>
      <description>This isn’t a post about the layoffs in Epic Games this week, there’s been plenty written about that and I’m incredibly sympathetic to those affected (there are some amazing people so if you’re hiri…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dylancollins.com/2023/09/30/layoffs-from-the-founders-perspective/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beginning CMake : Quick Getting Started with CMake</title>
      <link>https://norabellm.github.io/posts/beginning-cmake/</link>
      <description>CMake is build system intented for organize C/C++ project. Not only saving me from write long compiler command to build program, it also become project definition. Cmake handle dependencies, build, compiler selection, testing and many others. If you familiar with GNU Make, this may the niche version of it that specialize to C/C++ code.
CMake works by compiling CMakeList.txt (Your project definition) into native build system such Makefile, ninja, meson or other.</description>
      <author> (Minako Norabell)</author>
      <guid>https://norabellm.github.io/posts/beginning-cmake/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content filtering with CSS :has() selector</title>
      <link>https://ronaldsvilcins.com/2023/09/30/content-filtering-with-css-has-selector/</link>
      <description>Filter content with checkboxes and CSS, no JavaScript.</description>
      <author> (Ronalds Vilcins - https://ronaldsvilcins.com/)</author>
      <guid>https://ronaldsvilcins.com/2023/09/30/content-filtering-with-css-has-selector/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Should Switch Off IPv4 Internet</title>
      <link>https://rohanrd.xyz/posts/india-should-switch-off-ipv4-internet/</link>
      <description>IPv6 migration has been dragging on for a decades now and there’s no end in sight for this migration to complete. Huge software companies like Amazon are buying even more IPv4 addresses to continue to support IPv4 users. Given the current stance of corporations and many governments it seems that Internet will forever be split into two protocols.
Worldwide 45% of Internet users are on IPv6. This number is quite low if you take into consideration the fact that IPv6 was created almost 3 decades ago.</description>
      <author> (Rohan D)</author>
      <guid>https://rohanrd.xyz/posts/india-should-switch-off-ipv4-internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An easy-to-implement, arena-friendly hash map</title>
      <link>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/09/30/</link>
      <description>nullprogram.com/blog/2023/09/30/</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/09/30/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 01:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YAML config file?  Pain?  Try Lua - The Boston Diaries</title>
      <link>https://boston.conman.org/2023/09/29.1</link>
      <description>YAML config file?  Pain?  Try Lua</description>
      <author> (Conner, Sean P.)</author>
      <guid>https://boston.conman.org/2023/09/29.1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranking C# Versions</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ccs3ARj8PHE</link>
      <description>Ranking C# Versions based on their impact and importance</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ccs3ARj8PHE</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enforcing Architecture in .NET with tests</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=66GQSphX9kA</link>
      <description>In this video, we delve into architecture testing and compare two testing libraries, NetArchTest and ArchUnitNet.NetArchTest - https://github.com/BenMorris/N...</description>
      <author> (Codewrinkles
  
  
  
    Codewrinkles
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=66GQSphX9kA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 20:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TypeScript Origins: The Documentary</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=U6s2pdxebSo%3Fsi%3DCFLl3a645d_pNLIK</link>
      <description>TypeScript Origins: The Documentary is bought to you by OfferZen - the community-first developer jobs platform. The documentary features core contributors an...</description>
      <author> (Honeypot
  
  
  
    Honeypot
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=U6s2pdxebSo%3Fsi%3DCFLl3a645d_pNLIK</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 20:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor in Action with Chris Sainty | The Azure DevOps Podcast, ep.238</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=h3r6W02V5Hk%3Fsi%3D9bpRMsGsWq2tn9JS</link>
      <description>Chris is a Microsoft MVP, author, and software engineer with over 17 years of experience with ASP.NET. Passionate about sharing his knowledge with the commun...</description>
      <author> (NDC Conferences
  
  
  
    NDC Conferences
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=h3r6W02V5Hk%3Fsi%3D9bpRMsGsWq2tn9JS</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 20:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Jagged Technological Frontier | Digital Data Design Institute at Harvard</title>
      <link>https://d3.harvard.edu/navigating-the-jagged-technological-frontier/</link>
      <description>In collaboration with Boston Consulting Group (BCG), new research from Digital Data Design Institute at Harvard chair and co-founder Karim Lakhani and In collaboration with Boston Consulting Group (BCG), new research from Digital Data Design Institute at Harvard chair and co-founder Karim Lakhani and others involved evaluating the performance of 758 consultants, which make up 7% of the individual contributor workforce of the company. The tasks spanned a consultant&amp;#39;s daily work, including creativity, analytical thinking, writing proficiency, and persuasiveness.</description>
      <author> (D^3 Faculty)</author>
      <guid>https://d3.harvard.edu/navigating-the-jagged-technological-frontier/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 20:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using FontAwesome Pro Icons in Flutter | Doumer&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://doumer.me/using-fontawesome-pro-icons-in-flutter/</link>
      <description>No package required, and a couple lines of code only, This article will show you how add FontAwesome Pro Icons in Flutter apps easily.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/DamienDoumer)</author>
      <guid>https://doumer.me/using-fontawesome-pro-icons-in-flutter/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 19:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drinking diet sodas and aspartame-sweetened beverages daily during pregnancy linked to autism in male offspring - UT Health San Antonio</title>
      <link>https://news.uthscsa.edu/drinking-diet-sodas-and-aspartame-sweetened-beverages-daily-during-pregnancy-linked-to-autism-in-male-offspring/</link>
      <description>Contact: Steven Lee, (210) 450-3823, lees22@uthscsa.edu SAN ANTONIO, Sept. 20, 2023 – A new published study led by researchers at The University of Texas Health Science Center at San Antonio (UT Health San Antonio) has found an association between autism diagnosis in boys and daily consumption of either diet soda or a comparable amount of […]</description>
      <author> (Steven Lee)</author>
      <guid>https://news.uthscsa.edu/drinking-diet-sodas-and-aspartame-sweetened-beverages-daily-during-pregnancy-linked-to-autism-in-male-offspring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 18:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring your apps with Sentry in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://askxammy.com/monitoring-your-apps-with-sentry-in-net-maui/</link>
      <description>Launching our apps is just the first step; maintaining user satisfaction is the ongoing challenge. After releasing our apps in the store, our primary goal is ensuring this satisfaction by delivering a seamless and relevant experience. Yet, we often lack insights into issues some users may encounter. This underscores the necessity for tools that serve as our eyes, tracking pivotal user interactions and events. Why is monitoring vital? It helps in timely identification and even prediction of potential glitches, enabling us to address them before users report. While various tools offer these capabilities, this article will delve into Sentry, a renowned remote crash reporting tool, discussing its features and step-by-step implementation
The explanation will be divided into the following points:
&amp;#128313; What exactly Sentry is?
&amp;#128313; Getting started with Sentry implementation
&amp;#128313; Initiating the App Monitoring
&amp;#128313; Getting Familiar with the Sentry Dashboard

Let &amp;#39;s start!
What exactly Sentry is?
It&amp;#39;s an open-source tool designed to track errors within your applications. Sentry monitors any issues arising in your app, offering detailed insights that help prioritize, identify, and reproduce each problem, ensuring a swift and effective resolution. With this tool you can take action on broken lines of code, crashes, and failed API calls.
Getting started with Sentry implementation
To apply Sentry monitoring to your applications, you must do the following steps:
Step 1⃣: Create your Sentry account
Go to the Sentry site and click on the Get Started button, located at the top right of the page.





You can choose how to register:

Directly with Sentry: You&amp;#39;ll find a form asking for basic personal information to complete your registration. (✍️ I will use this option for this article.)







Via third-party accounts: At the bottom of the form you also have the option to register using your Google, Github, or Azure Devops accounts.

Step 2⃣: Setting up Sentry
After your account is created, a screen will pop up offering you the choice to install Sentry or set up your team. For now, we&amp;#39;ll concentrate on installing Sentry, please press its Start button.





Choosing the Platform to Monitor
In the next step, you must choose the platform you want to monitor. Sentry provides support for a wide variety, categorized by their main functionalities, such as Desktop, Web, Mobile, among others. The detailed list can be seen in the attached animation. To reach this article, you will navigate to the Mobile tab and select .NET Multiplatform App UI (MAUI).








Once you have selected the platform you are going to work with, click the Configure SDK button located at the lower right corner of the page.
Configuring your MAUI SDK
Sentry details every necessary step for its integration into your application: from the necessary Nuget package to initialization and implementation. It even offers a sample application. This information is essential for your setup, so make sure to keep it handy; you will need it in the next steps.








⚠ Save the DSN endpoint that this step shows you; you&amp;#39;ll need it for the Visual Studio implementation.
Step 3⃣: Implementing Sentry in our MAUI App
Open your MAUI project in Visual Studio. For this demonstration, I created one named SentrySample.
&amp;#128295; Initial setup
➖ From the NuGet Package, add the Sentry.Maui package to your project.





➖ Go to your MauiProgram.cs file
In the CreateMauiApp method, find the .UseMauiApp&amp;lt;App&amp;gt;() line. Right below it, add UserSentry(). This function has various useful overloads to explore. However, in this article, we will focus on the one that uses a DSN as a parameter.
What is the DSN?
The DSN (Data Source Name) in Sentry acts as a distinctive identifier for the data source of a specific project. It facilitates the direct linking of events from your application to the corresponding Sentry project. This address instructs Sentry on how to organize and store incoming data. Essentially, it guarantees that error and performance metrics from your application are correctly channeled to the right project within your Sentry account.
Let’s implement it in code
Do you remember the endpoint DSN saved in the previous step? Add it in this method.

Initiating the App Monitoring
With your initial configuration in place, you&amp;#39;re all set to begin monitoring the various events and scenarios in your app.
Where should you start with your monitoring? Here&amp;#39;s my recommendation:
&amp;#128313; Begin with a pre-established document outlining the specific events or scenarios you want to track.
&amp;#128313; Assign unique identifiers for each scenario within this document. It&amp;#39;s essential to use clear and intuitive naming so it&amp;#39;s easily understandable to anyone reviewing it. For instance, if you aim to track when a user logs in via Facebook, a potential identifier might be facebook_login, accompanied by pertinent data like the user&amp;#39;s name and email.
Exploring App Monitoring &amp;#160;available methods
Now that our monitoring scenarios are set up, let&amp;#39;s dive into the various methods provided by the SentrySdk. In this guide, I&amp;#39;ll introduce you to some of the main Sentry methods:
➖ CaptureMessage
While Sentry SDKs don&amp;#39;t auto-capture messages, this method enables manual submission of textual information to Sentry, enhancing monitoring precision.
It receives the following parameters:
&amp;#128313; Message: Is the message to send. - Receives a string as a value - [Mandatory]
&amp;#128313; SentryLevel: Allows you to define the level of severity or importance of the event that is sent to Sentry. It’s important to specify the appropriate level, as it allows us to ensure that messages are prioritized and categorized correctly within the Sentry system. &amp;#160;[Optional]
It’s an Enum that contains the following values:
▪ Debug: Offers insights for debugging purposes, detailing the inner workings or state of the system.
▪ Info: Provides general informational messages that signify normal, non-error events.
▪ Warning: Flags potential problems or unusual occurrences that don&amp;#39;t currently impact functionality but may do so in the future.
▪ Error: Highlights a significant issue, which though not fatal, may impede functionality.
▪ Fatal: Indicates a critical error that might cause the system to terminate.
How can we implement this in code?

➖ CaptureException
Enables you to capture exceptions that arise within your app.
&amp;#128313; Exception: Capturers a exception. - [Mandatory]
&amp;#128313; Configure scope: &amp;#160;It allows you to define a specific context for exceptions that you forward to Sentry. In your report, you can include details such as the severity of the error and assign specific tags, among others. I will provide an example that showcases some essential configurations, and we invite you to further explore its capabilities.

➖ CaptureEvent
Allows you to capture the monitoring of an event. This method accepts data of the SentryEvent type. You can include various essential details for your monitoring, such as the error level, a message, and more. I encourage you to delve deeper into its features.
How can we implement it in code?

We have explored some of the main methods. I invite you to continue delving deeper into others.
⚠ Some of these methods necessitate capturing detailed user information, like their email or name. In such cases, it&amp;#39;s crucial to inform the user about the collection of their data.









Getting Familiar with the Sentry Dashboard
At last, you&amp;#39;ll discover where to view all the data you’ve been monitoring! Let&amp;#39;s start with a straightforward example: capturing a message that we&amp;#39;ll then observe on the Sentry Dashboard.
Creating the example
I&amp;#39;ll demonstrate using the default .NET MAUI application as an example. Head to MainPage.xaml.cs—I&amp;#39;ll be working with the built-in counter code. Further, we&amp;#39;ll incorporate Sentry&amp;#39;s CaptureMessage function, as outlined below:

To get information for Sentry, it’s important that you run the application and click the counter button.

Entering to the dashboard
In your Sentry Dashboard, navigate to Issues. A list of your monitoring records will promptly display. While other examples might appear in this segment, let&amp;#39;s concentrate on the entry we generated earlier—highlighted with pink lines—that reads, You clicked the counter button 1 time.&amp;#160;









Click on the highlighted item. On this page, you can view the record&amp;#39;s comprehensive details, including the name of the originating application, the .NET version in use at the time of the record&amp;#39;s creation, the operating system version, and of course, the message you sent, among others information. There is a wealth of crucial information here that warrants your attention and that will allow you to make decisions in your app. Scroll through to take it all in!
Here&amp;#39;s a glimpse of what it looks like:








&amp;#160;

&amp;#128640; Voil&amp;#224;! You&amp;#39;re now all set to monitor your .NET MAUI applications with Sentry. Keep building awesome apps and enjoy the peace of mind Sentry provides!&amp;#160; &amp;#128214;&amp;#128588;
Spanish post:

https://es.askxammy.com/monitoreando-tus-aplicaciones-con-sentry-en-net-maui

References:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9-50zH8fqYA

Thanks for reading my article! &amp;#128154;&amp;#128149;</description>
      <author> (About Leomaris Reyes)</author>
      <guid>https://askxammy.com/monitoring-your-apps-with-sentry-in-net-maui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 13:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers Should Deploy Their Own Code</title>
      <link>https://matt-rickard.com/developers-should-deploy-their-own-code</link>
      <description>This is the platonic ideal. We&amp;#39;re not there yet, but the all signs point to this rather than specialization.

Applications and their infrastructure (functions, queues, permissions, runtime) have always been closely intertwined. Fewer handoffs mean quicker deployments and less context loss.

So – Why can&amp;#39;t developers deploy their own code (yet)?

 1. Provisioned infrastructure economy1

Competing product teams must be allocated resources at companies with provisioned infrastructure. Finance depar</description>
      <author> (Matt Rickard)</author>
      <guid>https://matt-rickard.com/developers-should-deploy-their-own-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 13:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>