<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Coding Is Fun—But Vibe Refactoring Pays the Bills</title>
      <link>https://dawidmakowski.com/en/2025/04/vibe-coding-is-fun-but-vibe-refactoring-pays-the-bills/</link>
      <description>So let’s flip the script to something that actually compounds: vibe refactoring. Same spontaneous energy, but aimed at shrinking technical debt and sharpening your architecture instead of amping up the commit count.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/dawid.makowski)</author>
      <guid>https://dawidmakowski.com/en/2025/04/vibe-coding-is-fun-but-vibe-refactoring-pays-the-bills/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSS doesn't necessarily means firehose • AndreGarzia.com</title>
      <link>https://andregarzia.com/2025/04/rss-doesnt-necessarily-means-firehose.html</link>
      <description>AndreGarzia.com website</description>
      <guid>https://andregarzia.com/2025/04/rss-doesnt-necessarily-means-firehose.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Manager Survival Guide</title>
      <link>https://yusufaytas.com/new-manager-survival-guide/</link>
      <description>Everything they don’t teach you about becoming a manager. Raw lessons, real advice, and survival tactics for first-time leaders.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/yusufaytas)</author>
      <guid>https://yusufaytas.com/new-manager-survival-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Seven-Year Rule - MacSparky</title>
      <link>https://www.macsparky.com/blog/2025/04/the-seven-year-rule/</link>
      <description>Years ago, I encountered a fascinating concept in a book by the Dalai Lama: every seven years, human beings transform into entirely new versions of themselves. This idea stems from the biological principle that our bodies replace virtually all their cells over a seven-year cycle. The person you are today doesn’t share a single cell... Continue reading →</description>
      <guid>https://www.macsparky.com/blog/2025/04/the-seven-year-rule/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TPSV</title>
      <link>https://chtenb.dev/?page=tpsv</link>
      <description>Despite CSV (Comma-Separated-Values) being ubiquitous, its cousin TSV (Tab-Separated-Values) has
direct advantages over CSV in many situations. Tab characters don’t
normally occur in the data being encoded, which avoids the need for
quoting. Moreover, if your columns all have a similar width, you can
configure the tab-width in any text editor such that all columns align
nicely. Unfortunately, in many cases columns do not have a similar
width.</description>
      <guid>https://chtenb.dev/?page=tpsv</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jon Atkinson | Trust but Verify: Sensible Ways to Use LLMs in Production</title>
      <link>https://www.jonatkinson.co.uk/blog/trust-but-verify</link>
      <description>Trust but Verify: Sensible Ways to Use LLMs in Production - Jon Atkinson's personal homepage.</description>
      <guid>https://www.jonatkinson.co.uk/blog/trust-but-verify</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9/11's Impacts on Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://chrisgillett.org/9-11</link>
      <description>The functioning of society depends on collective confidence in the government’s guarantee of our security. On September 11, as that confidence shattered in a...</description>
      <author> (https://chrisgillett.org/)</author>
      <guid>https://chrisgillett.org/9-11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's a C+ at best</title>
      <link>https://okmanideep.me/its-a-c-at-best/</link>
      <description>A mindset to have balanced expectations about adopting AI at work</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/okmanideep)</author>
      <guid>https://okmanideep.me/its-a-c-at-best/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - joexbayer/RetrOS-32: A x86 32bit Hobby Operatingsystem with graphics, multitasking, networking and 32bit C-Compiler for i386 architecture.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/joexbayer/RetrOS-32</link>
      <description>A x86 32bit Hobby Operatingsystem with graphics, multitasking, networking and 32bit C-Compiler for i386 architecture. - joexbayer/RetrOS-32</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/joexbayer/RetrOS-32</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 21:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Friendship Recession: The Lost Art of Connecting — The Leadership &amp; Happiness Laboratory</title>
      <link>https://www.happiness.hks.harvard.edu/february-2025-issue/the-friendship-recession-the-lost-art-of-connecting</link>
      <description>February 2025 Issue       Carolyn Bruckmann, Harvard Kennedy School MPP ‘25     The so-called “Friendship Recession” is making its way into the vernacular—a profound shift in how Americans experience and sustain friendships. The data paints a stark picture. According to the  American Perspectives Su</description>
      <guid>https://www.happiness.hks.harvard.edu/february-2025-issue/the-friendship-recession-the-lost-art-of-connecting</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 19:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watching o3 guess a photo’s location is surreal, dystopian and wildly entertaining</title>
      <link>https://simonwillison.net/2025/Apr/26/o3-photo-locations/</link>
      <description>Watching OpenAI’s new o3 model guess where a photo was taken is one of those moments where decades of science fiction suddenly come to life. It’s a cross between the …</description>
      <guid>https://simonwillison.net/2025/Apr/26/o3-photo-locations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 17:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An end to all this prostate trouble?</title>
      <link>https://yarchive.net/blog/prostate/</link>
      <description>The prostate gland causes entirely too many problems.  In the US,
prostate cancer kills about one man of every forty.  “Benign
prostate hyperplasia” (BPH) is even more common, affecting most
men over age 60.  It pinches the urinary tract, making it hard to
urinate, and is constantly in danger of transforming from
“benign” to “malignant”.  Even the difficulty urinating is enough
of a problem that men often get surgery for it, usually TURP, a
sort of roto-rooter job (except cutting through the pipe instead
of just cleaning it out).</description>
      <guid>https://yarchive.net/blog/prostate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 16:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That joke isn't funny any more</title>
      <link>https://samj.substack.com/p/that-joke-isnt-funny-any-more</link>
      <description>In 2003, I wrote a book called Crap Towns. It seemed funny at the time. But plenty of people say it would not be possible to publish it today. Is that a problem?</description>
      <guid>https://samj.substack.com/p/that-joke-isnt-funny-any-more</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 12:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Quick Guide to Learn JWT - Coding Sonata</title>
      <link>https://codingsonata.com/your-quick-guide-to-learn-jwt/</link>
      <description>Learn about JWT, its security model, structure, decoding tools, and how you can generate a JWT using symmetric algorithm in .NET 9.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/aram1987)</author>
      <guid>https://codingsonata.com/your-quick-guide-to-learn-jwt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 11:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategic Networking For Software Engineers - Engineering Manager AMA</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=h9N46FX0snM</link>
      <description>Everyone is focused on getting their LeetCode skills ramped up and building side projects -- two things I think definitely help when it comes to interviewing in general.

But... you're not even getting interviews. What's going on? How are those OTHER people doing it?! Let's discuss some options.

As with all livestreams, I'm looking forward to answering YOUR questions! So join me live and ask in the chat, or you can comment now and I can try to get it answered while I stream.

----
🔑 Membership &amp; Subscriptions:
- 📨 Weekly Newsletter: https://weekly.devleader.ca
- 🏘️ Private Discord Community: https://sidestack.io/devleader

🧠 Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Get Promoted As A Software Engineer: https://dometrain.com/course/career-getting-promoted-as-a-software-engineer/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?ref=nick-cosentino
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

🗣️ Social Media &amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs: @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp; Products/Services That I Love:
-  @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper @opusclip : https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----
#ama #askmeanything #softwareengineering #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=h9N46FX0snM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 09:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Recap - 2025-04-25</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/04/26/weekly-recap-20250425</link>
      <description>Check out this week from Dev Leader! Here's a list including articles and videos on software engineering, career development, and programming in C#!
</description>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/04/26/weekly-recap-20250425</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refactoring Overgrown Bounded Contexts in Modular Monoliths</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/refactoring-overgrown-bounded-contexts-in-modular-monoliths</link>
      <description>Learn how to untangle bloated services and split them into clean, modular bounded contexts in a .NET modular monolith - one practical refactor at a time.</description>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/refactoring-overgrown-bounded-contexts-in-modular-monoliths</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70% Size, 100% Accuracy: Lossless LLM Compression for Efficient GPU Inference via Dynamic-Length Float</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.11651</link>
      <description>Large Language Models (LLMs) have grown rapidly in size, creating significant challenges for efficient deployment on resource-constrained hardware. In this paper, we introduce Dynamic-Length Float (DFloat11), a lossless compression framework that reduces LLM size by 30% while preserving outputs that are bit-for-bit identical to the original model. DFloat11 is motivated by the low entropy in the BFloat16 weight representation of LLMs, which reveals significant inefficiency in existing storage format. By applying entropy coding, DFloat11 assigns dynamic-length encodings to weights based on frequency, achieving near information-optimal compression without any loss of precision. To facilitate efficient inference with dynamic-length encodings, we develop a custom GPU kernel for fast online decompression. Our design incorporates the following: (i) decomposition of memory-intensive lookup tables (LUTs) into compact LUTs that fit in GPU SRAM, (ii) a two-phase kernel for coordinating thread read/write positions using lightweight auxiliary variables, and (iii) transformer-block-level decompression to minimize latency. Experiments on recent models, including Llama-3.1, Qwen-2.5, and Gemma-3, validates our hypothesis that DFloat11 achieves around 30% model size reduction while preserving bit-for-bit exact outputs. Compared to a potential alternative of offloading parts of an uncompressed model to the CPU to meet memory constraints, DFloat11 achieves 1.9-38.8x higher throughput in token generation. With a fixed GPU memory budget, DFloat11 enables 5.3-13.17x longer context lengths than uncompressed models. Notably, our method enables lossless inference of Llama-3.1-405B, an 810GB model, on a single node equipped with 8x80GB GPUs. Our code and models are available at https://github.com/LeanModels/DFloat11.</description>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.11651</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Building MCP Servers with ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=x_6iUhdHnhc</link>
      <description>Check out how you can build Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers with ASP.NET Core and the new MCP C# SDK to extend AI systems with all sorts of useful information and tools.

Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/aspnet-standup-20250429

Featuring: Daniel Roth, Mike Kistler, Sam Spencer

#dotnet #aspnetcore</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=x_6iUhdHnhc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 00:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Emulation via Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://madebyoll.in/posts/world_emulation_via_dnn/</link>
      <description>I turned a forest trail near my apartment into a playable neural world.
You can explore that world in your web browser by clicking right here:</description>
      <guid>https://madebyoll.in/posts/world_emulation_via_dnn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O(no) You Didn’t 😱</title>
      <link>https://mrshiny608.github.io/MrShiny608/optimisation/2025/04/22/OhNoYouDidnt.html</link>
      <description>A deep dive into why real-world performance often defies Big-O expectations and why context and profiling matter more than theoretical complexity</description>
      <guid>https://mrshiny608.github.io/MrShiny608/optimisation/2025/04/22/OhNoYouDidnt.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>staring into the abyss</title>
      <link>https://medhir.com/blog/staring-into-the-abyss</link>
      <description>reflections on working in tech in America in 2025 and a rant about the general state of affairs of our industry.</description>
      <guid>https://medhir.com/blog/staring-into-the-abyss</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A journey into character decoding</title>
      <link>https://www.benjacksondev.co.uk/2025/04/25/how-character-decoding-works-kinda.html</link>
      <description>Disclaimer: This post isn’t a complete or technically rigorous explanation of UTF-8 decoding. It’s more of a “here’s how I started to wrap my head around it” kind of thing. The Lua code is intentionally simplified — it skips over edge cases like invalid byte sequences, overlong encodings, and error handling. If you’re looking for a formal spec, check out RFC 3629 or the Unicode Standard.</description>
      <guid>https://www.benjacksondev.co.uk/2025/04/25/how-character-decoding-works-kinda.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land with no aunties</title>
      <link>https://kanyilmaz.me/2025/03/28/aunties.html</link>
      <description>Land with no aunties

</description>
      <guid>https://kanyilmaz.me/2025/03/28/aunties.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We don't notice slow improvement</title>
      <link>https://notes.npilk.com/slow-improvement</link>
      <description>Technologies take off before they're perfected, and we anchor to those early versions. But over time, they are quietly optimized until one day, they just work - and we hardly notice.</description>
      <guid>https://notes.npilk.com/slow-improvement</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apps Tell Us Who Matters Now?</title>
      <link>https://kwakubiney.github.io/posts/Apps-Tell-Us-Who-Matters-Now/</link>
      <description>A recent event got me thinking. Why do we give social media that much power over our lives? I’m fairly young, but I’ve had an experience of life without social media as it exists today. There was a time when we gauged how close certain friends were using more realistic metrics. Or at least I thought we were. A friend recently got into an argument with their real life bestfriend, mainly because one was not the other’s number one best friend on Snapchat, leaving my friend very confused. If you don’t use Snapchat a lot, you probably won’t know what I’m talking about, so here’s some brief context. Snapchat assigns “best friend” tags to people you interact with, based on some algorithm that isn’t public. Now, was the person who got jealous wrong? Maybe not. But it’s alarming to witness the level of trust and reliance a person can place on such tagging to make real life decisions and judgments. I, for one, am not sure how exactly the tagging works because I do not work at Snapchat, but the more you interact with someone, the higher they appear on their best friend list. Yes, there’s a ranking as well, absurd. My whole issue is with Snapchat. Judging who someone’s best friend is, based solely on conversation frequency, is weird. Conversations have so much more depth to them, and context matters in every conversation*. The whole gist of such tagging is uncalled for and should be an opt-in feature. Well, enough of me ranting. I can only control what I can control, so I’ve deleted Snapchat. My friend is, on the other hand, still treading the considerate route, soothing the ego of someone who seems a bit out of touch with reality.</description>
      <guid>https://kwakubiney.github.io/posts/Apps-Tell-Us-Who-Matters-Now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dario Amodei — The Urgency of Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://www.darioamodei.com/post/the-urgency-of-interpretability</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://www.darioamodei.com/post/the-urgency-of-interpretability</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shut Up and Dance</title>
      <link>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/shut-up-and-dance/</link>
      <description>A human interest piece about a person who never existed, who has spent his entire adult life doing something I don't know anything about.</description>
      <guid>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/shut-up-and-dance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from video games</title>
      <link>https://the-nerve-blog.ghost.io/learning-from-video-games/</link>
      <description>In 2005, Steve Jobs told the graduating class of Stanford a now-famous story about connecting the dots - a story about the calligraphy courses he took in his college years, which later influenced the industry-leading digital fonts that shipped with the Macintosh. He said:

Again, you can’t connect the</description>
      <guid>https://the-nerve-blog.ghost.io/learning-from-video-games/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Our Parents Lacked | thoughts</title>
      <link>https://www.trynathinkoutloud.com/blogs/what-our-parents-lacked/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://www.trynathinkoutloud.com/blogs/what-our-parents-lacked/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think less, ship more</title>
      <link>https://cassidoo.co/post/think-less/</link>
      <description>I do too much thinking about what I want to make, and not enough actually making the thing.</description>
      <guid>https://cassidoo.co/post/think-less/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The seven bridges of Konigsberg puzzle</title>
      <link>https://jdhwilkins.com/the-bridges-of-konigsberg/</link>
      <description>The sun dipped low over the bustling City of Königsberg, casting golden reflections over the Pregel River. Its waters divided the town into four distinct land masses, connected by seven foot-bridge…</description>
      <guid>https://jdhwilkins.com/the-bridges-of-konigsberg/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>