<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - trailbaseio/trailbase: A blazingly fast, single-file, open-source application server with type-safe APIs, Auth, and Admin UI built on Rust+SQLite.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/trailbaseio/trailbase</link>
      <description>A blazingly fast, single-file, open-source application server with type-safe APIs, Auth, and Admin UI built on Rust+SQLite.  - GitHub - trailbaseio/trailbase: A blazingly fast, single-file, open-so...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/trailbaseio/trailbase</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 18:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Death of Intel: When Boards Fail</title>
      <link>https://www.fabricatedknowledge.com/p/the-death-of-intel-when-boards-fail</link>
      <description>Pat lost his seat because of an incompetent board. Let&amp;#39;s meet them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.fabricatedknowledge.com/p/the-death-of-intel-when-boards-fail</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job Cancellations Using CancellationTokenSource</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=mulpHgpa1bg</link>
      <description>Learn how to cancel long-running jobs in .NET the right way. Using Redis and CancellationToken, I’ll show you how to build a system for on-demand cancellations. Simple, clear, and effective!

Join my mailing list: https://mdbouk.com/
Follow me on X: https://x.com/mhdbouk
Buy me a coffee: https://buymeacoffee.com/mdbouk

Don’t forget to like, subscribe, and share this video with your fellow developers.

Happy Coding!</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Dbouk)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=mulpHgpa1bg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# Web Development on SharpSite with a focus on Auth part 3</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=swdvckvntU4</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Fritz is working on adding authentication to SharpSite https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/SharpSite</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=swdvckvntU4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Master Refresh Tokens in ASP.NET Core (building from scratch)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=kR_9gRBeRMQ</link>
      <description>Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Join a community of 1000+ .NET developers: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic

Master the implementation of refresh tokens in ASP.NET Core! In this video, we&amp;#39;ll build a secure authentication system from the ground up. You&amp;#39;ll learn how Refresh Tokens actually work, follow along with a step-by-step implementation, and discover best practices for token storage and security. We&amp;#39;ll also cover token revocation so you avoid common pitfalls that many developers face. No fluff, just practical code, and real-world implementation.

Problem Details for ASP.NET Core APIs
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/problem-details-for-aspnetcore-apis

Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters
0:00 Access Token problems
1:46 Creating a Refresh Token entity
4:29 Returning Refresh Token with JWT
7:38 The reason behind Refresh Tokens
8:34 Logging in with a Refresh Token
13:54 Revoking Refresh Tokens</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=kR_9gRBeRMQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 14:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT vs. Advent of Code 2024 Day 6: Guard Gallivant</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5s3xaf4D3ik</link>
      <description>Will ChatGPT protect us from the lab guard, or will we end up walking endlessly till the end of times?

#openai #chatgpt #python #ai #codeinterpreter #adventofcode 

Contents:
0:00 - Intro
0:06 - Part 1
8:45 - Part 2
14:40 - Summary</description>
      <author> (Martin Zikmund)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5s3xaf4D3ik</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 14:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 70% problem: Hard truths about AI-assisted coding</title>
      <link>https://addyo.substack.com/p/the-70-problem-hard-truths-about</link>
      <description>A field guide and why we need to rethink our expectations</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://addyo.substack.com/p/the-70-problem-hard-truths-about</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J: UI 2 (Category Compilation) #09～#15</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=O8b0I6r8p5I</link>
      <description>In Category J: User Interface  (&amp;quot;UI&amp;quot; for short), I explain the menus, information, and other displays shown on-screen during a game.

[Index]
0:00 Opening
0:11 J-09 I Want to Choose Fast!
2:57 J-10 Let Them Skip, Let Them Pause
5:16 J-11 Button Settings
8:33 J-12 Advancing Text
11:27 J-13 Adding Help Text to Menus
13:56 J-14 Making Things Clear, Even Without Words
16:26 J-15 HUDs

[Playlist J: UI]
https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLgKCjZ2WsVLTVcEHQFioJF263Ip_yoxen</description>
      <author> (Masahiro Sakurai on Creating Games)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=O8b0I6r8p5I</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StarCellar E02: Adjusting basics with Apizr</title>
      <link>https://www.respawnsive.com/starcellar-e02-adjusting-basics-with-apizr/</link>
      <description>Episode 02 of an Apizr walkthrough building a MAUI app requesting a backend API. Apizr is a Refit based web api client manager, but resilient (retry, connectivity, cache, auth, log, priority, etc...). This episode is about adjusting some basic options. APIZR If you&amp;#39;re new to Apizr, you shoud k</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.respawnsive.com/starcellar-e02-adjusting-basics-with-apizr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmic Aspirations: A Workaround for the Cosmos DB Emulator Explorer in Aspire</title>
      <link>https://goforgoldman.com/posts/cosmos-aspire-workaround/</link>
      <description>If you’ve been struggling to get the Cosmos DB Emulator’s Explorer Dashboard working in Aspire, hopefully this will help. Recently, I encountered a frustrating issue where the dashboard refused to work, resulting in a deep dive into the emulator’s configuration, Aspire’s abstraction, and containerised environments. After hours of digging, I discovered that the root cause lies in the emulator image itself.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://goforgoldman.com/posts/cosmos-aspire-workaround/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 11:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland Airport Grows With Expansive Mass Timber Roof Canopy</title>
      <link>https://design-milk.com/portland-airport-grows-with-expansive-mass-timber-roof-canopy/</link>
      <description>Architecture firm ZGF has revamped Portland Airport (PDX) with locally + sustainably sourced mass timber for a brand-new, all wood roof.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://design-milk.com/portland-airport-grows-with-expansive-mass-timber-roof-canopy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 10:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The correct amount of ads is zero – Manu</title>
      <link>https://manuelmoreale.com/the-correct-amount-of-ads-is-zero</link>
      <description>The Verge has finally shipped the new paywalled version of their site and added a subscription. I personally have nothing against that move and I …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://manuelmoreale.com/the-correct-amount-of-ads-is-zero</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bjarne Stroustrup: Why you should avoid Linked Lists</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YQs6IC-vgmo</link>
      <description>The part in Bjarne Stroustrup&amp;#39;s keynote in GoingNative 2012 where he explains the reason that linked lists, and linked structures, are so bad for performance, even in the scenarios that programmers think that linked lists would be good.</description>
      <author> (Al&amp;#234; Loup)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YQs6IC-vgmo</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 10:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Bananymous/banan-os: Mirror of banan-os, my hobby operating system</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Bananymous/banan-os</link>
      <description>Mirror of banan-os, my hobby operating system. Contribute to Bananymous/banan-os development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Bananymous/banan-os</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Spirit of Open Source in a Modern .NET World with Scott Harden</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=8IN9VKDpago</link>
      <description>RJJ Software&amp;#39;s Software Development Service This episode of The Modern .NET Show is supported, in part, by RJJ Software&amp;#39;s Podcasting Services, whether your company is looking to elevate its UK operations or reshape its US strategy, we can provide tailored solutions that exceed expectations.

 Show Notes &amp;quot;One of the projects that I work on right now that&amp;#39;s probably one of my more successful ones, It&amp;#39;s a scientific data visualization library for .NET. It&amp;#39;s called ScottPlot. The name is silly. It&amp;#39;s because when I made it, I thought I was the only person going to be using it. And then some other people started using it and that wasn&amp;#39;t totally unexpected. But now it&amp;#39;s about a million and a half installs on NuGet. I think it has like 5,000 stars on GitHub. It&amp;#39;s really cool just to watch this thing grow.&amp;quot;— Scott Harden

 Welcome friends to The Modern .NET Show; the premier .NET podcast, focusing entirely on the knowledge, tools, and frameworks that all .NET developers should have in their toolbox. We are the go-to podcast for .NET developers worldwide, and I am not your host: Jamie. I&amp;#39;m Delilah and I will be recording the intro for this episode because Jamie is suffering with a throat infection.

 In this episode, Scott Harden joined us for the first of three episodes on .NET, open source, and NuGet. This part of the conversation is all about what Scott calls &amp;quot;The Spirit of Open Source in a Modern .NET World.&amp;quot; This is the background information on why Scott (and Jamie) believe that developers should look to creating open source works, putting them out there, and gathering feedback from people. Not only will it enhance your technical skill set (and very quickly), but it will also allow you to get experience at failing in a safe space: in public.

 &amp;quot;Now, humans evolved to like helping people in our in-group. And I think it means a lot that we treat anonymous strangers on the Internet, or we can treat them. Obviously, this can go wrong. But we can treat them as part of our in-group. Like, &amp;quot;hey, we are all in this technical world together. We are struggling. Let&amp;#39;s figure this out together.&amp;quot; And that bridge of trust and effort and you&amp;#39;re sharing your knowledge with another person, it is such a positive experience all around the table&amp;quot;— Scott Harden

 This episode has a lot of resources in the  accompanying show notes, so if you&amp;#39;re listening along in a podcast player make sure to head to the website (there&amp;#39;ll be a link). That way you don&amp;#39;t miss out on all the wonderful things Scott and Jamie talked about.

 And remember, this is just part one. In the next two parts, Scott and I talk about creating NuGet packages, ensuring their safety and security, and how to be a good citizen of the open source community. Talk about a festive gift for you all.

 And definitely go ahead and check out Scott&amp;#39;s work and writings. He&amp;#39;s a really interesting person, an amazing open source contributor, and an all-round great person.

 Anyway, without further ado, let&amp;#39;s sit back, open up a terminal, type in `dotnet new podcast` and we&amp;#39;ll dive into the core of Modern .NET.

 Supporting the Show If you find this episode useful in any way, please consider supporting the show by either leaving a review (check our review page for ways to do that), sharing the episode with a friend or colleague, buying the host a coffee, or considering becoming a Patron of the show.

 Full Show Notes The full show notes, including links to some of the things we discussed and a full transcription of this episode, can be found at:  https://dotnetcore.show/season-7/the-spirit-of-open-source-in-a-modern-net-world-with-scott-harden/

 Scott&amp;#39;s Links:  scottplot.net swharden.com GitHub LinkedIn  Useful Links  Job crafting Left-Pad incident  The story behind colors.js and faker.js  What we know about the xz Utils backdoor that almost infected the world Hello, Duende  Double-precision floating-point format Dave Farley Sigstore Add support for sigstore as signing method for NuGet packages The Primeagen Coding Blocks  Some episodes of this show focusing on App Security and dependency management   The Risks of Third Party Code With Niels Tanis  Application Security with Tanya Janca  Building Secure Software: Unveiling the Hidden Dependencies with Niels Tanis  Managing Dependencies with M. Scott Ford  Breaking Up with Tech Debt: A Love Story with M. Scott Ford  Books that Jamie gives to interns:   The Life-Changing Magic of Tidying Up by Marie Kondo  Start With Why by Simon Sinek  Essentialism: The Disciplined Pursuit of Less by Greg McKeown  ScottPlot.NET:  GitHub NuGet scottplot.net The charts that Scott was referring to when talking about downloads per day, can be seen here  Code Licenses mentioned (in order):  MIT  CC0 Apache 2  L-GPL v3  WTFPL  Programming languages Jamie mentioned (in order)  Go Odin Zig  Supporting the show:  Leave a rating or review Buy the show a coffee Become a patron  Getting in Touch:  Via the contact page Joining the...</description>
      <author> (Jamie Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=8IN9VKDpago</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>react/CHANGELOG.md at main &amp;#183; facebook/react</title>
      <link>https://github.com/facebook/react/blob/main/CHANGELOG.md</link>
      <description>The library for web and native user interfaces. Contribute to facebook/react development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/facebook/react/blob/main/CHANGELOG.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 06:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zen of Batch Pipelines - A recipe to reduce cognitive load &amp;#183; Focus on the objective</title>
      <link>https://ragulpr.github.io/2024/12/04/Zen-of-batch-pipelines/</link>
      <description>04 Dec 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ragulpr.github.io/2024/12/04/Zen-of-batch-pipelines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frameworkism: Senior Software Developers&amp;#39; Pit of Doom</title>
      <link>https://aaronstannard.com/frameworkism/</link>
      <description>Mistakes so insane and destructive that they require experience to make.</description>
      <author> (https://aaronstannard.com/about/)</author>
      <guid>https://aaronstannard.com/frameworkism/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s a New Custom Element Superclass on the Block</title>
      <link>https://thathtml.blog/2024/12/new-custom-element-superclass-on-the-block/</link>
      <description>Reactive Mastro: a tiny reactive GUI library for your existing MPA.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thathtml.blog/2024/12/new-custom-element-superclass-on-the-block/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Built the World&amp;#39;s Largest Database of LEGO Minifigure Ratings</title>
      <link>https://brickelo.com/blog/how-i-built-the-worlds-largest-database-of-lego-minifigure-ratings/</link>
      <description>It All Started with Mark Zuckerberg and FaceMash</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://brickelo.com/blog/how-i-built-the-worlds-largest-database-of-lego-minifigure-ratings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons Learned from Working at Startups</title>
      <link>https://chrlschn.dev/blog/2024/12/lessons-learned-from-working-at-startups/</link>
      <description>Self-note on some lessons learned from working at a variety of startups over my career</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chrlschn.dev/blog/2024/12/lessons-learned-from-working-at-startups/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Your Developer Audience Through Technical Blogging</title>
      <link>https://ronaldsvilcins.com/2024/12/04/growing-your-developer-audience-through-technical-blogging/</link>
      <description>Learn how to start a technical blog that impacts developers. Get practical tips on content planning, writing best practices, and building your developer community presence.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ronaldsvilcins.com/2024/12/04/growing-your-developer-audience-through-technical-blogging/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Containers on NixOS</title>
      <link>https://bkiran.com/blog/deploying-containers-nixos</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s make managing infrastructure on your own machine less cumbersome. Simplify it with NixOS and containers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bkiran.com/blog/deploying-containers-nixos</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did Silicon Valley turn right?</title>
      <link>https://www.programmablemutter.com/p/why-did-silicon-valley-turn-right</link>
      <description>The &amp;quot;pounded progressive ally&amp;quot; thesis has limits</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.programmablemutter.com/p/why-did-silicon-valley-turn-right</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Greatness Cannot Be Planned?</title>
      <link>https://www.sanju.sh/thoughts/why-greatness-cannot-be-planned</link>
      <description>The funny thing about success - it usually shows up when you least expect it. Let&amp;#39;s talk about why.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sanju.sh/thoughts/why-greatness-cannot-be-planned</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organizing Items with RFID Coin Tags</title>
      <link>https://www.pavlinbg.com/posts/organizing-items-with-rfid-coin-tags</link>
      <description>Learn to organize your items using RFID Coin Tags! This guide covers everything from storage solutions to NFC tech, helping you declutter and streamline your space!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pavlinbg.com/posts/organizing-items-with-rfid-coin-tags</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most stale bots are anti-user and anti-contributor, but they don&amp;#39;t have to be</title>
      <link>https://jacobtomlinson.dev/posts/2024/most-stale-bots-are-anti-user-and-anti-contributor-but-they-dont-have-to-be/</link>
      <description>If you’ve been around open source projects on GitHub you may have encountered a project with a stale bot.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jacobtomlinson.dev/posts/2024/most-stale-bots-are-anti-user-and-anti-contributor-but-they-dont-have-to-be/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Elderly People to Use Android - Lessons Learned</title>
      <link>https://kopiascsaba.hu/blog/teaching-elderly-people-to-use-android/</link>
      <description>This is my story about an adventure into online teaching, video course making, and choosing a hard-to-reach audience, who desperately needs help.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kopiascsaba.hu/blog/teaching-elderly-people-to-use-android/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using AI to automate foreign key discovery - Erik Edin</title>
      <link>https://erikedin.com/2024/09/30/using-ai-to-automate-foreign-key-discovery/</link>
      <description>When setting up a data warehouse, understanding the relationships between various objects—both within a system and across systems—is essential. Foreign keys are the connective tissue, linking tables and datasets. When dealing with undocumented legacy systems, discovering these relationships manually can be tedious. Automated foreign key discovery, aided by AI, helps you get up to speed […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://erikedin.com/2024/09/30/using-ai-to-automate-foreign-key-discovery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does the internet  really need even more TLDs?</title>
      <link>https://www.netmeister.org/blog/new-new-tlds.html</link>
      <description>ICANN
announced it is looking for applicants for new generic
top-level domain names (gTLDs) - but do we really need
more TLDs? Really?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.netmeister.org/blog/new-new-tlds.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligence Arbitrage</title>
      <link>https://sdan.io/blog/intelligence-arbitrage</link>
      <description>$25T Services Market</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sdan.io/blog/intelligence-arbitrage</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From .NET 6 to .NET 8, my migration experience: Migrating Durable Functions .NET 8 isolated</title>
      <link>https://anthonygiretti.com/2024/12/05/from-net-6-to-net-8-my-migration-experience-migrating-durable-functions-net-8-isolated/</link>
      <description>Introduction We recently started migrating our applications from .NET 6 to .NET 8. The migration...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anthonygiretti.com/2024/12/05/from-net-6-to-net-8-my-migration-experience-migrating-durable-functions-net-8-isolated/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Weather Service - Tsunami Hazards</title>
      <link>https://www.tsunami.gov/?p=PAAQ%2F2024%2F12%2F05%2Fso1aq0%2F1%2FWEAK51</link>
      <description>Your official U.S. government weather forecasts, warnings, meteorological products for forecasting the weather, tsunami hazards, and information about seismology.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tsunami.gov/?p=PAAQ%2F2024%2F12%2F05%2Fso1aq0%2F1%2FWEAK51</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyset Cursors, Not Offsets, for Postgres Pagination</title>
      <link>https://blog.sequinstream.com/keyset-cursors-not-offsets-for-postgres-pagination/</link>
      <description>We&amp;#39;re building Sequin, a Postgres CDC tool to streams and queues like Kafka, SQS, HTTP endpoints, and more. Efficient, correct pagination is paramount for our backfill process, so we use keyset cursors extensively.




You&amp;#39;ve probably heard about the limitations of offset/limit in Postgres. There are two primary concerns with</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sequinstream.com/keyset-cursors-not-offsets-for-postgres-pagination/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# Web Development on SharpSite with a focus on Auth part 2</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SSdWGa1n2x0</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Fritz is working on adding authentication to SharpSite https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/SharpSite</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SSdWGa1n2x0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>