<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>WebGPU Unleashed: A Practical Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://shi-yan.github.io/webgpuunleashed/</link>
      <description>WebGPU Unleashed, your ticket to the dynamic world of graphics programming. Dive in and discover the magic of creating stunning visuals from scratch, mastering the art of real-time graphics, and unlocking the power of WebGPU - all in one captivating tutorial.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shi-yan.github.io/webgpuunleashed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Citizens&amp;#39; Initiative</title>
      <link>https://eci.ec.europa.eu/045/public/</link>
      <description>Give your support !</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://eci.ec.europa.eu/045/public/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I program in 2024</title>
      <link>http://akkartik.name/post/programming-2024</link>
      <description>Jul 31, 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://akkartik.name/post/programming-2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - lvkv/whenfs: A FUSE Filesystem for your Google calendar</title>
      <link>https://github.com/lvkv/whenfs</link>
      <description>A FUSE Filesystem for your Google calendar. Contribute to lvkv/whenfs development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (lvkv)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/lvkv/whenfs</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using your Kindle as an e-ink monitor</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/adtac/eb639d3c707b55a28f0ee9a420aa7e0c</link>
      <description>Using your Kindle as an e-ink monitor. GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/adtac/eb639d3c707b55a28f0ee9a420aa7e0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting hospice. The end</title>
      <link>https://jakeseliger.com/2024/08/04/starting-hospice-the-end/</link>
      <description>I’m entering hospice. It’s time, and realistically past time. The squamous cell carcinoma tumors are growing, and the two doses of spot radiation I got on June 10 and 12 have utterly destroyed what…</description>
      <author> (By  Jake Seliger)</author>
      <guid>https://jakeseliger.com/2024/08/04/starting-hospice-the-end/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organizing Parameters in Minimal API with the AsParametersAttribute</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/ee26a396-8f5a-40a7-9dd5-f08cd8c03518</link>
      <description>Even though it was introduced in .NET 7, I came across recently the AsParametersAttribute. Let&amp;#39;s have a look what it is good for.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/ee26a396-8f5a-40a7-9dd5-f08cd8c03518</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HOWTO] Report code coverage of .NET solution in SonarCloud when using Azure DevOps Microsoft-hosted linux agent</title>
      <link>https://blog.rufer.be/2024/08/05/howto-report-code-coverage-of-net-solution-in-sonarcloud-when-using-azure-devops-microsoft-hosted-linux-agent/</link>
      <description>This blog post discusses the integration of SonarCloud code coverage reporting in an Azure DevOps YAML pipeline for .NET projects. It highlights adjustments needed when running such a pipeline on A…</description>
      <author> (Published by Marc Rufer)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.rufer.be/2024/08/05/howto-report-code-coverage-of-net-solution-in-sonarcloud-when-using-azure-devops-microsoft-hosted-linux-agent/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Praise my GitHub profile!</title>
      <link>https://praise-me.fly.dev/</link>
      <description>Use your GitHub profile as a way to get personalized messages of praise and encouragement.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://praise-me.fly.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines Are Running Out Of Flight Numbers, And They Don&amp;#39;t Know What To Do About It - View from the Wing</title>
      <link>https://viewfromthewing.com/airlines-are-running-out-of-flight-numbers-and-they-dont-know-what-to-do-about-it/</link>
      <description>Airlines use up to four digits for flight numbers. That means they can have up to 9,999 flights (since there’s no flight zero), and no one comes close. American Airlines operates around 6,700 daily flights including its American Eagle regional services. So they should have plenty of room to grow!  Except they don’t. American Airlines, Delta, and United are running out of flight numbers, and nobody knows what to do about it.</description>
      <author> (garyleff)</author>
      <guid>https://viewfromthewing.com/airlines-are-running-out-of-flight-numbers-and-they-dont-know-what-to-do-about-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create your own DIY Password Manager with Vim and Syncthing</title>
      <link>https://robleshermoso.com/posts/gestor-contrasenas-vim-syncthing-seguridad/</link>
      <description>Password management is a hassle, but worse is using the same password or a very similar one across all accounts. Eventually, regrets come when we fall victim to hacking. Unfortunately, my trust in password managers like LastPass or 1Password is zero. Just remember the LastPass hack, where a multitude of passwords were decrypted.
The LastPass Hack In the attack on LastPass, hackers used phishing techniques and compromised users’ personal and administrative data.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robleshermoso.com/posts/gestor-contrasenas-vim-syncthing-seguridad/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing folium map sizes</title>
      <link>https://andrewpwheeler.com/2024/08/04/reducing-folium-map-sizes/</link>
      <description>Recently for a crimede-coder project I have been building out a custom library to make nice leaflet maps using the python folium library. See the example I have posted on my website. Below is a scr…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewpwheeler.com/2024/08/04/reducing-folium-map-sizes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can&amp;#39;t Spell WebRTC without RCE - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://margin.re/2024/07/you-cant-spell-webrtc-without-rce-part-1/</link>
      <description>Injecting and Exploiting Synthetic Remote Vulnerabilities to explore Signal-iOS and WebRTC

It’s another average Friday morning and my iPhone shows 705 unread Signal messages. Signal has not completely supplanted my use of iMessage, but it does dominate communications with industry peers and privacy-conscious friends. If you are a cybersecurity</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://margin.re/2024/07/you-cant-spell-webrtc-without-rce-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against XMPP+OMEMO - Dhole Moments</title>
      <link>https://soatok.blog/2024/08/04/against-xmppomemo/</link>
      <description>XMPP is a messaging protocol (among other things) that needs no introduction to any technical audience. Its various implementations have proliferated through technical communities for decades. Many…</description>
      <author> (By Soatok)</author>
      <guid>https://soatok.blog/2024/08/04/against-xmppomemo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>why It’s good to reflect on boycotts – Daniel Frank</title>
      <link>https://danfrank.ca/cocaine-kim-jong-un-and-blackrock-why-its-good-to-reflect-on-boycotts/</link>
      <description>One of the recurring themes on this blog is the exploration of small, often overlooked actions that can significantly improve one’s own life, the world or enhance the lives of those around us with minimal effort.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://danfrank.ca/cocaine-kim-jong-un-and-blackrock-why-its-good-to-reflect-on-boycotts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;m back, Ruby on Rails</title>
      <link>https://blog.wildcat.io/2024/08/i-m-back-rails/</link>
      <description>Last year, I wrote a blog post called Goodbye, Ruby on Rails. One year later, after creating my own business, I decided to be back to Ruby on Rails. I’m withdrawing my previous statements on DHH and Rails. Though I still have some concerns about the directions of Ruby on Rails, especially the rejection of TypeScript, I still believe that Ruby on Rails is a great framework for web development,</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.wildcat.io/2024/08/i-m-back-rails/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Cured My Procrastination - Learn How To Learn</title>
      <link>https://learnhowtolearn.org/how-i-cured-procrastination/</link>
      <description>I went from a C student to an A engineering student while enjoying work more and having 100x more freedom TLDR (because I also hate digging through articles for the thing I clicked for): When I went to college I did extremely poorly sophomore year for numerous reasons, mostly being lazy and procrastinating. After immense […]</description>
      <author> (dnbt777)</author>
      <guid>https://learnhowtolearn.org/how-i-cured-procrastination/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t use LIMIT OFFSET for pagination in PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://mirio.dev/2024/08/03/pagination-in-postgresql/</link>
      <description>Introduction LIMIT / OFFSET pagination is one of the most common ways to implement pagination in your service. You can find countless tutorials online describing the method and its even the default in the popular web framework Django1. While it gets the job done for most use cases and smaller tables, you may begin to run into performance issues when paginating tables with millions of rows. Django and Laravel2 even have warnings in their documentation about this type of pagination.</description>
      <author> (Cole MacKenzie)</author>
      <guid>https://mirio.dev/2024/08/03/pagination-in-postgresql/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you have to optimize, it isn&amp;#39;t good enough</title>
      <link>https://notes.npilk.com/optimizing-isnt-good-enough</link>
      <description>Success is determined by your initial conditions, not whatever improvements you can make on the margin.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.npilk.com/optimizing-isnt-good-enough</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing a system call tracer using eBPF</title>
      <link>https://sh4dy.com/2024/08/03/beetracer/</link>
      <description>Pre-RequisitesSystem calls, eBPF, C, basics of low-level programming. IntroductioneBPF (Extended Berkeley Packet Filter) is a technology that allows users to run custom programs within the kernel. BPF</description>
      <author> (sh4dy)</author>
      <guid>https://sh4dy.com/2024/08/03/beetracer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The birth of ILC</title>
      <link>https://marty.zalega.me/2024/08/04/the-birth-of-ilc.html</link>
      <description>I don’t think I am the only one who creates a lot of ad-hoc Bash scripts and programs. Whether it be for work or for ourselves, they become part of our perso...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marty.zalega.me/2024/08/04/the-birth-of-ilc.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building software brick by brick &amp;amp; New Internet</title>
      <link>https://amal.bearblog.dev/mvp-rants/</link>
      <description>I think most of software engineering today has been reduced to building it brick by brick like how a mason would build walls. In the name of MVPs, we have pr...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://amal.bearblog.dev/mvp-rants/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porting my JavaScript Game Engine to C for No Reason</title>
      <link>https://phoboslab.org/log/2024/08/high_impact</link>
      <description>— Sunday, August 4th 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://phoboslab.org/log/2024/08/high_impact</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Figma Component Variants map to XAML Visual States in Windows UI - Nick&amp;#39;s .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/figma-winui-xaml/</link>
      <description>In a previous post I covered using Figma to design and develop applications for Windows and the &amp;#160;Uno Platform. This was a high level post that didn’t get into either Figma files (Fluent and Material) in much detail. One thing that is common to both files is the use of components, and component variants, to ... Read more</description>
      <author> (Nick)</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/figma-winui-xaml/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>