<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Sort</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3026/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3026/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Ambient Context Pattern in .NET: From Theory to Production</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/understanding-ambient-context-pattern-net/</link>
      <description>Introduction

In our previous exploration of execution context in .NET Core, we delved into the intricacies of AsyncLocal and ThreadLocal.

Execution Context Management with AsyncLocal and ThreadLocal in .NET CoreIntroduction In modern distributed .NET applications, managing context across execution boundaries is a critical architectural concern. While both AsyncLocal&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; and</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/understanding-ambient-context-pattern-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone gets bidirectional BFS wrong</title>
      <link>https://zdimension.fr/everyone-gets-bidirectional-bfs-wrong/</link>
      <description>People really need to stop blindly copying code from the Internet.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zdimension.fr/everyone-gets-bidirectional-bfs-wrong/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 10:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some news about .NET 10: BackgroundServices and new String Comparer</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/3a8c29a3-750a-40f0-aa43-c236b855813e</link>
      <description>Recently, there were two new features merged in .NET 10 I think are small little quality of life improvements: Avoid Blocking on startup with BackgroundServices and a new string comparer.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/3a8c29a3-750a-40f0-aa43-c236b855813e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 05:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s CRUNCH! | More magic</title>
      <link>https://www.more-magic.net/posts/crunch.html</link>
      <description>NOTE: This is another guest post by Felix Winkelmann, the founder and one of the current maintainers of CHICKEN Scheme.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.more-magic.net/posts/crunch.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 05:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making the creation of before/after comparisons for OpenStreetMap more accessible</title>
      <link>https://tzovar.as/map-comparisons/</link>
      <description>If you pick dates close to each other, they also make for a great “find the differences”-puzzle. tl;dr: One can now create before/after maps of OpenStreetMap with osm-mapping-party-before-after right in the browser, thanks to MyBinder. Just click here to launch it. For a good 6 months now, I’ve been contributing...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tzovar.as/map-comparisons/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technology: rights or responsibilities? - Part X</title>
      <link>https://techrights.org/n/2024/12/17/Technology_rights_or_responsibilities_Part_X.shtml</link>
      <description>By Dr. Andy Farnell</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://techrights.org/n/2024/12/17/Technology_rights_or_responsibilities_Part_X.shtml</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vector Search — Lucene is All You Need | Shaped Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.shaped.ai/blog/vector-search-lucene-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description>Recent research is challenging long-held assumptions about AI-powered search, questioning whether dedicated vector stores are truly necessary. As AI and search technologies continue to evolve, organizations are searching for solutions that balance efficiency, cost, and scalability. While dedicated vector databases have traditionally been considered essential for managing vector search tasks, they come with significant resource and infrastructure demands. Researchers from the University of Waterloo and Roma Tre University, however, suggest an alternative: leveraging the widely-used Lucene search library to handle vector search operations with OpenAI embeddings. This finding could offer a more accessible and versatile approach to advanced search capabilities, prompting organizations to rethink their reliance on specialized vector storage solutions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.shaped.ai/blog/vector-search-lucene-is-all-you-need</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Multi-Modal LLMs and Diffusion Models for Customized Manga Generation</title>
      <link>https://jianzongwu.github.io/projects/diffsensei/</link>
      <description>DiffSensei: Bridging Multi-Modal LLMs and Diffusion Models for Customized Manga Generation</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jianzongwu.github.io/projects/diffsensei/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How We Scraped Global Hotel Data to Track Economic Trends</title>
      <link>https://substack.thewebscraping.club/p/how-we-scraped-global-hotel-data</link>
      <description>Tracking Tourism and Economic Flows with Global Hotel Data Scraping</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://substack.thewebscraping.club/p/how-we-scraped-global-hotel-data</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why large language models struggle with long contexts</title>
      <link>https://www.understandingai.org/p/why-large-language-models-struggle</link>
      <description>Transformer-based LLMs get less efficient as context windows grow.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.understandingai.org/p/why-large-language-models-struggle</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking into Vision</title>
      <link>https://blog.bawolf.com/p/breaking-into-vision</link>
      <description>Fine-tuning a vision model to recognize break dance power moves</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.bawolf.com/p/breaking-into-vision</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why too much Pydantic can be a bad thing — Motleycrew</title>
      <link>https://blog.motleycrew.ai/blog/why-too-much-pydantic-can-be-a-bad-thing</link>
      <description>Recently, there has been a fashion among open source packages (such as Langchain and CrewAI) to have all their objects, such as agents and tools, inherit from...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.motleycrew.ai/blog/why-too-much-pydantic-can-be-a-bad-thing</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An obsession with measurement</title>
      <link>https://squiretothegiants.com/2024/12/13/an-obsession-with-measurement/</link>
      <description>I recently wrote a measurement guide and a hugely important (and definitely too short) section within is titled ‘Beware the allure of measurement’. Unfortunately, our working worlds seem to be obse…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://squiretothegiants.com/2024/12/13/an-obsession-with-measurement/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$200k in 60 days: Honest Review of AppSumo Select for my AI B2B SaaS Product (2024)</title>
      <link>https://octolens.com/blog/200k-in-60-days-honest-review-of-appsumo-select-for-my-ai-b2b-saas-product-2024</link>
      <description>Honest review of AppSumo Select Lifetime deal, with pros, cons, and if it&amp;#39;s worth it for recurring-cost products. Discover insights on revenue, user quality, and support.</description>
      <author> (Charlotte Schmitt)</author>
      <guid>https://octolens.com/blog/200k-in-60-days-honest-review-of-appsumo-select-for-my-ai-b2b-saas-product-2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So I was bored and wrote a rant about GenAI, and then fed it to ChatGPT-4o, and this was the output – Data, Reflections, and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://datareflections.net/so-i-was-bored-and-wrote-a-rant-about-genai-and-then-fed-it-to-chatgpt-4o-and-this-was-the-output/</link>
      <description>So I was bored and irritated by incessant buzzing of news about “GenerativeAI” being this, that, and the other, and I wrote this rant, and then decided to feed it to ChatGPT-4o, and this is what I got.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://datareflections.net/so-i-was-bored-and-wrote-a-rant-about-genai-and-then-fed-it-to-chatgpt-4o-and-this-was-the-output/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta&amp;#39;s MySQL Fork You Never Knew About • Kir Shatrov</title>
      <link>https://kirshatrov.com/posts/facebook-mysql-fork</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s not very well widely known — but in the world of MySQL forks like Percona and MariaDB, Facebook&amp;#39;s fork might be the most interesting one!
Unlike Oracle or Percona, at Facebook they&amp;#39;ve been building cutting edge features into MySQL that allow them to run at a hyper scale.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kirshatrov.com/posts/facebook-mysql-fork</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running NetBSD on IBM ThinkPad 380Z</title>
      <link>https://luke8086.dev/netbsd-on-thinkpad-380z.html</link>
      <description>Launched in 1998, the 380Z was one very fine ThinkPad.

  It was the last ThinkPad to come in the classic bulky and rectangular form factor.

  It was also one of the first to feature a huge 13.3&amp;quot; TFT display, powerful 233MHz Pentium II, and whopping 160 megs of RAM.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://luke8086.dev/netbsd-on-thinkpad-380z.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Janet RPC | Joe Creager</title>
      <link>https://joecreager.com/introduction-to-janet-rpc/</link>
      <description>Janet is a modern Lisp with a rich standard library in a tiny package. Janet is quickly becoming my favorite Lisp for tasks I might have accomplished with bash/sh or python in the past thanks to its ability to produce small statically linked binaries. In this article we’ll explore remote procedure calls (RPC) with the spork package. Since RPC involves making calls over a network all code examples are divided by the client and server implementation in client.janet and server.janet. Follow along by running the examples on your own machine. You can view the example in once place as a gist.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joecreager.com/introduction-to-janet-rpc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel vector graphics rasterization on CPU.</title>
      <link>https://gasiulis.name/parallel-rasterization-on-cpu/</link>
      <description>Utilizing all CPU cores for rendering complex vector graphics images.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gasiulis.name/parallel-rasterization-on-cpu/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Having fun with Godot Movie Maker - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://simondalvai.org/blog/godot-moviemaker-part1/</link>
      <description>How I created a simple Steam trailer for my upcoming game 99 Managers Futsal Edition with Godot Movie Maker</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://simondalvai.org/blog/godot-moviemaker-part1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I experimented with Programmatic SEO and get instant traction</title>
      <link>https://www.xvrc.net/posts/how-i-experimented-with-programmatic-seo-and-get-instant-traction/</link>
      <description>Discover how I used programmatic SEO to build roxnation.fr, a Hyrox gym directory in under 12 hours. Learn step-by-step strategies, tools, and SEO techniques to gain instant traction with minimal cost. Perfect for marketers and no-code enthusiasts!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.xvrc.net/posts/how-i-experimented-with-programmatic-seo-and-get-instant-traction/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magic of Solving Problems with 3D Printing &amp;#183; Alex Meub</title>
      <link>https://alexmeub.com/the-magic-of-solving-problems-with-3d-printing/</link>
      <description>3D printing empowers individuals to solve their own problems by designing solutions while enabling others to reproduce those designs at minimal cost and effort.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alexmeub.com/the-magic-of-solving-problems-with-3d-printing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 01:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform Live Coding: Looking at language qualifiers for resources files</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=9XflTMim9iM</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io</description>
      <author> (Uno Platform)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=9XflTMim9iM</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 22:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform Live Coding: Looking at language qualifiers for resources files</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=tLuQMzDXrNw</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io</description>
      <author> (Uno Platform)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=tLuQMzDXrNw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 21:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee and Open Source Conversation - Jeramiah Dooley</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=gOJkIletFt4</link>
      <description>Jeramiah Dooley (he/him) leads the advocacy team focused on Enterprise customers, making sure that the product and content are aligned for organizations who are using GitHub every day. For more than 19 years he has spent his career at the intersection of &amp;#39;enterprise&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;what&amp;#39;s next&amp;#39; and is excited to focus on bringing the best experience possible to developers and platform teams.

Prior to GitHub, Jeramiah led the advocacy efforts around serverless container services at AWS, and was a Principal Cloud Advocate in Azure Engineering, leading the team that supported Enterprise Platforms and Tools. Jeramiah was also the Manager of NetApp’s Global Technical Pursuit team, focusing on helping customers and partners architect next generation solutions using their entire portfolio, focusing on VMware, OpenStack, and container integrations.

Jeramiah also has worked in the healthcare, legal and service provider industries.

You can follow Jeramiah on Social Media
https://bsky.app/profile/jeramiah.net
https://www.linkedin.com/in/jeramiah/
https://github.com/jdooley-clt

PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO THE PODCAST

- Spotify: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-spotify
- Apple Podcasts: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-apple
- Google Podcasts: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-google
- RSS: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-rss

You can check out more episodes of Coffee and Open Source on https://www.coffeeandopensource.com

Coffee and Open Source is hosted by Isaac Levin (https://twitter.com/isaacrlevin)</description>
      <author> (Isaac Levin)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=gOJkIletFt4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 20:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon – Bartosz Ciechanowski</title>
      <link>https://ciechanow.ski/moon/</link>
      <description>Interactive article about the Moon</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ciechanow.ski/moon/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 19:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf 2024 Recap - Celebrating .NET 9, AI, Community, &amp;amp; More - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-conf-2024-recap/</link>
      <description>.NET Conf 2024 is over, but you can catch up with all the announcement and fun with video recordings, slides, demos, and more.</description>
      <author> (facebook.com/dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-conf-2024-recap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 19:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting to Two Million Users as a One Woman Dev Team</title>
      <link>https://brightonruby.com/2024/getting-to-2-million-users-as-a-one-woman-dev-team/</link>
      <description>The story of the The StoryGraph with graphs</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://brightonruby.com/2024/getting-to-2-million-users-as-a-one-woman-dev-team/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 17:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA&amp;#39;s $249 Secret Weapon for Edge AI - Jetson Orin Nano Super: Driveway Monitor</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=QHBr8hekCzg</link>
      <description>FREE GIVEAWAY OF JENSEN-HUANG-SIGNED ORIN NANO SUPER!  See Below!
Join Dave as he explores NVIDIA&amp;#39;s Jetson Orin Nano, a compact AI powerhouse with 1024 CUDA cores and 6 ARM cores for just $249. Learn why this could be the best AI board for your projects in robotics, IoT, or AI development.  Free Sample of my Book on the Spectrum: https://amzn.to/3zBinWM

Orin Nano Super: https://nvda.ws/41DSukS

We&amp;#39;re giving away a free Jetson Orin Nano to a lucky winner randomly selected from the comments.  Better yet, it&amp;#39;s personally signed by Jensen Huang!

Leave a useful comment to be automatically entered to win!  Winner will be announced by their ebay username in a FUTURE VIDEO.  I will not contact you on YouTube, and I do not use Telegram. 

Highlights:
Unboxing and First Impressions
Performance Comparison: Against Raspberry Pi and high-end desktops
Real-World Use: Smart driveway with AI vehicle detection
Software Setup: Ubuntu, CUDA, and AI models like YOLOv8
AI Experiments: Running Llama 3.2 on this tiny board

Why Watch:
Dive into edge computing and AI on a budget
See practical applications of AI hardware
Understand NVIDIA&amp;#39;s CUDA cores for machine learning

Python Code:
https://github.com/davepl/ObjectDetect</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=QHBr8hekCzg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C#, Web Dev, Accessibility, GitHub Actions, and YOUR contributions!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=44zZYwF5fwo</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Fritz is working on adding a plugin system to SharpSite https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/SharpSite</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=44zZYwF5fwo</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>