<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Agenda 2020 - NDC Sydney 2020 | Online Developers Conference</title>
      <link>http://ndcsydney.com/agenda</link>
      <description>NDC Sydney 2020 is a 5-Day Online Conference Event</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://ndcsydney.com/agenda</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Better Mousetrap - Turnerj (aka. James Turner)</title>
      <link>https://turnerj.com/blog/a-better-mousetrap</link>
      <description>My journey to launch a product and take the next steps in my career</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://turnerj.com/blog/a-better-mousetrap</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 09:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>  The Morning Brew #3069</title>
      <link>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/2020/09/15/the-morning-brew-3069/</link>
      <description>A daily link blog covering all aspects of the Microsoft Development World, published every working week day</description>
      <author> (Chris Alcock)</author>
      <guid>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/2020/09/15/the-morning-brew-3069/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 09:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How HTTPS works</title>
      <link>https://howhttps.works/</link>
      <description>🙀 A cat explains how HTTPS works...in a comic! 😻</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://howhttps.works/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 09:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://www.projectoberon.com/</link>
      <description>Project Oberon: The Design of an Operating System, 
a Compiler, and a Computer</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.projectoberon.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 09:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moment.js | Docs</title>
      <link>https://momentjs.com/docs/#/-project-status/</link>
      <description>Moment.js has been successfully used in millions of projects, and we are happy to have contributed to making date and time better on the web.
As of September 2020, Moment gets over 12 million downloads per week!  However, Moment was built for the previous era of the JavaScript ecosystem.
The modern web looks much different these days.  Moment has evolved somewhat over the years, but it has essentially the same design as it did when it was created in 2011.
Given how many projects depend on it, we choose to prioritize stability over new features.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://momentjs.com/docs/#/-project-status/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 08:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi as a local server for self hosting applications</title>
      <link>https://cri.dev/posts/2020-09-12-Raspberry-Pi-as-a-local-server-for-self-hosting-applications/</link>
      <description>Doing an experiment with my RPi 4, using it as a small but powerful local server  My current PC is a 10 year old Macbook Pro 13&amp;amp;quot; 2010, which is sluggish sometimes  So I want to offload some heavy tasks (ffmpeg time-lapse creation, long-running tasks and services) to the Raspberry Pi and connect to it either via LAN or Wi-Fi  Below you can read my findings about performance, applications and general issues I encountered and tried to solve   Table of Contents   First steps Connection via LAN to PC  Internet Sharing from PC to RPi  Connection via Wi-Fi Benchmarking Transfer speeds via iperf  Benchmark over LAN Benchmark over Wi-Fi  Applications  ffmpeg for time-lapse n8n for automation emby for media server hakatime  Final words  First steps I started by:  Flashing a minimal RaspiOS Buster Lite image on a 32GB SD card (prob better for the future if I used a 128GB one) No setup of Wi-Fi connectivity through wpa_supplicant Creating an empty ssh file in the SD card to enable SSH access  Powered up the Pi and I was able to connect via LAN</description>
      <author> (Christian Fei)</author>
      <guid>https://cri.dev/posts/2020-09-12-Raspberry-Pi-as-a-local-server-for-self-hosting-applications/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 08:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2020-09-15</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/09/app-developer-links-2020-09-15/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/09/app-developer-links-2020-09-15/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 07:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters Weekly 182 -  Sending Dates from JavaScript to .NET</title>
      <link>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/09/monsters-weekly/ep182/</link>
      <description>Getting the logic right when dealing with dates is hard in any application but it’s even harder when your application logic crosses platform boundaries. In today’s episode, we take a look at some of t</description>
      <author> (The Monsters)</author>
      <guid>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/09/monsters-weekly/ep182/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 06:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Visual Studio Code August 2020 (version 1.49) update gets several improvements</title>
      <link>https://www.kunal-chowdhury.com/2020/09/visual-studio-code-august-2020-update.html</link>
      <description>Microsoft Visual Studio Code 2020 Update (version 1.49) brings several improvements listed here, and here's how to download the latest update.</description>
      <author> (Kunal Chowdhury)</author>
      <guid>https://www.kunal-chowdhury.com/2020/09/visual-studio-code-august-2020-update.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 06:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Adds Latent Bug Discovery Feature</title>
      <link>https://www.i-programmer.info/news/89-net/13990-net-adds-latent-bug-discovery-feature.html</link>
      <description>Programming book reviews, programming tutorials,programming news, C#, Ruby, Python,C, C++, PHP, Visual Basic, Computer book reviews, computer history, programming history, joomla, theory, spreadsheets and more.</description>
      <author> (Editor)</author>
      <guid>https://www.i-programmer.info/news/89-net/13990-net-adds-latent-bug-discovery-feature.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 06:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Index Usage: finding indexes not being used - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/blogs/index-usage-finding-indexes-not-being-used-2/</link>
      <description>Index not being used are not only wasting space, but also hurting update performance, because these indexes need to be updated when records are changed</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/dennes.torres)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/blogs/index-usage-finding-indexes-not-being-used-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 06:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>– Wren</title>
      <link>https://wren.io/</link>
      <description>Think Smalltalk in a Lua-sized package with a dash of Erlang and wrapped up in
a familiar, modern syntax.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wren.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 05:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update .NET frameworks to .NET 5.0 by benaadams · Pull Request #6000 · TechEmpower/FrameworkBenchmarks</title>
      <link>https://github.com/TechEmpower/FrameworkBenchmarks/pull/6000</link>
      <description>.NET 5.0 has moved to rc 2 which means it's now officially supported in production</description>
      <author> (TechEmpower)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/TechEmpower/FrameworkBenchmarks/pull/6000</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 04:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A database for every repl</title>
      <link>https://blog.repl.it/database</link>
      <description>Repl.it is already the best place to build your apps. But there was a missing piece: where do you store your data? We’re introducing…</description>
      <author> (Mon Sep 14 2020 by Sidney Kochman)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.repl.it/database</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 04:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't get burned by missing await Calls for Async Code in ASP.NET Core Middleware</title>
      <link>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2020/Sep/14/Dont-get-burned-by-missing-await-Calls-for-Async-Code-in-ASPNET-Core-Middleware</link>
      <description>I recently got burned in an upgraded ASP.NET Core server application where a missing `await` statement caused wildly inconsistent and puzzling output failures. While a simple thing to avoid, once introduced it's possible to live with this error for some time before it manifests. In this post I show a scenario where a missing `await` was causing infrequent HTTP response errors, even though the client apparently receives a valid response.</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/rickstrahl)</author>
      <guid>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2020/Sep/14/Dont-get-burned-by-missing-await-Calls-for-Async-Code-in-ASPNET-Core-Middleware</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds: IBM did discriminate against older workers in making layoffs | WRAL TechWire</title>
      <link>https://www.wraltechwire.com/2020/09/14/feds-ibm-did-discriminate-against-older-workers-in-making-layoffs/</link>
      <description>Tech giant IBM discriminated against older workers when making thousands of layoffs between 2013 and 2018, according to a letter sent to IBM by the US Equal Employment Opportunity Commission.</description>
      <author> (by Rick Smith — September 14, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wraltechwire.com/2020/09/14/feds-ibm-did-discriminate-against-older-workers-in-making-layoffs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 01:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft.EntityFrameworkCore 5.0.0-rc.1.20451.13</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Microsoft.EntityFrameworkCore/5.0.0-rc.1.20451.13</link>
      <description>Entity Framework Core is a modern object-database mapper for .NET. It supports LINQ queries, change tracking, updates, and schema migrations. EF Core works with SQL Server, Azure SQL Database, SQLite, Azure Cosmos DB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, and other databases through a provider plugin API.

Commonly Used Types:
Microsoft.EntityFrameworkCore.DbContext
Microsoft.EntityFrameworkCore.DbSet</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Microsoft.EntityFrameworkCore/5.0.0-rc.1.20451.13</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support ECDiffieHellman on X509Certificate2 by vcsjones · Pull Request #42180 · dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/42180/commits/2d4fda5076435e90ccf8bfea22f481d3795ee4af</link>
      <description>This adds ECDiffieHellman functionality to X509Certificate2. In addition, this also adds arbitrary SubjectPublicKeyInfo support for PublicKey.
This also makes some under-the-hood changes. Previousl...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/42180/commits/2d4fda5076435e90ccf8bfea22f481d3795ee4af</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phosphine gas in the cloud decks of Venus</title>
      <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-020-1174-4</link>
      <description>The detection of ~20 ppb of phosphine in Venus clouds by observations in the millimetre-wavelength range from JCMT and ALMA is puzzling, because according to our knowledge of Venus, no phosphine should be there. As the most plausible formation paths do not work, the source could be unknown chemical processes—maybe even life?</description>
      <author> (Jim Hoge)</author>
      <guid>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41550-020-1174-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Turboing</title>
      <link>http://www.macwhiz.com/blog/art-of-turboing/</link>
      <description>I first learned the term “turboing” when I worked second-level telephone
technical support at Xerox. It refers to the actions of a customer who goes
around the normal technical support process by contacting a senior person in
the chain of command.</description>
      <author> (CompUSA: How not to handle
a turboing customer)</author>
      <guid>http://www.macwhiz.com/blog/art-of-turboing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Way To Monetize An Audience</title>
      <link>https://stayingqold.github.io/2020/09/14/a-new-way-to-monetize-an-audience.html</link>
      <description>“Coffee operates like a subscription… there is almost no other subscription that you have that costs that much money.” - Samir, The Colin and Samir Podcast</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stayingqold.github.io/2020/09/14/a-new-way-to-monetize-an-audience.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The compositor is evil</title>
      <link>https://raphlinus.github.io/ui/graphics/2020/09/13/compositor-is-evil.html</link>
      <description>First, I want to make it clear that I’m not accusing the compositor of true evil, which I define roughly as deliberately causing suffering. There’s unfortunately too much of that in the world. I mean it in the more metaphorical sense that it causes serious problems and forces other parts of the system to be more complex to work around its limitations.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://raphlinus.github.io/ui/graphics/2020/09/13/compositor-is-evil.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBM, and a lament for the software industry</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2020/09/14/ubm-and-a-lament-for-the-software-industry/</link>
      <description>I grew up in tech as a UBM fan. Ok, not really a fan, but a “there’s very few voices writing books about ‘how to write code well’, and this person seems to know what they’re doing, so I’m going to listen to him”.  I read all his books; attended talks he gave at SCNA, and thought for a while that his way was the right way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2020/09/14/ubm-and-a-lament-for-the-software-industry/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Office Project: Overkill Workbench Series Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.techprowd.com/home-office-project-overkill-workbench-series/</link>
      <description>After moving into a new apartment I have already had plans in my to build a custom workbench setup for my home office room so this series will be oriented in the home office room and workbench design. Currently, my room looks pretty simple it's 6.5 tatamis sized room</description>
      <author> (Aurimas Niekis)</author>
      <guid>https://www.techprowd.com/home-office-project-overkill-workbench-series/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never Invest in the Business Model</title>
      <link>https://jayriverlong.github.io/2020/09/12/angel.html</link>
      <description>I am an angel investor. I have been investing personally in early-stage companies, Pre-Seed through Series B, since 2015. I do it not for money but for love of the game; the greatest pleasure to me is to learn from entrepreneurs smarter than me, and help them succeed.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jayriverlong.github.io/2020/09/12/angel.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNSS Jamming and Spoofing, aka Galileo's Authentication Algorithm Part 3 - Articles</title>
      <link>https://berthub.eu/articles/posts/galileos-authentication-algorithm-part-3/</link>
      <description>Welcome to part 3 of my series on OSNMA, the proposed Galileo Navigation Message Authentication protocol. This part can be read independently from part 1 and part 2, but it might be useful to read the introduction to part 1.
This post attempts to explain GPS (GNSS) jamming and spoofing, so it might be a useful read even if you don’t care about Galileo or its authentication.
As usual, I’ve been helped tremendously by Daniel Estévez &amp; many other researchers and Galileo professionals, and again I am very greatful for all the links, corrections, suggestions and knowledge you provided.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://berthub.eu/articles/posts/galileos-authentication-algorithm-part-3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Febraury 13, 2020 - Blazor TreeView GridLines and starting the FormView component</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nXup9SeWjSM</link>
      <description>Today Fritz finished the GridLine implementation for the TreeView Blazor component and built a sample to show how the FormView should behave.

Questions:
15:13 - Does a TreeView really need grid lines?
44:38 - Do the TreeNodes register with the parent in Onlnitalized?
45:46 - Can TreeNodes register with the parent TreeNode as they're drawn?
47:41 - This is as close to a "Pattern" with Blazor: Child Components register with their Parent component
51:14 - Should I create my 'Creative Coding' stream? What worked for you and why did you start?
1:39:15 - Am I the only one that gets an SSL error for docs.microsoft.com?
2:07:40 - With Git push, shouldn't it be pushing the current branch if you don't provide a branch name? 

Source Code at https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/BlazorWebFormsComponents
Watch live at https://www.twitch.tv/csharpfritz</description>
      <author> (Jeffrey T. Fritz)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nXup9SeWjSM</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimum Viable Air Quality Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://igor.moomers.org/minimal-viable-air-quality</link>
      <description>If you, like me, live in the Bay Area, you may have woken up to something like this last week:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://igor.moomers.org/minimal-viable-air-quality</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Gaussian Blurs - Digital Bunker</title>
      <link>https://digitalbunker.dev/2020/09/13/understanding-gaussian-blurs/</link>
      <description>We'll take a look at Gaussian distributions, image convolution, and create our own Gaussian blur implementation.</description>
      <author> (By Aryaman Sharda)</author>
      <guid>https://digitalbunker.dev/2020/09/13/understanding-gaussian-blurs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countdown Show: Microsoft Ignite 2020 - Episode 2</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/The-Countdown-Show/Countdown-Show-Microsoft-Ignite-2020-Episode-2</link>
      <description>Amy Boyd goes behind the scenes with Karuana Gatimu to discuss M365 adoption and solutions using learning pathways. Register at https://myignite.microsoft.com/! </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/The-Countdown-Show/Countdown-Show-Microsoft-Ignite-2020-Episode-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February 14, 2020 - Blazor Coding with Squirrel</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HbiJXs6QFZc</link>
      <description>In a fun-filled episode that was just NUTS to make, Fritz dons a squirrel costume provided by viewers as he writes code.  After about 30 minutes of shenanigans and more puns than you can shake a stick at, Fritz gets back into working on the BlazorWebFormsComponents.

He continues working on the FormView component for Blazor, adding support for FooterTemplates.  He is challenged by the viewers to use the Peanut Font while coding (http://www.fontriver.com/font/peanut/) and spends 15 minutes in that configuration.  He adds the Pager feature to the FormView along with appropriate integration tests to show it off.

1:22:11 - Would you recommend a novice developer learn command line Git? Or is a GUI acceptable in 2002?

Source Code at https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/BlazorWebFormsComponents
Watch live at https://www.twitch.tv/csharpfritz</description>
      <author> (Jeffrey T. Fritz)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HbiJXs6QFZc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikola admits prototype was rolling downhill in promotional video</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/cars/2020/09/nikola-admits-prototype-was-rolling-downhill-in-promotional-video/</link>
      <description>“This thing fully functions,” Trevor Milton said in 2016. It didn't.</description>
      <author> (Timothy B. Lee
    -  9/14/2020, 10:58 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/cars/2020/09/nikola-admits-prototype-was-rolling-downhill-in-promotional-video/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modelling a Wealth Tax Correctly · Krishna's words</title>
      <link>https://blog.nindalf.com/posts/wealth-tax/</link>
      <description>Joker of all trades 🃏</description>
      <author> (Krishna Sundarram)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.nindalf.com/posts/wealth-tax/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 23:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>npgsql/efcore.pg</title>
      <link>https://github.com/npgsql/efcore.pg/milestone/24?closed=1</link>
      <description>Entity Framework Core provider for PostgreSQL. Contribute to npgsql/efcore.pg development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (npgsql)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/npgsql/efcore.pg/milestone/24?closed=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 22:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMOs You’ve Never Heard Of: Age of Ascent, Little Sim World, Arcane Showdown, Riders Republic</title>
      <link>https://massivelyop.com/2020/09/14/mmos-youve-never-heard-of-age-of-ascent-little-sim-world-arcane-showdown-riders-republic/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Justin Olivetti -  September 11, 2020 59)</author>
      <guid>https://massivelyop.com/2020/09/14/mmos-youve-never-heard-of-age-of-ascent-little-sim-world-arcane-showdown-riders-republic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor Gets Faster (Even Without AOT) -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/09/14/aspnet-5-rc1.aspx</link>
      <description>The C#-based Blazor web development framework received a performance boost with the new Release Candidate (RC) of the unifying .NET 5, scheduled for one more RC before go-live general availability next month.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel09/14/2020)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/09/14/aspnet-5-rc1.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 21:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare your cloud environments using Azure landing zones | Azure Friday</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Prepare-your-cloud-environments-using-Azure-landing-zones</link>
      <description>Brian Blanchard joins Scott Hanselman to discuss Azure landing zones and how you can prepare your destination Azure environment.</description>
      <author> (by Scott Hanselman, Rob Caron)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Prepare-your-cloud-environments-using-Azure-landing-zones</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 21:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disassembly improvements for optimized managed debugging | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/disassembly-improvements-for-optimized-debugging/</link>
      <description>If you are focused on squeezing out the last bits of performance for your .NET service or application, you might choose to take advantage of JIT compiler optimizations. However, debugging optimized code can be a challenge. In this blog I’ll show you how the Disassembly Window,</description>
      <author> (Mark Downie Senior Program Manager, Visual Studio Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/disassembly-improvements-for-optimized-debugging/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 21:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Sept 8 2020 - New Identity experience with Microsoft.Identity.Web</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hxDli4imREE</link>
      <description>The ASP.NET Core project templates now integrate with Microsoft.Identity.Web to handle authentication with Azure Activity Directory (Azure AD). Chrisos and JP will show you how the Microsoft.Identity.Web package provides a better experience for authentication through Azure AD as well as an easier way to access Azure resources on behalf of your users, including Microsoft Graph.

Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/aspnet-standup-2020-09-08

Featuring: Christos Matskas (@ChristosMatskas), John Patrick Dandison (@AzureAndChill)</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hxDli4imREE</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 20:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staples discloses data breach exposing customer info</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/staples-discloses-data-breach-exposing-customer-info/</link>
      <description>Giant office retail company Staples informed some of its customers that data related to their orders has been accessed without authorization.</description>
      <author> (Ionut Ilascu)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/staples-discloses-data-breach-exposing-customer-info/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 20:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Like an Experimental Concentration Camp’: Whistleblower Complaint Alleges Mass Hysterectomies at ICE Detention Center</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/like-an-experimental-concentration-camp-whistleblower-complaint-alleges-mass-hysterectomies-at-ice-detention-center/</link>
      <description>Several legal advocacy groups on Monday filed a whistleblower complaint on behalf of a nurse at an Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) detention center documenting "jarring medical neglect" within the facility, including a refusal to test detainees for the novel coronavirus and an exorbitant rate of hysterectomies being performed on immigrant women.</description>
      <author> (Jerry LambeSep 14th, 2020, 12:58 pm)</author>
      <guid>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/like-an-experimental-concentration-camp-whistleblower-complaint-alleges-mass-hysterectomies-at-ice-detention-center/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 20:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core Configuration – Securing Sensitive Data Locally - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/aspnet-configuration-securing-sensitive-data/</link>
      <description>We've come to the most important part of this series - securing sensitive data when working with the configuration in ASP.NET Core</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/aspnet-configuration-securing-sensitive-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 19:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shawn Wildermuth's Blog</title>
      <link>http://wildermuth.com/2020/09/13/Hosting-Vue-in-ASP-NET-Core-A-Different-Take</link>
      <description>Hosting Vue in ASP.NET Core: A Different Take - Shawn Wildermuth</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://wildermuth.com/2020/09/13/Hosting-Vue-in-ASP-NET-Core-A-Different-Take</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 19:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL - Fiyaz Hasan</title>
      <link>https://fiyazhasan.me/tag/graphql/</link>
      <description>We have N + 1 problem in our solution. To overcome this problem, we introduce DataLoader. DataLoader adds support for batching and caching in your GraphQL queries.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fiyazhasan.me/tag/graphql/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 19:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Entity Framework Core (EFCore) 5.0 RC1 | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-entity-framework-core-efcore-5-0-rc1/</link>
      <description>Announcing Entity Framework EFCore 5.0 RC1, a "go-live" supported release. This release includes new features such as many-to-many.</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/cdaJeremyLikness)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-entity-framework-core-efcore-5-0-rc1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 19:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Windows Terminal with WinUI</title>
      <link>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2020/09/08/building-windows-terminal-with-winui/</link>
      <description>WinUI and Windows Terminal have a strong relationship that goes back to the origins of Windows Terminal. This blog post goes into the history and architecture of how these two technologies came together.
History
The history of </description>
      <author> (Windows Developer Blog)</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2020/09/08/building-windows-terminal-with-winui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 18:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing .NET 5.0 RC 1 | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-net-5-0-rc-1/</link>
      <description>Today, we are shipping .NET 5.0 Release Candidate 1 (RC1). It is a near-final release of .NET 5.0, and the first of two RCs before the official release in November. RC1 is a “go live” release; you are supported using it in production.</description>
      <author> (Richard Lander Program Manager, .NET Team Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-net-5-0-rc-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 18:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hints of life on Venus</title>
      <link>https://ras.ac.uk/news-and-press/news/hints-life-venus</link>
      <description>An international team of astronomers, led by Professor Jane Greaves of Cardiff University, today announced the discovery of a rare molecule – phosphine –
in the ...</description>
      <author> (Submitted by  Press Press  on Mon, 14/09/2020 - 16:00)</author>
      <guid>https://ras.ac.uk/news-and-press/news/hints-life-venus</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 18:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core updates in .NET 5 Release Candidate 1 | ASP.NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/asp-net-core-updates-in-net-5-release-candidate-1/</link>
      <description>.NET 5 Release Candidate 1 (RC1) is now available and is ready for evaluation. Here’s what’s new in this release: Blazor WebAssembly performance improvements Blazor component virtualization Blazor WebAssembly prerendering Browser compatibility analyzer for Blazor WebAssembly Blazor JavaScript isolation and object references Blazor file input support Custom validation class attributes in Blazor Blazor support for ontoggle event Model binding DateTime as UTC Control Startup class activation Open API Specification (Swagger) on-by-default in ASP.NET Core API projects Better F5 Experience for ASP.NET Core API Projects SignalR parallel hub invocations Added Messagepack support in SignalR Java client Kestrel endpoint-specific options via configuration See the .NET 5 release notes for additional details and known issues.</description>
      <author> (Daniel Roth)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/asp-net-core-updates-in-net-5-release-candidate-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 18:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phosphine Detected In The Atmosphere of Venus - An Indicator of Possible Life?</title>
      <link>http://nasawatch.com/archives/2020/09/phosphine-detec.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://nasawatch.com/archives/2020/09/phosphine-detec.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 17:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Vim It! Learning Vim For Fun and Profit</title>
      <link>https://exceptionnotfound.net/learning-vim-for-fun-and-profit/</link>
      <description>Have you ever pressed Esc or Alt + F4 to close this weird text editor? Have you ever Googled how to exit Vim? Let's see why you should learn Vim and how to start using it!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://exceptionnotfound.net/learning-vim-for-fun-and-profit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 17:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life, part 35</title>
      <link>https://ericlippert.com/2020/09/14/life-part-35/</link>
      <description>Last time we implemented what looked like Gosper’s algorithm and got a disappointing result; though the quadtree data structure is elegant and the recursive algorithm is simple, and even thou…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ericlippert.com/2020/09/14/life-part-35/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 17:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"await Task.WhenAll" Shows One Exception - Here's How to See Them All</title>
      <link>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2020/09/await-taskwhenall-shows-one-exception.html</link>
      <description>   When we use "await" in C#, we can use the typical try/catch blocks that we're   used to. That's a great thing, and it makes asynchronous ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2020/09/await-taskwhenall-shows-one-exception.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWC9: Microsoft Ignite, Surface Duo Release, WSL2 Updates, Xbox Series S and more</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/This+Week+On+Channel+9/TWC9-Microsoft-Ignite-Surface-Duo-Release-WSL2-Updates-Xbox-Series-S-and-more</link>
      <description>We had some technical difficulties this week with, well everything. So apologies for the quality of this production. But Christina is still back with the latest developer news, including:   [00:34] Mi</description>
      <author> (by Christina Warren)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/This+Week+On+Channel+9/TWC9-Microsoft-Ignite-Surface-Duo-Release-WSL2-Updates-Xbox-Series-S-and-more</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running a .NET Core application in Kubernetes - high level walk-through</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=moMK6iPAIRA</link>
      <description>As I've been messing around with Kubernetes lately, thought it would be interesting to do a high level walk-through of running a .NET Core application in it.

It's far from a tutorial, but more for the folks that keep hearing about Kubernetes but are still a bit confused about what it does and how it may impact their daily work.

GitHub repository: https://github.com/joaofbantunes/HangfireSample

Feel free to leave feedback here or hit me up on:
- https://twitter.com/joaofbantunes
- https://blog.codingmilitia.com
- https://dev.to/joaofbantunes</description>
      <author> (Coding Militia)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=moMK6iPAIRA</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevChatter - Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/videos/739277648</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/videos/739277648</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>219: Move over float, it is time for Half</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/219</link>
      <description>Is it possible for us to talk about a new floating point time in .NET for 30 minutes and make it super fun? Find out!</description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/219</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lazy load assemblies in a Blazor WebAssembly application - Gérald Barré</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/lazy-load-assemblies-in-a-blazor-webassembly-application.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to lazy load assemblies in a ASP.NET Core Blazor WebAssembly application.</description>
      <author> (Gérald Barré)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/lazy-load-assemblies-in-a-blazor-webassembly-application.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Tries to Charge as Much as a New MacBook Pro for a Screen Replacement</title>
      <link>https://luketully.ca/macbook-screen-replacement-costs-as-much-as-a-brand-new-model/</link>
      <description>Apple quoted the same price for a screen replacement on two models of MacBook Pro as brand new models. and used heavy-handed sales tactics to push them.</description>
      <author> (Luke Tully)</author>
      <guid>https://luketully.ca/macbook-screen-replacement-costs-as-much-as-a-brand-new-model/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>  The Morning Brew #3068</title>
      <link>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/2020/09/14/the-morning-brew-3068/</link>
      <description>A daily link blog covering all aspects of the Microsoft Development World, published every working week day</description>
      <author> (Chris Alcock)</author>
      <guid>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/2020/09/14/the-morning-brew-3068/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Svitla Smart Talk: Most Common Mistakes in Using Tasks and in Asynchronous Code</title>
      <link>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233838-svitla-smart-talk-most-common-mistakes-in-using-tasks-and-in-asynchronous-code</link>
      <description>Jiří Činčura is an independent developer focusing on data and business layers, language constructs, parallelism and databases. Specifically Entity Framework, asynchronous and parallel programming, cloud and Azure. He's Microsoft Most Valuable Professional and you can read his articles, guides, tips and tricks at www.tabsoverspaces.com.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233838-svitla-smart-talk-most-common-mistakes-in-using-tasks-and-in-asynchronous-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Niek/Niek</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Niek/Niek/blob/master/facebook-scam/README.md</link>
      <description>My GitHub profile. Contribute to Niek/Niek development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (Niek)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Niek/Niek/blob/master/facebook-scam/README.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DotFest 2020: Using Roslyn to improve your codebase</title>
      <link>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233839-dotfest-2020-using-roslyn-to-improve-your-codebase</link>
      <description>13 Sep 2020
	
	 1 mins
	
	 Presentations &amp; Speaking</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233839-dotfest-2020-using-roslyn-to-improve-your-codebase</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dew Drop – September 14, 2020 (#3274)</title>
      <link>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/2020/09/14/dew-drop-september-14-2020-3274/</link>
      <description>About Me</description>
      <author> (Alvin A.)</author>
      <guid>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/2020/09/14/dew-drop-september-14-2020-3274/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2020-09-14</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/09/app-developer-links-2020-09-14/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/09/app-developer-links-2020-09-14/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevChatter - Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/videos/739277649</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/videos/739277649</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Chicago’s Taxis data with RavenDB</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/191873-C/analyzing-chicagos-taxis-data-with-ravendb?Key=2b1f4dc9-697e-4256-878d-ea8df7ab3910</link>
      <description>Chicago publishes its taxi’s trips in an easy to consume format, so I decided to see what kind of information I can dig out of the data using RavenDB. Here i...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/191873-C/analyzing-chicagos-taxis-data-with-ravendb?Key=2b1f4dc9-697e-4256-878d-ea8df7ab3910</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create an Application with Web Template Studio</title>
      <link>https://elanderson.net/2020/09/create-an-application-with-web-template-studio/</link>
      <description>Creating new applications is something I do a fair amount of. Most of the time they are throwaway projects used to test something out or demo projects used for this blog. With all the project creat…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://elanderson.net/2020/09/create-an-application-with-web-template-studio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's CO2 Emissions Have Fallen to Levels Last Seen in 1890</title>
      <link>https://e360.yale.edu/digest/britains-co2-emissions-have-fallen-to-levels-last-seen-in-1890</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (By  Glenn Hurowitz)</author>
      <guid>https://e360.yale.edu/digest/britains-co2-emissions-have-fallen-to-levels-last-seen-in-1890</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Kubernetes Programming?</title>
      <link>https://www.codingblocks.net/podcast/is-kubernetes-programming/</link>
      <description>We gather around the water cooler to discuss some random topics, while Joe sends too many calendar invites, Allen interferes with science, and Michael was totally duped.</description>
      <author> (About Michael Outlaw)</author>
      <guid>https://www.codingblocks.net/podcast/is-kubernetes-programming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevChatter - Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/videos/739093864</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/videos/739093864</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's up with error C4838: a WinRT type cannot be a member of a union, and how can I work around it? | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20200914-00/?p=104218</link>
      <description>If you try to put a Windows Runtime type inside a std::optional from C++/CX, you get this error: std::optional&lt;::Windows::Foundation::Rect&gt; optRect;  error C2848: 'std::_Optional_destruct_base&lt;_Ty,true&gt;::Value': A WinRT type cannot be a member of a union  Why can’t a WinRT type be a member of a union?</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20200914-00/?p=104218</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 15:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's so hard about PDF text extraction?  ​</title>
      <link>https://filingdb.com/b/pdf-text-extraction</link>
      <description>There is a common view that extracting text from a PDF document should not be too difficult. After all, the text is right there in front of our eyes and humans consume PDF content all the time with great success. Why would it be difficult to automatically extract the text data? Turn</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://filingdb.com/b/pdf-text-extraction</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 12:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>