<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - pwr-Solaar/Solaar: Linux device manager for Logitech devices</title>
      <link>https://github.com/pwr-Solaar/Solaar</link>
      <description>Linux device manager for Logitech devices. Contribute to pwr-Solaar/Solaar development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/pwr-Solaar/Solaar</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 03:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go&amp;#39;s Weird Little Iterators &amp;#183; mcyoung</title>
      <link>https://mcyoung.xyz/2024/12/16/rangefuncs/</link>
      <description>A second post on Go silliness (Miguel, aren’t you a C++ programmer?): in 1.23, Go finally added custom iterators. Now, back when I was at Google and involved in the Go compiler as “the annoying Rust guy who gets lunch with us”, there were proposals suggesting adding something like this, implemented as either an interface or a func:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mcyoung.xyz/2024/12/16/rangefuncs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failing Randomly: Linux Seccomp and Kernel Hacking</title>
      <link>https://mejedi.dev/posts/failing-randomly-linux-seccomp/</link>
      <description>Seccomp filters system calls with cBPF code. One can blacklist certain system call numbers or even make a decision based on call arguments. Both Docker and Chromium use seccomp to protect host from malicious or misbehaving programs.
With seccomp we can make a syscall fail consistently. We can’t make a syscall fail with a certain probability though. How hard could it be to extend seccomp for a complete kernel newbie?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mejedi.dev/posts/failing-randomly-linux-seccomp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neovim: Tips and tricks for OCaml&amp;#39;s LSP server</title>
      <link>https://moritzhamann.com/blog/2024-12-18-ocamllsp-in-neovim.html</link>
      <description>How to ensure ocamllsp uses up to date build information</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://moritzhamann.com/blog/2024-12-18-ocamllsp-in-neovim.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new era of aerial combat. – Tochnyi.info</title>
      <link>https://tochnyi.info/2024/11/fpv-interceptors-2024/</link>
      <description>In a first for modern warfare, the Ukrainian Defense Forces have been using FPV drones to intercept Russian surveillance drones and other UAVs. In recent months, a variety of published sources have included video evidence showing the considerable success Ukraine has had in doing so. This article examines aggregated open-source data on interceptions of Russian “fixed-wing” drones.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tochnyi.info/2024/11/fpv-interceptors-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient German Language Learning: Is Anki the Answer?</title>
      <link>https://www.argpar.se/posts/misc/efficient-german-language-learning-is-anki-the-answer</link>
      <description>My quest to master German vocabulary. Follow me on how I&amp;#39;m leveraging Anki to overcome years of procrastination.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/jonathan.sundqvist)</author>
      <guid>https://www.argpar.se/posts/misc/efficient-german-language-learning-is-anki-the-answer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on ray casting | nielssp.dk</title>
      <link>https://nielssp.dk/2024/11/notes-on-raycasting</link>
      <description>The website and blog of a 31 year old software developer</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nielssp.dk/2024/11/notes-on-raycasting</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make LLMs Shut Up</title>
      <link>https://www.greptile.com/blog/make-llms-shut-up</link>
      <description>Everything that went wrong trying to make our LLMs say less.</description>
      <author> (Daksh Gupta)</author>
      <guid>https://www.greptile.com/blog/make-llms-shut-up</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, You can’t bet on everything (and that’s okay)</title>
      <link>https://rnikhil.com/2024/12/18/prediction-market-crypto</link>
      <description>Prediction markets, despite their theoretical promise and success in sports ($330B US betting volume) and elections ($40B in 2024), are unlikely to become mainstream for all future events due to fundamental demand and liquidity constraints. The core issue isn’t regulation or technology - it’s that none of the three key market participants find prediction markets appealing: gamblers want quick resolutions (42% of 2020 election volume traded in final week), long-term investors prefer growing wealth in traditional assets, and market makers can’t operate without consistent retail flow (there is no demand for betting on topics except elections and sports).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rnikhil.com/2024/12/18/prediction-market-crypto</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lies, damned lies, and Impact Hero (refoorest, allcolibri)</title>
      <link>https://palant.info/2024/10/01/lies-damned-lies-and-impact-hero-refoorest-allcolibri/</link>
      <description>I found 17 extensions using the Impact Hero SDK in Chrome Web Store. These mislead users about their functionality, enable it without real consent, then lie about its ecological impact. And there is more shady stuff going on.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://palant.info/2024/10/01/lies-damned-lies-and-impact-hero-refoorest-allcolibri/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing the World Through Your Field</title>
      <link>https://www.sebastianmellen.com/post/2024/seeing-the-world-through-your-field/</link>
      <description>Something funny happens if you work in a particular field long enough, which is that you start to see everything that happens through the lens of the field you work in.
For example, my current company (Cerebrum) operates in the background screening space. So I’ve started to see everything through the lens of background checks.
 Economic news is about companies, and news about companies is really news about the people in those companies, which is really news about who those people are hiring, which is really news about the background screening industry.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sebastianmellen.com/post/2024/seeing-the-world-through-your-field/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Made My SIMD Code 1700x Faster Without Writing Any Intrinsics</title>
      <link>https://bhavana.io/bridging-the-cpu-gpu-divide-experimenting-with-ispc-and-compute-shaders/</link>
      <description>Background

This is the story of a project to add an efficient CPU backend for a shader language that is meant to compile down to GPU programs. Allow me to set the scene with a few prerequisite pieces of technology to become acquainted with:


The Forge Framework

The Forge is</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bhavana.io/bridging-the-cpu-gpu-divide-experimenting-with-ispc-and-compute-shaders/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How concurrecy works: A visual guide</title>
      <link>https://wyounas.github.io/concurrency/2024/12/12/how-concurrency-works-a-visual-guide/</link>
      <description>Welcome to Waqas&amp;#39; blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wyounas.github.io/concurrency/2024/12/12/how-concurrency-works-a-visual-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another List of Random Opinions on Writing Readable Code and Other Rants | Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.lucavall.in/blog/yet-another-list-of-random-opinions-on-writing-readable-code-and-other-rants</link>
      <description>After more than a decade of writing software, I&amp;#39;ve read lots of opinions on how to write good software. Everyone loves to throw around rules and principles, so I&amp;#39;ll do it too.</description>
      <author> (Luca Cavallin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.lucavall.in/blog/yet-another-list-of-random-opinions-on-writing-readable-code-and-other-rants</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building blogmate.io: Recursive Phoenix Components</title>
      <link>https://davidbishai.com/elixir/phoenix/2024/12/14/recursive-phoenix-components.html</link>
      <description>This post is part of a series on building blogmate.io, a rich comment system for static blogs and sites. If you have a static blog, or are thinking of starting one, please go check it out and spread the word!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidbishai.com/elixir/phoenix/2024/12/14/recursive-phoenix-components.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penny Game Debrief</title>
      <link>https://zarar.dev/penny-game-debrief/</link>
      <description>

This is a debrief of the popular  which demonstrates flow. The questions a facilitator can ask during a debrief are varied. Some examples are below:




...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zarar.dev/penny-game-debrief/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Ruby’s JSON, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://byroot.github.io/ruby/json/2024/12/18/optimizing-ruby-json-part-2.html</link>
      <description>In the previous post, I covered my motivations for improving ruby/json’s performance, and detailed the first 4 notable optimizations applied to speed up JSON generation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://byroot.github.io/ruby/json/2024/12/18/optimizing-ruby-json-part-2.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building A Simple Filesystem Backed Cache With Golang</title>
      <link>https://mzfit.app/blog/2024/12/07/building_a_filesystem_backed_cache_with_golang/</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t write software that&amp;#39;s too gross</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mzfit.app/blog/2024/12/07/building_a_filesystem_backed_cache_with_golang/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1-800-ChatGPT - Calling and Messaging ChatGPT with your phone | OpenAI Help Center</title>
      <link>https://help.openai.com/en/articles/10193193-1-800-chatgpt-calling-and-messaging-chatgpt-with-your-phone</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://help.openai.com/en/articles/10193193-1-800-chatgpt-calling-and-messaging-chatgpt-with-your-phone</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything we shipped in 2024</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/everything-we-shipped-in-2024/</link>
      <description>Pixel-Perfect Multi-Platform Applications with C# and WinUI for Windows, WebAssembly, iOS, macOS, Android and Linux</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/everything-we-shipped-in-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing a free GitHub Copilot for VS Code</title>
      <link>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/12/18/free-github-copilot</link>
      <description>Announcing a free plan for GitHub Copilot in Visual Studio Code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/12/18/free-github-copilot</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s new for the Microsoft Fluent UI Blazor library 4.11</title>
      <link>https://baaijte.net/blog/microsoft-fluentui-aspnetcore.components-4.11/</link>
      <description>Just before the end of year holiday period, we are bringing you a new version. Before you start upgrading, please go through the post here and the notes on the site first because we had to make some breaking changes. Read on to learn more...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://baaijte.net/blog/microsoft-fluentui-aspnetcore.components-4.11/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wiki - SurveyOfSystemLanguages2024</title>
      <link>https://wiki.alopex.li/SurveyOfSystemLanguages2024</link>
      <description>In case you missed it, there’s a whole new generation of low-level
programming languages being created right now. Rust demonstrated vividly
in 2016 that there is a massive unmet need in this space, and it has
spawned a bunch of successor languages, though none of them have really
hit the relative big-time like Rust has. I’m one of those programmers
that has spent 20 years or so asking “can we PLEASE do low-level code in
anything besides C and C++?” so I wanted to take an actual look at the
languages I know about and do a bit of compare-and-contrast.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wiki.alopex.li/SurveyOfSystemLanguages2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Devin AI</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=o7Jl1IFsnKI</link>
      <description>In this edition of #tech on ice, I talk about the new #ai agent Devin, and if we are seeing a shift in how we are going to leverage #llm to be more productive developer teams.
#technology #developer #programming #coldplunge</description>
      <author> (Isaac Levin)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=o7Jl1IFsnKI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build AI Agents in Minutes with AutoGen Studio | Complete Guide and Live Demo</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5bI7TRcObMY</link>
      <description>Get a subscription and improve your career: https://courses.devs.school

Unlock the power of AutoGen Studio to create intelligent agents and workflows effortlessly! In this video, I guide you step-by-step through this revolutionary tool powered by Azure OpenAI, designed to streamline the development of AI-driven automation and multi-agent systems.

In this video, you will learn:

What AutoGen Studio is and how it works.

How to configure AI agents with custom skills.

How to define complex workflows and multi-agent conversations.

Practical demos: Generating images, PDF documents, PowerPoint slides, and more.

If you are a developer, AI enthusiast, or looking to streamline AI-driven projects, AutoGen Studio is the tool you need to explore. Empower your creativity and productivity with this game-changing platform!

Links mentioned in the video:

Official Repository: https://github.com/microsoft/AutoGen

If you find this content helpful, don’t forget to like, subscribe, and hit the bell icon for more AI and tech tutorials!</description>
      <author> (Devs School)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5bI7TRcObMY</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Translations, C#, and Web Dev</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=20xM8qy3Na4</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Fritz is working on an open source application that YOU can get the source code to and follow along.  Check out SharpSite https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/SharpSite</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=20xM8qy3Na4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Sort</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3026/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3026/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Ambient Context Pattern in .NET: From Theory to Production</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/understanding-ambient-context-pattern-net/</link>
      <description>Introduction

In our previous exploration of execution context in .NET Core, we delved into the intricacies of AsyncLocal and ThreadLocal.

Execution Context Management with AsyncLocal and ThreadLocal in .NET CoreIntroduction In modern distributed .NET applications, managing context across execution boundaries is a critical architectural concern. While both AsyncLocal&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; and</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/understanding-ambient-context-pattern-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone gets bidirectional BFS wrong</title>
      <link>https://zdimension.fr/everyone-gets-bidirectional-bfs-wrong/</link>
      <description>People really need to stop blindly copying code from the Internet.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://zdimension.fr/everyone-gets-bidirectional-bfs-wrong/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 10:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>