<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How does a .NET profiler work?</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/gabbersepp/how-does-a-net-profiler-work-49e5</link>
      <description>Before doing cool stuff with your .NET profiler, we should understand a few principles</description>
      <author> (Josef Biehler)</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/gabbersepp/how-does-a-net-profiler-work-49e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 20:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How assembly language loops work</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZYJIakkcLYw</link>
      <description>More 6502: https://eater.net/6502

Support these videos on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/beneater or https://eater.net/support for other ways to support.

------------------

Social media:
Website: https://www.eater.net
Twitter: https://twitter.com/ben_eater
Patreon: https://patreon.com/beneater
Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/beneater

Special thanks to these supporters for making this video possible:
Adam Lininger, Adrien Friggeri, Alexander Wendland, Anson VanDoren, Anthony Cuccia, Armin Brauns, Ben Dyson, Ben Kamens, Ben Williams, Bill Cooksey, Bouke Groenescheij, Bradley Pirtle, Bryan Brickman, Carlos Ambrozak, Charles Haseltine, Christopher Blackmon, Clayton Parker Coleman, Cole Johnson, Daniel Jeppsson, Daniel Tang, Dave Walter, David Boardman, David Brown, David Clark, David H. Friedman, David House, David Sastre Medina, David Turnbull, David Turner, Dean Winger, Dmitry Guyvoronsky, Dušan Dželebdžić, Dzevad Trumic, Emilio Mendoza Palafox, Eric Brummer, Eric Busalacchi, Eric Dynowski, Eric Twilegar, Erik Broeders, Eugene Bulkin, fxshlein, George Miroshnykov, Harry McDow, HaykH, Hidde de Jong, Ian Tait, Ingo Eble, Ivan Sorokin, Jason DeStefano, Jason Specland, JavaXP, Jay Binks, Jayne Gabriele, Jeremy A., Jeremy Wise, Joe Pregracke, Joel Jakobsson, Joel Messerli, Joel Miller, Johannes Lundberg, John Fenwick, John Meade, Jon Dugan, Jordan Scales, Joshua King, Kefen, Kenneth Christensen, Kent Collins, Koreo, Lambda GPU Workstations, London Dobbs, Lucas Nestor, Lukasz Pacholik, Maksym Zavershynskyi, Marcel Wiget, Marcus Classon, Martin Roth, Mats Fredriksson, Matt Alexander, Matteo Mohr, Matthäus Pawelczyk, Michael, Michael Burke, Michael Garland, Michael Tedder, Michael Timbrook, Miguel Ríos, Nicholas Counts, Nicholas Moresco, Örn Arnarson, Örper Forilan, Paul Pluzhnikov, Paul Randal, Pete Dietl, Philip Hofstetter, Randy True, Ric King, Richard Wells, Rob Bruno, Robert Butler, Robert Diaz, Sachin Chitale, sam raza, Sam Rose, Scott, Sergey Ten, SonOfSofaman , Stefan Nesinger, Stefanus Du Toit, Stephen Riley, Stephen Smithstone, Steve  Jones, Steve Gorman, Steven Pequeno, TheWebMachine, Vladimir Kanazir, Warren Miller, xisente, Yusuke Saito</description>
      <author> (Ben Eater)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZYJIakkcLYw</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 19:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 20.04 LTS’ snap obsession has snapped me off of it</title>
      <link>https://jatan.blog/2020/05/02/ubuntu-snap-obsession-has-snapped-me-off-of-it/</link>
      <description>Once lauded for its sane defaults, the latest Ubuntu release has usability issues.</description>
      <author> (Jatan Mehta)</author>
      <guid>https://jatan.blog/2020/05/02/ubuntu-snap-obsession-has-snapped-me-off-of-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 19:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How We Created a Realtime Patient Monitoring System With Go and Vue in 3 days</title>
      <link>https://kasvith.me/posts/how-we-created-a-realtime-patient-monitoring-system-with-go-and-vue/</link>
      <description>A Pandemic started In the last November in 2019, we heard about the first case of unknown deadly diseases from China. Now everyone knows it as Covid-19 Now it seems to change our lives forever. The virus is deadly and it is highly contagious. Still, we know very little about it. I truly hope we will find some cure soon.
 Corona Virus
  Covid-19 attacked Sri Lanka Due to the nature of the virus, it was very hard to stop it from spreading.</description>
      <author> (Kasun Vithanage)</author>
      <guid>https://kasvith.me/posts/how-we-created-a-realtime-patient-monitoring-system-with-go-and-vue/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 19:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awk in 20 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://ferd.ca/awk-in-20-minutes.html</link>
      <description>Awk is a tiny programming language and a command line tool. It's
particularly appropriate for log parsing on servers, mostly because Awk will
operate on files, usually structured in lines of human-readable text.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ferd.ca/awk-in-20-minutes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 17:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complexity Has to Live Somewhere</title>
      <link>https://ferd.ca/complexity-has-to-live-somewhere.html</link>
      <description>We try to get rid of the complexity, control it, and seek simplicity. I think framing things that way is misguided. Complexity has to live somewhere. Embrace it</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ferd.ca/complexity-has-to-live-somewhere.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 17:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing allocations using Span&lt;T&gt; and Memory&lt;T&gt;</title>
      <link>https://stebet.net/real-world-example-of-reducing-allocations-using-span-t-and-memory-t/</link>
      <description>I decided to look at the RabbitMQ .NET Client source code to make improvements. During that exploration I saw opportunities to reduce memory allocations.</description>
      <author> (Stefán Jökull Sigurðarson)</author>
      <guid>https://stebet.net/real-world-example-of-reducing-allocations-using-span-t-and-memory-t/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endorse COVIDSafe</title>
      <link>https://endorsecovidsafe.com/</link>
      <description>Together we can keep Australia safe</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://endorsecovidsafe.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 23:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Periods</title>
      <link>https://leeoniya.github.io/uPlot/demos/time-periods.html</link>
      <description>Hourly Users</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://leeoniya.github.io/uPlot/demos/time-periods.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>on the usability of editable software</title>
      <link>https://flak.tedunangst.com/post/on-the-usability-of-editable-software</link>
      <description>I’m aware of two occasions on which Knuth advised editing existing code, as opposed to simply using it. One mention is in this interview, advocating for “re-editable” code instead of the fashionable reusable code, although it doesn’t amount to much more than that statement. In Coders at Work he describes a system of working that’s basically patch and diff. He writes a program, the master version that works for him, and ships it out. People receive and it and then modify it with change files so it works for them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://flak.tedunangst.com/post/on-the-usability-of-editable-software</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatsby and Sanity - Part 4 (Live Stream)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oXho2r-cNvY</link>
      <description>Gatsby and Sanity.io are a great pair for creating JAMstack projects like blogs. In these videos, I am working to migrate my Gatsby blog from using markdown files to using the Headless CMS called Sanity.io. After starting this migration, I am loving Gatsby and Sanity.io

https://www.jamesqquick.com
https://www.jamesqquick.com/uses/ (hardware, software, etc.)
https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
https://www.learnbuildteach.com/

Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code!!
https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/

Build a Quiz App with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/

Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/jamesqquick</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oXho2r-cNvY</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Firefox service will generate unique email aliases to enter in online forms | ZDNet</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/new-firefox-service-will-generate-unique-email-aliases-to-enter-in-online-forms/</link>
      <description>Firefox Private Relay add-on to help users safeguard their email addresses from spammers.</description>
      <author> (https://twitter.com/campuscodi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.zdnet.com/article/new-firefox-service-will-generate-unique-email-aliases-to-enter-in-online-forms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 21:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open file links directly in Office desktop apps</title>
      <link>https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/office/open-file-links-directly-in-office-desktop-apps-fe241745-9e05-4142-9ba8-1bb1dc044773?ns=winword&amp;version=90&amp;syslcid=1033&amp;uilcid=1033&amp;appver=zwd900&amp;helpid=74835&amp;ui=en-us&amp;rs=en-us&amp;ad=us</link>
      <description>Some users prefer the Office web apps, others prefer the Office desktop apps. We've designed an experience where users get to tell us what they prefer, and then their links open in their preferred mode - either Office web apps or the Office desktop apps.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/office/open-file-links-directly-in-office-desktop-apps-fe241745-9e05-4142-9ba8-1bb1dc044773?ns=winword&amp;version=90&amp;syslcid=1033&amp;uilcid=1033&amp;appver=zwd900&amp;helpid=74835&amp;ui=en-us&amp;rs=en-us&amp;ad=us</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 21:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>