<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>PCB Business Cards Gone Wild [Keyboards, Computers, Drums!]</title>
      <link>https://www.techadjacent.io/p/extreme-pcb-business-cards-gone-wild</link>
      <description>With the proper skills and a–physically and metaphorically–fat wallet, you too can make and distribute your own ridiculously awesome business card</description>
      <guid>https://www.techadjacent.io/p/extreme-pcb-business-cards-gone-wild</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro for the Nintendo E-Reader</title>
      <link>https://mattgreer.dev/blog/balatro-for-the-nintendo-ereader/</link>
      <description>What if the best game of 2024 came out on an old, obscure and weird platform?</description>
      <guid>https://mattgreer.dev/blog/balatro-for-the-nintendo-ereader/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stuck Between 24 Rocks and an NP-hard Place</title>
      <link>https://jacksonslipock.bearblog.dev/stuck-between-24-rocks-and-an-np-hard-place/</link>
      <description>I became interested in the ) after my friend, who has incredible number sense, told me a story[^1] about how he dominated the game when he played it in eleme...</description>
      <guid>https://jacksonslipock.bearblog.dev/stuck-between-24-rocks-and-an-np-hard-place/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The long-term cost of short-term platforms</title>
      <link>https://www.jonoalderson.com/wordpress/the-long-term-cost-of-short-term-platforms/</link>
      <description>Most platforms get you online fast - but trap you later. Let's unpack the hidden cost of short-term convenience, and why flexibility matters.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/jono.alderson)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jonoalderson.com/wordpress/the-long-term-cost-of-short-term-platforms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pytorch Reshaping With None</title>
      <link>https://blog.detorch.xyz/post/2025-06-21-pytorch-reshaping-with-none.md</link>
      <description>Currently I am learning attention mechanism from Dive into Deep Learning book. In the book I see following implementation in masked softmax:</description>
      <guid>https://blog.detorch.xyz/post/2025-06-21-pytorch-reshaping-with-none.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trader Ladder: Why Edge Alone Won’t Make You Profitable</title>
      <link>https://www.fractiz.com/trading-performance-ladder/</link>
      <description>Discover why having a trading edge is just the beginning. This guide breaks down the Trader Profitability Ladder—from the bottom 90% to the top 1%—and reveals what skills, mindset shifts, and tools you need at each stage.</description>
      <guid>https://www.fractiz.com/trading-performance-ladder/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why doesn't OpenAI build GPT Search Console?</title>
      <link>https://robertdruska.com/blog/why-doesnt-openai-build-gpt-search-console/</link>
      <description>More and more people are using an LLM instead of a traditional search engine. As a result, website owners can observe that an increasing share of their website audience is coming from an LLM chat, most often chatgpt.com. These users are also very relevant - famously, 10% of new Vercel users come from ChatGPT.</description>
      <guid>https://robertdruska.com/blog/why-doesnt-openai-build-gpt-search-console/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Security Vulnerabilities and Attack Vectors | Forge Code</title>
      <link>https://forgecode.dev/blog/prevent-attacks-on-mcp/</link>
      <description>Found some concerning security patterns in MCP implementations. Here's what I've been seeing and why you should care.</description>
      <author> (https://github.com/tusharmath)</author>
      <guid>https://forgecode.dev/blog/prevent-attacks-on-mcp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 18:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triggers not executed following foreign key updates/deletes</title>
      <link>https://bugs.mysql.com/bug.php?id=11472</link>
      <description />
      <guid>https://bugs.mysql.com/bug.php?id=11472</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 17:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY Good AI News From Google Boss - Dev Leader Weekly 99</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/06/21/finally-good-ai-news-from-google-boss-dev-leader-weekly-99</link>
      <description>Welcome to another issue of Dev Leader Weekly! In this issue, I discuss my take on the interview between Sundar Pichai and Lex Fridman interview on AI.
</description>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/06/21/finally-good-ai-news-from-google-boss-dev-leader-weekly-99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 14:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AbsenceBench: Language Models Can't Tell What's Missing</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.11440</link>
      <description>Large language models (LLMs) are increasingly capable of processing long inputs and locating specific information within them, as evidenced by their performance on the Needle in a Haystack (NIAH) test. However, while models excel at recalling surprising information, they still struggle to identify clearly omitted information. We introduce AbsenceBench to assesses LLMs' capacity to detect missing information across three domains: numerical sequences, poetry, and GitHub pull requests. AbsenceBench asks models to identify which pieces of a document were deliberately removed, given access to both the original and edited contexts. Despite the apparent straightforwardness of these tasks, our experiments reveal that even state-of-the-art models like Claude-3.7-Sonnet achieve only 69.6% F1-score with a modest average context length of 5K tokens. Our analysis suggests this poor performance stems from a fundamental limitation: Transformer attention mechanisms cannot easily attend to "gaps" in documents since these absences don't correspond to any specific keys that can be attended to. Overall, our results and analysis provide a case study of the close proximity of tasks where models are already superhuman (NIAH) and tasks where models breakdown unexpectedly (AbsenceBench).</description>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.11440</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 13:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - nxtscape/nxtscape: Nxtscape is an open-source agentic browser.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/nxtscape/nxtscape</link>
      <description>Nxtscape is an open-source agentic browser. Contribute to nxtscape/nxtscape development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/nxtscape/nxtscape</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Recap - 2025-06-20</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/06/21/weekly-recap-20250620</link>
      <description>Check out this week from Dev Leader! Here's a list including articles and videos on software engineering, career development, and programming in C#!
</description>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/06/21/weekly-recap-20250620</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Letter to Samsung: End Forced Israeli-Founded Bloatware Installations in the WANA Region</title>
      <link>https://smex.org/open-letter-to-samsung-end-forced-israeli-app-installations-in-the-wana-region/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent months, we have received numerous reports from users across West Asia and North Africa (WANA) expressing alarm over…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid>https://smex.org/open-letter-to-samsung-end-forced-israeli-app-installations-in-the-wana-region/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harper: Free, Open Source Grammar Checker</title>
      <link>https://writewithharper.com/</link>
      <description>Harper checks your writing fast, without compromising your privacy.</description>
      <guid>https://writewithharper.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 08:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practices that set great software architects apart</title>
      <link>https://www.cerbos.dev/blog/best-practices-of-software-architecture</link>
      <description>Great software architects don’t just make technical decisions—they balance competing priorities, navigate messy org charts, and align engineering with business strategy. This post explores the habits and mindset that separate competent architects from truly impactful ones, and why those differences matter. Whether you're eyeing the role or already in it, these are the practices that move the needle.</description>
      <guid>https://www.cerbos.dev/blog/best-practices-of-software-architecture</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 06:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube’s new anti-adblock measures</title>
      <link>https://iter.ca/post/yt-adblock/</link>
      <description>How I wrote filter rules for YouTube</description>
      <guid>https://iter.ca/post/yt-adblock/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 05:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>