<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Is Elden Ring an existential risk to humanity?</title>
      <link>http://togelius.blogspot.com/2023/04/is-elden-ring-existential-risk-to.html</link>
      <description>The discussion about existential risk from superintelligent AI is back, seemingly awakened by the recent dramatic progress in large language...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://togelius.blogspot.com/2023/04/is-elden-ring-existential-risk-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting things done is overrated</title>
      <link>https://www.adamgrant.info/Being+a+Better+Human/Getting+things+done+is+overrated</link>
      <description>Getting things done is overrated - Adam Grant</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.adamgrant.info/Being+a+Better+Human/Getting+things+done+is+overrated</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a Data Visualization With No Coding Skills Using ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://nightingaledvs.com/data-visualization-using-chatgpt-to-code/</link>
      <description>An exercise in building a data visualization with ChatGPT writing—and debugging!—the code</description>
      <author> (Soonk Paik)</author>
      <guid>https://nightingaledvs.com/data-visualization-using-chatgpt-to-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Linus Tech Tips Got Hacked</title>
      <link>https://tomblake.me/projects/How-Linus-Tech-Tips-Got-Hacked</link>
      <description>Session Hijacking and deepfakes take down Linus Tech Tips</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tomblake.me/projects/How-Linus-Tech-Tips-Got-Hacked</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using TLA⁺ at Work</title>
      <link>https://ahelwer.ca/post/2023-04-05-checkpoint-coordination/</link>
      <description>Designing a snapshot coordination system</description>
      <author> (Andrew Helwer)</author>
      <guid>https://ahelwer.ca/post/2023-04-05-checkpoint-coordination/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outperforming Warren Buffet</title>
      <link>https://blog.satwikkansal.xyz/personal/outperforming-warren-buffet/</link>
      <description>It was my third year of university (2017), and one of my friends told me about how it’s possible to buy Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies from some app. He doubled his investments in the last couple of weeks and made his uncle invest some amount, who called him and thanked him for the recommendation. The spark was already kindled.   The infamous scene from the Bollywood movie Phir Hera Pheri.</description>
      <author> (Satwik Kansal)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.satwikkansal.xyz/personal/outperforming-warren-buffet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Expected Value of Artificial General Intelligence | Essays &amp;#183; Will Holley</title>
      <link>https://willholley.com/essays/agi-ev</link>
      <description>If you are intellectually honest, you should be taking the risk articulated in Eliezer Yudkowsky’s Time op-ed seriously. Should humanity collectively and indefinitely halt the development of AGI?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://willholley.com/essays/agi-ev</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildcard certificates are not always a security risk</title>
      <link>https://code.mendhak.com/use-wildcard-certificates-for-internal-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>Using wildcard certificates can be a security mitigation for internal websites and infrastructure.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code.mendhak.com/use-wildcard-certificates-for-internal-infrastructure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Pipelines as Code With Delta Live Tables</title>
      <link>https://www.fabianstadler.com/2023/04/data-pipelines-as-code-with-delta-live-tables.html</link>
      <description>In this blog post, I will explore how to create data pipelines as code with Delta Live Tables, the latest ETL framework from Databricks. By leveraging the power of Delta Live Tables, developers can create pipelines that are reliable, scalable, and easy to maintain.</description>
      <author> (Fabian Stadler)</author>
      <guid>https://www.fabianstadler.com/2023/04/data-pipelines-as-code-with-delta-live-tables.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Attempts and Failures, 2021 – 2023</title>
      <link>https://nathanleclaire.com/blog/2023/04/05/startup-attempts-and-failures-2021-2023/</link>
      <description>In 2021, I quit my job at Honeycomb to set out on my own and try to build a company. At first, I wasn’t sure the exact model I’d follow, and had a (perhaps too lofty) aspiration that maybe I’d have a hybrid model, doing a bit of consulting, a bit of real estate, and a bit of product/SaaS/4-hour-workweek livin’ the dream. And, of course, if I happened to hit on something big, I could go raise venture and pursue that.</description>
      <author> (Startup Attempts and Failures, 2021 – 2023)</author>
      <guid>https://nathanleclaire.com/blog/2023/04/05/startup-attempts-and-failures-2021-2023/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remaining Relevant Over Four Decades</title>
      <link>https://thecodist.com/how-i-stayed-relevant-over-four-decades/</link>
      <description>Four decades is a long time to be a programmer. I started in 1981 and retired in 2021. During that time, almost everything changed, and I had to change with it. While my situation may be different than starting today, much of what I learned over time can still be</description>
      <author> (Andrew Wulf
                
                    Mar 17, 2023
                        • 6 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://thecodist.com/how-i-stayed-relevant-over-four-decades/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim K&amp;#228;chele: Naming is everything</title>
      <link>https://blog.timkaechele.me/2023/04/05/naming-is-everything.html</link>
      <description>Naming things is important, not only when programming, but also in the real world.
How you name something shapes how you think about it, and by extension limits it.
A well known real world instance where you can experience the power of names first hand is law making.
Think about it, what sounds better:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.timkaechele.me/2023/04/05/naming-is-everything.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Real Money Gaming (RMG) in India</title>
      <link>https://rnikhil.com/2023/04/03/gaming-state-india.html</link>
      <description>The gaming industry in India has been growing exponentially in recent years, with many people joining the ranks of avid and serious players. India has now become one of the leading countries in the world in terms of gaming, and this is largely due to the large population, the availability of technology, and the increasing enthusiasm and accessibility of gaming platforms. With more and more people playing games, India has become a massive and vibrant gaming community, with people of all ages and backgrounds enjoying the many styles and genres of gaming. From console and PC gaming, to mobile and online gaming, there is something for everyone to enjoy in India’s gaming scene. This post mostly focusses on the real money gaming market, potential profit pool and if somebody is starting a RMG company in India - this document can serve as a preliminary primer in understanding the market.</description>
      <author> (Nikhil)</author>
      <guid>https://rnikhil.com/2023/04/03/gaming-state-india.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I think I’m not alone that Mastodon is giving me the ick</title>
      <link>https://andy-bell.co.uk/i-think-im-not-alone-that-mastodon-is-giving-me-the-ick/</link>
      <description>I first joined Mastodon in 2018 (even though my old profile says 2016?), so I’d say I’ve seen a lot of its evolution. I’m on my second private instance now and would definitely co…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andy-bell.co.uk/i-think-im-not-alone-that-mastodon-is-giving-me-the-ick/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The real &amp;quot;must have&amp;quot; tools for programmers</title>
      <link>https://jamesdunne.dev/posts/must-have-programming-tools/</link>
      <description>Forget programs. The most important productivity tool for programming is your mind. And the next best set of software development tools are ones that take care of you.
It isn’t about Git. Or Docker. Or testing frameworks. These are all useful tools. I use them daily. But they are not the most important software development tools.
Your wellbeing is, in fact, the most important factor in your ability to write good software.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jamesdunne.dev/posts/must-have-programming-tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Language Wars Are Over: ChatGPT Won</title>
      <link>https://bourgoin.dev/posts/programming-languages/</link>
      <description>Languages Don&amp;#39;t Matter Anymore</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bourgoin.dev/posts/programming-languages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>advice - Chad Nauseam Home</title>
      <link>https://chadnauseam.com/advice/writing-advice</link>
      <description>writing-advice - Chad Nauseam Home</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chadnauseam.com/advice/writing-advice</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What CTOs Say vs. What Their Developers Hear w/ DataStax&amp;#39;s Shankar Ramaswamy</title>
      <link>https://devinterrupted.substack.com/p/what-ctos-say-vs-what-their-developers</link>
      <description>From the archives: As we progress through Season 3, we thought it would be nice to look back at some of our best episodes that haven’t been posted to our Substack page. This episode was originally published on February 5th, 2022. Enjoy! Anyone who’s been in a rapidly scaling company with an ever-expanding engineering team knows that communication is never as simple as it seems.</description>
      <author> (Dev Interrupted)</author>
      <guid>https://devinterrupted.substack.com/p/what-ctos-say-vs-what-their-developers</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 20:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speeding up Queries by Pre-computation &amp;amp; Transformation</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=hQVisFBAQio</link>
      <description>Many applications are more read-intensive than write-intensive. Meaning your application performs more reads than writes. However, we often persist data that...</description>
      <author> (@arvilagomaa4887
            
          
        
        
        


        1 hour ago)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=hQVisFBAQio</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 17:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Developers - .NET Day 2023</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=3kffvMeDoGE</link>
      <description>Experience Cloud Computing in Full Force with .NET on Azure. See the full agenda: https://learn.microsoft.com/events/learn-events/azuredeveloper-dotnetday/As...</description>
      <author> (Interview Happy
  
  
  
    Interview Happy
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=3kffvMeDoGE</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 15:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s New in dotTrace</title>
      <link>https://jb.gg/0d23ij</link>
      <description>Recent release highlights include support for .NET Core and native memory profiling
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jb.gg/0d23ij</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 14:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TR04/23] Minimal API 7, WinUI 3, DotnetIsolator, Git-TFS, Frameworks Cloud – devdevdev.net</title>
      <link>https://devdevdev.net/tr04-23-minimal-api-7-winui-3-dotnetisolator-git-tfs-frameworks-cloud/</link>
      <description>Pour ce d&amp;#233;j&amp;#224; 18&amp;#232;me &amp;#233;pisode de notre podcast, j’ai le plaisir d’accueillir pour notre table ronde mensuelle par un, ni deux mais six Microsoft MVP. Autant vous le dire tout de suite, les sujets abord&amp;#233;s sont vari&amp;#233;s et couvrent de nombreuses technologies : du web avec les minimals API de .NET 7, du windows avec la pr&amp;#233;sentation de WinUI 3, du cloud avec des frameworks vous aidant &amp;#224; concevoir et d&amp;#233;velopper correctement vos environnements, de l’outillage avec la migration de TFVC &amp;#224; Git et de l’exp&amp;#233;rimental avec dotnetisolator, le dernier b&amp;#233;b&amp;#233; de Steve Sanderson pour ex&amp;#233;cuter du code compil&amp;#233; &amp;#224; la vol&amp;#233;e.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devdevdev.net/tr04-23-minimal-api-7-winui-3-dotnetisolator-git-tfs-frameworks-cloud/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 14:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I modify the contents of a boxed Windows Runtime value? - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230405-00/?p=108017</link>
      <description>Once it&amp;#39;s in the box, you can&amp;#39;t change it.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230405-00/?p=108017</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 14:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seinfeld - Next Wednesday issue</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=71nvWNAvZfs</link>
      <description>Copyright&amp;#169; Sony Pictures Entertainment.I DO NOT own any of the Copyrights, just a small clip that liked.-----------------------------------------------------...</description>
      <author> (TheSeinfeldScenes
  
  
  
    TheSeinfeldScenes
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=71nvWNAvZfs</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 13:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impersonation-as-a-Service: Characterizing the Emerging Criminal Infrastructure for User Impersonation at Scale</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2009.04344</link>
      <description>In this paper we provide evidence of an emerging criminal infrastructure
enabling impersonation attacks at scale. Impersonation-as-a-Service (ImpaaS)
allows attackers to systematically collect and enforce user profiles
(consisting of user credentials, cookies, device and behavioural fingerprints,
and other metadata) to circumvent risk-based authentication system and
effectively bypass multi-factor authentication mechanisms. We present the
ImpaaS model and evaluate its implementation by analysing the operation of a
large, invite-only, Russian ImpaaS platform providing user profiles for more
than $260&amp;#39;000$ Internet users worldwide. Our findings suggest that the ImpaaS
model is growing, and provides the mechanisms needed to systematically evade
authentication controls across multiple platforms, while providing attackers
with a reliable, up-to-date, and semi-automated environment enabling target
selection and user impersonation against Internet users as scale.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 9 Sep 2020 (v1), last revised 5 Nov 2020 (this version, v2)])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2009.04344</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 13:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Write Logs From Startup.cs/Program.cs in .NET - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/dotnet-how-to-write-logs-from-startup-program-classes/</link>
      <description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll learn how to write logs from the startup of .NET Core applications including the Program and Startup classes.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/dotnet-how-to-write-logs-from-startup-program-classes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Showcases Reliable Web App Patterns for Resilient Cloud Applications </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/04/reliable-web-app-pattern/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has shared the source code and the documentation for the Reliable Web App pattern, a set of best practices that help on-premise web application developers create secure, reliable and cost-optimised cloud applications in Azure with minimal changes.</description>
      <author> (Edin Kapić
                
            
            
        Lead Software EngineerFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/04/reliable-web-app-pattern/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source Generators and Regular Expressions</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/667db4f5-d34a-4625-bc3d-aa47187c591a</link>
      <description>Source Generators are more and more an integral part of the .NET ecosystem. But how does that play together with everyone&amp;#39;s favorite: Regular Expressions?
In this blog post we will dive in how we can leverage source generators in combination with regular expression to have a debuggable, but also very performant way of executing regular expressions!
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/667db4f5-d34a-4625-bc3d-aa47187c591a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing SPAs and Blazor Applications using the BFF (Backend for Frontend) Pattern</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DdNssiaIY_Q</link>
      <description>Modern web development means that more and more application code is running in the browser. Traditionally this has been JavaScript but more recently there ha...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DdNssiaIY_Q</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Build a React Admin Dashboard Sample App—Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/lets-build-react-admin-dashboard-sample-app-part-2</link>
      <description>In this two-part series, we’ll build an admin dashboard app using KendoReact. In this second part, we’ll add navigation breadcrumbs and some charts and graphs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/lets-build-react-admin-dashboard-sample-app-part-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 06:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An abstract example of refactoring from interaction-based to property-based testing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2023/04/03/an-abstract-example-of-refactoring-from-interaction-based-to-property-based-testing/</link>
      <description>A C# example with xUnit.net and CsCheck</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2023/04/03/an-abstract-example-of-refactoring-from-interaction-based-to-property-based-testing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 06:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning off Tracking for Find and FindAsync in Entity Framework | no dogma blog</title>
      <link>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2023/04/turning-off-tracking-for-find-and-findasync-in-entity-framework/</link>
      <description>Find/FindAsync is a popular way to retrieve a single entity using its primary key with Entity Framework, but by default Entity Framework tracks that entity for changes. This post shows how to turn off tracking for Find/FindAsync.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2023/04/turning-off-tracking-for-find-and-findasync-in-entity-framework/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 06:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facade Pattern: A Beginner’s How-To for Simplified Code - Dev Leader</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/03/31/facade-pattern-a-beginners-how-to-for-simplified-code/</link>
      <description>Facade design patterns are useful for hiding complexity and allowing code extensibility by moving dependencies behind an API. Read this C# article to see how!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa/)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/03/31/facade-pattern-a-beginners-how-to-for-simplified-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 06:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bliki: Slack</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/Slack.html</link>
      <description>a bliki entry for Slack</description>
      <author> (Martin Fowler)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/Slack.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 06:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating SVG Images with ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://praeclarum.org/2023/04/03/chatsvg.html</link>
      <description>TL;DR I used ChatGPT, with varying levels of success, to generate SVG images. With enough patience and prompting, you can get it to draw basic shapes and simple scenes about as well as a five year old can. (Which, hey, let’s face is, is good enough a lot of the time.)

</description>
      <author> (https://praeclarum.org/about/)</author>
      <guid>https://praeclarum.org/2023/04/03/chatsvg.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 06:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How SerenityOS declares ssize_t</title>
      <link>https://awesomekling.github.io/How-SerenityOS-declares-ssize_t/</link>
      <description>This post explores one of my favorite hacks in SerenityOS. I don’t recommend doing this in your codebase, but it has worked for us so far. :^)

</description>
      <author> (Andreas Kling)</author>
      <guid>https://awesomekling.github.io/How-SerenityOS-declares-ssize_t/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 06:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monorepos, fast maps, and more – Gleam</title>
      <link>https://gleam.run/news/v0.28-monorepos-fast-maps-and-more/</link>
      <description>The Gleam programming language</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gleam.run/news/v0.28-monorepos-fast-maps-and-more/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 05:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>