<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing the July 2020 e-commerce and marketing data breach -- A Message From Ledger’s Leadership | Ledger</title>
      <link>https://www.ledger.com/addressing-the-july-2020-e-commerce-and-marketing-data-breach</link>
      <description>What happened On the 14th of July 2020, a researcher participating in our bounty program made us aware of a potential data breach on the Ledger website. We immediately fixed this breach after receiving the researcher’s report and underwent an internal investigation. A week after patching the breach, we discovered It had been further exploited …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ledger.com/addressing-the-july-2020-e-commerce-and-marketing-data-breach</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 09:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full data set for the 2020 Developer Survey now available! - Stack Overflow Blog</title>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.blog/2020/07/27/public-data-release-of-stack-overflows-2020-developer-survey/</link>
      <description>We love to learn about what moves developers and technical workers. That’s why each year, we ask the tech community about their jobs, their tools, and their aspirations. We also love open source, so since 2011, we’ve made the raw data set available for you to explore! We’re happy to announce that this year’s raw…</description>
      <author> (Ben Popper    
    Director of Content)</author>
      <guid>https://stackoverflow.blog/2020/07/27/public-data-release-of-stack-overflows-2020-developer-survey/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 06:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three reasons to migrate your ASP.NET apps and SQL Server data to Azure</title>
      <link>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/three-reasons-to-migrate-your-aspnet-apps-and-sql-server-data-to-azure/</link>
      <description>The way we work and live has changed. Over the last several months, enterprises have had to shift their strategy from physical first to digital first and accelerate their digital transformation to enable remote productivity, reduce costs, or rapidly address new opportunities.</description>
      <author> (Naga Surendran
            Director, Product Marketing, Azure)</author>
      <guid>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/three-reasons-to-migrate-your-aspnet-apps-and-sql-server-data-to-azure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 06:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters Weekly 175 -  YARP!</title>
      <link>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/07/monsters-weekly/ep175/</link>
      <description>YARP, not to be confused with YARR which is what a pirate says, is a managed reverse proxy that provides some interesting functionality for ASP.NET Core applications or really any web application. In</description>
      <author> (The Monsters)</author>
      <guid>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/07/monsters-weekly/ep175/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 06:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problems and Solutions for Agility with Legacy Monolith Databases - Redgate Software</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/problems-and-solutions-for-agility-with-legacy-monolith-databases</link>
      <description>Large legacy databases with complex dependencies are daunting for those implementing DevOps. Learn why Redgate focused on solving this problem and which practices enable you to successfully include legacy monolith databases in your DevOps transformation.</description>
      <author> (Red Gate Software Ltd)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/problems-and-solutions-for-agility-with-legacy-monolith-databases</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 06:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pimp up your Blazor EditForms with Tailwind CSS!</title>
      <link>https://jonhilton.net/pimp-up-blazor-edit-forms-with-tailwind-css/</link>
      <description>EditForms are a unstyled by default, so it falls to you to make your forms pop!</description>
      <author> (Jon Hilton)</author>
      <guid>https://jonhilton.net/pimp-up-blazor-edit-forms-with-tailwind-css/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 06:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Write Object-Oriented TypeScript Well – .NET Tools Blog | JetBrains</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/07/28/write-object-oriented-typescript-well/</link>
      <description>TypeScript enables you to code using object-oriented principles and techniques, and Rider helps you write TypeScript more efficiently and easily. In this blog post, we’ll look at the object-oriented f</description>
      <author> (Rachel Appel)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/07/28/write-object-oriented-typescript-well/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 06:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>poteto/hiring-without-whiteboards</title>
      <link>https://github.com/poteto/hiring-without-whiteboards</link>
      <description>⭐️  Companies that don't have a broken hiring process - poteto/hiring-without-whiteboards</description>
      <author> (poteto)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/poteto/hiring-without-whiteboards</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 06:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shawn Wildermuth's Blog</title>
      <link>http://wildermuth.com/2020/07/27/The-Maintainers-Brad-Wilson-and-xUnit</link>
      <description>The Maintainers: Brad Wilson and xUnit - Shawn Wildermuth</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://wildermuth.com/2020/07/27/The-Maintainers-Brad-Wilson-and-xUnit</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 06:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dunzo suffers data breach, launches internal investigation</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewsminute.com/article/dunzo-suffers-data-breach-launches-internal-investigation-128415</link>
      <description>Hyperlocal delivery startup Dunzo has revealed that it has suffered a security breach that involved unauthorized access to one of its databases. The database that was compromised contained user phone numbers and email address information. Dunzo has said that it has launched an internal investigation into the same but hasn’t yet disclosed details on how many users’ data has been compromised.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.thenewsminute.com/article/dunzo-suffers-data-breach-launches-internal-investigation-128415</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 05:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>felixrieseberg/macintosh.js</title>
      <link>https://github.com/felixrieseberg/macintosh.js</link>
      <description>A virtual Apple Macintosh with System 8, running in Electron. I'm sorry. - felixrieseberg/macintosh.js</description>
      <author> (felixrieseberg)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/felixrieseberg/macintosh.js</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 04:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fireworks: Sugar Stars</title>
      <link>https://wybiral.github.io/fireworks/comps/sugar_stars.html</link>
      <description>Here's a collection of firework star recipes using common sugar
                (sucrose) as the fuel source. This approach is impractical for
                commercial pyrotechnics due to being so sensetive to moisture
                and heat. But for homemade fireworks it has several advantages.
                It doubles as a binder and is water soluble so there's no need
                for noxious solvents. It's also widely available and cheap.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wybiral.github.io/fireworks/comps/sugar_stars.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 03:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development Containers in Education with Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2020/07/27/containers-edu</link>
      <description>Development Containers in Education with Visual Studio Code</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2020/07/27/containers-edu</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 03:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview with a Pornhub Web Developer</title>
      <link>https://davidwalsh.name/pornhub-interview</link>
      <description>A chat with the PornHub development team, about working in the adult website industry, technology, virtual reality, and more.</description>
      <author> (David Walsh)</author>
      <guid>https://davidwalsh.name/pornhub-interview</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 02:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Developer Landing Page and Issues Repo - Windows Developer Blog</title>
      <link>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2020/07/28/new-developer-landing-page-and-issues-repo/</link>
      <description>We are excited to announce two new online resources for developers using Windows: A new docs landing-page for developers building and deploying apps and systems running on non-Microsoft operating systems like Linux and Android A new GitHub issues repo for filing developer-oriented issues with Windows Let’s dig into these two announcements: New Landing Page for …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2020/07/28/new-developer-landing-page-and-issues-repo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 02:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability doesn’t come after trust – it precedes it.</title>
      <link>https://davidneely.wordpress.com/2020/07/28/vulnerability-doesnt-come-after-trust-it-precedes-it/</link>
      <description>Brene Brown, a researcher from the University of Texas, became the “vulnerability expert” after she recorded a TED Talk  on The Power of Vulnerability 9 years ago in 2011. I remember th…</description>
      <author> (Author: David Neely)</author>
      <guid>https://davidneely.wordpress.com/2020/07/28/vulnerability-doesnt-come-after-trust-it-precedes-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 23:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conversations and Ideas</title>
      <link>https://harj.posthaven.com/conversations-and-ideas</link>
      <description>Conversations about ideas should help you understand what you think. They need more tension than a regular conversation but not so much that you're afraid to share nascent thoughts. The best...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://harj.posthaven.com/conversations-and-ideas</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 23:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2019 for Mac - Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/visualstudio/releasenotes/vs2019-mac-relnotes#--visual-studio-2019-for-mac-version-868-8682</link>
      <description>Get information on the latest release features, bug fixes, and support for Visual Studio 2019 for Mac. Download today.</description>
      <author> (sevoku)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/visualstudio/releasenotes/vs2019-mac-relnotes#--visual-studio-2019-for-mac-version-868-8682</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great CRO Tool or Privacy Nightmare – SystemTrap</title>
      <link>https://systemtrap.org/503</link>
      <description>The past few years have seen many different SaaS apps pop up and appeal to businesses. From CDPs to AI, to session replay, there have been many different advanced platforms marketers can add to their toolbelts. One of my personal favorite tools over the past few years has been FullStory. FullStory is a session replay web app that allows site owners to literally watch what a user does on their website – in full video. Previously martech folks were stuck with heat mapping software like Kissmetrics and HotJar – and even to a lesser extent Google Analytics. While these tools were certainly helpful in addressing which parts of a web page were clicked on or interacted with the most, they were static interpretations of the data.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://systemtrap.org/503</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trademarking Infocom, again, part one</title>
      <link>https://blog.zarfhome.com/2020/07/trademarking-infocom-again-part-one.html</link>
      <description>It must be a Monday -- someone has trademarked "Infocom"!  No, this doesn't happen every  Monday. But over the past twenty years, a surprisi...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.zarfhome.com/2020/07/trademarking-infocom-again-part-one.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increasing Battery Life on an Arch Linux Laptop (ThinkPad T14s) - Austin G. Walters</title>
      <link>https://austingwalters.com/increasing-battery-life-on-an-arch-linux-laptop-thinkpad-t14s/</link>
      <description>Configure and Arch Linux laptop to maximize battery performance while not reducing performance. In this case, we cover T14s and stretch battery life 2hrs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://austingwalters.com/increasing-battery-life-on-an-arch-linux-laptop-thinkpad-t14s/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack of all trades, master of none</title>
      <link>https://sketch.nono.ma/jack-of-all-trades-master-of-none</link>
      <description>Back in the Renaissance, having skill in many different areas was seen as a good thing. But things changed. Movements such as the industrial revolution…</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/nonoesp)</author>
      <guid>https://sketch.nono.ma/jack-of-all-trades-master-of-none</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alcohol delivery service Drizly hit by data breach – TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2020/07/28/drizly-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A well-known data seller on the dark web claims to be selling the site's stolen user data.</description>
      <author> (Zack Whittaker@zackwhittaker / 12:06 pm PDT•July 28, 2020comment Comment)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2020/07/28/drizly-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 22:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apparel - Unisex - .NET Foundation Store</title>
      <link>https://store.dotnetfoundation.org/dotnetfoundation/apparel-unisex</link>
      <description>Store Policies |
            Contact Us |
          Powered by Kotis Design</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://store.dotnetfoundation.org/dotnetfoundation/apparel-unisex</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 22:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox 79: The safe return of shared memory, new tooling, and platform updates – Mozilla Hacks - the Web developer blog</title>
      <link>https://hacks.mozilla.org/2020/07/firefox-79/</link>
      <description>Firefox 79 offers a new Promise method, more secure target=_blank links, logical assignment operators, tooling improvements for better JavaScript debugging, and many other updates of interest to web developers. In ...</description>
      <author> (https://developer.mozilla.org@floscholz)</author>
      <guid>https://hacks.mozilla.org/2020/07/firefox-79/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 21:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Toxoplasma Of Rage</title>
      <link>https://slatestarcodex.com/2014/12/17/the-toxoplasma-of-rage/</link>
      <description>I. Some old news I only just heard about: PETA is offering to pay the water bills for needy Detroit families if (and only if) those families agree to stop eating meat. Predictably, the move caused …</description>
      <author> (by Scott Alexander)</author>
      <guid>https://slatestarcodex.com/2014/12/17/the-toxoplasma-of-rage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 20:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>github/roadmap</title>
      <link>https://github.com/github/roadmap</link>
      <description>GitHub public roadmap. Contribute to github/roadmap development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (github)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/github/roadmap</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 20:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historical programming-language groups disappearing from Google</title>
      <link>https://lwn.net/Articles/827233/</link>
      <description>As Alex McDonald notes in this
support request, Google has recently banned the old Usenet groups
comp.lang.forth and comp.lang.lisp from the Google Groups system.
"Of specific concern is the archive. These are some of the oldest
groups on Usenet, and the depth &amp; breadth of the historical material that
has just disappeared from the internet, on two seminal programming
languages, is huge and highly damaging. These are the history and
collective memories of two communities that are being expunged, and it's
not great, since there is no other comprehensive archive after Google's
purchase of Dejanews around 20 years ago."
Perhaps Google can be convinced to restore the content, but it also seems
that some of this material could benefit from a more stable archive.</description>
      <author> ([Posted July 28, 2020 by corbet])</author>
      <guid>https://lwn.net/Articles/827233/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 20:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Program Manager II in Redmond, Washington, United States | Engineering at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/867619/Program-Manager-II</link>
      <description>Apply for Program Manager II job with Microsoft in Redmond, Washington, United States. Engineering at Microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/867619/Program-Manager-II</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 19:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>runlyio/core-dotnet</title>
      <link>https://github.com/runlyio/core-dotnet</link>
      <description>Multi-threaded batch processing and background jobs for .NET Core - runlyio/core-dotnet</description>
      <author> (runlyio)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/runlyio/core-dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 19:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing GitHub's OpenAPI Description - The GitHub Blog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/2020-07-27-introducing-githubs-openapi-description/</link>
      <description>The GitHub REST API has been through three major revisions since it was first released, only a month after the site was launched. We often receive feedback that our REST API is an inspiration to</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/2020-07-27-introducing-githubs-openapi-description/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 19:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WasmBoxC: Simple, Easy, and Fast VM-less Sandboxing</title>
      <link>https://kripken.github.io/blog/wasm/2020/07/27/wasmboxc.html</link>
      <description>The software ecosystem has a lot of useful but unsafe code, and the easier it is to sandbox that code, the moreoften that’ll happen. If it were as simple as ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kripken.github.io/blog/wasm/2020/07/27/wasmboxc.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 17:53:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>github/renaming</title>
      <link>https://github.com/github/renaming</link>
      <description>Guidance for changing the default branch name for GitHub repositories - github/renaming</description>
      <author> (github)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/github/renaming</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 17:24:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the GitHub public roadmap - The GitHub Blog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/2020-07-28-announcing-the-github-public-roadmap/</link>
      <description>The public roadmap is designed to give your team more information about what features and functionality you can expect from GitHub over the coming quarters.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/2020-07-28-announcing-the-github-public-roadmap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 17:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move C# 9 specs to sub-folder by jcouv · Pull Request #3731 · dotnet/csharplang</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/csharplang/pull/3731/files</link>
      <description>File renamed without changes.</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/csharplang/pull/3731/files</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 17:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expanding Beyond 64kb of Memory with Bank Switching (16-Bit VM in JavaScript 012)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=araYkE3KAms</link>
      <description>In this episode we're learning about memory bank switching - a technique common in the retro game console days - that allows us to address more memory than the limited address space that 16 bits provides!

=[ ℹ About ℹ ]=


This series is all about building a powerful virtual machine in JavaScript with the following features:

- A flexible, extensible, register-based virtual machine
- Support for signed, unsigned and floating point operations
- A call stack 
- Interrupt capabilities
- Ability to do memory mapping for IO
- An assembly language with macro and module support
- A higher level, C like language. We'll use and expand the library from the parser combinators from scratch series
- And finally, to be able to take the whole thing into the browser and extend it to create a sort of fantasy console - an emulator for a machine that never existed

- 💌 Updates to your inbox: https://tinyletter.com/lowleveljavascript
- ⭐️ Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/lowleveljavascript

- Series Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLP29wDx6QmW5DdwpdwHCRJsEubS5NrQ9b&amp;playnext=1&amp;index=1
- Github Repo: https://github.com/LowLevelJavaScript/16-Bit-Virtual-Machine


- Bank Switching: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bank_switching
- 16BitVM Episode 5: https://youtu.be/hLYGTpvoMgE


=[ 🔗 Links 🔗 ]=

- Playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLP29wDx6QmW5DdwpdwHCRJsEubS5NrQ9b&amp;playnext=1&amp;index=1
- Github Repo: https://github.com/LowLevelJavaScript/16-Bit-Virtual-Machine</description>
      <author> (Low Level JavaScript)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=araYkE3KAms</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 17:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating a 40TB SQL Server Database</title>
      <link>https://www.tarynpivots.com/post/migrating-40tb-sql-server-database/</link>
      <description>Initially, I wasn’t sure whether to write about this migration project, but when I randomly asked if people would be interested, the response was overwhelming. This was a long, kind of boring, very repetitive, and at times incredibly frustrating project, but I learned a lot, and maybe someone else will learn from this too. There may be far better ways to move this amount of data. In the path I went down, there was a huge amount of juggling that had to take place (I’ll explain that later).</description>
      <author> (Taryn)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tarynpivots.com/post/migrating-40tb-sql-server-database/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 16:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IEvangelist/Blazing.Twilio.Video</title>
      <link>https://github.com/IEvangelist/Blazing.Twilio.Video</link>
      <description>A Blazor WASM video chat app, built using the Twilio SDK for .NET and JavaScript. - IEvangelist/Blazing.Twilio.Video</description>
      <author> (IEvangelist)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/IEvangelist/Blazing.Twilio.Video</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 16:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting duplicate routes in ASP.NET Core: Visualizing ASP.NET Core 3.0 endpoints using GraphvizOnline - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/detecting-duplicate-routes-in-aspnetcore/</link>
      <description>In this post I show how you can use a unit test to identify duplicate routes that would fail at runtime</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/detecting-duplicate-routes-in-aspnetcore/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 15:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chessprogramming wiki</title>
      <link>https://www.chessprogramming.org/Main_Page</link>
      <description>The Chess Programming Wiki is a repository of information about programming computers to play chess. Our goal is to provide a reference for every aspect of chess-programming, information about programmers, researcher and engines. You'll find different ways to implement LMR and bitboard stuff like best magics for most dense magic bitboard tables. For didactic purposes the CPW-Engine has been developed by some wiki members.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.chessprogramming.org/Main_Page</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 15:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lazy Load Images with Vanilla JavaScript and Intersection Observer</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BmRZi4ryiMQ</link>
      <description>Website performance is crucial for user experience. If you leave the user looking at a blank screen for too long they will leave. In this video, learn how to lazy load images to improve your site performance and user experience. To do this, we'll use vanilla JavaScript and the Intersection Observer API.

Scrimba Frontend Developer Career Path - https://bit.ly/scrimbapath

_____________________________________________

Newsletter 🗞
Interested in exclusive content and discounts? 🤯 Sign up for the newsletter!
https://www.jamesqquick.com
_____________________________________________

Connect with me 😀
Live streams on Twitch - https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
Follow me on Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Join the 💬 Discord Server 💬 - https://discord.gg/vM2bagU
_____________________________________________

COURSES  💻
Learn how to build Fullstack apps with React and Serverless Functions - https://www.jamesqquick.com/courses/react-and-serverless-fullstack-developmnent
Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code - https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/
Build a Quiz App  - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BmRZi4ryiMQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 15:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fody/MethodDecorator</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Fody/MethodDecorator</link>
      <description>Compile time decorator pattern via IL rewriting. Contribute to Fody/MethodDecorator development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (Fody)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Fody/MethodDecorator</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 14:58:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polymorphic Encryption Algorithms — Generating Code Dynamically</title>
      <link>https://www.pelock.com/articles/polymorphic-encryption-algorithms</link>
      <description>Polymorphic encryption of code, an article presenting all the concepts and steps involved in creating a polymorphic engine in C++.</description>
      <author> (Bartosz Wójcik)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pelock.com/articles/polymorphic-encryption-algorithms</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 14:08:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ritterim/stuntman</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ritterim/stuntman</link>
      <description>Library for impersonating users during development leveraging ASP.NET Identity. - ritterim/stuntman</description>
      <author> (ritterim)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ritterim/stuntman</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 14:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some SQL Tricks of an Application DBA</title>
      <link>https://hakibenita.com/sql-tricks-application-dba</link>
      <description>Non-trivial tips for database development</description>
      <author> (Haki Benita)</author>
      <guid>https://hakibenita.com/sql-tricks-application-dba</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 14:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official Support for Remote Debugging a .NET Core Linux app in WSL2 from Visual Studio on Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/OfficialSupportForRemoteDebuggingANETCoreLinuxAppInWSL2FromVisualStudioOnWindows.aspx</link>
      <description>I've blogged before about Developing on Docker with the new and improved Visual Studio Container Tools (and WSL2) and ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/OfficialSupportForRemoteDebuggingANETCoreLinuxAppInWSL2FromVisualStudioOnWindows.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 13:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor DataGrid Demos - Overview | Telerik UI for Blazor</title>
      <link>https://demos.telerik.com/blazor-ui/grid/overview?utm_source=chrissainty&amp;utm_medium=cpm&amp;utm_campaign=blazor-grid-awareness-twitter</link>
      <description>Get familiar with the Telerik Blazor DataGrid demos and examples demonstrating multiple features such as paging, sorting, filtering, editing and many more.</description>
      <author> (Telerik)</author>
      <guid>https://demos.telerik.com/blazor-ui/grid/overview?utm_source=chrissainty&amp;utm_medium=cpm&amp;utm_campaign=blazor-grid-awareness-twitter</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 12:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why It's Easier to Manage 4 People Than It Is to Manage 1 Person · Stay SaaSy</title>
      <link>https://staysaasy.com/management/2020/07/24/Managing-One-Person.html</link>
      <description>It’s easier to manage 4 people than it is to manage one person. The primary reason for this is the inherent over-reliance in the relationship between a manager and a single report. Let’s dive deeper.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://staysaasy.com/management/2020/07/24/Managing-One-Person.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 12:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>