<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Can Duplicate Keys from the Sounds They Make in Locks</title>
      <link>https://kottke.org/20/08/researchers-can-duplicate-keys-from-the-sounds-they-make-in-locks</link>
      <description>Researchers have demonstrated that they can make a working 3D-printed copy of a key just by listening to how the key sounds when i</description>
      <author> (posted by Jason Kottke   Aug 18, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://kottke.org/20/08/researchers-can-duplicate-keys-from-the-sounds-they-make-in-locks</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 10:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Hunt</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/?hss_channel=tw-2925438791</link>
      <description>Hi, I'm Troy Hunt, I write this blog, run "Have I Been Pwned" and am a Microsoft Regional Director and MVP who travels the world speaking at events and training technology professionals</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/?hss_channel=tw-2925438791</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 09:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cloudflare worker to redirect image requests from dickhead content scraper's site to a Rick Roll</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/troyhunt/bc89905862398ce0d2984858a9f3a8b5</link>
      <description>A Cloudflare worker to redirect image requests from dickhead content scraper's site to a Rick Roll - rick-roll-content-scraper.js</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/troyhunt/bc89905862398ce0d2984858a9f3a8b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 08:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetric and Asymmetric Encryption in .NET Core</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2020/08/19/symmetric-and-asymmetric-encryption-in-net-core/</link>
      <description>This post looks at symmetric and asymmetric encryption and how this could be implemented in .NET Core. Symmetric encryption is fast and can encrypt or decrypt large amounts of text, streams or file…</description>
      <author> (damienbod)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2020/08/19/symmetric-and-asymmetric-encryption-in-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 08:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kowainik - Haskell mini-patterns handbook</title>
      <link>https://kowainik.github.io/posts/haskell-mini-patterns</link>
      <description>Collection of small Haskell patterns with detailed description, examples and exercises</description>
      <author> (Kowainik  — Dmitrii Kovanikov &lt;&gt; Veronika Romashkina)</author>
      <guid>https://kowainik.github.io/posts/haskell-mini-patterns</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 08:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Death Of Corporate Research Labs</title>
      <link>https://blog.dshr.org/2020/05/the-death-of-corporate-research-labs.html?m=1</link>
      <description>In American innovation through the ages , Jamie Powell wrote:   who hasn’t finished a non-fiction book and thought “Gee, that could have bee...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.dshr.org/2020/05/the-death-of-corporate-research-labs.html?m=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 05:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy Femtoduino a Coffee. ko-fi.com/femtoduino</title>
      <link>https://ko-fi.com/femtoduino</link>
      <description>Buy a Coffee for Femtoduino with Ko-fi.com</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ko-fi.com/femtoduino</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 04:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing C# 9: Native-sized integers</title>
      <link>https://anthonygiretti.com/2020/08/19/introducing-c-9-native-sized-integers/</link>
      <description>Introduction First what are native-sized integers ? They are designed to be a integer whose...</description>
      <author> (by anthonygiretti)</author>
      <guid>https://anthonygiretti.com/2020/08/19/introducing-c-9-native-sized-integers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 03:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise operator Carnival hit by ransomware</title>
      <link>https://www.itnews.com.au/news/cruise-operator-carnival-hit-by-ransomware-551880</link>
      <description>Guest and employee personal data taken.</description>
      <author> (Juha Saarinen)</author>
      <guid>https://www.itnews.com.au/news/cruise-operator-carnival-hit-by-ransomware-551880</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 01:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShinyHunters Serving up 21 New Compromised Databases - Binary Defense</title>
      <link>https://www.binarydefense.com/threat_watch/shinyhunters-serving-up-21-new-compromised-databases/</link>
      <description>ShinyHunters: ShinyHunters is showing no signs of slowing their slew of attacks anytime soon.  Early yesterday, 21 new databases were listed for sale by ShinyHunters on RaidForums. The new collection of victims from the threat group appears to be a random assortment with no unifying pattern among the targets of the now infamous hacker(s). Along […]</description>
      <author> (Garrett Thompson)</author>
      <guid>https://www.binarydefense.com/threat_watch/shinyhunters-serving-up-21-new-compromised-databases/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$5 DIY "Smart" Garage Door Opener using Sonoff SV</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QMepwpyjMCY</link>
      <description>READ THIS UPDATE!!!! 
Tasmota updates have changed some necessary settings!
Here's what you need now:  (Thanks Chris Norton)
Switchretain 1
Powerretain 1
switchtopic2 garagestate
switchmode1 0
switchmode2 2

GPIO 14 to 10 Switch2

GPIO 4 to 22 Relay2


cover.yaml

  - platform: mqtt
    name: "Sonoff SV Garage"
    state_topic: "cmnd/garagestate/POWER2"
    command_topic: "cmnd/sonoffsv01/POWER"
    payload_open: "ON"
    payload_close: "ON"
    payload_stop: "ON"
    state_open: "ON"
    state_closed: "OFF"
    optimistic: false

customize.yaml
   
    cover.sonoff_sv_garage:
      device_class: garage
      friendly_name: Garage 

group.yaml

  Garage Door:
    name: Garage Door
    view: no
    control: hidden
    icon: mdi:garage
    entities:
      - cover.sonoff_sv_garage


just thought I’d share the full details of a sonoff sv garage switch with 6.2.1 firmware. 

A few common problems people have can be solved by:
#1 - in the Tasmota Console, type "Switchretain 1".  That will make it so HA gets the last state from the door sensor after a reboot. 
#2 - pick an unused GPIO pin on the Sonoff SV and set it as "Relay2".  Use D4 or D5, not D1 or D3. That should stop the reed switch from triggering the relay.  I haven't had to do this, but I think it may be because I'm using an older version of Tasmota. 
#3 - in the Tasmota Console type "Powerretain 1". That will stop the relay from randomly triggering when the Sonoff disconnects and reconnects to the MQTT broker. 

I know I went kinda fast in this one.  Everything you need is here. 

To Smarten up your garage doors you’ll need:
Sonoff SV https://www.itead.cc/sonoff-sv.html
Reed Switch http://a.co/6qMTS35
USB cord and wall plug or some other power adapter
Jumper wires http://a.co/0htfCkL
Soap dish https://www.walmart.com/ip/iGo-Travel-Soap-Holder/13814222
There is soldering involved. No way around it on this one 
Garage SV setup
Open sonoff.ino
Set a project name and your Wifi and MQTT info in user_config.h
Upload Tasmota
Find the IP address of your new Tasmotized Sonoff (you can look in your router)
Put the Sonoff IP address in your browser, go to Configuration Configure Module and and change the Module Type to Sonoff SV. Save and it’ll restart. 
Go back into Configure Module and set GPIO 14 to Switch2 save and it’ll restart again
Click Console and type: switchmode1 0 and then switchmode2 2, restart one more time
Now we’ve got some work to do in Home Assistant
Open configuration.yaml
Make a heading called “cover:” and paste these lines

cover:
  - platform: mqtt
    name: "test"
    state_topic: "cmnd/2/POWER2"
    command_topic: "cmnd/sonoffSV04/POWER"
    payload_open: "ON"
    payload_close: "ON"
    payload_stop: "ON"
    state_open: "ON"
    state_closed: "OFF"
    optomistic: false
    retain: false
Under Customize: set the device class and give it a friendly name
    cover.test:
      device_class: garage
      friendly_name: Justin Garage

If you want to make a card that says Garage Doors instead of Cover then open your groups.yaml.  If you don’t have one just create and new empty file with that name and past these lines. 

    garage_doors:
      name: Garage Doors
      view: no
      control: hidden
      icon: mdi:garage
      entities:
        - cover.test

Save both config and groups. In Home Assistant UI check the config and restart. 
Now go to the Automation editor, make a new automation. The trigger is the MQTT topic that fires whenever the relay is turned ON. The action is to turn it back off after one second. Save and reload Automations. 
Now the hardware setup:
To isolate the power to the ESP chip from what’s being switched by the relay, use a small screwdriver to pop the 2 resistors. 
Solder 2 lengths of small wire, one on the Input + and one on the output +, these wires will connect to the switch contacts on your garage door motor. 
Connect female end of jumper wires to GPIO 14 and Ground. These are going to the reed switch and will tell you if the garage is open or closed. 
Use a USB cable for power. The red wire is + and the uncovered wire and the outer metal sheath are negative. 
Connect those to female jumpers and plug them into + and - for the ESP chip. 
Test:
Lay it out. Connect the reed switch, power up the board, and open Home Assistant. 
Move the magnet to test the reed switch 
Click the open/close buttons to check the relay. 
If it all works it’s time to install
Install:
I put mine up near the garage motor. You don’t have to do it this way. 
Mount the reed switch. I put mine on the track and the magnet on the top of the door.  Took a few tries to find something that would keep them connected. There’s a lot of motion on that track. 
Find the contacts for your open/close button. Connect the wire from the input side of the relay to one contact, and the wire from the output side to the other. 
On my garage door those wires are 12v.
Connect the +/- jumpers from the USB cord, for power to the ESP, and plug it in. 
You’re done!</description>
      <author> (DrZzs)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QMepwpyjMCY</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction &amp; Table of Contents</title>
      <link>https://magcius.github.io/xplain/article/</link>
      <description>The goal of Explanations is to try to allow people to play with fun parts of computers. Graphics,
            compression, audio. The tagline is my biggest inspiration: "Play, don't show", riffing off the
            typical "Show, don't tell" rule of writers and authors everywhere. Why bother giving a diagram when
            I give you an inspector and let you poke at things yourself!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://magcius.github.io/xplain/article/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 23:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Look at the Current 2020 Hard Drive Failure Rates</title>
      <link>https://www.backblaze.com/blog/backblaze-hard-drive-stats-q2-2020/</link>
      <description>Hard drive failure rates on an annualized and quarterly basis for 139,867 hard drives by make and manufacturer.</description>
      <author> (About  Andy Klein)</author>
      <guid>https://www.backblaze.com/blog/backblaze-hard-drive-stats-q2-2020/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 23:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Need a Password Manager. Here Are the Best Ones</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-password-managers/</link>
      <description>Keep your logins under lock and key. We picked our favorites for PC, Mac, Android, iPhone, and web browsers.</description>
      <author> (Scott Gilbertson)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wired.com/story/best-password-managers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrum is not for humans</title>
      <link>https://maroun-baydoun.com/blog/scrum-is-not-for-humans/</link>
      <description>Scrum is not the agility beacon it claims to be. It is time for self-organising teams to release themselves from the shackles of Agile.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://maroun-baydoun.com/blog/scrum-is-not-for-humans/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphical Linear Algebra</title>
      <link>https://graphicallinearalgebra.net/</link>
      <description>Applications are open for the ACT Applied Category Theory Research School 2018! And because arithmetic science and geometric science are connected, and support one another, the full knowledge of numbers cannot be presented without encountering some geometry, or without seeing that operating in this way on numbers is close to geometry; the method is full…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://graphicallinearalgebra.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big money, not big data</title>
      <link>http://dangoldin.com/2020/08/16/big-money-not-big-data/</link>
      <description>When people complain about big data they're just complaining about the cost, not the technical challenges.</description>
      <author> (Dan Goldin)</author>
      <guid>http://dangoldin.com/2020/08/16/big-money-not-big-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerabilities in ATM Milano's mobile app</title>
      <link>https://blog.jacopojannone.com/en/post/atm-app-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Some design flaws left ATM Milano’s mobile app vulnerable to attacks: anyone could access any users’ data and tickets by just knowing their e-mail address. Meanwhile, some apparent security features made the vulnerabilities harder to spot and to exploit.</description>
      <author> (jacopo-j @jacopoj_ jacopoj E-mail RSS)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jacopojannone.com/en/post/atm-app-vulnerability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Economics of OnlyFans | XSRUS</title>
      <link>https://www.xsrus.com/writing/explain/onlyfans/</link>
      <description>Publish date: 2020-04-24</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.xsrus.com/writing/explain/onlyfans/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Startup Employees and Company Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.kracov.co/writing/early-startup-employees-and-company-growth</link>
      <description>Early employees often join startups to learn new skills and fast track career growth. The common thinking is that if you join an early-stage company then you’ll be a company leader in the future. But keeping up with the company growth curve can be a difficult challenge.</description>
      <author> (By Alex Kracov)</author>
      <guid>https://www.kracov.co/writing/early-startup-employees-and-company-growth</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release v0.0.1 · wybiral/zap</title>
      <link>https://github.com/wybiral/zap/releases/tag/v0.0.1</link>
      <description>First release!</description>
      <author> (wybiral)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/wybiral/zap/releases/tag/v0.0.1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many pieces can a puzzle have?</title>
      <link>https://gottwurfelt.com/2020/08/17/how-many-pieces-can-a-puzzle-have/</link>
      <description>Patrick Honner tweeted a few days ago: My 7 yo pointed out that our 300 piece puzzle actually contains 18 x 18 = 324 pieces and I just don’t know what to believe anymore. — Patrick Honner (@M…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gottwurfelt.com/2020/08/17/how-many-pieces-can-a-puzzle-have/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Contrary Consultant</title>
      <link>https://tomcritchlow.com/2020/08/18/the-fool/</link>
      <description>Tom Critchlow. Move. Think. Create.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tomcritchlow.com/2020/08/18/the-fool/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinesys Advantage2 - Review after three years of use</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/articles/kinesis-advantage2.html</link>
      <description>A brief review of the Kinesys Advantage2 ergonomic keyboard, now I've been using it for three-and-a-half years.</description>
      <author> (Martin Fowler)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/articles/kinesis-advantage2.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/tree/release/5.0</link>
      <description>.NET is a cross-platform runtime for cloud, mobile, desktop, and IoT apps. - dotnet/runtime</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/tree/release/5.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Remote Work Will Convince You to Relocate -</title>
      <link>https://dougantin.com/2020/08/18/why-remote-work-will-convince-you-to-relocate/</link>
      <description>The ability to work remotely on a permanent basis will lead to a reshuffling of factors impacting how workers decide where to live.</description>
      <author> (Doug)</author>
      <guid>https://dougantin.com/2020/08/18/why-remote-work-will-convince-you-to-relocate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The little guide to CI/CD for frontend developers - Maxime Heckel's Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.maximeheckel.com/posts/guide-to-cicd-for-frontend-developers/</link>
      <description>How to ship your app faster, more reliably and make your team unstoppable with good testing practices and automation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.maximeheckel.com/posts/guide-to-cicd-for-frontend-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth Tax</title>
      <link>https://blog.libove.org/posts/wealth-tax/</link>
      <description>Paul Graham wrote an article about wealth tax. In the article he ‘models’ the effect of a wealth tax on the fortune of a person. His assumption for the modeling is a person who earned a lot of money with a startup in her 20s. Paul Graham shows how much of the earned stocks/money would be taken by the government by a wealth tax.
Paul Graham comes to the conclusion that wealth taxes have “dramatic effects” and that “even a .</description>
      <author> (H4kor)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.libove.org/posts/wealth-tax/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 22:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigapixel AI Accidentally Added Ryan Gosling's Face to This Photo</title>
      <link>https://petapixel.com/2020/08/17/gigapixel-ai-accidentally-added-ryan-goslings-face-to-this-photo/</link>
      <description>Photographer Jomppe Vaarakallio has been a professional retoucher for 30 years, but he's never seen anything quite like this before. While working on an</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://petapixel.com/2020/08/17/gigapixel-ai-accidentally-added-ryan-goslings-face-to-this-photo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 21:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Aug 11th 2020 - Blazor Updates in .NET 5</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KRNd8JDRqRc&amp;index=0</link>
      <description>Join members from the Blazor team to hear about what's on the way in .NET 5! Lots of new demos and fun new features! 🥳

Community links for this week: https://www.theurlist.com/aspnet-standup-2020-08-11

#Blazor #ASPNET</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KRNd8JDRqRc&amp;index=0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 20:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the Phone Gap closed in 2020?－firt.dev</title>
      <link>https://firt.dev/phonegap-end/</link>
      <description>Adobe announced the end of the PhoneGap product line and the end of Adobe's investment in Apache Cordova because the PWA platform is now ready. Is the native-web gap closed in 2020 thanks to PWAs?</description>
      <author> (by Maximiliano Firtman
              Twitter @firt About Newsletter)</author>
      <guid>https://firt.dev/phonegap-end/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 20:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Apple:  Your Services Are No Longer Required.</title>
      <link>https://lowendmac.com/2020/dear-apple-your-services-are-no-longer-required/</link>
      <description>Anyone who knows me knows that I was among the biggest Apple Evangelists to ever live. Apple was in my DNA.  I believed in Apple’s products, Apple’s services, and Apple’s mission (or at least what …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lowendmac.com/2020/dear-apple-your-services-are-no-longer-required/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 20:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uzay-G/archivy</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Uzay-G/archivy</link>
      <description>Contribute to Uzay-G/archivy development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (Uzay-G)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Uzay-G/archivy</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 19:41:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Scraping without getting blocked</title>
      <link>https://www.scrapingbee.com/blog/web-scraping-without-getting-blocked/</link>
      <description>Browser fingerprinting, TLS fingerprinting, Chrome headless, headers spoofing and more. Here is everything we know about how to scrape the web without getting blocked.</description>
      <author> (Pierre de Wulf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.scrapingbee.com/blog/web-scraping-without-getting-blocked/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 19:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Learn x86-64 Assembly! Part 0</title>
      <link>https://gpfault.net/posts/asm-tut-0.txt.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gpfault.net/posts/asm-tut-0.txt.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 18:14:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular seafood species in sharp decline around the world</title>
      <link>https://news.ubc.ca/2020/07/21/popular-seafood-species-in-sharp-decline-around-the-world/</link>
      <description>Fish market favourites such as orange roughy, common octopus and pink conch are among the species of fish and invertebrates in rapid decline around the world, according to new research.</description>
      <author> (Jul 21, 2020     |   For more information, contact Valentina Ruiz Leotaud)</author>
      <guid>https://news.ubc.ca/2020/07/21/popular-seafood-species-in-sharp-decline-around-the-world/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 18:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ASP.NET Team @TheASPNETTeam</title>
      <link>https://www.pscp.tv/w/cgquqzFyYWpaeUJKTE9aS3p8MVprSnptRWVBWXFHdoeAWauLMyP5mjqAR29RBGK_Pi7PFV1l-FYwPP8Opggd</link>
      <description>ASP.NET Community Standup - Aug 18th 2020 - ASP.NET Core Linker with David Fowler</description>
      <author> (Twitter Inc)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pscp.tv/w/cgquqzFyYWpaeUJKTE9aS3p8MVprSnptRWVBWXFHdoeAWauLMyP5mjqAR29RBGK_Pi7PFV1l-FYwPP8Opggd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 18:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ignatandrei/NETCoreBlockly</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ignatandrei/NETCoreBlockly</link>
      <description>.NET Core API to Blockly - generate from WebAPI, Swagger, OData, GraphQL =&gt; - ignatandrei/NETCoreBlockly</description>
      <author> (ignatandrei)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ignatandrei/NETCoreBlockly</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 17:45:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running headless Chromium in Azure Functions with Puppeteer and Playwright</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/azure/running-headless-chromium-in-azure-functions-with-puppeteer-and-playwright-2fgk</link>
      <description>With a recent update to Azure Functions, it is now possible to run headless Chromium in the Linux Consumption plan. This enables some serverless browser automation scenarios using popular frameworks such as Puppeteer and Playwright.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/azure/running-headless-chromium-in-azure-functions-with-puppeteer-and-playwright-2fgk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 17:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>umami</title>
      <link>https://umami.is/</link>
      <description>Learn moreLive demo</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://umami.is/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 17:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling a Wealth Tax</title>
      <link>http://paulgraham.com/wtax.html</link>
      <description>Some politicians are proposing to introduce wealth taxes in addition
to income taxes. Let's try modeling the effects of various levels
of wealth tax to see what they would mean in practice for a startup
founder.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://paulgraham.com/wtax.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 17:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling IHostedService execution order in ASP.NET Core 3.x</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/controlling-ihostedservice-execution-order-in-aspnetcore-3/</link>
      <description>In this post I show how to control whether your IHostedService runs before or after the GenericWebHostService starts the Kestrel HTTP server</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/controlling-ihostedservice-execution-order-in-aspnetcore-3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 17:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laying the foundation for Rust's future | Rust Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2020/08/18/laying-the-foundation-for-rusts-future.html</link>
      <description>Empowering everyone to build reliable and efficient software.</description>
      <author> (Aug. 18, 2020 · The Rust Core Team)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2020/08/18/laying-the-foundation-for-rusts-future.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 17:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Founders Treated Their Investors The Same Way They Treated Their Employees</title>
      <link>https://software.rajivprab.com/2020/08/18/if-founders-treated-their-investors-the-same-way-they-treated-their-employees/</link>
      <description>Founder: Hey Joe! How are you doing? Everyone here loved meeting you, and we would really love to have you on board as our investor! We really respect your expertise, and think this could be a grea…</description>
      <author> (RP)</author>
      <guid>https://software.rajivprab.com/2020/08/18/if-founders-treated-their-investors-the-same-way-they-treated-their-employees/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 16:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://www.iacr.org/archive/crypto2005/36210017/36210017.pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.iacr.org/archive/crypto2005/36210017/36210017.pdf</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.iacr.org/archive/crypto2005/36210017/36210017.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 16:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo DS Architecture | A Practical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.copetti.org/projects/consoles/nintendo-ds/</link>
      <description>An in-depth analysis that explains how this console works internally</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.copetti.org/projects/consoles/nintendo-ds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 16:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sourcegen.dev - Source Generator Playground</title>
      <link>https://sourcegen.dev/</link>
      <description>Source Generator Playground - 1.0.13+769e760e81</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sourcegen.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 16:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>privacycg/first-party-sets</title>
      <link>https://github.com/privacycg/first-party-sets</link>
      <description>Contribute to privacycg/first-party-sets development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (privacycg)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/privacycg/first-party-sets</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 15:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperIlu/DOjS</title>
      <link>https://github.com/SuperIlu/DOjS</link>
      <description>A DOS JavaScript Canvas with sound. Contribute to SuperIlu/DOjS development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (SuperIlu)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/SuperIlu/DOjS</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 14:31:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.5 Million Medical Records Leaked By AI Company</title>
      <link>https://securethoughts.com/medical-data-of-auto-accident-victims-exposed-online/</link>
      <description>Secure Thoughts collaborated with Cyber Security Expert Jeremiah Fowler to expose an AI company which leaked millions of patient medical records online</description>
      <author> (Written by Jeremiah Fowler       Last updated on August 18, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://securethoughts.com/medical-data-of-auto-accident-victims-exposed-online/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 14:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporting Encrypted Content-Encoding in HttpClient - Replacing Bouncy Castle With .NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.tpeczek.com/2020/08/supporting-encrypted-content-encoding.html</link>
      <description>Some time ago I've shown how to extend HttpClient with payload encryption. In this post I'm revisiting the subject with some .NET Core 3.1 goodness.</description>
      <author> (Tomasz Pęczek)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tpeczek.com/2020/08/supporting-encrypted-content-encoding.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 14:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canon's cloud platform has lost users' files – and it CAN'T restore them</title>
      <link>https://www.digitalcameraworld.com/news/canon-websites-held-to-ransom-by-hackers</link>
      <description>After losing users' photo &amp; video files, Canon has admitted that it can only restore photos – but not at their original resolution</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/Digitalcameraworld/)</author>
      <guid>https://www.digitalcameraworld.com/news/canon-websites-held-to-ransom-by-hackers</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 13:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RC-Network Modellsport e.V.</title>
      <link>https://rc-network.de/</link>
      <description>Liebe RC-Network Besucher,</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rc-network.de/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 12:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDC Workshops Q4 2020: Call for Speakers / Call for Papers (CfP) @ Sessionize.com</title>
      <link>https://sessionize.com/ndc-workshops-q4-2020</link>
      <description>Sessionize is the smart way to manage Call for Papers, Speakers and Agenda for your conference.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sessionize.com/ndc-workshops-q4-2020</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 12:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>