<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>3D Printing Log</title>
      <link>https://madebynathan.com/logs/3d-printing/</link>
      <description>I bought a Bambu Lab X1-Carbon 3D printer in March 2023.

I&amp;#39;m extremely happy with this 3D printer and highly recommend it! It&amp;#39;s more expensive than entry-level printers, but it&amp;#39;s a very high quality machine and is very reliable. I can focus on designing and making things instead of spending</description>
      <author> (Nathan Broadbent)</author>
      <guid>https://madebynathan.com/logs/3d-printing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Microsoft developer says Windows 11&amp;#39;s performance is &amp;quot;comically bad,&amp;quot; even with monster PC</title>
      <link>https://www.blobstreaming.org/former-microsoft-developer-says-windows-11s-performance-is-comically-bad-even-with-monster-pc/</link>
      <description>Microsoft Windows 11 performance has noticeably deteriorated, a former Microsoft senior software engineer has pointed out. Some prominent user interface (UI) elements were &amp;quot;comically bad,&amp;quot; while others took almost a full second to load, he noted.


Important user interface elements cannot be loaded for unknown reasons

Microsoft recently reminded Windows</description>
      <author> (Mohamed Aboelez)</author>
      <guid>https://www.blobstreaming.org/former-microsoft-developer-says-windows-11s-performance-is-comically-bad-even-with-monster-pc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear is a Trainable Animal</title>
      <link>https://www.bendingpinksteel.com/p/fear</link>
      <description>Forget being fearless. This is better.</description>
      <author> (David Ramos)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bendingpinksteel.com/p/fear</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphics offload revisited – GTK Development Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.gtk.org/2024/04/17/graphics-offload-revisited/</link>
      <description>We first introduced support for dmabufs and graphics offload last fall, and it is included in GTK 4.14. Since then, some improvements have happened, so it is time for an update.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.gtk.org/2024/04/17/graphics-offload-revisited/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Msty</title>
      <link>https://msty.app/blog/llama3-vs-gpt-4-vs-gemini-pro</link>
      <description>Msty is simplest way to use local and online LLMs. Its chat interface packed with powerful features make it easy to use LLMs. Run Ollama models such as Mixtral, Llama2, Qwen, or online models such as GPT-3, GPT-4, Mistral, Gemini, Groq, Claude, and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://msty.app/blog/llama3-vs-gpt-4-vs-gemini-pro</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Dolphin Isn&amp;#39;t Coming to the App Store - oatmealdome.me</title>
      <link>https://oatmealdome.me/blog/why-dolphin-isnt-coming-to-the-app-store/</link>
      <description>Two weeks ago, Apple modified their App Store guidelines to allow retro game emulators in the App Store. This week, Delta, a multi-system emulator that was previously only available via AltStore, was released on the App Store. Since these events happened, we&amp;#39;ve been asked many times if we will submit…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://oatmealdome.me/blog/why-dolphin-isnt-coming-to-the-app-store/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stopping a badly behaved bot the wrong way. - Lemmy</title>
      <link>https://lemmy.ml/post/14612626</link>
      <description>I host a few small low-traffic websites for local interests. I do this for free
- and some of them are for a friend who died last year but didn’t want all his
work to vanish. They don’t get so many views, so I was surprised when I happened
to glance at munin and saw my bandwidth usage had gone up a lot. I spent a
couple of hours working to solve this and did everything wrong. But it was a
useful learning experience and I thought it might be worth sharing in case
anyone else encounters similar. My setup is: Cloudflare DNS -&amp;gt; Cloudflare Tunnel
(Because my residential isp uses CGNAT) -&amp;gt; Haproxy (I like Haproxy and amongst
other things, alerts me when a site is down) -&amp;gt; Separate Docker containers for
each website. On a Debian server living in my garage. From Haproxy’s stats page,
I was able to see which website was gathering attention. It’s one running PhpBB
for a little forum. Tailing apache’s logs in that container quickly identified
the pattern and made it easy to see what was happening. It was seeing a lot of
404 errors for URLs all coming from the same user-agent “claudebot”. I know what
you’re thinking - it’s an exploit scanning bot, but a closer look showed it was
trying to fetch normal forum posts, some which had been deleted months
previously, and also robots.txt. That site doesn’t have a robots.txt so that was
failing. What was weird is that the it was requesting at a rate of up to 20 urls
a second, from multiple AWS IPs - and every other request was for robots.txt.
You’d think it would take the hint after a million times of asking. Googling
that UA turns up that other PhpBB users have encountered this quite recently -
it seems to be fascinated by web forums and absolutely hammers them with the
same behaviour I found. So - clearly a broken and stupid bot, right? Rather than
being specifically malicious. I think so, but I host these sites on a rural
consumer line and it was affecting both system load and bandwidth. What I did
wrong: 1. In docker, I tried quite a few things to block the user agent, the
country (US based AWS, and this is a UK regional site), various IPs. It took me
far too long to realise why my changes to .htaccess were failing - the phpbb
docker image I use mounts the root directory to the website internally, ignoring
my mounted vol. (My own fault, it was too long since I set it up to remember
only certain sub-dirs were mounted in)
2. Figuring that out, I shelled into the container and edited that .htaccess,
but wouldn’t have survived restarting/rebuilding the container so wasn’t a real
solution. Whilst I was in there, I created a robots.txt file. Not surprisingly,
claudebot doesn’t actually honour whats in there, and still continues to request
it ten times a second. 3. Thinking there must be another way, I switched to
Haproxy. This was much easier - the documentation is very good. And it actually
worked - blocking by Useragent (and yep, I’m lucky this wasn’t changing) worked
perfectly. I then had to leave for a while and the graphs show it’s working.
(Yellow above the line is requests coming into haproxy, below the line are
responses).
[https://lemmy.ml/pictrs/image/2bc99426-0356-4010-a0e5-f7b8dbfeb14a.png] Great -
except I’m still seeing half of the traffic, and that’s affecting my latency.
(Some of you might doubt this, and I can tell you that you’re spoiled by an
excess of bandwidth…) 4. That’s when the penny dropped and the obvious occured.
I use cloudflare, so use their firewall, right? No excuses - I should have gone
there first. In fact, I did, but I got distracted by the many options and
focused on their bot fighting tools, which didn’t work for me. (This bot is
somehow getting through the captcha challenge even when bot fight mode is
enabled) But, their firewall has an option for user agent. The actual fix was
simply to add this in WAF for that domain.
[https://lemmy.ml/pictrs/image/98041b82-de04-4cdc-bfb1-05f4e5656903.png] And
voila - no more traffic through the tunnel for this very rude and stupid bot.
After 24 hours, Cloudflare has blocked almost a quarter of a million requests by
claudebot to my little phpbb forum which barely gets a single post every three
months.
[https://lemmy.ml/pictrs/image/f3170d6c-fec1-4820-9fbb-b54b14db46f8.png] Moral
for myself: Stand back and think for a minute before rushing in and trying to
fix something in the wrong way. I’ve also taken this as an opportunity to
improve haproxy’s rate limiting internally. Like most website hosts, most of my
traffic is outbound, and slowing things down when it gets busy really does help.
This obviously isn’t a perfect solution - all claudebot has to do is change its
UA, and by coming from AWS it’s pretty hard to block otherwise. One hopes it
isn’t truly malicious. It would be quite a lot more work to integrate Fail2ban
for more bots, but it might yet come to that. Also, if you write any kind of web
bot, please consider that not everyone who hosts a website has a lot of
bandwidth, and at least have enough pride to write software good enough to not
keep doing the same thing every second. And, y’know, keep an eye on what your
stuff is doing out on the internet - not least for your own benefit. Hopefully
AWS really shaft claudebot’s owners with some big bandwidth charges… EDIT: It
came back the next day with a new UA, and an email address linking it to
anthropic.com [http://anthropic.com] - the Claude3 AI bot, so it looks like a
particularly badly written scraper for AI learning.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lemmy.ml/post/14612626</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIFs are a flat circle</title>
      <link>https://rhizome.org/editorial/GIFs-are-a-flat-circle/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (by 
Kayla Drzewicki,)</author>
      <guid>https://rhizome.org/editorial/GIFs-are-a-flat-circle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stateful Migrations using Mutations</title>
      <link>https://stack.convex.dev/migrating-data-with-mutations</link>
      <description>Online migrations in Convex using mutations. Including a helper to track migration state!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stack.convex.dev/migrating-data-with-mutations</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS Certification - I should be exempt</title>
      <link>https://cestlaz.github.io/post/i-should-be-exempt/</link>
      <description>Over the past few years, a number of states have acknowledged Computer Science as an academic area of study and have created pathways for certification. The actual requirements vary from state to state and indeed, even within a given state, there&amp;#39;s a lot of variation. Here in New York, for instance there are some strong programs that will truly prepare a candidate to teach CS in K12 but too many others that are just &amp;quot;certificate mills&amp;quot; and the state doesn&amp;#39;t seem to care.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cestlaz.github.io/post/i-should-be-exempt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Ordinary Blogs Usually Suck</title>
      <link>https://www.sungho.blog/p/why-ordinary-blogs-usually-suck</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Sungho Yahng)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sungho.blog/p/why-ordinary-blogs-usually-suck</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Optimal Workspace</title>
      <link>https://elijahpotter.dev/articles/the_optimal_workspace</link>
      <description>How I intend on living better.</description>
      <author> (Elijah Potter)</author>
      <guid>https://elijahpotter.dev/articles/the_optimal_workspace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>do tiny projects expecting them to fail</title>
      <link>https://gueejla.com/do-tiny-projects-expecting-them-to-fail/</link>
      <description>My goal

I will do tiny projects expecting them to fail.

I will post updates (sometimes here, sometimes on my youtube) on what I did, how it failed, and what I learned.

Rinse and repeat.

If you find this framing helpful or have suggestions, feel free to comment or reach</description>
      <author> (Greg)</author>
      <guid>https://gueejla.com/do-tiny-projects-expecting-them-to-fail/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iDOS 3 waiting for review</title>
      <link>https://litchie.com/2024/04/new-hope#disqus_thread?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</link>
      <description>April 14, 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://litchie.com/2024/04/new-hope#disqus_thread?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLVM is Smarter Than Me</title>
      <link>https://blog.sulami.xyz/posts/llvm-is-smarter-than-me/</link>
      <description>Weak Opinions, Strongly Held</description>
      <author> (Robin Schroer)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sulami.xyz/posts/llvm-is-smarter-than-me/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do electronic passports work? | Burak Can&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.burakcankus.com/2024/04/18/how-do-electronic-passports-work.html</link>
      <description>I explain how electronic passports (eMRTDs) work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.burakcankus.com/2024/04/18/how-do-electronic-passports-work.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Terry A. Davis</title>
      <link>https://schizophrenic.io/blog/on-terry-a-davis</link>
      <description>As someone formally diagnosed with schizophrenia who happens to be a
programmer, I often get questions such as,</description>
      <author> (Daniel Jaouen)</author>
      <guid>https://schizophrenic.io/blog/on-terry-a-davis</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quill - Your powerful rich text editor</title>
      <link>https://quilljs.com/</link>
      <description>Quill is a free, open source WYSIWYG editor built for the modern web. Completely customize it for any need with its modular architecture and expressive API.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://quilljs.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 03:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Distributed Tracing With OpenTelemetry in .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/introduction-to-distributed-tracing-with-opentelemetry-in-dotnet</link>
      <description>Distributed systems offer flexibility but introduce complexity, making troubleshooting a headache. Understanding how requests flow through your system is crucial for debugging and performance optimization. OpenTelemetry is an open-source observability framework that makes this possible.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/introduction-to-distributed-tracing-with-opentelemetry-in-dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 01:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding state to the update notification pattern, part 3 - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240419-00/?p=109689</link>
      <description>Abandoning the background work if we know that it is pointless.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240419-00/?p=109689</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supabase Storage: now supports the S3 protocol</title>
      <link>https://supabase.com/blog/s3-compatible-storage</link>
      <description>Supabase Storage is now officially an S3-Compatible Storage Provider.</description>
      <author> (https://github.com/fenos)</author>
      <guid>https://supabase.com/blog/s3-compatible-storage</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pub Trivia</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2922/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2922/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>