<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>14 Advanced Python Features</title>
      <link>https://blog.edward-li.com/tech/advanced-python-features/</link>
      <description>Python is one of the most widely adopted programming languages in the world. Yet, because of it’s ease and simplicity to just “get something working”, it’s also one of the most underappreciated.
If you search for Top 10 Advanced Python Tricks on Google or any other search engine, you’ll find tons of blogs or LinkedIn articles going over trivial (but still useful) things like generators or tuples.
However, as someone who’s written Python for the past 12 years, I’ve come across a lot of really interesting, underrated, unique, or (as some might say) “un-pythonic” tricks to really level up what Python can do.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.edward-li.com/tech/advanced-python-features/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 14:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does This Azure Developer Have What It Takes?!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=uCwJzWtpcFk</link>
      <description>This senior software engineer has loads of experience building in the Azure tech stack -- but do they have what it takes?!

Let's review what makes this resume stand out, the opportunities for improvement, and how they might apply to YOUR resume!

----
Want a chance to have your resume reviewed? Submit it to resumes [at] devleader [dot] ca!
----
🔑 Membership &amp; Subscriptions:
- 📨 Weekly Newsletter: https://weekly.devleader.ca
- 🏘️ Private Discord Community: https://sidestack.io/devleader

🧠 Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Get Promoted As A Software Engineer: https://dometrain.com/course/career-getting-promoted-as-a-software-engineer/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?ref=nick-cosentino
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

🗣️ Social Media &amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs:  @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp; Products/Services That I Love:
- @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper Opus Clip: https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----

#softwareengineering #softwaredeveloper #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=uCwJzWtpcFk</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 14:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native visionOS platform support by rsanchezsaez · Pull Request #105628 · godotengine/godot</title>
      <link>https://github.com/godotengine/godot/pull/105628</link>
      <description>Dear Godot community,
I&amp;#39;m on Apple&amp;#39;s visionOS engineering team, and we would like to contribute Vision Pro support to the Godot engine. This is the first PR that lays the foundation for tha...</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/godotengine/godot/pull/105628</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLnet; 42 Free and Open Source Projects Receive Funding to Reclaim the Public Nature of the Internet</title>
      <link>https://nlnet.nl/news/2025/20250422-announcement-grants-CommonsFund.html</link>
      <description>It is wonderful to see the growing number of people working on digital commons, inventing and improving technologies to the benefit of all humanity. 42 of such projects have been selected for funding in the October call of the NGI Zero Commons Fund. In terms of applications, it was the largest call round in NGI Zero's life time. And we'd like to take this space to thank all applicants for their contributions to an internet for people rather than for profit.</description>
      <guid>https://nlnet.nl/news/2025/20250422-announcement-grants-CommonsFund.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 13:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The way to use CancellationTokens on xUnit v3 #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=c4S2xAU95q4</link>
      <description>💌 Free Developer Insights: https://guiferreira.me/newsletter

#dotnet #xunit</description>
      <author> (Gui Ferreira)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=c4S2xAU95q4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 13:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac or PC, what to use for .NET MAUI Development</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=77ynTSn0cBw</link>
      <description>Are you diving into .NET MAUI development and wondering whether a Mac or PC is the better choice? In this video, we compare the pros and cons of both platforms—performance, tooling, and ease of development—to help you make the best decision for your workflow. Whether you're a Windows enthusiast or a macOS aficionado, we've got insights to guide you.

Which side are you on? Let me know in the comments! 👇

#dotnetmaui #MacVsPC #AppDevelopment #VisualStudio</description>
      <author> (Daniel Hindrikes)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=77ynTSn0cBw</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Real‑Time iOS Apps with SignalR: Introducing the Official Swift Client (Public Preview) - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/building-real%E2%80%91time-ios-apps-with-signalr-introducing-the-official-swift-client-public-preview/</link>
      <description>Introduction Until now, iOS developers who wanted real‑time, bi‑directional communication with SignalR had to rely on community‑built clients or roll their own Swift implementation—both of which introduced maintenance and compatibility headaches. We’re excited to announce that the official SignalR Swift client is now available in public preview. With this release, you can: Quickly add real‑time […]</description>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/building-real%E2%80%91time-ios-apps-with-signalr-introducing-the-official-swift-client-public-preview/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 05:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atuin Desktop: Runbooks that Run</title>
      <link>https://blog.atuin.sh/atuin-desktop-runbooks-that-run/</link>
      <description>Atuin Desktop looks like a doc, but runs like your terminal. Script blocks, embedded terminals, database clients and prometheus charts - all in one place.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.atuin.sh/atuin-desktop-runbooks-that-run/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 03:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - alexykn/sapphire: Rust based package manager for macOS</title>
      <link>https://github.com/alexykn/sapphire</link>
      <description>Rust based package manager for macOS. Contribute to alexykn/sapphire development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/alexykn/sapphire</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 02:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Interviewed 100 Eng Teams. The Problem With Modern Engineering Isn't Speed. It's Chaos.</title>
      <link>https://earthly.dev/blog/lunar-launch/</link>
      <description>Last year, our team spent a lot of time interviewing fellow Platform, DevOps, DevEx, CI/CD, and SRE engineers, as well as engineering leaders, in o...</description>
      <author> (Vlad A. Ionescu)</author>
      <guid>https://earthly.dev/blog/lunar-launch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 01:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glitching STM32 Read Out Protection - Anvil Secure</title>
      <link>https://www.anvilsecure.com/blog/glitching-stm32-read-out-protection-with-voltage-fault-injection.html</link>
      <description>Security Engineer Luigi Fragale demonstrates how to glitch the STM32F401 to read protected memory using Python and fault injection.</description>
      <guid>https://www.anvilsecure.com/blog/glitching-stm32-read-out-protection-with-voltage-fault-injection.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT Finally Jumps Out of the System</title>
      <link>https://matthodges.com/posts/2025-04-21-openai-o4-mini-high-mu-puzzle/</link>
      <description>OpenAI’s o4-mini-high Model Solves the MU Puzzle and Demonstrates Why</description>
      <guid>https://matthodges.com/posts/2025-04-21-openai-o4-mini-high-mu-puzzle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Embedding to Rule Them All | Shaped Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.shaped.ai/blog/one-embedding-to-rule-them-all</link>
      <description>Pinterest’s OmniSearchSage represents a major step forward in unified semantic search. By extending the two-tower model into a multi-task, multi-entity framework, it enables a single query embedding to power retrieval across pins, products, and related queries. The system integrates GenAI captions, user-curated board metadata, and behavioral signals to overcome sparse content, while maintaining compatibility with legacy models like PinSage. Deployed at massive scale, OmniSearchSage delivers strong gains in search fulfillment, ad performance, and downstream tasks, showcasing a pragmatic and scalable approach to representation learning in production.</description>
      <guid>https://www.shaped.ai/blog/one-embedding-to-rule-them-all</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burn your title | notes.eatonphil.com</title>
      <link>https://notes.eatonphil.com/2025-04-22-burn-your-title.html</link>
      <description>Burn your title</description>
      <guid>https://notes.eatonphil.com/2025-04-22-burn-your-title.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I'd do as a College Freshman in 2025</title>
      <link>https://muratbuffalo.blogspot.com/2025/04/what-id-do-as-college-freshman.html</link>
      <description>Do Computer Science Absolutely. Still would. Many are spooked by LLMs. Some, like Jensen Huang, argue that "nobody has to learn how to progr...</description>
      <guid>https://muratbuffalo.blogspot.com/2025/04/what-id-do-as-college-freshman.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating cyber flashing in video calls</title>
      <link>https://timbrell.dev/ai/2025/01/09/cyber-flashing.html</link>
      <description>Content warning: This post discusses cyber flashing, including discussion of unsolicited explicit images and experiences related to online sexual harassment. Reader discretion is advised.</description>
      <guid>https://timbrell.dev/ai/2025/01/09/cyber-flashing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Document Symbols in Neovim</title>
      <link>https://laladrik.xyz/blog/enhancedDocumentSymbolMenuInNeovim/</link>
      <description>The fuzzy search in Neovim is implemented by a couple of plugins.  Personally, I prefer Telescope, mainly it's easy to extend it, thank the rich documentation.  Also, Neovim supports Tree-sitter to get the Abstract Syntax Tree (AST) to build the symbol paths, the plugin Nvim Treesitter does the work.  Therefore, the high level plan is this:</description>
      <guid>https://laladrik.xyz/blog/enhancedDocumentSymbolMenuInNeovim/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lode Coding</title>
      <link>https://fjzeit.github.io/coding/lode-coding</link>
      <description>A Disciplined Approach to AI-Assisted Coding</description>
      <guid>https://fjzeit.github.io/coding/lode-coding</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cold Start Problem: Using Network Effects to Scale Your Product - A Review</title>
      <link>https://madhavajay.com/the-cold-start-problem-using-network-effects-to-scale-your-product/</link>
      <description>So you wanna build a Network?
⏱️ Time to read: 12 minutes
👋 Hi to all the HN traffic! Discussion here.
I have to say this is one of the best books I have ever read. Author @andrewchen (Andrew Chen) from a16z goes into depth from personal experience and research on what it takes to build a networked p… </description>
      <guid>https://madhavajay.com/the-cold-start-problem-using-network-effects-to-scale-your-product/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Hire Engineers Who Ship Kernels</title>
      <link>https://vaibhawvipul.github.io/2025/04/22/How-to-Hire-Engineers-Who-Ship-Kernels.html</link>
      <description>** Note - This is from my perspective and learnings as a founding engineer. This is my personal take on how to build tech teams for the future. Not affiliated with any company or my current employer.</description>
      <guid>https://vaibhawvipul.github.io/2025/04/22/How-to-Hire-Engineers-Who-Ship-Kernels.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nix: Better way for fun and profit</title>
      <link>https://www.birkey.co/2025-04-15-nix:-better-way-for-fun-and-profit.html</link>
      <description>Every project depends on existing software that is beyond your
control. Nix DSL enables you to declaratively specify your projects
dependencies, a repo or a tar-ball down to the file digest of its
content, which is what gives nix superpowers of being a deterministic
and reproducible package manager. This means that if your inputs stays
the same, nix guarantees that it produces the exact same output
regardless of when and where. Below is a flake that pulls in latest
version of Clojure into your project.</description>
      <guid>https://www.birkey.co/2025-04-15-nix:-better-way-for-fun-and-profit.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP supply chain attack: Official NPM package infected with crypto stealing backdoor</title>
      <link>https://www.aikido.dev/blog/xrp-supplychain-attack-official-npm-package-infected-with-crypto-stealing-backdoor</link>
      <description>The official XPRL (Ripple) NPM package was compromised by sophisticated attackers who put in a backdoor to steal cryptocurrency private keys and gain access to cryptocurrency wallets.</description>
      <guid>https://www.aikido.dev/blog/xrp-supplychain-attack-official-npm-package-infected-with-crypto-stealing-backdoor</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 22:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the AI Dev Gallery: Your Gateway to Local AI Development with .NET - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-ai-dev-gallery-gateway-to-local-ai-development/</link>
      <description>Discover the new AI Dev Gallery, a Windows application that provides interactive local AI samples, easy model downloads, and source code export - all built with .NET AI building blocks.</description>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-ai-dev-gallery-gateway-to-local-ai-development/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 18:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do We Maintain Code Quality and Technical Debt in Our .NET Codebase?</title>
      <link>https://www.berkansasmaz.com/how-do-we-maintain-code-quality-and-technical-debt-in-our-net-codebase/</link>
      <description>Maintaining code quality and managing technical debt is a never-ending journey in any codebase — and it’s no different for us working with .NET. As a maintainer of the ABP Framework and someone who regularly provides support and training for developers building real-world enterprise applications with ABP, I want to</description>
      <guid>https://www.berkansasmaz.com/how-do-we-maintain-code-quality-and-technical-debt-in-our-net-codebase/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Engineer Scott Seiber on Early AI with Microsoft Bob's Rover and Our AI Future</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=kSsLuEkmkII</link>
      <description>Register for Microsoft Build - https://build.microsoft.com

Scott helped revolutionize how Microsoft software operates on Mac, bridging the Windows-Mac divide long before cross-platform excellence was the norm. He also contributed significantly to Microsoft Bob, a daring initiative designed to bring a human touch to computing by creating an engaging, accessible interface. Join me as we explore the fascinating stories behind these pivotal contributions!

Scott on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/scott-seiber-46088a/

Chapters:
00:00 - Intro
01:05 - Scott's Origin Story
03:00 - Natural Computing with Bob
04:15 - Software Engineer Journey
08:20 - Infusing AI into work and live
09:30 - Why Still at Microsoft &amp; Future Excitement? 
11:04 - Wrap-up

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCENTmbKaTphpWV2R2evVz2A/join

👕 Buy some swag! - https://jamesmontemagno.myspreadshop.com/
☕️ Buy me a coffee - https://www.buymeacoffee.com/jamesmontemagno

Follow:
👨‍💻 GitHub: https://github.com/jamesmontemagno
🦜 X: https://x.com/jamesmontemagno
📄 Website: https://www.montemagno.com
📰 Newsletter: https://newsletter.montemagno.com/

Disclaimer: This channel, videos, and streams are created in my spare time and are a product of me... James Montemagno! They are NOT officially affiliated or endorsed by Microsoft (my employer) in any way. Opinions and views are my own.

What is on my hat? It is the CLE clothing logo because I am from Cleveland! Checkout their awesome CLE merch: https://cleclothingco.myshopify.com/

What is that art on my wall? It is an original piece from the French street artist Gregos of La Butte Montmartre: https://www.instagram.com/p/BceZ1oNHiQx/

My Setup:
📷 Canon M50 Mark II - https://amzn.to/3P8R7lp
💡 Nanoleaf Elements Lights - https://amzn.to/3umwJVW
🎙 Blue Spark Microphone - https://amzn.to/3qgtYkq
🎙 Blue Pop Filter - https://amzn.to/3jEWM3r
🤳 Rode Microphone Arm - https://amzn.to/2Z68AlE
🎧 Sony MDR7306 Headphones - https://amzn.to/372jxta
📲 Stream Deck - https://amzn.to/373Uk1n
🖱 MX Master 2S Mouse - https://amzn.to/3d7J2gj
⌨️ Tecware Phantom Keyboard - https://amzn.to/3aUP4y9

Using links I provide I may receive a commission if you buy something which helps support the channel.

#Microsoft50 #microsoftemployee #windows #developer #interview #microsoftbob #ai</description>
      <author> (James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=kSsLuEkmkII</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>