<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>US government agencies demand fixable ice cream machines</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2024/03/ftc-and-doj-want-to-free-mcdonalds-ice-cream-machines-from-dmca-repair-rules/</link>
      <description>McFlurries are a notable part of petition for commercial and industrial repairs.</description>
      <author> (Kevin Purdy
    -    3/15/2024, 9:26 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2024/03/ftc-and-doj-want-to-free-mcdonalds-ice-cream-machines-from-dmca-repair-rules/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A noisy place</title>
      <link>https://notes.ghed.in/posts/2024/a-noisy-place/</link>
      <description>In A quiet place, horrible and hypersensitive monsters kill human beings who make any noise. May my peers forgive me, but I think the monsters in the movie h...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.ghed.in/posts/2024/a-noisy-place/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Soft Delete With EF Core</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/implementing-soft-delete-with-ef-core</link>
      <description>A soft delete is a data persistence strategy that prevents the permanent deletion of records from your database. Today, we&amp;#39;ll dive into the details of how to implement soft deletes using EF Core.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/implementing-soft-delete-with-ef-core</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Offshoring of Thought and Memory - multiverses</title>
      <link>https://www.multiverses.xyz/facts/the-offshoring-of-thought-and-memory/</link>
      <description>In The Secret Miracle by Borges, a man condemned to death is granted an unusual reprieve by God. As he stands before the firing squad, the soldiers, his body, the world stop. Only his thoughts continue. In the year of mental time given, he labours on a play. At the point of completion, he is</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.multiverses.xyz/facts/the-offshoring-of-thought-and-memory/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partnerships vs Solopreneurship and Partnership Do’s and Don’ts - Dan Norris</title>
      <link>https://dannorris.me/partnerships-vs-solopreneurship-and-partnership-dos-and-donts/</link>
      <description>I had someone reach out to me recently and ask if I’d written anything on this topic and I don’t believe I have since my first book, The 7 Day Startup, where I talked a lot about the importance of finding a co-founder.&amp;#160; In the years since, all of my business partnerships have ultimately broken […]</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/dannorrisprofile)</author>
      <guid>https://dannorris.me/partnerships-vs-solopreneurship-and-partnership-dos-and-donts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A web framework for Zig – Kamil Tomš&amp;#237;k</title>
      <link>https://tomsik.cz/posts/tokamak/</link>
      <description>I’ve been recently extracting some parts of Ava into a separate open-source
projects, and one of them is Tokamak, a web framework for Zig.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tomsik.cz/posts/tokamak/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Translations Are Important, Too</title>
      <link>https://bgammon.org/blog/20240315-translations-are-important-too/</link>
      <description>An essay on the importance of free software translations</description>
      <author> (Trevor Slocum)</author>
      <guid>https://bgammon.org/blog/20240315-translations-are-important-too/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing technology to kids through storytelling</title>
      <link>https://pigro.me/blog/teaching-journey-day-1/</link>
      <description>This blog post shares my experiences and challenges in bringing the magic of tech to a young audience in Turin. It is a reflection on bridging the gap between curiosity and understanding, tailored for educators parents, and anyone interested in the transformative power of tech education.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pigro.me/blog/teaching-journey-day-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Code Review of My Earliest Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.dannyguo.com/blog/a-code-review-of-my-earliest-projects</link>
      <description>While I was cleaning my personal files, I found my earliest programming
projects, which are over a decade old. I decided to do a code review for fun. Do
you know that feeling of reading code that’s only vaguely familiar, being mildly
horrified, and then realizing that you were in fact the one who wrote it? Yeah,
I got that a lot while looking at this code. Here are the highlights from three
projects: forex trading, The Daily Lore, and MovieSeer.</description>
      <author> (Bad Commit Author)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dannyguo.com/blog/a-code-review-of-my-earliest-projects</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> The demise of coding is greatly exaggerated</title>
      <link>http://muratbuffalo.blogspot.com/2024/03/the-demise-of-coding-is-greatly.html</link>
      <description>NVDIA CEO Jensen Huang recently made very contraversial remarks : &amp;quot;Over the course of the last 10 years, 15 years, almost everybody who sits...</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>http://muratbuffalo.blogspot.com/2024/03/the-demise-of-coding-is-greatly.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataviz is Hierarchical</title>
      <link>https://docs.malloydata.dev/blog/2024-02-29-hierarchical-viz/</link>
      <description>If only our data tools agreed</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://docs.malloydata.dev/blog/2024-02-29-hierarchical-viz/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the BYOD, BYOC (briging your own cloud): a journey from Home to the World</title>
      <link>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2024/03/09/after-the-byod-byoc-briging-your-own-cloud-a-journey-from-home-to-the-world.html</link>
      <description>Discover how I transformed my reMarkable tablet into a portable whiteboard &amp;#128210;✨, accessible from anywhere via a secure WireGuard VPN (tailscale) and cloud-based reverse proxy setup.
From the comforts of WFH to the dynamic world of mobility, learn the tech behind the solution.</description>
      <author> (Olivier Wulveryck)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2024/03/09/after-the-byod-byoc-briging-your-own-cloud-a-journey-from-home-to-the-world.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving awful compression with digits of pi</title>
      <link>https://ntietz.com/blog/why-we-cant-compress-messages-with-pi/</link>
      <description>Compression is a really hard problem, and it attracts a lot of interesting ideas.
There are some numbers whose digits contain all sequences of digits1.
People have long hypothesized that pi is one such number; a proof remains elusive.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ntietz.com/blog/why-we-cant-compress-messages-with-pi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the BYOD, BYOC (bringing your own cloud): a journey from Home to the World</title>
      <link>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2024/03/09/after-the-byod-byoc-bringing-your-own-cloud-a-journey-from-home-to-the-world.html</link>
      <description>Discover how I transformed my reMarkable tablet into a portable whiteboard &amp;#128210;✨, accessible from anywhere via a secure WireGuard VPN (tailscale) and cloud-based reverse proxy setup.
From the comforts of WFH to the dynamic world of mobility, learn the tech behind the solution.</description>
      <author> (Olivier Wulveryck)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2024/03/09/after-the-byod-byoc-bringing-your-own-cloud-a-journey-from-home-to-the-world.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Built a Bootstrapped Consulting Company: From Zero To 60k€ Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.eidel.io/building-consulting-company-60k/</link>
      <description>I’m part of a few incubators where I mingle with future startup founders and pretend to have knowledge on how to build a startup. Generally speaking, I perceive myself as being relatively clueless, but then again, when the founders ask me some questions, I briefly think that I actually have something useful to share.</description>
      <author> (Oliver Eidel)</author>
      <guid>https://www.eidel.io/building-consulting-company-60k/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browser Ball Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://romanbaiocco.github.io/browser-ball-reloaded/</link>
      <description>Definitely more cool than you think it will be</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://romanbaiocco.github.io/browser-ball-reloaded/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>failing miserably to scale kubes</title>
      <link>https://breadchris.com/blog/failing-miserably-to-scale-kubes/</link>
      <description>I run a cyber security competition for high schoolers every year. Yesterday was the 7th iteration. Months of planning go into designing the story and putting together digital evidence for the competitors to try to solve a murder mystery. It was a special event because the organizers who built it for my high school self stoked my passion for security. Unfortunately, it did not go as planned this year. After giving the introduction talk to 350 students, the site got DOSed from the concurrent load of everyone accessing it.</description>
      <author> (breadchris)</author>
      <guid>https://breadchris.com/blog/failing-miserably-to-scale-kubes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acquired in 99 days</title>
      <link>https://austinhenley.com/blog/acquiredin99days.html</link>
      <description>I joined a startup as CTO, then we were acquired 99 days later.</description>
      <author> (Austin Z. Henley)</author>
      <guid>https://austinhenley.com/blog/acquiredin99days.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest year in human history</title>
      <link>https://shobhitic.com/longest-year</link>
      <description>I was just casually thinking about the Roman Empire (as one usually does).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shobhitic.com/longest-year</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read TLS/SSL Certificate in Azure App Service from C# Code</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/03/read-tlsssl-certificate-in-azure-app.html</link>
      <description>.NET, .NET Core, ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2024/03/read-tlsssl-certificate-in-azure-app.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Decline of Work-Life Balance: A 12-Year Tech Industry Perspective</title>
      <link>https://enginebogie.com/public/charchaa/post/the-decline-of-work-life-balance-a-12-year-tech-industry-perspective/144</link>
      <description>Work-life culture is ruined today. I can say it confidently because I have spent 12+ years in the industry. Situations, now and 12 years back when I started, were pretty different in tech than what they are today.

When I started back in 2012, I remember the situation was not like this. People valued work-life balance. People valued that the employees have a life too outside their work.

I remember a time of around 2014, when I was working on something pretty late like 8 pm or so. And my skip-level manager saw me working. His statement exactly was “Udit never work so late, it harms your health. You should go back home on time”. I never knew in the later years of my career, that I would starve for such a a culture. Since then trust me, nowhere I have experienced the same culture. It is ruining day by day.

Today, the situation is everywhere working at 8 pm is pretty normal and people would expect you to be working at even 11 pm too. And actually, people boast about it. They get promoted for working late creating pressure on others. If someone is completing their work timely and maintaining good work and life, they are called underperformers.

The rant will keep going on. I am not against any specific person. Nor do I think any single person is to blame. But then the shift has happened and I HATE &amp;#128545; it.

I have some theories of my own like what could have led to it. But want to hear what thoughts all of you have?
 Whatever kind of mentorship session you need. Be it mock interview, career guidance or anything. We have got you covered. We have various experts with different background and expertise. Just find the one best suited for you and schedule a session.</description>
      <author> (Engine Bogie)</author>
      <guid>https://enginebogie.com/public/charchaa/post/the-decline-of-work-life-balance-a-12-year-tech-industry-perspective/144</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwa</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2907/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2907/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollama now supports AMD graphics cards &amp;#183; Ollama Blog</title>
      <link>https://ollama.com/blog/amd-preview</link>
      <description>Ollama now supports AMD graphics cards in preview on Windows and Linux. All the features of Ollama can now be accelerated by AMD graphics cards on Ollama for Linux and Windows.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ollama.com/blog/amd-preview</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 21:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How well does WRL ComPtr support class template argument deduction (CTAD)? - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240315-00/?p=109537</link>
      <description>It tries too hard and accidentally breaks CTAD.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240315-00/?p=109537</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 17:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - RajSolai/TextSnatcher: How to Copy Text from Images ? Answer is TextSnatcher !. Perform OCR operations in seconds on Linux Desktop.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/RajSolai/TextSnatcher</link>
      <description>How to Copy Text from Images ? Answer is TextSnatcher !. Perform OCR operations in seconds on Linux Desktop. - RajSolai/TextSnatcher</description>
      <author> (RajSolai)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/RajSolai/TextSnatcher</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from looking at 900 most popular open source AI tools</title>
      <link>https://huyenchip.com/2024/03/14/ai-oss.html</link>
      <description>Four years ago, I did an analysis of the open source ML ecosystem. Since then, the landscape has changed, so I revisited the topic. This time, I focused exclusively on the stack around foundation models.</description>
      <author> (Chip Huyen)</author>
      <guid>https://huyenchip.com/2024/03/14/ai-oss.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More powerful Go execution traces - The Go Programming Language</title>
      <link>https://go.dev/blog/execution-traces-2024</link>
      <description>New features and improvements to execution traces from the last year.</description>
      <author> (Michael Knyszek
      14 March 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://go.dev/blog/execution-traces-2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 11:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Getty Makes Nearly 88,000 Art Images Free to Use However You Like</title>
      <link>https://www.openculture.com/2024/03/the-getty-makes-nearly-88000-art-images-free-to-use-however-you-like.html</link>
      <description>Since the J. Paul Getty Museum launched its Open Content program back in 2013, we&amp;#39;ve been featuring their efforts to&amp;#160;make their vast collection of cultural artifacts freely accessible online.</description>
      <author> (in Archives, Museums |   	March 8th, 2024  6 Comments)</author>
      <guid>https://www.openculture.com/2024/03/the-getty-makes-nearly-88000-art-images-free-to-use-however-you-like.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Performance Tip: Retrieving the Process Id</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/03/15/general-performance-tips-for-microsoft-net-retrieving-the-process-path/</link>
      <description>When working with .NET, there are two options to obtain the initiating process ID. The Process type and System.Environment both provide methods for this. Benchmark tests reveal that using the Proce…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/03/15/general-performance-tips-for-microsoft-net-retrieving-the-process-path/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboarding roulette: deleting our employee accounts daily</title>
      <link>https://graphite.dev/blog/onboarding-roulette</link>
      <description>I’m a strong believer in automated tests - and a moderately disciplined author of them. Software engineering is exceptionally hard to get functionally correct, and even harder to avoid regressing later. As my wise teammate Dave says, “Legacy code is any code that doesn’t have a test.”</description>
      <author> (Written by)</author>
      <guid>https://graphite.dev/blog/onboarding-roulette</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINQ Query Improvements in Marten 7</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/03/14/linq-query-improvements-in-marten-7/</link>
      <description>Working inside of the LINQ provider code that’s ultimately interpreting C# code and trying to turn that into the most efficient Pgpsql code possible somehow makes me think about Alice in Wond…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/03/14/linq-query-improvements-in-marten-7/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate Local .NET Secrets from Azure Deployments - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/generate-dotnet-secrets-automatically-from-azure-deployment/</link>
      <description>This post shows how to automatically generate .NET secrets that a .NET app can use from the Azure deployment.</description>
      <author> (Frank Boucher)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/generate-dotnet-secrets-automatically-from-azure-deployment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NuGet.org repository signing certificate will be updated as soon as April 8th, 2024 - The NuGet Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/nuget/the-nuget-org-repository-signing-certificate-will-be-updated-as-soon-as-april-8th-2024/</link>
      <description>Action required: If you validate that packages are repository signed by NuGet.org using a NuGet client policy, NuGet.exe verify command, or the dotnet nuget verify command, please follow these steps by April 8th, 2024 to avoid potential disruptions when installing new NuGet.org packages.</description>
      <author> (Erick Yondon)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/nuget/the-nuget-org-repository-signing-certificate-will-be-updated-as-soon-as-april-8th-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Github Copilot– Some experimentation</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/03/github-copilot-some-experimentation.html</link>
      <description>I was reading the following blog post  when I thought:  &amp;quot;How good (or bad) would Github Copilot handle the scenario&amp;#39;s mentioned in the post?...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/03/github-copilot-some-experimentation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot in Visual Studio: A Recap of 2023 - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/github-copilot-in-visual-studio-a-recap-of-2023/</link>
      <description>In the rapidly evolving world of software development, staying ahead of the curve is crucial. The introduction of AI in Visual Studio, particularly GitHub Copilot, has revolutionized the way developers code. With Copilot integrated into Visual Studio, you can leverage AI to streamline your workflows,</description>
      <author> (Amy Nguyen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/github-copilot-in-visual-studio-a-recap-of-2023/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>