<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>This Insane 2.5 Gigapixel Image of the Orion Constellation Took Five Years To Complete</title>
      <link>https://petapixel.com/2020/10/23/this-insane-2-5-gigapixel-image-of-the-orion-constellation-took-five-years-to-complete/</link>
      <description>In a project that took 5 years to capture, 500 hours of editing, and 42 total hours to process, astrophotographer Matt Harbison has completed a dream</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://petapixel.com/2020/10/23/this-insane-2-5-gigapixel-image-of-the-orion-constellation-took-five-years-to-complete/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 19:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anki as Learning Superpower: Computer Science Edition | G Research</title>
      <link>https://www.gresearch.co.uk/article/anki-as-learning-superpower-computer-science-edition/</link>
      <description>Create today. Predict tomorrow.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.gresearch.co.uk/article/anki-as-learning-superpower-computer-science-edition/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 19:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am an Uighur who faced China’s concentration camps. This is my story.</title>
      <link>https://www.varsity.co.uk/interviews/19990</link>
      <description>In the first installment of our new series shedding light on current humanitarian crises, Victor Jack sits with Ӧmir Bekali, a Uighur Muslim who recounts his imprisonment, torture and indoctrination at the han</description>
      <author> (by Victor Jack)</author>
      <guid>https://www.varsity.co.uk/interviews/19990</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 17:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Ball &amp;#187; Announcing GitTorrent: A Decentralized GitHub</title>
      <link>https://blog.printf.net/articles/2015/05/29/announcing-gittorrent-a-decentralized-github/</link>
      <description>(This post is an aspirational transcript of the talk I gave to the Data Terra Nemo conference in May 2015. If you’d like to watch the less eloquent version of the same talk that I actually gave, the video should be available soon!)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.printf.net/articles/2015/05/29/announcing-gittorrent-a-decentralized-github/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 15:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The .NET Stacks #22: .NET 5 RC 2 ships, .NET Foundation all hands, and links</title>
      <link>https://daveabrock.com/2020/10/24/dotnet-stacks-22</link>
      <description>I messaged a developer friend to see if he liked my puns, and he said “false.” I told him I didn’t appreciate the cyber boolean.</description>
      <author> (Dave Brock)</author>
      <guid>https://daveabrock.com/2020/10/24/dotnet-stacks-22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 15:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>prabhuignoto/react-chrono</title>
      <link>https://github.com/prabhuignoto/react-chrono</link>
      <description>Modern Timeline component for React. Contribute to prabhuignoto/react-chrono development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (prabhuignoto)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/prabhuignoto/react-chrono</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 14:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 U.S. Traffic Deaths Lowest Since 2014, but 2020 Numbers Aren&amp;#39;t Looking Good</title>
      <link>https://www.caranddriver.com/news/a34240145/2019-2020-traffic-deaths-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>In the COVID-19 era, fatal accident percentages are up this year despite the smaller number of vehicles on the roads, NHTSA&amp;#39;s latest data shows.</description>
      <author> (By
					Sebastian Blanco)</author>
      <guid>https://www.caranddriver.com/news/a34240145/2019-2020-traffic-deaths-coronavirus/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 13:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Play Music, Music Play Store &amp;amp; Music Manager are going away – everything you need to know</title>
      <link>https://support.google.com/youtubemusic/thread/62843644</link>
      <description>We’re gradually going to shut down Google Play Music, the Music Store on Google Play and Music Manager soon, with everyone losing access in the months to come. You can read our full announcement here. This announcement follows the launch of our new migration process (back in May) which lets all Google Play Music listeners easily transfer their data and make the simple switch to YouTube Music. To know more about these shut downs and what it means for you, read on below.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://support.google.com/youtubemusic/thread/62843644</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 12:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tin-eared, tone-deaf - Selaine Saxby gets it very, very wrong - West Country Bylines</title>
      <link>https://westcountrybylines.co.uk/tin-eared-tone-deaf-selaine-saxby-gets-it-very-very-wrong/</link>
      <description>No-one should have to tolerate abuse in the workplace and bullying is wholly unacceptable. An MP is a public servant with a duty of care to his or her constituents. Having taken on a public role, MPs must expect to attract opprobrium if they act in ways which their constituents do not like. They should […]</description>
      <author> (Anthea Simmons)</author>
      <guid>https://westcountrybylines.co.uk/tin-eared-tone-deaf-selaine-saxby-gets-it-very-very-wrong/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 11:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electoral College Decision Tree</title>
      <link>https://observablehq.com/@observablehq/electoral-college-decision-tree</link>
      <description>An Observable notebook.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://observablehq.com/@observablehq/electoral-college-decision-tree</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 08:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gnu.org</title>
      <link>https://www.gnu.org/philosophy/right-to-read.en.html</link>
      <description>This article appeared in the February 1997 issue
of Communications of the ACM (Volume 40, Number
2).</description>
      <author> (by Richard Stallman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gnu.org/philosophy/right-to-read.en.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 04:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Entity Framework Core with Azure SQL DB and Azure Cosmos DB | Azure Friday</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Using-Entity-Framework-Core-with-Azure-SQL-DB-and-Azure-Cosmos-DB</link>
      <description>Jeremy Likness shows Scott Hanselman how to use Entity Framework (EF) Core with Azure SQL DB and Azure Cosmos DB.</description>
      <author> (by Scott Hanselman, Rob Caron)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Using-Entity-Framework-Core-with-Azure-SQL-DB-and-Azure-Cosmos-DB</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 03:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>r/csharp - Matlab porting to C# goes really slow</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/csharp/comments/jgjw4s/matlab_porting_to_c_goes_really_slow/</link>
      <description>2 votes and 39 comments so far on Reddit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/csharp/comments/jgjw4s/matlab_porting_to_c_goes_really_slow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 02:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>github/dmca</title>
      <link>https://github.com/github/dmca/blob/master/2020/10/2020-10-23-RIAA.md</link>
      <description>Repository with text of DMCA takedown notices as received. GitHub does not endorse or adopt any assertion contained in the following notices. Users identified in the notices are presumed innocent u...</description>
      <author> (github)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/github/dmca/blob/master/2020/10/2020-10-23-RIAA.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Drag and Drop Bookmarklet</title>
      <link>https://joeldare.com/creating_a_drag_and_drop_bookmarklet</link>
      <description>Bookmarklets are small JavaScript snippets that are invoked when you click on a bookmark.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joeldare.com/creating_a_drag_and_drop_bookmarklet</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On self-tracking, exobrains and quantified self</title>
      <link>https://existentialist.xyz/on-self-tracking-exobrains-and-quantified-self/</link>
      <description>&amp;#129504; The art, science and technology of understanding oneself. </description>
      <author> (Slav)</author>
      <guid>https://existentialist.xyz/on-self-tracking-exobrains-and-quantified-self/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penetration Testing and Low-Cost Freelancing</title>
      <link>https://sophron.github.io/lowcost-freelancing-pentest/</link>
      <description>Penetration testing is complex. For it to be successful, the tester needs to possess a variety of different abilities and skills. Some testers rely only on automated tools, while others focus more on manual analysis. While a creative and unconventional way of thinking is necessary, it is also important for the tester to possess the mental discipline to adhere to the time constraints set by the client. It is common for a creative penetration tester to spend a significant amount of time investigating a fun and uncommon exploit, only to realize later that there is not enough time left to provide complete coverage. It is, therefore, not surprising that two different testers will produce two separate reports that include different findings.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sophron.github.io/lowcost-freelancing-pentest/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Still Dislike My Home Work Setup (and I don&amp;#39;t know what to do about it)</title>
      <link>https://blog.eyas.sh/2020/10/bad-home-work-setup/</link>
      <description>Six months in, I still hate my work from home setup. I  can&amp;#39;t  be the only one
with problems, but my inability to figure this out makes it feel like it. This
is…</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/eyas.sharaiha)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.eyas.sh/2020/10/bad-home-work-setup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The YouTube-DL Takedown</title>
      <link>https://resynth1943.net/articles/youtube-dl-takedown/</link>
      <description>GitHub has removed the ability to access youtube-dl&amp;#39;s source code due to a DMCA.</description>
      <author> (resynth1943)</author>
      <guid>https://resynth1943.net/articles/youtube-dl-takedown/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parenting doesn’t do what I thought</title>
      <link>https://critter.blog/2020/10/23/parenting-doesnt-do-what-i-thought/</link>
      <description>Turns out, there’s very little changing we can do to our kids. That’s both scary and freeing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://critter.blog/2020/10/23/parenting-doesnt-do-what-i-thought/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Solution to Big Tech Isn&amp;#39;t Legislation, It&amp;#39;s Technology</title>
      <link>https://battlepenguin.com/tech/the-solution-to-big-tech-isnt-legislation-its-technology/#fnref:12</link>
      <description>Over the course of 2020, we’ve seen increased censorship from every major digital content platform. It culminated with both Facebook and Twitter bloc...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://battlepenguin.com/tech/the-solution-to-big-tech-isnt-legislation-its-technology/#fnref:12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So Many Notebooks, So Little Time...</title>
      <link>https://mco.dev/so-many-notebooks-so-little-time.../</link>
      <description>Jupyter Notebooks are awesome but there are so many. Just at Google we have Colab, Kaggle Notebooks, and Cloud AI Platform Notebooks. So which should you use? The answer is “it depends”. This session will summarize your options and try to help you choose the best notebook for your needs.</description>
      <author> (Marc Cohen)</author>
      <guid>https://mco.dev/so-many-notebooks-so-little-time.../</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should I buy the dip?</title>
      <link>https://carlosbaraza.com/should-i-buy-the-dip/</link>
      <description>For quite some time I&amp;#39;ve been monitoring the markets, and waiting for a dip to invest my cash. However, a few weeks ago I decided to put this assumption to the test. Is buying the dip the best I could do with my hard earned cash? The contextLike most employees,</description>
      <author> (Carlos Baraza)</author>
      <guid>https://carlosbaraza.com/should-i-buy-the-dip/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;m handing over maintenance of wlroots and sway to Simon Ser</title>
      <link>https://drewdevault.com/2020/10/23/Im-handing-wlroots-and-sway-to-Simon.html</link>
      <description>Over the past several months, I’ve been gradually weaning down my role in both
projects, and as a contributor to Wayland in general. I feel that I’ve already
accomplished everything I set out to do with Wayland — and more! I have
been happily using sway as my daily driver for well over a year with no
complaints or conspicuously absent features. For me, there’s little reason to
stay involved. This will likely come as no surprise to many who’ve kept their
ear to the ground in these communities.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://drewdevault.com/2020/10/23/Im-handing-wlroots-and-sway-to-Simon.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>r/dotnet - What would be the reasons to use an IoC framework instead of the default container?</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/dotnet/comments/jg1gcs/what_would_be_the_reasons_to_use_an_ioc_framework/</link>
      <description>54 votes and 65 comments so far on Reddit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/dotnet/comments/jg1gcs/what_would_be_the_reasons_to_use_an_ioc_framework/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Buy a Computer for Cross-Platform Development</title>
      <link>https://christianfindlay.com/2020/10/23/buy-crossplatform-dev-computer/</link>
      <description>
Computers are expensive, and you may need to buy a Mac and a PC as a mobile developer. As a mobile developer, you will spend a large amount of time building and deploying to phones or using emulators. All this can eat time on a slow computer. This article aims at guiding you on the decision-making process of buying a computer, and hopefully, how to save money. I&amp;#39;m a&amp;#160;Xamarin&amp;#160;developer, but most of this article will help people who develop for&amp;#160;Flutter,&amp;#160;React Native, Blazor, Vue.js, React, ,Angular, or do cross-platform development in general.&amp;#160;



Support this blog by signing up to my course Introduction to Uno Platform



Disclaimer: I&amp;#39;m not a hardware expert, and this is not business advice. This is information based on my experience only.



CPU Mark



I will refer to a measurement called CPU mark. This is a good, reasonably objective way to measure the speed of your CPU. I won&amp;#39;t spend hours explaining the intricacies of different CPU features for different purposes. You should know that CPU Mark will give you a rough indicator of speed, and it is very useful for comparing computers.



Mac, PC, or Both?



The first question you need to ask is whether or not you need both. Mac looks like a good option because you can deploy to iOS and Android, and you can simulate iOS on a Mac. You can also run&amp;#160;Parallels&amp;#160;to run Windows as a virtual machine. This means that you can do Windows development. However, there are drawbacks to Macs. The main drawback is that generally speaking, they are more expensive than PCs. If you have a large budget, you should probably go for the top of the range Mac that suits your needs. If you need portability, you should go for a MacBook Pro, but the faster Mac Pros will be faster than the MacBooks. If you have plenty of money and only want one computer, and the Mac is fast enough, go for the Mac. Personally, I have both because Macs are really nice for certain things, while a high-end PC is far less expensive than a high-end Mac.



Mac



For many people, high-end Macs are prohibitively expensive, but if you don&amp;#39;t have a high-end one, you will be wasting time. It will be slow, and your ability to code will suffer. I have the best custom spec mac-mini available at the time of writing. This is a good computer, and I would recommend it if you want to spend the money. However, it&amp;#39;s not as fast as a PC at around the same price. Generally speaking, Mac-minis have decent value, are very quiet, and reliable.



Mac mini (2018)



3.2 GHz 6-Core Intel Core i7-8700B&amp;#160;16 GB 2667 MHz DDR4Intel UHD Graphics 630 1536 MB



I believe&amp;#160;this article&amp;#160;to describe the CPU. It rates the CPU Mark at about 12,200, which is very good for the price.



Opt for Mac if you want to write macOS apps, prefer the operating system, and want more iOS support.



PC



If you go for a PC only, you won&amp;#39;t get an iOS simulator out of the box. It is possible to deploy apps to a physical iOS device from Windows, and many people prefer doing this. However, this is a relatively recent turn of events and is not well-supported yet.&amp;#160;Apparently, it is possible to run a macOS Virtual Machine from Windows, but I have never tried this, and I can&amp;#39;t vouch for how well this works. Apple has a habit of making it difficult for people to use their OS without the official hardware. Please hit me up if you try this.&amp;#160;This article&amp;#160;walks you through deploying a Xamarin app to iOS from Windows.



As you will see, PC gives you a lot of options for the $1000-$2000 mark that Macs simply don&amp;#39;t. You can buy a very fast PC for under $2000 USD if the parts are cheap in your local area.



AMD has recently entered the market with CPUs that have outstanding value. I bought this computer which was actually cheaper than the mac-mini. If you go by CPU Mark, this computer is about 2.5x faster than the Mac mini. It has double the RAM and double the disk space. The case is massive, but this computer is almost as quiet as a Mac-mini, and I can also run nearly any modern game at very high detail.&amp;#160;



DYI PC



CPU-AMD-3900X&amp;#160; &amp;lt;- CPU 32,000+ CPU MarkMB-ASU-X570PC RAM-DD4-32GVK8DRAM-DD4-32GVK8D &amp;lt;- 32 GB RAMVGA-MSI-1650VXS &amp;lt;- Decent gaming graphicsNET-TPL-T5ECAS-CLM-S600TGPOW-CLM-MPY750C SER-SYS-ASS-70 &amp;lt;- Very quiet power supplyCT1000MX500SSD1 MX500 1TB 2.5 SATA SSD &amp;lt;- 1TB SSD



Opt for PC if iOS is not your focus, and you don&amp;#39;t need to build for macOS. If you have a lower budget and choose this option, you will save time on builds, etc. This is a money-saving option, but you won&amp;#39;t have as good an experience on the Mac front.



Value For Money



When you buy a Mac, you pay for the hardware, the 5-year guarantee, and the finished product. If you buy a PC, you might have hardware compatibility issues, and you may have to add and remove hardware. You may need to take some parts back to the store or install Windows yourself. But, you get to choose the CPU. The CPU is the heart of your computer, and a fast CPU will decrease build and deploy times. CPU power is particularly relevant today because there has been a sudden jump in value for money. AMD are back, and they are challenging Intel. As you can see, most of the CPUs with the best value for money are AMD CPUs. Apple may also embrace AMD CPUs, but you are only free to buy the best value CPUs on PC for now.



Snapshot as at 23rd October 2020



If you choose a PC, keep an eye on this page because it gives you a good idea of the best value CPUs. Use it as a guideline, so you don&amp;#39;t waste money on CPUs with poor value.



Wrap-Up



PCs can give you better value for money, but it comes at the cost of piecing the computer together or buying from a manufacturer. You could look at Macs as having excellent value because of the integration of the hardware, software, and the guarantee that all this will last for five years.



Of course, the development experience is a large factor. If you have the luxury of choosing, then go for the OS that suits you the best. Using the other OS as a Virtual Machine may be an option.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://christianfindlay.com/2020/10/23/buy-crossplatform-dev-computer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How bare metal provisioning works in theory</title>
      <link>https://gianarb.it/blog/how-bare-metal-works-in-theory</link>
      <description>What I learned about how bare metal provisioning works developing tinkerbell.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gianarb.it/blog/how-bare-metal-works-in-theory</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No More Politics in the Workplace – jake lazaroff</title>
      <link>https://jake.nyc/words/no-more-politics-in-the-workplace/</link>
      <description>Last night, Expensify CEO David Barrett sent an email urging all their customers to vote for Joe Biden. The response was predictably polarizing, with a lot of people arguing that workplaces shouldn’t be politicized.
    Okay, fine. But if we’re doing this, can we carry it through to the end? Because I can think of a lot of corporate political activism that the people complaining are suspiciously quiet about.
    </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jake.nyc/words/no-more-politics-in-the-workplace/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Twitch: Join the Live Coding Community!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=paFHjYhtKVU</link>
      <description>Have you heard about Twitch.tv? Twitch is a live streaming platform that allows you to connect, ask questions and learn by watching developers code live! It&amp;#39;s a great place to join virtual communities to continue your learning journey. In this session we&amp;#39;ll share everything you need to know to get started with twitch and live streaming - whether you want to watch them or produce your own. You won&amp;#39;t want to miss this session and opportunity to learn from Brian Clark who&amp;#39;s been live coding for over two years!

Join the Twitch Microsoft Developer Community: https://www.twitch.tv/microsoftdeveloper?WT.mc_id=SDC-8397-Brian.Clark</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Developer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=paFHjYhtKVU</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 23:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Maze Weekly #48 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-48/</link>
      <description>Hey everyone, W…. eekend is coming, and that’s our favorite time to relax and recharge. We’ve prepared a fresh batch of interesting articles for you to enjoy this time. So prepare your favorite brew, sit down, and pick your favorite topic from the list. .NET and C# How to Use F# from C# [christianfindlay.com] Just […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-48/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 23:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks On Gcm With Repeated Nonces: Poc Or It Didn&amp;#39;t Happen</title>
      <link>https://www.cryptologie.net/links/link/2380</link>
      <description>Your name</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cryptologie.net/links/link/2380</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 22:04:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lets Talk .NET 5, with Scott Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Accra-NET-User-Group/events/274017403/</link>
      <description>Sat, Oct 31, 2020, 4:00 PM: .NET has undergone a lot of improvements over the years from the introduction of the open-source .NET Core and other awesome features from language down to compiler. We are</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/Accra-NET-User-Group/events/274017403/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 22:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King County Elections</title>
      <link>https://www.kingcounty.gov/depts/elections.aspx</link>
      <description>King County, with more than 1.3 million registered voters, is the largest jurisdiction in the United States to conduct all elections by mail.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.kingcounty.gov/depts/elections.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 22:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use “pseudo-sets” to control how many actions people take</title>
      <link>https://ariyh.substack.com/p/influence-how-many-actions-people</link>
      <description>When you group tasks or items into a set that when reached feels ‘complete’, you encourage people to reach that exact number.</description>
      <author> (Thomas McKinlay)</author>
      <guid>https://ariyh.substack.com/p/influence-how-many-actions-people</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:36:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How data saves lives: Using the Power Platform to gain amazing insights</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Less-Code-More-Power/How-data-saves-lives-Using-the-Power-Platform-to-gain-amazing-insights</link>
      <description>The DATA Episode: Join Dona and Sarah as we talk to Justyna about how Power BI works and go beyond just throwing data in some charts. Justyna shares with us her journey on how she found Power BI and s</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Less-Code-More-Power/How-data-saves-lives-Using-the-Power-Platform-to-gain-amazing-insights</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# Slides in Usage Ranking of Programming Languages -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/10/23/slashdata-csharp.aspx</link>
      <description>&amp;#39;The fact that C# lost three places in the ranking of language communities during the last three years is mostly explained by its slower growth compared to C/C++ and PHP.&amp;#39;</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel10/23/2020)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/10/23/slashdata-csharp.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Profiling | .NET Async Tool</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Performance-Profiling--NET-Async-Tool</link>
      <description>You know that asynchronous programming makes your UI more responsive. Did you know that you can use the .NET Async tool to profile your async code? Diagnostics PM Sagar Shetty shows how to use this to</description>
      <author> (by Robert Green, Leslie Richardson [MSFT])</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Performance-Profiling--NET-Async-Tool</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fowl Language</title>
      <link>https://social.tinyview.com/fowl-language</link>
      <description>Imperfect parent and coffee enthusiast, Brian Gordon, records his struggles to raise his children while trying to maintain his sanity.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://social.tinyview.com/fowl-language</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro to the Show</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Learn-with-Dr-G/Intro-to-the-Show</link>
      <description>Learning to code is full of AHA moments, epic fails, clarity, confusion, and everything in between. And learning how data plays a role is the code we write adds another layer of excitement. Sarah (Dr.</description>
      <author> (by Sarah Guthals)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Learn-with-Dr-G/Intro-to-the-Show</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryo–electron microscopy breaks the atomic resolution barrier at last</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/10/cryo-electron-microscopy-breaks-atomic-resolution-barrier-last</link>
      <description>Improvements help the technique rival x-ray crystallography</description>
      <author> (By Robert F. ServiceOct. 21, 2020 , 11:00 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/10/cryo-electron-microscopy-breaks-atomic-resolution-barrier-last</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:04:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Entity Framework Core with Azure SQL DB and Azure Cosmos DB | Azure Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FFgS_k_Muk8</link>
      <description>Jeremy Likness shows Scott Hanselman how to use Entity Framework (EF) Core with Azure SQL DB and Azure Cosmos DB. EF Core is a lightweight, extensible, open source, and cross-platform version of the popular Entity Framework data access technology.

0:00 – Overview
1:43 – Using Entity Framework Core with Azure SQL DB (existing)
10:23 – Sidebar: Resolving a demo hiccup
15:07 – Using Entity Framework Core with Azure Cosmos DB (new)
22:09 – Wrap-up

◉ Entity Framework Core overview – https://aka.ms/azfr/647/01
◉ Getting Started with EF Core – https://aka.ms/azfr/647/02
◉ Entity Framework documentation – https://aka.ms/azfr/647/03
◉ Learn: Persist and retrieve relational data with Entity Framework Core – https://aka.ms/azfr/647/04
◉ Create a free account (Azure) – https://aka.ms/azfr/647/free

#Microsoft #Azure</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Azure)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FFgS_k_Muk8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin.Forms 5 Is Here!</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/XamarinForms-5-Is-Here</link>
      <description>This week, James is joined by David Ortinau, Xamarin Principal Program Manager, who is here to talk about all of the goodies that are available in the brand new release Xamarin.Forms 5.0! He walks us </description>
      <author> (by James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/XamarinForms-5-Is-Here</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data’s Role in Moon Missions: Fictional and Real </title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Learn-with-Dr-G/Datas-Role-in-Moon-Missions-Fictional-and-Real</link>
      <description>Completing a successful Moon Mission doesn&amp;#39;t only involve getting to the moon, but also returning safely to Earth – ideally with some rocks to learn from! Join Dr. G as she draws inspiration from the </description>
      <author> (by Sarah Guthals)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Learn-with-Dr-G/Datas-Role-in-Moon-Missions-Fictional-and-Real</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>