<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Building Real-Time Applications With SignalR &amp;amp; .NET 7</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/9_pRk7PwkpY</link>
      <description>&amp;#128640; Support me on Patreon to access the source code: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovicSignalR is probably the most enjoyable library to work with in .NET...</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/9_pRk7PwkpY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 06:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Want a New Drug but it&amp;#39;s a Dream Theater Song</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Rt3v3e5yITo</link>
      <description>Huey Lewis and the NewsI Want a New Drugedited with the time signature changes from Dream Theater&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;Dance of Eternity&amp;quot;from Sports (1983)multitrack audio fro...</description>
      <author> (hueylewisofficial
  
  
  
    hueylewisofficial
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Rt3v3e5yITo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 06:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open source with profanity in comments is statistically better than code without it</title>
      <link>https://blog.desdelinux.net/en/open-source-with-profanity-in-comments-is-statistically-better-than-code-without-it/</link>
      <description>A study details that open source code that contains swear words exhibits significantly better code quality...</description>
      <author> (Darkcrizt)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.desdelinux.net/en/open-source-with-profanity-in-comments-is-statistically-better-than-code-without-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 06:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staff Developer Advocate</title>
      <link>https://jobs.smartrecruiters.com/ni/Square/d6a82029-93a4-46ce-9f6d-28b3591e1368-staff-developer-advocate</link>
      <description>Company Description: TBD is building platforms and protocols that enable developers — from startups to established financial institutions — to more easily create solutions in the decentralized financial space that further economic empowerment globally. TBD’s vision is a decentralized future that returns ownership and control over finances, data, and identity to individuals.&amp;amp;nbsp; We invite the world to join us in creating and adopting open and decentralized technologies that solve real problems for real people. You will be an essential contributor as we deliver this mission.

Job Description: We build platforms and protocols to advance the state of decentralized technologies, and we&amp;#39;re doing it all in the open!&amp;amp;nbsp;We know the best innovations on the web were born in public. They&amp;#39;ve been built with a diverse online community that is willing to question how the internet can better connect us.&amp;amp;nbsp;As a Staff Developer Advocate, your job will be to educate and advocate for one of the most important young communities in the world - the builders of the decentralized web.&amp;amp;nbsp;We’re gaining momentum with our open source projects, and the development community is eager for educational material that helps them navigate this new technology and enable them to build decentralized applications using our Web5 platform.&amp;amp;nbsp;You’ll report to TBD’s Head of Developer Programs, Angie Jones.

Qualifications: If you’re an excellent candidate for this role, you:Are empathetic towards and eager to help others who are seeking to learn about our projects

&amp;amp;nbsp;Excel at effectively explaining complex technical concepts in an engaging way

&amp;amp;nbsp;Get excited about creating unique and interesting content for various mediums (e.g. video, written, audio)

&amp;amp;nbsp;Enjoy diving into specs, API docs, and others’ code to prototype new things on your own

&amp;amp;nbsp;Are a strong programmer with experience in JavaScript/TypeScript and open and willing to work with unfamiliar programming languages to create content as necessary

&amp;amp;nbsp;Are happy to leverage your technical influence to usher a new wave of inclusion and innovation for the web

&amp;amp;nbsp;Appreciate the subject matter expertise of your colleagues and view them as a resource for your own work

&amp;amp;nbsp;Are comfortable working independently

&amp;amp;nbsp;Thrive in ambiguity and are able to quickly adapt to changes

&amp;amp;nbsp;Are excited to advance Self-Sovereign Identity and Decentralized Web Nodes to help developers deliver decentralized applications

&amp;amp;nbsp;* Have 5+ years of relevant experience in Developer Relations
ResponsibilitiesWrite and maintain tutorials and code samples for our projects

&amp;amp;nbsp;Develop small toy applications that demonstrate the use of our platforms and SDKs

&amp;amp;nbsp;Write and curate relevant blog posts

&amp;amp;nbsp;Record demonstrative videos showcasing key project features

&amp;amp;nbsp;Speak at meetups, conferences, and webinars (travel required)

&amp;amp;nbsp;Teach workshops that give developers hands-on experience building decentralized web applications with our open source offerings

&amp;amp;nbsp;Engage with the TBD community via our external social channels

&amp;amp;nbsp;Be an internal advocate for the community and communicate their needs

&amp;amp;nbsp;Create new and exciting initiatives to build engagement with the developer community (e.g. hackathons, contests, etc)

&amp;amp;nbsp;* Collaborate with our various teams such as Open Source Engineering, Open Source Programs, Product, Partnerships, and Marketing/Brand
Developer Relations PortfolioKindly submit samples of your DevRel work that showcase technical content. Links to these samples can be placed in a document and included as a page of your resume.Blog Posts2 - 3 blog posts that you’ve written on technical conceptsTechnical Talks2 - 3 videos of you speaking on a technical topic at a conference, meetup, etc.



Code Samples

1 - 3 examples of code you’ve written for DevRel. This can be GitHub repos of demo apps, workshops, or tutorials that include code samples

&amp;amp;nbsp;Other Relevant Work (optional)

Links to any other relevant DevRel work such as:* podcast episodes where you’ve been a guest or host
* Twitter threads where you’ve explained a technical concept
* Live streams where you’ve talked about a technical concept
* Videos you’ve produced and edited
* Twitter Spaces where you’ve been a guest or host
* Online courses you’ve taught
* Newsletters you’ve authored
* StackOverflow answers you’ve submitted


Additional Information: Block takes a market-based approach to pay, and pay may vary depending on your location. U.S. locations are categorized into one of four zones based on a cost of labor index for that geographic area. The successful candidate’s starting pay will be determined based on job-related skills, experience, qualifications, work location, and market conditions. These ranges may be modified in the future.



Zone A: USD $202,500 - USD $247,500

Zone B: USD $192,400 - USD $235,200

Zone C: USD $182,300 - USD $222,800

Zone D: USD $172,200 - USD $210,400To find a location’s zone designation, please refer to this resource. If a location of interest is not listed, please speak with a recruiter for additional information.&amp;amp;nbsp;Full-time employee benefits include the following:* Healthcare coverage (Medical, Vision and Dental insurance)
* Health Savings Account and Flexible Spending Account
* Retirement Plans including company match&amp;amp;nbsp;
* Employee Stock Purchase Program
* Wellness programs, including access to mental health, 1:1 financial planners, and a monthly wellness allowance&amp;amp;nbsp;
* Paid parental and caregiving leave
* Paid time off (including 12 paid holidays)
* Paid sick leave (1 hour per 26 hours worked (max 80 hours per calendar year to the extent legally permissible) for non-exempt employees and covered by our Flexible Time Off policy for exempt employees)&amp;amp;nbsp;
* Learning and Development resources
* Paid Life insurance, AD&amp;amp;amp;D, and disability benefits&amp;amp;nbsp;
* Additional Perks such as WFH reimbursements and free access to caregiving, legal, and discounted resources&amp;amp;nbsp;
These benefits are further detailed in Block&amp;#39;s policies. This role is also eligible to participate in Block&amp;#39;s equity plan subject to the terms of the applicable plans and policies, and may be eligible for a sign-on bonus. Sales roles may be eligible to participate in a commission plan subject to the terms of the applicable plans and policies. Pay and benefits are subject to change at any time, consistent with the terms of any applicable compensation or benefit plans.
We’re working to build a more inclusive economy where our customers have equal access to opportunity, and we strive to live by these same values in building our workplace. Block is a proud equal opportunity employer. We work hard to evaluate all employees and job applicants consistently, without regard to race, color, religion, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, pregnancy, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation, citizenship, or any other legally protected class.&amp;amp;nbsp;We believe in being fair, and are committed to an inclusive interview experience, including providing reasonable accommodations to disabled applicants throughout the recruitment process. We encourage applicants to share any needed accommodations with their recruiter, who will treat these requests as confidentially as possible. Want to learn more about what we’re doing to build a workplace that is fair and square? Check out our I+D page.Additionally, we consider qualified applicants with criminal histories for employment on our team, assessing candidates in a manner consistent with the requirements of the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance.&amp;amp;nbsp;
Block, Inc. (NYSE: SQ) is a global technology company with a focus on financial services. Made up of Square, Cash App, Spiral, TIDAL, and TBD, we build tools to help more people access the economy. Square helps sellers run and grow their businesses with its integrated ecosystem of commerce solutions, business software, and banking services. With Cash App, anyone can easily send, spend, or invest their money in stocks or Bitcoin. Spiral (formerly Square Crypto) builds and funds free, open-source Bitcoin projects. Artists use TIDAL to help them succeed as entrepreneurs and connect more deeply with fans. TBD is building an open developer platform to make it easier to access Bitcoin and other blockchain technologies without having to go through an institution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jobs.smartrecruiters.com/ni/Square/d6a82029-93a4-46ce-9f6d-28b3591e1368-staff-developer-advocate</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 06:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MediatR 12.1 Released</title>
      <link>https://jimmybogard.com/mediatr-12-1-released/</link>
      <description>This release removes all scanning around behaviors, stream behaviors, and pre/post processors. That proved too problematic so you MUST register each of these explicitly with the appropriate registration methods inside AddMediatR. This also ensures that the order of behaviors and pre/post processors reflects the explicit order of registration.</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Bogard)</author>
      <guid>https://jimmybogard.com/mediatr-12-1-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 05:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy: ASUS ProArt Studiobook 16&amp;quot; OLED Touch Laptop Intel 13 Gen Core i9 with 32GM RAM NVIDIA GeForce RTX 4070 1TB SSD Mineral Black H7604JI-DS96T</title>
      <link>https://www.bestbuy.com/site/asus-proart-studiobook-16-oled-touch-laptop-intel-13-gen-core-i9-with-32gm-ram-nvidia-geforce-rtx-4070-1tb-ssd-mineral-black/6545155.p?skuId=6545155</link>
      <description>Shop ASUS ProArt Studiobook 16&amp;quot; OLED Touch Laptop Intel 13 Gen Core i9 with 32GM RAM NVIDIA GeForce RTX 4070 1TB SSD Mineral Black at Best Buy. Find low everyday prices and buy online for delivery or in-store pick-up. Price Match Guarantee.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bestbuy.com/site/asus-proart-studiobook-16-oled-touch-laptop-intel-13-gen-core-i9-with-32gm-ram-nvidia-geforce-rtx-4070-1tb-ssd-mineral-black/6545155.p?skuId=6545155</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 02:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLS ROYCE of CREATOR Laptops | ASUS ProArt Studiobook 16 2023 [i9 13980HX + RTX 4070]</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/RIhyi1rTopI</link>
      <description>THIS is FASTER than the APPLE M2 ULTRA, Creators, GET EXCITED!Sponsored Message:Mid-Year Sale whokeys 25% Coupon Code: TN20 Windows 10 Pro OEM Key ($17): htt...</description>
      <author> (Action Retro
  
  
  
    Action Retro
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/RIhyi1rTopI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 02:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>htmx in 100 seconds</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=r-GSGH2RxJs</link>
      <description>Learn the basics of htmx - an HTML-focused UI library that can handle data fetching and rendering in web applications without complex JavaScript code or fram...</description>
      <author> (Fireship
  
  
  
    Fireship
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=r-GSGH2RxJs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 02:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Container Registry and Azure Container Apps: The Perfect Combination for Containerized Application Deployment</title>
      <link>https://luismts.com/azure-container-registry-and-azure-container-apps-the-perfect-combination-for-containerized-application-deployment/</link>
      <description>Azure Container Registry and Azure Container Apps: The Perfect Combination for Containerized Application Deployment.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/luismatosluna/)</author>
      <guid>https://luismts.com/azure-container-registry-and-azure-container-apps-the-perfect-combination-for-containerized-application-deployment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 02:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsing in Python: all the tools and libraries you can use</title>
      <link>https://tomassetti.me/parsing-in-python/</link>
      <description>We present and compare all possible alternatives you can use to parse languages in Python. From libraries to parser generators, we present all options</description>
      <author> (Gabriele Tomassetti)</author>
      <guid>https://tomassetti.me/parsing-in-python/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emulator Debugging: PIANOMAN 3.0</title>
      <link>https://martypc.blogspot.com/2023/07/emulator-debugging-pianoman-30.html</link>
      <description>Early in development I was looking for a utility to test my crude PC speaker emulation.&amp;#160; I found a simple keyboard-piano program called PIAN...</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>https://martypc.blogspot.com/2023/07/emulator-debugging-pianoman-30.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&amp;#39;s 2023. Your API should have a schema</title>
      <link>https://nishtahir.com/your-api-should-have-a-schema/</link>
      <description>Here&amp;#39;s a story you might find relatable. We kicked off a new integration project that started 3 months later than everyone wanted. APIs just shipped after a bunch of delays. We were handed API docs and a test environment and started work building out the new feature. The documentation was</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nishtahir.com/your-api-should-have-a-schema/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the carbon footprint of pizzas</title>
      <link>https://maxhalford.github.io/blog/carbon-footprint-pizzas/</link>
      <description>Making environmentally friendly decisions can only be done with the right information. At Carbonfact, we’ve realized a big challenge is the lack of information about industrial processes. We tackle that slowly but surely by gathering data from various sources, and making it available to our customers.
Regarding food, the French government has a great initiative called Agribalyse. It’s a free database of environmental footprints for various food products. It includes raw ingredients straight out from the farm, as well as ready to eat dishes from the supermarket.</description>
      <author> (Max Halford)</author>
      <guid>https://maxhalford.github.io/blog/carbon-footprint-pizzas/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The secret life of .well-known</title>
      <link>https://ishan.page/blog/2023-07-02-well-known</link>
      <description>My first encounter with the .well-known directory was when Let&amp;#39;s Encrypt first hit the scene and I was learning about VPS-es and how Linux on the server worked.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ishan.page/blog/2023-07-02-well-known</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being a good mentor - a developers guide</title>
      <link>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/good-mentor/</link>
      <description>Let’s talk about the process where the experienced welcome the inexperienced under their wing and illuminate the path ahead. I’ve worn many hats over the</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/vadim.kravcenko.dev)</author>
      <guid>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/good-mentor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Against Reality</title>
      <link>https://borretti.me/article/test-against-reality</link>
      <description>Against mocking.</description>
      <author> (Fernando Borretti)</author>
      <guid>https://borretti.me/article/test-against-reality</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Succeed: Lessons from Sam Altman</title>
      <link>https://aarushgupta.com/2023/07/08/success-sam-altman.html</link>
      <description>This is an escape from my usual stream of posts, for I wanted to attempt to expand the horizons of my routine writing.</description>
      <author> (Aarush Gupta)</author>
      <guid>https://aarushgupta.com/2023/07/08/success-sam-altman.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WinUI 3 | Workaround for ItemsRepeater issue #560 | WinAppSDK | XAML | C# | .NET | UWP | WPF</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=vVmtt89G8q8</link>
      <description>In this video we&amp;#39;ll see a workaround for an issue in the WinUI GitHub repo.ElementName bindings don&amp;#39;t work inside ItemsRepeater DataTemplatehttps://github.co...</description>
      <author> (Andrew KeepCoding
  
  
  
    Andrew KeepCoding
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=vVmtt89G8q8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 18:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matcheroni, a tiny C++20 header library for building lexers/parsers</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/programming/comments/14snec5/matcheroni_a_tiny_c20_header_library_for_building/</link>
      <description>Posted in r/programming by u/hellotanjent • 48 points and 62 comments</description>
      <author> (hellotanjent)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/programming/comments/14snec5/matcheroni_a_tiny_c20_header_library_for_building/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 17:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 6 Added DateOnly and TimeOnly - Did You Know? #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DcWUs2rpazg</link>
      <description>&amp;#128640; Support me on Patreon to access the source code: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovicJoin my weekly .NET newsletter:https://www.milanjovanovic.techRead ...</description>
      <author> (Jonathan Edwards
  
  
  
    Jonathan Edwards
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DcWUs2rpazg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 12:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Code Navigation Tips While Debugging .NET Apps in Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SGVXVLyzd6Q</link>
      <description>Leslie is here to show off some tips &amp;amp; tricks for code navigation while debugging your .NET apps inside of Visual Studio. More tips: https://aka.ms/vsdebugge...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=SGVXVLyzd6Q</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 10:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Razor Formatting Feedback</title>
      <link>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/RCP97ZY</link>
      <description>Take this survey powered by surveymonkey.com. Create your own surveys for free.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/RCP97ZY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 10:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>