<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How we built a $1M ARR open source SaaS</title>
      <link>https://plausible.io/blog/open-source-saas</link>
      <description>We’ve reached a significant milestone of $1 million in annual recurring revenue (ARR) with Plausible Analytics. This post is a recap of how we got to this point.</description>
      <author> (Marko Saric)</author>
      <guid>https://plausible.io/blog/open-source-saas</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 10:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 101 - Open Source .NET for Fun with Drake Williams</title>
      <link>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-101-open-source-net-for-fun-with-drake-williams/</link>
      <description>In this episode, Drake Williams joined us to talk about some of his Open Source projects which he started for fun, including Rom Sorter and the GPS game server Praxis Mapper. He also shares some top tips for building applications without breaking out of your personal bandwidth.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-101-open-source-net-for-fun-with-drake-williams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 09:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 301</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/pBmNHh8xgpk</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Tom Bilyeu
  
  
  
    Tom Bilyeu
  




  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/pBmNHh8xgpk</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 07:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Subsystem for Android and .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://dvlup.com/2022/06/22/windows-subsystem-for-android-and-net-maui/</link>
      <description>
Did you know you can deploy and debug your Android projects from Visual Studio 2022 (17.3+) to WSA (Windows Subsystem for Android)? This is a quick post to show you how to have your WSA appear in the list of target Android devices in Visual Studio.



WSA as the target device



First, make sure you have WSA installed and enabled, find the instructions here Windows Subsystem for Android™️ | Microsoft Docs. Once it is installed, start the Amazon App Store app to ensure WSA has been started. 



Starting up WSA



Open the Windows Subsystem for Android™ Settings app (this gets installed with WSA) and make sure the Developer &amp;gt; Developer Mode setting is enabled. After it is enabled, you should now see an loopback IP address (127.0.0.1) and a port number (58526).



WSA IP address and port number for ADB



With WSA setup and running you can now deploy from Visual Studio 2022. The first step is in Visual Studio, expand the Tools &amp;gt; Android menu and select Android Adb Command Prompt menu item.



ADB Command Prompt



When the ADB command prompt window is opened, you can connect ADB to WSA using the &amp;#39;connect&amp;#39; command and IP:port number for WSA. Here is the full command: adb connect 127.0.0.1:58526and here&amp;#39;s a screenshot of a successful connection:



Successful ADB connection



Finally, in your MAUI project; make sure the target framework is set to net6.0-android and you should find WSA listed under the Android Local Devices menu.



WSA listed as a local Android device in Visual Studio 2022 Preview



Here&amp;#39;s what it looks like after I deployed an early prototype of my current Microsoft Store app Hacked? as a .NET MAUI Android app!



.NET MAUI app running in WSA



Troubleshooting



Troubleshooting Tip 1 - Missing &amp;#39;Android Local Devices&amp;#39;



Problem: If you do not see Android Local Devices in the menu, then it means your WSA is probably put back to sleep by Windows because it wasn&amp;#39;t being used.



Solution 1: Just open any Android app, like the Amazon App Store, to start WSA again (you can keep that app open to prevent WSA from going back to sleep). Note: After it has been stopped and started, you&amp;#39;ll need to reconnect ADB again.



Solution 2: Another option is to tell Windows 11 to never put WSA to sleep. It will start up with Windows and always use system resources. Open the Windows Subsystem for Android Settings app and change the System &amp;gt; Subsystem Resources setting to Continuous (see screenshot)







Troubleshooting Tip 2 - No Internet in WSA



Problem: If you do not have any internet in your WSA apps, check to see if you have a VPN active. It is known that Cisco AnyConnnect&amp;#39;s network adapter can interfere if the split tunnel routes traffic with the same IP as the WSA vm. 



Solution 1: If you disconnect the VPN, the internet will work in WSA again. 



Disconnect option in the AnyConnect tray icon&amp;#39;s context menu



Solution 2: There is a semi-permanent solution for this by changing the AnyConnect network adapter to have a higher InterfaceMetric value than the WSA Hyper-V adapter one has. Here&amp;#39;s a screenshot of the two PowerShell commands I used to do that:



Increasing AnyConnect&amp;#39;s InterfaceMetric value
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dvlup.com/2022/06/22/windows-subsystem-for-android-and-net-maui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps 101: Introducing Database DevOps</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/database-devops/devops-101-introducing-database-devops</link>
      <description>What are the challenges - and the opportunities - waiting for you when introducing Database DevOps? Grant Fritchey explains.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/GFritchey)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/blog/database-devops/devops-101-introducing-database-devops</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Layout Options in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/exploring-layout-options-dotnet-maui</link>
      <description>.NET MAUI has four layout classes to help you organize the user interface of your app. Let’s look at them!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/exploring-layout-options-dotnet-maui</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asked and answered: the results for the 2022 Developer survey are here!</title>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.blog/2022/06/22/asked-and-answered-the-results-for-the-2022-developer-survey-are-here/</link>
      <description>The state of software development is...</description>
      <author> (David Gibson and Ryan Donovan)</author>
      <guid>https://stackoverflow.blog/2022/06/22/asked-and-answered-the-results-for-the-2022-developer-survey-are-here/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perhaps Too Much Validation &amp;#183; Aspiring Craftsman</title>
      <link>http://aspiringcraftsman.com/2022/06/22/perhaps-too-much-validation.html</link>
      <description>22 June, 2022. It was a Wednesday.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://aspiringcraftsman.com/2022/06/22/perhaps-too-much-validation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Simple .NET Lambda Function | no dogma blog</title>
      <link>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2022/06/creating-a-simple-net-lambda-function/</link>
      <description>This post shows how easy it is to create a simple Lambda function written in C#.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2022/06/creating-a-simple-net-lambda-function/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a React-based app with ASP.NET Minimal APIs and MongoDB storage</title>
      <link>https://stvansolano.github.io/2022/06/20/Creating-a-react-app-with-AspNet-Minimal-APIs-and-MongoDb-CosmosDb/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been using React for while by mixing it up with .NET stuff and enjoying it a lot. For this post, I decided to combine them along Compose containers, ASP.NET Minimal APIs and MongoDB support!</description>
      <author> (Esteban Solano G.)</author>
      <guid>https://stvansolano.github.io/2022/06/20/Creating-a-react-app-with-AspNet-Minimal-APIs-and-MongoDb-CosmosDb/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RequestDelegateFactory Class (Microsoft.AspNetCore.Http)</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/api/microsoft.aspnetcore.http.requestdelegatefactory</link>
      <description>Creates RequestDelegate implementations from Delegate request handlers. </description>
      <author> (dotnet-bot)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/api/microsoft.aspnetcore.http.requestdelegatefactory</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 03:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draknek New Voices Puzzle Grant</title>
      <link>https://grants.draknek.org/</link>
      <description>The Draknek New Voices Puzzle Grant is a grant opportunity for game developers from traditionally underrepresented groups and backgrounds who are interested in designing and developing puzzle games.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://grants.draknek.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 03:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interchain Security is Coming to the Cosmos Hub</title>
      <link>https://blog.cosmos.network/interchain-security-is-coming-to-the-cosmos-hub-f144c45fb035</link>
      <description>One of the features that make blockchain technology so appealing is its high degree of security and resistance to attack. In a…</description>
      <author> (https://billyrennekamp.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cosmos.network/interchain-security-is-coming-to-the-cosmos-hub-f144c45fb035</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 01:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digesting Technical Content</title>
      <link>https://abyteofcoding.com/blog/digesting-technical-content/</link>
      <description>An article on how to learn and retain technical knowledge.</description>
      <author> (Alex Zdanov)</author>
      <guid>https://abyteofcoding.com/blog/digesting-technical-content/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model: Difficult Problems vs. Hard Work</title>
      <link>https://benjamincongdon.me/blog/2022/06/22/Mental-Model-Difficult-Problems-vs.-Hard-Work/</link>
      <description>How to model work that interacts with ambiguity</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://benjamincongdon.me/blog/2022/06/22/Mental-Model-Difficult-Problems-vs.-Hard-Work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to plan the architectural attributes?</title>
      <link>https://kalali.blog/2022/06/software-architecture-attributes-how-to-decide/</link>
      <description>Deciding between software architecture attributes primacy is hard. I follow some practices that I will talk a little about them here.</description>
      <author> (Masoud Kalali)</author>
      <guid>https://kalali.blog/2022/06/software-architecture-attributes-how-to-decide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My LASIK Eye Surgery Experience</title>
      <link>https://shubhamjain.co/2022/06/23/lasik-eye-surgery-experience/</link>
      <description>Usually, there’s a trigger involved in making you opt for LASIK. Something happens and you say to yourself, “that’s it, I am tired of glasses.” For me, it was joining a gym and realizing how big of a nuisance they were—always slipping off, always having them to wear them off and on.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shubhamjain.co/2022/06/23/lasik-eye-surgery-experience/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commit 1 to 1000 and beyond: Two years of maintaining an open-source project</title>
      <link>https://ohsayan.github.io/2022/06/commit-1-to-1000-and-beyond/</link>
      <description>Back in June 2020, I started writing what is now known as Skytable. Ever since, I have been maintaining Skytable, mostly in my free time and have recently been spending a lot of time on it. Here’s a little story on my two years of experience in maintaining an open-source project: what it’s like, the highs and lows and the future.
Before I go deep into things, what is open-source? The definition with regard to the license used today would be “any project that uses an OSI-approved license.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ohsayan.github.io/2022/06/commit-1-to-1000-and-beyond/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The many definitions of Server-Side Rendering—zachleat.com</title>
      <link>https://www.zachleat.com/web/ssr-overloaded/</link>
      <description>A post by Zach Leatherman (zachleat)</description>
      <author> (Zach Leatherman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.zachleat.com/web/ssr-overloaded/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kind and True</title>
      <link>https://stevenwaterman.uk/kind-and-true/</link>
      <description>For years, I&amp;#39;ve followed a kind of &amp;#39;heuristic triangle&amp;#39; to determine whether a thought is worth sharing. However, that triangle has one implication that I&amp;#39;ve avoided until now, because it feels vulnerable, alien, and uncomfortable.</description>
      <author> (By Steven Waterman)</author>
      <guid>https://stevenwaterman.uk/kind-and-true/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build your Golang package docs locally</title>
      <link>https://mdaverde.com/posts/golang-local-docs/</link>
      <description>Previewing the HTML of your go docs from localhost</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mdaverde.com/posts/golang-local-docs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A simple guide to Mastodon</title>
      <link>https://mybackpages.jeremysarber.com/a-simple-guide-to-mastodon</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a microblogging social network similar to Twitter. Unlike Twitter, however, it is community-owned and ad-free. You can post relatively</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mybackpages.jeremysarber.com/a-simple-guide-to-mastodon</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start all of your commands with a comma</title>
      <link>https://rhodesmill.org/brandon/2009/commands-with-comma/</link>
      <description>Like many Unix users,
  I long ago created a ~/bin/ directory in my home directory
  and added it to my PATH
  so that I could supplement
  the wonderfully rich set of basic Unix commands
  with some conveniences and shell scripts of my own devising.</description>
      <author> (by Brandon Rhodes
  • Home)</author>
      <guid>https://rhodesmill.org/brandon/2009/commands-with-comma/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code and Visual Studio Rock the 2022 Stack Overflow Developer Report -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/06/23/stack-overflow-2022-survey.aspx</link>
      <description>Stack Overflow&amp;#39;s huge developer survey is out for 2022, showing that Visual Studio Code and Visual Studio have cemented their positions as the two most popular IDEs among more than 70,000 developers who were polled.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel06/23/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/06/23/stack-overflow-2022-survey.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 23:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed ISeq marking by using a bitmap and rearranging inline caches by tenderlove &amp;#183; Pull Request #6053 &amp;#183; ruby/ruby</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ruby/ruby/pull/6053</link>
      <description>A large percentage of major GC time is spent marking instruction sequence objects.  This PR aims to speed up major GC by speeding up marking instruction sequence objects.
Marking ISeq objects
Today...</description>
      <author> (ruby)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ruby/ruby/pull/6053</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 23:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QBE - Compiler Backend</title>
      <link>https://c9x.me/compile/releases.html</link>
      <description>8 years after the first commit in the git repo, at the ask of
some package managers and users, I release QBE 1.0. All targets
are at parity thanks to great work from contributors, and QBE
is used somewhat seriously by a couple people.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://c9x.me/compile/releases.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 22:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whatever happened to SHA-256 support in Git?</title>
      <link>https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/898522/9cf50ee3f96f90c1/</link>
      <description>The news has been proclaimed
loudly and often: the SHA-1 hash algorithm is terminally broken and should
not be used in any situation where security matters.  Among other things,
this news gave some impetus to the longstanding
effort to support a more robust hash algorithm in the Git source-code
management system.  As time has passed, though, that work seems to have
slowed to a stop, leaving some users wondering when, if ever, Git will
support a hash algorithm other than SHA-1.</description>
      <author> (By Jonathan CorbetJune 23, 2022)</author>
      <guid>https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/898522/9cf50ee3f96f90c1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEGA: Malleable Encryption Goes Awry</title>
      <link>https://mega-awry.io/</link>
      <description>MEGA is a leading cloud storage platform with more than 250 million users and 1000 Petabytes of stored data, which aims to achieve user-controlled end-to-end encryption.
                We show that MEGA&amp;#39;s system does not protect its users against a malicious server and present five distinct attacks, which together allow for a full compromise of the confidentiality of user files.
                Additionally, the integrity of user data is damaged to the extent that an attacker can insert malicious files of their choice which pass all authenticity checks of the client.
                We built proof-of-concept versions of all the attacks, showcasing their practicality and exploitability.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mega-awry.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 22:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hands On with Latest Visual Studio 2022 Preview Features -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/06/23/vs2022-preview-features.aspx</link>
      <description>Trying out some hidden functionality that can be enabled with a few mouse clicks (and maybe an IDE restart).</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel06/23/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/06/23/vs2022-preview-features.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=72daIfgD-3E</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restre.am/yt</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
  
    .NET Foundation
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=72daIfgD-3E</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - dolthub/dolt: Dolt – It&amp;#39;s Git for Data</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dolthub/dolt</link>
      <description>Dolt – It&amp;#39;s Git for Data. Contribute to dolthub/dolt development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (dolthub)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dolthub/dolt</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incremental ASP.NET Migration Tooling Preview 2</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/incremental-asp-net-migration-tooling-preview-2/</link>
      <description>Introducing preview 2 of incremental ASP.NET migration tooling, including support for shared authentication.</description>
      <author> (Mike Rousos)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/incremental-asp-net-migration-tooling-preview-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Launch of Microsoft&amp;#39;s new offices in Atlanta #microsoftatlanta #atlanticyards</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/saZT3wKOY6c</link>
      <description>In May Microsoft opened their new Atlanta Campus known as Atlantic Yards. Let me take you through the day and around this amazing property. ******* &amp;#127927; Musici...</description>
      <author> (JerryRigEverything
  
  
  
    JerryRigEverything
  




  
    
    
  
  Verified





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/saZT3wKOY6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 18:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenIddict 4.0 preview1 is out</title>
      <link>https://kevinchalet.com/2022/06/22/openiddict-4-0-preview1-is-out/</link>
      <description>Earlier today, the first OpenIddict 4.0 preview was pushed to NuGet.org &amp;#127881; As always, all the changes can be found on GitHub but here&amp;#39;s a recap of the most interesting ones: What changed?OpenIddic</description>
      <author> (K&amp;#233;vin Chalet)</author>
      <guid>https://kevinchalet.com/2022/06/22/openiddict-4-0-preview1-is-out/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 18:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principal Product Manager in Austin, Texas, United States | Product Management at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/1362692/Principal-Product-Manager</link>
      <description>Apply for Principal Product Manager job with Microsoft in Austin, Texas, United States. Product Management at Microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/1362692/Principal-Product-Manager</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 12:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GHSA-5crp-9r3c-p9vr - GitHub Advisory Database</title>
      <link>https://github.com/advisories/GHSA-5crp-9r3c-p9vr</link>
      <description>Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions in Newtonsoft.Json</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/advisories/GHSA-5crp-9r3c-p9vr</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 12:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>