<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Sketchnote: Responsilibilty Driven Development Revisted by Ian Cooper</title>
      <link>https://www.planetgeek.ch/2025/07/25/sketchnote-responsilibilty-driven-development-revisted-by-ian-cooper/</link>
      <description>YouTube: https://youtu.be/xOpUpRIpH6k?si=YV443HeEUkMjkkxV</description>
      <guid>https://www.planetgeek.ch/2025/07/25/sketchnote-responsilibilty-driven-development-revisted-by-ian-cooper/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 20 years of MDN | MDN Blog</title>
      <link>https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/blog/mdn-turns-20/</link>
      <description>MDN turns 20! Let's look at how we started, how MDN became the most trusted resource for web developers, the impact it's had on the open web, and yes, there's cake, too.
</description>
      <guid>https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/blog/mdn-turns-20/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel CEO Letter to Employees</title>
      <link>https://morethanmoore.substack.com/p/intel-ceo-letter-to-employees</link>
      <description>Lip-Bu Tan announces 15% workforce reduction</description>
      <guid>https://morethanmoore.substack.com/p/intel-ceo-letter-to-employees</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 09:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trisomic rescue via allele-specific multiple chromosome cleavage using CRISPR-Cas9 in trisomy 21 cells</title>
      <link>https://academic.oup.com/pnasnexus/article/4/2/pgaf022/8016019</link>
      <description>Abstract. Human trisomy 21, responsible for Down syndrome, is the most prevalent genetic cause of cognitive impairment and remains a key focus for prenatal</description>
      <guid>https://academic.oup.com/pnasnexus/article/4/2/pgaf022/8016019</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 06:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphene OS: a security-enhanced Android build</title>
      <link>https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/1030004/898017c7953c0946/</link>
      <description>People tend to put a lot of trust into their phones.  Those devices have access to no end of se [...]</description>
      <guid>https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/1030004/898017c7953c0946/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 06:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visa and Mastercard: The Global Payment Duopoly</title>
      <link>https://quartr.com/insights/edge/visa-and-mastercard-the-global-payment-duopoly</link>
      <description>Explore one of the world's largest and most discussed duopolies, from the origins of the credit card to its combined market value of $850 billion.</description>
      <author> (https://quartr.com/authors/peter-westberg)</author>
      <guid>https://quartr.com/insights/edge/visa-and-mastercard-the-global-payment-duopoly</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There is no memory safety without thread safety</title>
      <link>https://www.ralfj.de/blog/2025/07/24/memory-safety.html</link>
      <description>Memory safety is all the rage these days. But what does the term even mean? That turns out to be harder to nail down than you may think. Typically, people use this term to refer to language...</description>
      <guid>https://www.ralfj.de/blog/2025/07/24/memory-safety.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Can’t We Just… Send an HTML Email</title>
      <link>https://blog.julik.nl/2025/07/html-emails-the-hard-way</link>
      <description>A few months ago my partner-in-love-and-in-crime came with a seemingly innocuous request, which went as follows: We have an event coming up, and I need to send out a press release via email. It’s simple enough - just a couple of images and a few blurbs of text. I can’t seem to be able to make it look good in Gmail nor in Apple Mail. How does one do such a thing? Now, we computer-savvy household members know darn well that HTML email is, on the list of terrible IT things we have to help others with, right below the “can we get this printer to work?”. It can get… challenging. And yet, given that I have done this “HTML email” thing for a while – this piqued my curiosity. How hard can it be, thought I, to manually code an HTML email with images - and then use some Advanced Technology™ to turn it into a proper HTML email? While doing that using current commercial platforms turned out to be very hard indeed - for reasons having nothing to do with technology – I did come to an elegant solution that I came to appreciate. And it did allow me exactly what I wanted: Quickly layout an HTML email by source editing Turn it into an actual email Preview it in Apple Mail (on macOS and an iPhone) and in Gmail (desktop Web and iOS) …rinse and repeat until it looks great And here’s the delightful surprise: the solution turned out to be not just functional, but genuinely elegant. It’s one of those rare moments where the constraints of email clients actually led to a cleaner, more maintainable approach than the “modern” alternatives. Instead of fighting with WYSIWYG editors or wrestling with complex templating systems, I ended up with a simple script that does exactly what I need - nothing more, nothing less. The real “aha moment” came when I realized that the tools I needed were already sitting right there in my Rails stack, just waiting to be used in a slightly different way. Premailer, Nokogiri, and the Mail gem - these aren’t exotic dependencies or bleeding-edge libraries. They’re battle-tested, well-documented tools that handle the hard parts of email creation while giving you complete control over the output. It’s the kind of solution that makes you wonder why you didn’t think of it sooner. Curious where I ended up with that? Read on!</description>
      <guid>https://blog.julik.nl/2025/07/html-emails-the-hard-way</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I wrote the worlds worst emulator</title>
      <link>http://geon.github.io/programming/2025/07/24/bubble-bobble-c64-rng-emulator</link>
      <description>This would be my website, I guess.</description>
      <guid>http://geon.github.io/programming/2025/07/24/bubble-bobble-c64-rng-emulator</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Strings Attached : How Modern Physics Came Unmoored - Slow thoughts</title>
      <link>https://slow-thoughts.com/no-strings-attached/</link>
      <description>Once a source of radical insight, theoretical physics now finds itself stuck in a beautiful dead end. A meditation on string theory, scientific orthodoxy, and the quiet disappearance of dreamers.</description>
      <guid>https://slow-thoughts.com/no-strings-attached/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asking users to share their ChatGPT conversation leading them to site visit</title>
      <link>https://robertdruska.com/blog/asking-users-to-share-their-chatgpt-conversation-leading-them-to-site-visit/</link>
      <description>July 23, 2025</description>
      <guid>https://robertdruska.com/blog/asking-users-to-share-their-chatgpt-conversation-leading-them-to-site-visit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cognitive inertia</title>
      <link>https://andwati.xyz/posts/inertia/</link>
      <description>inertia</description>
      <guid>https://andwati.xyz/posts/inertia/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RABBIT TEETH PART TWO</title>
      <link>https://kaiwenwang.com/writing/rabbit-teeth-part-two</link>
      <description>This is the follow-up to Rabbit Teeth &amp; Misalignments. A clear and simple explanation, definitions, and progression.</description>
      <guid>https://kaiwenwang.com/writing/rabbit-teeth-part-two</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>testcontainers: improving E2E tests</title>
      <link>https://mfbmina.dev/en/posts/testcontainers/</link>
      <description>In a previous post
 I showed some ways to improve tests by creating API mocks that we call. However, that’s not always enough, and we might need E2E tests (or acceptance tests), for example, to test integrations with databases, messaging services, or anything else. For these cases, I’m here to introduce the Testcontainers tool.
The Testcontainers
 library is an open-source tool that lets you create containers during test execution. The idea is for your application’s test dependencies to be part of the code, avoiding the need for mocks and even local dependency installation. Another big advantage is that it makes it easier to achieve test isolation and replicability among developers. The tool supports various programming languages like Go, Ruby, Elixir, Java, etc.</description>
      <guid>https://mfbmina.dev/en/posts/testcontainers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient streaming of Markdown in the terminal</title>
      <link>https://willmcgugan.github.io/streaming-markdown/</link>
      <description>While working on Toad, it occurred to me there was a missing feature I would need. Namely streaming markdown. When talking to an LLM via an API, the Markdown doesn’t arrive all at once. Rather you get fragments of markdown (known as tokens) which should be appended to an existing document. Until recently the only way to render this in Textual was to remove the Markdown widget and add it again with the updated markdown. This worked, but it would get slower to append content as the document grew. It wasn’t a scalable solution.</description>
      <guid>https://willmcgugan.github.io/streaming-markdown/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🐞 One of the Weirdest Bugs</title>
      <link>https://softuts.com/one-of-the-weirdest-bugs/</link>
      <description>In n8n, some workflows suddenly stopped working. ⚠️

They were still listed, but when I tried to access them — 404 Not Found.
Yet, I could find them in the Postgres DB, so clearly the 404 was wrong. ⁉️


Digging Deeper 🕵️

 * Only the workflows with a Gmail trigger were broken.
 * Tried creating a</description>
      <guid>https://softuts.com/one-of-the-weirdest-bugs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clojure as a First Language</title>
      <link>https://mccue.dev/pages/7-14-25-clojure-as-a-first-language</link>
      <description>by:   Ethan McCue</description>
      <guid>https://mccue.dev/pages/7-14-25-clojure-as-a-first-language</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlouState | Unlock Your True Coding Potential</title>
      <link>https://floustate.com/blog/why-i-was-wrong-about-coding-time</link>
      <description>The intelligent focus timer that automatically categorizes your coding work. Understand your productivity, eliminate guesswork, and become a more effective developer.</description>
      <guid>https://floustate.com/blog/why-i-was-wrong-about-coding-time</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on rewriting JSX as Astro | Carlos Neves / Blog</title>
      <link>https://carlosn.com.br/blog/post/notes-on-rewriting-jsx-as-astro/</link>
      <description>Notes on rewriting JSX as Astro</description>
      <guid>https://carlosn.com.br/blog/post/notes-on-rewriting-jsx-as-astro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Product Engineer</title>
      <link>https://nandinfinitum.com/posts/the-product-engineer/</link>
      <description>An attempt to organize some scattered thoughts and ideas on product engineering</description>
      <guid>https://nandinfinitum.com/posts/the-product-engineer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>