<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Making the Matrix Screensaver in C on a PDP-11/83</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=-foAV_zU2as</link>
      <description>Dave shows you how to create the famous Matrix screensaver in pure C on a PDP-11/83 running 211BSD UNIX!  Free Sample of my Book on the Spectrum: https://amzn.to/3zBinWM

Watch ShopTalk Now on Dave&amp;#39;s Attic: https://youtu.be/5Emgx0lhllE

Follow me on X: https://x.com/davepl1968
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/davepl

Highlights

- Bringing a vintage PDP-11/83 Minicomputer back to life with BSD Unix and K&amp;amp;R C
- Showcasing a custom-built MATRIX screensaver that uses classic VT220 control sequences
- Demonstrating four different retro-style “screensavers,” including Conway’s Game of Life
- Exploring the shared lineage between 211BSD and modern macOS through easy cross-compilation

Why to Watch

- Learn how to write and compile retro C code on authentic PDP-11 hardware
- See how low-level terminal control codes enable surprisingly dynamic on-screen visuals
- Discover tips and tricks for preserving a usable UNIX environment after custom programs exit
- Experience a hands-on approach to bridging decades of computing history in one fun project</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=-foAV_zU2as</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 16:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more needles! Tracking blood sugar on your wrist | Waterloo News</title>
      <link>https://uwaterloo.ca/news/media/no-more-needles-tracking-blood-sugar-your-wrist</link>
      <description>Imagine shrinking satellite technology that predicts the weather into a device that transmits vital information about the health of the person wearing it. University of Waterloo engineers have achieved this technological feat to help people faced with chronic health problems such as diabetes monitor their glucose levels. The Waterloo team’s breakthrough addresses the major</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://uwaterloo.ca/news/media/no-more-needles-tracking-blood-sugar-your-wrist</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker on MacOS is still slow?</title>
      <link>https://www.paolomainardi.com/posts/docker-performance-macos-2025/</link>
      <description>TLDR Link to heading Two years after my first analysis of Docker performance on MacOS, things have improved significantly. VirtIOFS is now much faster (bind mounts are only 3x slower instead of 5-6x), and we have new solutions in the ecosystem. Lima (open-source) performs well and sometimes better than Docker Desktop, while Docker’s new file synchronization feature offers impressive speed improvements (59% faster) but requires a paid subscription. For the most stable performance, the hybrid approach (combining bind mounts with volumes) remains the best practice. Choose your setup based on your needs:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.paolomainardi.com/posts/docker-performance-macos-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web page annoyances that I don&amp;#39;t inflict on you here</title>
      <link>http://rachelbythebay.com/w/2025/01/04/cruft/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been thinking about things that annoy me about other web pages.  
Safari recently gained the ability to &amp;quot;hide distracting items&amp;quot; and I&amp;#39;ve 
been having great fun telling various idiot web &amp;quot;designers&amp;quot; to stuff it.  
Reclaiming a simple experience free of wibbly wobbly stuff has been 
great.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://rachelbythebay.com/w/2025/01/04/cruft/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 12:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to redirect across repository websites with Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://msicc.net/2024-12-19-how-to-redirect-across-repository-websites-with-github-pages/</link>
      <description>In this post, I will walk you through how to set up redirects across Github Pages websites with a straightforward approach.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://msicc.net/2024-12-19-how-to-redirect-across-repository-websites-with-github-pages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 10:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Proven Path to Creating Unique and Meaningful Work</title>
      <link>https://jamesclear.com/stay-on-the-bus</link>
      <description>This one mantra will help you uncover your creativity and do work that matters.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/jamesclear)</author>
      <guid>https://jamesclear.com/stay-on-the-bus</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sailboat Metaphor - Scott Barry Kaufman</title>
      <link>https://scottbarrykaufman.com/sailboat-metaphor/</link>
      <description>Chances are you’re familiar with Abraham Maslow’s&amp;#160;hierarchy of needs, a pyramid with self-actualization depicted at the top. You likely learned about it</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scottbarrykaufman.com/sailboat-metaphor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leave Me Alone.</title>
      <link>http://adaged.blogspot.com/2024/12/leave-me-alone.html</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m almost embarrassed to say how important LinkedIn is to my business. My network is large though not vaynerchukian. It&amp;#39;s taken a good amou...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://adaged.blogspot.com/2024/12/leave-me-alone.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What LLMs mean for EBITDA margins | Notes</title>
      <link>https://alexjvale.com/n/llms-and-margins</link>
      <description>This is a follow-on from a note on how adopting SaaS impacted industry’s EBITDA margins.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alexjvale.com/n/llms-and-margins</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>msmetko&amp;#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.msmetko.xyz/posts/9</link>
      <description>Sampling a sample from a distribution appears in a lot of places in natural
sciences, but lately it’s mostly been used to power LLMs, due to how the
Transformer architecture works internally. This blogpost will talk about how to
efficiently sample from a categorical distribution given logits.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.msmetko.xyz/posts/9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello the Last Day of 2024, Let&amp;#39;s See What We Achieved This Past Year!</title>
      <link>https://2coffee.dev/en/articles/hello-the-last-day-of-2024-lets-see-what-we-achieved-this-past-year</link>
      <description>This article summarizes the 2024 year of the blog 2coffee.dev, where the author shared notable achievements and statistics throughout the year.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2coffee.dev/en/articles/hello-the-last-day-of-2024-lets-see-what-we-achieved-this-past-year</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine Tuning the Erlang Virtual Machine &amp;#183; Anantha Kumaran</title>
      <link>https://ananthakumaran.in/2025/01/04/erlang-vm-tuning.html</link>
      <description>In my previous post, I discussed how to identify the causes of
high CPU usage. In this post, I’ll focus on addressing system
bottlenecks. Our production workload runs on 16-core machines, yet the
CPU usage has never exceeded 70%. In other words, the system
effectively uses no more than 11 cores.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ananthakumaran.in/2025/01/04/erlang-vm-tuning.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Better Way to Stand Out in the Job Hunt</title>
      <link>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/how-i-landed-my-dream-jobs-with-loom/</link>
      <description>Learn how Loom videos helped me land top roles in finance and fintech. My tips on video introductions will help you stand out, connect with hiring managers, and transform your job search.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/how-i-landed-my-dream-jobs-with-loom/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade Ideas’ Missed Opportunity</title>
      <link>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/trade-ideas-missed-opportunity/</link>
      <description>Trade Ideas offers a powerful tool for retail traders, but its focus on the wrong audience has led to high churn and unnecessary feature development.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/trade-ideas-missed-opportunity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is social media dead?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ambrzykowski.com/is-social-media-dead/</link>
      <description>Social media once carried a promise. It would bring us closer, enrich our relationships, and create a world of authentic connection. We bought into it wholeh...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ambrzykowski.com/is-social-media-dead/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Identities in the AT Protocol via Bluesky</title>
      <link>https://fusectore.dev/2025/01/04/atproto-identity.html</link>
      <description>The AT Protocol is an open, decentralized network for building social applications. Bluesky, a relatively new social network, is built on top of the AT Protocol. It recently piqued my interest as I came across this fascinating research paper Bluesky and the AT Protocol: Usable Decentralized Social Media. In this post, we’ll dive into one of the key elements of the AT Protocol: identities. We will start with Bluesky user handles, explore additional information about them, and see what else we can discover. DID Resolution A handle in Bluesky is associated with a DID, which can be resolved using DNS or HTTPS. decentralized identifier (DID) A globally unique persistent identifier that does not require a centralized registration authority and is often generated and/or registered cryptographically. […] Many—but not all—DID methods make use of distributed ledger technology (DLT) or some other form of decentralized network. From Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs) v1.0 The DID for @jay.bsky.team can be resolved via a DNS record. Example with dig: &amp;gt; dig _atproto.jay.bsky.team TXT [...] _atproto.jay.bsky.team. 14400 IN TXT &amp;quot;did=did:plc:oky5czdrnfjpqslsw2a5iclo&amp;quot; If you don’t have dig installed, try an online tool like nslookup.io. If no DNS TXT entry exists, the handle may resolve to a DID through a well-known HTTPS endpoint. Let’s take the example of @jamesgunn.bsky.social: &amp;gt; curl https://jamesgunn.bsky.social/.well-known/atproto-did did:plc:lotavzt36yanhfy3j3gpysyj If you don’t have curl installed, you can just open the link in your browser https://jamesgunn.bsky.social/.well-known/atproto-did. PLC Once you have a DID, examine the part after the first colon. This is known as the method. The above two examples use plc, which stands for Public Ledger of Credentials. These PLC DIDs can be looked up in the PLC directory at plc.directory. The AT Protocol also supports the web method, though we focus on plc here. We can use curl again to get more information about a DID. Let’s take @jay.bsky.team’s DID as example. &amp;gt; curl https://plc.directory/did:plc:oky5czdrnfjpqslsw2a5iclo/log | jq [ { &amp;quot;sig&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;KuN3A61golVNSDU71wZKLP9lVuXk6YekJAz1lwDzrPsNTEWHBBW_8zSyV6pDxV4KiYXuAXlS1Ik47XkjQZ94mA&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;prev&amp;quot;: null, &amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;create&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;handle&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;jay.bsky.social&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;service&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;https://bsky.social&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;signingKey&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shP5TBe1sQfSttXty15FAEHV1DZgcxRZNxvEWnPfLFwLxJ&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;recoveryKey&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shhCGUqDKjStzuDxPkTxN6ujddP4RkEKJJouJGRRkaLGbg&amp;quot; }, { &amp;quot;sig&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;TY3ot8yFF-0LL8ceoRwSGaNQj0F1aj-IApYXRGT21G1fnznKHUHT1QE7c1aTrYd9PQLVvXUGag6CZ9EEeIKqgA&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;prev&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;bafyreidswhiwi4ljkl4es4vwqhkas3spmmktortqbp6lkrb5v7qqdfr3mm&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;plc_operation&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;services&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;atproto_pds&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;AtprotoPersonalDataServer&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;endpoint&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;https://bsky.social&amp;quot; } }, &amp;quot;alsoKnownAs&amp;quot;: [ &amp;quot;at://jay.bsky.social&amp;quot; ], &amp;quot;rotationKeys&amp;quot;: [ &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shhCGUqDKjStzuDxPkTxN6ujddP4RkEKJJouJGRRkaLGbg&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shpKnbdPx3g3CmPf5cRVTPe1HtSwVn5ish3wSnDPQCbLJK&amp;quot; ], &amp;quot;verificationMethods&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;atproto&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shXjHeiBuRCKmM36cuYnm7YEMzhGnCmCyW92sRJ9pribSF&amp;quot; } }, { &amp;quot;sig&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;WmQmobHA6abtu8xIkBSrDkkoMNjOxP1Tl_1zl1DbIZlA9kjOyxjX-J1rzwWVy3stdzMowpBeBnedkAug84n_RQ&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;prev&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;bafyreicgb25yf5fro22oyhtkbgerzr4nume4sx757r525skxdzpeoeseha&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;plc_operation&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;services&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;atproto_pds&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;AtprotoPersonalDataServer&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;endpoint&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;https://bsky.social&amp;quot; } }, &amp;quot;alsoKnownAs&amp;quot;: [ &amp;quot;at://jay.bsky.team&amp;quot; ], &amp;quot;rotationKeys&amp;quot;: [ &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shhCGUqDKjStzuDxPkTxN6ujddP4RkEKJJouJGRRkaLGbg&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shpKnbdPx3g3CmPf5cRVTPe1HtSwVn5ish3wSnDPQCbLJK&amp;quot; ], &amp;quot;verificationMethods&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;atproto&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shXjHeiBuRCKmM36cuYnm7YEMzhGnCmCyW92sRJ9pribSF&amp;quot; } }, { &amp;quot;sig&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;dhstt4uPua8OVs8TVzHTqtCnNMsBDN7kjxIBmTIYBDRkknrtprBJ_AISXFoBZyqfoxq2altp-vlRAPEKSh5zeg&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;prev&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;bafyreihmf7dapx27fexc7jwj4cdpbxcmhnnwo3x5vrpvbr6lclzj7gpsmi&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;plc_operation&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;services&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;atproto_pds&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;AtprotoPersonalDataServer&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;endpoint&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;https://morel.us-east.host.bsky.network&amp;quot; } }, &amp;quot;alsoKnownAs&amp;quot;: [ &amp;quot;at://jay.bsky.team&amp;quot; ], &amp;quot;rotationKeys&amp;quot;: [ &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shhCGUqDKjStzuDxPkTxN6ujddP4RkEKJJouJGRRkaLGbg&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shpKnbdPx3g3CmPf5cRVTPe1HtSwVn5ish3wSnDPQCbLJK&amp;quot; ], &amp;quot;verificationMethods&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;atproto&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shtJpFGgEG3tv3ERKvjo7VHbjDPVyvjYvW7gpie49rtNtc&amp;quot; } } ] Again, feel free to click on it instead, https://plc.directory/did:plc:oky5czdrnfjpqslsw2a5iclo/log. This returns a list of all operations that were performed on this DID. The first entry is the genesis operation — the one that created the DID. It is the only one where prev (previous entry) is null, because it is the first one. Note that the first entry of this DID’s log has a different format. This entry uses the legacy format. Currently, newly created DIDs use the new format (subsequent records), but @jay.bsky.team has been around for a while (the account belongs to Bluesky’s CEO). If you look through the logs you will notice a couple of changes that were made to her identity over time: the handle was changed from jay.bsky.social to jay.bsky.team (note that the legacy format used handle whereas the new format uses alsoKnownAs) the handle now includes at:// the personal data server changed from https://bsky.social to https://morel.us-east.host.bsky.network Signatures Each entry in the log includes a sig field, which contains the signature. This cryptographic signature is derived from the other fields in the entry. For the genesis operation, the rotationKeys (or signingKey for legacy) field contains the public key(s) of the key pair(s) with which the entry was signed. Subsequent operations need to be signed with the key from the previous entry. Additionally, the prev field references the previous entry. Creating a DID The identifier in the DID, which is the last part of the colon-separated string, is constructed from the genesis operation. For @jay.bsky.team: the identifier is oky5czdrnfjpqslsw2a5iclo the genesis operation is this JSON document: { &amp;quot;sig&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;KuN3A61golVNSDU71wZKLP9lVuXk6YekJAz1lwDzrPsNTEWHBBW_8zSyV6pDxV4KiYXuAXlS1Ik47XkjQZ94mA&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;prev&amp;quot;: null, &amp;quot;type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;create&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;handle&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;jay.bsky.social&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;service&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;https://bsky.social&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;signingKey&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shP5TBe1sQfSttXty15FAEHV1DZgcxRZNxvEWnPfLFwLxJ&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;recoveryKey&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;did:key:zQ3shhCGUqDKjStzuDxPkTxN6ujddP4RkEKJJouJGRRkaLGbg&amp;quot; } Steps: encode the genesis operation in DAG-CBOR (this is a concise binary format and looks a bit like JSON) create a SHA256 hash of the encoded document encode the hash with base 32 and make its letters lowercase. take the first 24 characters add did:plc: as a prefix to create the 32-character DID Verification Based on what we’ve learned so far we can verify a handle from Bluesky. For example, if we want to check @jay.bsky.team: resolve DID via DNS: did:plc:oky5czdrnfjpqslsw2a5iclo look up DID in PLC directory the handle in the alsoKnownAs (or handle for legacy) field must match jay.bsky.team verify all operations using the public keys and signatures reconstruct the DID from the genesis operation and ensure it is the same as the one we found in the DNS TXT record Can we trust the PLC directory though? Say a malicious actor has taken over control and modified all entries in the log. The hacker even constructed the entries in the log so that all the signatures appear valid. How would we still know the PLC directory is compromised? Remember that the DID can be reconstructed from the genesis operation. If that were modified, we’d end up with a different DID from the one we found in the DNS TXT record. Summary This blog explores the AT Protocol, the decentralized foundation of social applications like Bluesky, with a focus on user identities and their technical underpinnings. It explains how Bluesky user handles are associated with Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs), which can be resolved using DNS records or HTTPS endpoints. Detailed examples demonstrate how tools like dig and curl retrieve DID data, revealing the method (plc) and structure used to catalog them in the Public Ledger of Credentials (PLC). The post also examines the DID lifecycle, showcasing how historical operations and changes—such as updates to handles or servers—are logged and accessible for transparency. There are several aspects that we did not investigate, such as: the web method for DIDs tombstone operations in the log recovery how exactly to construct the prev entry in the DID document what the other fields in the DID document mean If you are curious, the links in the next section will help you answer these questions. Links &amp;amp; Further Reading Bluesky Application AT Protocol AT Protocol Identity AT Protocol DID AT Protocol Handle Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs) v1.0 did:plc Method Specification Specification: DAG-CBOR</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fusectore.dev/2025/01/04/atproto-identity.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric Intuition for Jensen’s Inequality – Madiyar&amp;#39;s Page</title>
      <link>https://maitbayev.github.io/posts/jensens-inequality/</link>
      <description>Jensen’s inequality is fundamental in many fields, including machine learning and statistics. For example, it is useful in the diffusion models paper for understanding the variational lower bound. In this post, I will give a simple geometric intuition for Jensen’s inequality.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://maitbayev.github.io/posts/jensens-inequality/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do it in jeans first</title>
      <link>https://www.gkogan.co/jeans/</link>
      <description>It was six months after my trek through the cloud forests of Peru when I learned I&amp;#39;m not supposed to hike in jeans.

At least it&amp;#39;s what I was told, on a different mountain range and continent, by a Seattleite guide who volunteered to lead a group of hikers around</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.gkogan.co/jeans/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Path to StyleGan2 - The Finale</title>
      <link>https://ym2132.github.io/StyleGAN2</link>
      <description>This post concludes The Path to StyleGan2 series and will see us implement the StyleGAN2 model (there is a StyleGAN3 but I will not cover it, for now).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ym2132.github.io/StyleGAN2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passkeys are incompatible with open-source software (was: “Passkey marketing is lying to you”) – Smoking on a Bike</title>
      <link>https://www.smokingonabike.com/2025/01/04/passkey-marketing-is-lying-to-you/</link>
      <description>Update: After reading more of the spec authors’ comments on open-source Passkey implementations, I cannot support this tech. In addition to what I covered at the bottom of this blog post, I found more instances where the spec authors have expressed positions that are incompatible with open-source software and user freedom:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.smokingonabike.com/2025/01/04/passkey-marketing-is-lying-to-you/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak references and garbage collectors</title>
      <link>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/weakrefs/</link>
      <description>From 2018 to 2021, I worked on a greenfield Python runtime called Skybison. One of its major differences from CPython was that it used a moving garbage collector (GC). This I understood in theory—I knew that it ran when the heap filled up, knew we needed handles to update pointers in the runtime’s code, had read the Moon paper (PDF)—but the other day, I wanted to implement weak references and couldn’t immediately figure it out. Skybison thankfully has a reasonably clear implementation. So now I’m writing this post, mostly for myself, but maybe it will be useful to you as well.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/weakrefs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug Dilution</title>
      <link>https://www.kerrickstaley.com/2025/01/04/drug-dilution</link>
      <description>Caffeine and alcohol are the most commonly consumed psychoactive drugs in the world. They are most often consumed as beverages, which has a few benefits: dos...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.kerrickstaley.com/2025/01/04/drug-dilution</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://nrehiew.github.io/blog/2024/</link>
      <description>In the face of disruptive technologies, moats created by closed source are temporary.Even OpenAI’s closed source approach can’t prevent others from catching up.So we anchor our value in our team — our colleagues grow through this process,accumulate know-how, and form an organization and culture capable of innovation.That’s our moat.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nrehiew.github.io/blog/2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Your Personal Computer Reproducible − Lukas Convent</title>
      <link>https://lukas.convnet.de/blog/2025-01-how-to-make-your-personal-computer-reproducible/</link>
      <description>Published on January 5, 2025.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lukas.convnet.de/blog/2025-01-how-to-make-your-personal-computer-reproducible/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Websockets are Scaled</title>
      <link>https://www.mihirdeshpande.com/posts/how_websockets_are_scaled</link>
      <description>When a client initiates a Websocket connection, it sends an HTTP request with the `Upgrade` header set to `websocket`, signaling its intent to establish the connection. Once the TCP connection is established, each request must be routed to the correct server, which can add latency and processing overhead if examined at Layer 7...</description>
      <author> (Mihir Deshpande)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mihirdeshpande.com/posts/how_websockets_are_scaled</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Tokenizer Bias</title>
      <link>https://blog.tjbai.com/tokenizer-bias</link>
      <description>A Tale of Tokenizer Bias</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.tjbai.com/tokenizer-bias</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use distributed shared memory in CUDA for inter-thread-block communication</title>
      <link>https://jakobsachs.blog/posts/dsmem/</link>
      <description>tl;dr


how to share local memory across thread-blocks on the new Hopper architecture


possibly big deal for performance (no-more going to global for inter-thread-block comms.)


a super-basic demo on how to get started with it


Intro
I noticed there is very little information or easy examples for using the sm-to-sm communication network on the Hopper Architecture (Compute Capability 9.0/sm_90),
so I thought I would try to quickly give a super simple example.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jakobsachs.blog/posts/dsmem/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Ruby’s JSON, Part 5</title>
      <link>https://byroot.github.io/ruby/json/2025/01/04/optimizing-ruby-json-part-5.html</link>
      <description>In the previous post, we showed how we eliminated two malloc/free pairs of calls when generating small JSON documents, and how that put us ahead of Oj when reusing the JSON::State object.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://byroot.github.io/ruby/json/2025/01/04/optimizing-ruby-json-part-5.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 02:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Image Analysis with OpenAI and C#</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2MbfeS67TXs</link>
      <description>Fritz has been doing some analysis of his hat collection using AI, Azure, and C#.  In this video, he shows you how to setup Azure and a simple C# console application to analyze an image, in this case his hats, and get some structured data for later use.

Source code sample is on Gist at:  https://gist.github.com/csharpfritz/f6851c8af1e058b86f251145eac2fd7c
Pricing for Azure OpenAI is at:  https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/pricing/details/cognitive-services/openai-service

#csharp #openai #azure #ai #azureopenai #llm</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2MbfeS67TXs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 23:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cees Bassa (@cgbassa@astrodon.social)</title>
      <link>https://astrodon.social/@cgbassa/113770318993975063</link>
      <description>Attached: 1 image

For the 4th year in a row, my all-sky camera has been taking an image of the sky above the Netherlands every 15 seconds. Combining these images reveal the length of the night changing throughout the year, the passage of clouds and the motion of the Moon and the Sun through the sky. #astrophotography</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://astrodon.social/@cgbassa/113770318993975063</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 22:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software is mostly made of people</title>
      <link>https://hatwd.com/p/software-is-mostly-made-of-people</link>
      <description>Code is just one of many critical ingredients to cultivating value.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hatwd.com/p/software-is-mostly-made-of-people</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 21:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking the Code: A Beginner’s Guide to Network Protocols - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/cracking-the-code-a-beginners-guide-to-network-protocols/</link>
      <description>When you send a text message, watch a video online, or even check your email, countless interactions happen behind the scenes to make it all work seamlessly. These interactions rely on network protocols—a set of rules that ensures devices can talk to each other, even if they&amp;#39;re from completely different manufacturers or built for entirely different purposes.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/cracking-the-code-a-beginners-guide-to-network-protocols/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 18:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 ways to draw an outline</title>
      <link>https://ameye.dev/notes/rendering-outlines/</link>
      <description>&amp;#128397;️ Explaining multiple techniques for rendering outlines and highlights for real-time applications. This includes vertex object-space as well as screen-space methods. This can be used to render outlines in Unity or Unreal. Outlines can be used for gameplay reasons or aesthetics.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ameye.dev/notes/rendering-outlines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 18:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>