<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor WebAssembly on Azure Static Web Apps</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/BlazorWebAssemblyOnAzureStaticWebApps.aspx</link>
      <description>Many apps today are just static files on the front end - HTML and JavaScript - with something powerful on the server ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/BlazorWebAssemblyOnAzureStaticWebApps.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 09:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox usage is down 85% despite Mozilla's top exec pay going up 400%</title>
      <link>http://calpaterson.com/mozilla.html</link>
      <description>Mozilla is in an absolute state: high overheads, falling usage of Firefox, questionable sources of revenue and now making big cuts to engineering as their income falls.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://calpaterson.com/mozilla.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 09:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Codespaces Is Now Github Codespaces </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/09/visual-codespaces-now-github/</link>
      <description>Earlier this month, Microsoft announced that Visual Studio Codespaces is consolidating into GitHub Codespaces. Visual Studio Codespaces is a cloud-based, on-demand development environment similar to Gitpod. The consolidated product supports Azure Functions and can be used with Visual Studio 2019, Visual Studio Code, and modern browsers.</description>
      <author> (Arthur Casals
                
            
        Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/09/visual-codespaces-now-github/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 07:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2020-09-23</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/09/app-developer-links-2020-09-23/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/09/app-developer-links-2020-09-23/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 07:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No script is too simple</title>
      <link>https://nicolasbouliane.com/blog/no-script-is-too-simple</link>
      <description>I write very short scripts, sometimes for single-line commands. Here's why you should do it too.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicolasbouliane.com/blog/no-script-is-too-simple</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defend Your Web Apps from Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title>
      <link>https://auth0.com/blog/cross-site-scripting-xss/</link>
      <description>Learn how XSS works and how to prevent it in Web applications.</description>
      <author> (Search Results)</author>
      <guid>https://auth0.com/blog/cross-site-scripting-xss/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My personal Quality Assurance list before submitting my applications to QA</title>
      <link>https://askxammy.com/my-personal-quality-assurance-list-before-submitting-my-applications-to-qa/</link>
      <description>As developers, our responsibility is to create applications based on a list of specifications defined by the systems analyst in collaboration with the customer. Usually, we divide the application into deliverables that allow us to complete independent and useful functionalities for the user without having the application completely ready.
It’s very important to make our applications as clean and tested as possible before reaching QA, trying to make sure it has the least possible inconvenience, so I recommend that before reaching the QA stage to have your “Functional Completeness checklist”, so you can make sure that your application is ready! That’s why in this post I will be writing about my personal advices to complete the development cycle satisfactorily, to the extent possible.




Functional Completeness Checklist  What exactly does that mean for me? 
It's a personal list that I have established to determine the set of tasks that must be verified to say that a requirement is really ready in our App. This allows me to have my own quality control before going to QA, trying to minimize the risk to get the App returned because something did not go well.
So, for my “Functional Completeness Checklist”, I will be dividing the requirements in sections as following:
➖ UI/UX requirements
➖ Basic functionalities
➖ The Resources
➖ Validation requirements
➖ Usability




Let's start!
The first thing that we must have on hand to make sure that our application passes our personal quality controls is the requirements definition document, where all the requirements and deliverables are defined with their corresponding due date (In which it's assumed we will do this process). With this document, we can derive a list of requirements that should be completed on each date and these are the ones that we will make sure are ready!


.
Here we'll pay attention to the design. Our UIs are supposed to be crafted based on designs given by designers or some other source (It doesn’t matter). The important thing here is to make sure that these designs match the following:
.

✅ The design was correctly replicated for all the available platforms of our App?
✅ The design has preserved both landscape and portrait for all the available platforms of our App (This part can be ignored if it is indicated in the requirements since we can have applications with a specific orientation)
✅ Was the behavior of the design controls tested on each of the available platforms? (Buttons, Entry...)
✅ The user notices:  It’s important that we always keep the user informed of what is happening. (For example, notify them if the internet is leaving, when a process was successful (such as user registration) or when it failed (when the user could not register).)
These are things that we should keep in mind from the beginning, but if for some reason we did not have them, make sure they are fully applied now, this gives a good bonus to our UX.





✅ Functionalities: Do all the functionalities respond correctly as indicated in the definition of requirements? (For example: Make sure that the “Register users” button actually sends the registration request to the server)
✅ Navigation: Regarding the navigation between screens, do they all follow the corresponding logical flow?





✅ As we know, each platform has its own resource structure, and sometimes when we are developing we just add the image of the base dimension so that it can be seen on any device without having to generate the others. It is important not to forget to add all the dimensions corresponding to each platform.
✅ Make sure that all the icons are generated for the devices your App will be working on. (Here an article about how to do it!)








.
Every field that we have in our App, have to be validated (Of course depending of the goal). For example, if we have an email field we know that must validate if the data inserted ave an email structure or if we have a phone number field can not accept letters.
.
Create a list of all your app validation required and verify that all comply with the corresponding validations.
.

🙋‍♀️ For example: I have a user registration screen that has the following fields:
.


🟠  Full name              ➖ Only supports letters.

🟠  Phone Number    ➖ Only supports numbers and preferably has a mask.

🟠 Age                          ➖ Only supports numbers.

🟠  Email                     ➖  You must validate that the information you enter is a valid email.
.

You can do these validations fields with the Behaviors in Xamarin Forms. Here I leave an article about how to do it!.





We know that there are UI / UX experts but as developers, we can help with good practices too! Applying certain features for users to make a super big and favorable change for them!  💕
.

✅ There is a field that just accepts numbers/letters? Great! Set your app for that the device keyboard just shows numbers/letters respectively.
.

✅ There is a  password field? Active “IsPassword” property on your entry field so it appears masked with **** symbols.
.






That’s it! I hope these little tips work super well for you when developing your Apps! and build your own “Functional Completeness Checklist”!  😎

Thanks for reading! 💚💕

Spanish post: https://es.askxammy.com/mi-lista-personal-de-aseguramiento-de-calidad-antes-de-enviar-mis-solicitudes-a-qa/</description>
      <author> (About Leomaris Reyes)</author>
      <guid>https://askxammy.com/my-personal-quality-assurance-list-before-submitting-my-applications-to-qa/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run EF Core Queries on SQL Server From Blazor WebAssembly</title>
      <link>https://blog.jeremylikness.com/blog/run-efcore-queries-against-sql-from-blazor-webassembly/</link>
      <description>A diary of building Expression Power Tools, a library that helps work with expressions and queries. Includes the ability to deserialize and reserialize a query so you can write a LINQ query in a Blazor WebAssembly client and execute it remotely on an ASP.NET Core server using Entity Framework Core.</description>
      <author> (Empowering developers to be their best.📅 Sep 20, 2020
🕘 28 min read
💬 5924 words)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jeremylikness.com/blog/run-efcore-queries-against-sql-from-blazor-webassembly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding unit tests is boring. Wouldn't it be cool if an AI could do it for you? That's where Diffblue comes in</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2020/09/21/diffblue_let_ai_code_unit_tests/</link>
      <description>A big time saver – but 'we can't tell if the current logic that you have in the code is correct or not.' Oh</description>
      <author> (Mon 21 Sep 2020 // 10:15 UTC)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2020/09/21/diffblue_let_ai_code_unit_tests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Code Tired | Approval Tests: Write Tests More Quickly</title>
      <link>http://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Approval-Tests-Write-Tests-More-Quickly</link>
      <description>Don't Code Tired - Jason Roberts on Software Development and .NET -</description>
      <author> (Jason)</author>
      <guid>http://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Approval-Tests-Write-Tests-More-Quickly</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything about null in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://dmitripavlutin.com/javascript-null/</link>
      <description>null in JavaScript is a special value  that represents a missing object.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/dmitri.pavlutin)</author>
      <guid>https://dmitripavlutin.com/javascript-null/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate, modernize .NET applications with Azure</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/migrate-modernize-net-applications-with-azure/ba-p/1696499</link>
      <description>Digital demand for goods, services and information has never been higher and organizations of all sizes are bringing their web applications to the cloud to save costs and better support remote employees, customers, and partners.   As this demand grows, many of our customers have found that their cur...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/43956)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/migrate-modernize-net-applications-with-azure/ba-p/1696499</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to generate code using Roslyn source generators in real world scenarios</title>
      <link>https://www.cazzulino.com/source-generators.html</link>
      <description>A blog about .NET, C#, Visual Studio, Mobile, Xamarin and technology</description>
      <author> (Daniel Cazzulino)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cazzulino.com/source-generators.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing more ways, we’re making app development easier on Windows</title>
      <link>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2020/09/22/kevin-gallo-microsoft-ignite-2020/</link>
      <description>Building great apps on Windows should be easier – no matter how your app is written.  We want to ensure you have a path forward to make your apps better on Windows and we’re doing that with</description>
      <author> (Windows Developer Blog)</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2020/09/22/kevin-gallo-microsoft-ignite-2020/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The September 2020 release of Azure Data Studio is now available - SQL Server Blog</title>
      <link>https://cloudblogs.microsoft.com/sqlserver/2020/09/22/the-september-2020-release-of-azure-data-studio-is-now-available/</link>
      <description>The September release of Azure Data Studio is now available. Download Azure Data Studio and review the release notes to get started. Azure Data Studio is a multi-database, cross-platform desktop environment for data professionals using the Microsoft family of on-premises and cloud data platforms on Windows, MacOS, and Linux. To learn more, visit our GitHub.Read more</description>
      <author> (Alan Yu				
													Program Manager, SQL Server)</author>
      <guid>https://cloudblogs.microsoft.com/sqlserver/2020/09/22/the-september-2020-release-of-azure-data-studio-is-now-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 06:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using GitHub Codespaces with .NET Core | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/using-github-codespaces-with-net-core/</link>
      <description>Read about updated support for developing .NET Core applications using GitHub Codespaces and Visual Studio.</description>
      <author> (Tim Heuer Program Manager, .NET Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/using-github-codespaces-with-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 05:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Swift on Windows</title>
      <link>https://swift.org/blog/swift-on-windows/</link>
      <description>The Swift project is introducing new downloadable Swift toolchain images for Windows!  These images contain development components needed to build and run Swift code on Windows.

</description>
      <author> (Apple Inc.)</author>
      <guid>https://swift.org/blog/swift-on-windows/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 04:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Picture of Java in 2020 – IntelliJ IDEA Blog | JetBrains</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2020/09/a-picture-of-java-in-2020/</link>
      <description>This year Java hit an incredible milestone and reached the grand old age of 25 years. We celebrated its jubilee by running a special online Java day event, where lots of expert speakers shared their e</description>
      <author> (Valeriia Karpenko)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/idea/2020/09/a-picture-of-java-in-2020/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 04:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest gainers in Video Games sales rank over the past 24 hours</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/gp/movers-and-shakers/videogames/ref=as_li_ss_tl?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202009</link>
      <description>Amazon.com Movers &amp; Shakers: The biggest gainers in Video Games sales rank over the past 24 hours</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/gp/movers-and-shakers/videogames/ref=as_li_ss_tl?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202009</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 03:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>charliesome/doslinux</title>
      <link>https://github.com/charliesome/doslinux</link>
      <description>Contribute to charliesome/doslinux development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (charliesome)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/charliesome/doslinux</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 01:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com: Dell OEM Genuine USB 104-key Black Wired Keyboard (RH659 L100 SK-8115): Computers &amp; Accessories</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/Dell-Genuine-104-key-Keyboard-SK-8115/dp/B0037H8AB4?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202009</link>
      <description>Buy Dell OEM Genuine USB 104-key Black Wired Keyboard (RH659 L100 SK-8115): Keyboards - Amazon.com ✓ FREE DELIVERY possible on eligible purchases</description>
      <author> (Visit the Dell Store)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/Dell-Genuine-104-key-Keyboard-SK-8115/dp/B0037H8AB4?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202009</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acorn Woodpeckers Have Multi-Day Wars, and Birds Come From All Around to Watch</title>
      <link>https://www.atlasobscura.com/articles/acrorn-woodpecker-wars</link>
      <description>A window into complex avian sociopolitical lives. </description>
      <author> (Luna Shyr)</author>
      <guid>https://www.atlasobscura.com/articles/acrorn-woodpecker-wars</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Terminal Preview 1.4 Release | Windows Command Line</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/windows-terminal-preview-1-4-release/</link>
      <description>Welcome to another release of Windows Terminal Preview and Windows Terminal! Windows Terminal Preview is now on version 1.4 and will have the new features listed below. Windows Terminal has moved to version 1.3 and will have all the features from our previous preview release.</description>
      <author> (Kayla Cinnamon Program Manager, Windows Terminal, Console, Command Line, &amp; Cascadia Code Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/windows-terminal-preview-1-4-release/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Journal is Back | Linux Journal</title>
      <link>https://www.linuxjournal.com/content/linux-journal-back</link>
      <description>Opt-out for personal information &amp; cookies</description>
      <author> (by Webmaster)</author>
      <guid>https://www.linuxjournal.com/content/linux-journal-back</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is a good input method?</title>
      <link>https://thottingal.in/blog/2020/09/21/good-inputmethod/</link>
      <description>As more and more people enter to the Malayalam digital world, the issue of not having any formal training for Malayalam computing is more observed. People sometimes just search for input methods in web, ask friends or use whatever coming with the devices they have. Since I myself is an author of two input methods, sometimes people ask me too. This essay is about the characteristics of a good input method to help people make the right choice.</description>
      <author> (Santhosh Thottingal)</author>
      <guid>https://thottingal.in/blog/2020/09/21/good-inputmethod/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Management Flywheel</title>
      <link>https://link.medium.com/2Ml5sDYTZ9</link>
      <description>Have you ever worked on a team that felt like it was just stuck in a rut? Somehow things were always just one fix away from improving: the…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@skamille)</author>
      <guid>https://link.medium.com/2Ml5sDYTZ9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use your support system to get started with marketing today</title>
      <link>https://philippmuens.com/customer-support-driven-marketing/</link>
      <description>You love working on your product but marketing isn't your cup of tea? Learn how to use your support system to generate content marketing ideas for you.</description>
      <author> (Philipp Muens)</author>
      <guid>https://philippmuens.com/customer-support-driven-marketing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s New in Web Experiences, Ignite 2020: Need to secure your remote workers? Choose Microsoft Edge as your browser for business</title>
      <link>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2020/09/22/whats-new-in-web-experiences-ignite-2020-need-to-secure-your-remote-workers-choose-microsoft-edge-as-your-browser-for-business/</link>
      <description>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tYNDD_dtULc

The message is loud and clear, and we’ve heard it: Providing secure remote</description>
      <author> (Windows Experience Blog)</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsexperience/2020/09/22/whats-new-in-web-experiences-ignite-2020-need-to-secure-your-remote-workers-choose-microsoft-edge-as-your-browser-for-business/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Will Build Something Great...Once I Get an Idea</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/i-will-build-something-great-once-i-get-an-idea/</link>
      <description>Everything starts off with an idea. You can't build a business without an idea. You can't make a movie without an idea. You can't draw without an idea. So how do you get an idea?</description>
      <author> (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/i-will-build-something-great-once-i-get-an-idea/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Era of Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://blog.robenkleene.com/2020/09/21/the-era-of-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <description>Roben Kleene’s blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.robenkleene.com/2020/09/21/the-era-of-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I got married and had kids so you don't have to | Robert Heaton</title>
      <link>https://robertheaton.com/married-with-kids/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robertheaton.com/married-with-kids/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running SQL Server Integration Tests in .NET Core Projects via Docker - Dangl.Blog();</title>
      <link>https://blog.dangl.me/archive/running-sql-server-integration-tests-in-net-core-projects-via-docker/</link>
      <description>To ensure that your integration tests really match your production environment, you should test under the same conditions - here's how to manage your SQL Server databases via Docker</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.dangl.me/archive/running-sql-server-integration-tests-in-net-core-projects-via-docker/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report 2019-113</title>
      <link>https://www.auditor.ca.gov/reports/2019-113/sections.html#section1</link>
      <description>Use the links below to skip to the section you wish to view:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.auditor.ca.gov/reports/2019-113/sections.html#section1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the Pythagorean theorem</title>
      <link>https://xenaproject.wordpress.com/2020/09/19/thoughts-on-the-pythagorean-theorem/</link>
      <description>Pythagoras’ theorem says that a square is equal to two squares. What does equality mean here?</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://xenaproject.wordpress.com/2020/09/19/thoughts-on-the-pythagorean-theorem/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 23:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The beginners guide to breaking website security with nothing more than a Pineapple</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/the-beginners-guide-to-breaking-website/</link>
      <description>You know how security people get all uppity about SSL this and SSL that? Stuff like posting creds over HTTPS isn&amp;#x2019;t enough, you have to load login forms over HTTPS as well and then you can&amp;#x2019;t send auth cookies over HTTP because they&amp;#x2019;ll get</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/the-beginners-guide-to-breaking-website/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 22:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banjo Obayomi - Grimoire, A Data-Centric Blogging Platform [w/ASL Interpreting]</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RPjFJNDlGdw</link>
      <description>In this talk, I will describe how I built a new blogging platform focused on creating interactive data stories. By the end, you will understand the tools and techniques used to build a serverless first platform and a new place to communicate with data.
---
Banjo is a Senior Research Engineer at Two Six Labs, where he develops platform solutions for productizing various researched-based projects. Banjo is passionate about operationalizing data aka DataOps and has started a podcast and meetup around data.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RPjFJNDlGdw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 22:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft to Contribute to Java on Windows and Mac ARM </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/09/microsoft-windows-mac-arm/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is working to help port Java to Windows and Mac ARM on the AARCH64 chipset. The improvement should help enable Java applications to run on upcoming commercial ARM hardware.</description>
      <author> (Erik Costlow
                
            
        Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2020/09/microsoft-windows-mac-arm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 22:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Ignite</title>
      <link>https://myignite.microsoft.com/sessions/0b186c68-9e6d-4dae-a85c-ef861b80fd6e</link>
      <description>Microsoft Ignite | Microsoft’s annual gathering of technology leaders and practitioners will be launched as a digital event experience this September.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://myignite.microsoft.com/sessions/0b186c68-9e6d-4dae-a85c-ef861b80fd6e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 22:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>773219 - Warning if HTTP/2 pushed items are not collected</title>
      <link>https://bugs.chromium.org/p/chromium/issues/detail?id=773219#c11</link>
      <description>About Monorail
 User Guide
 Release Notes
 Feedback on Monorail
 Terms
 Privacy</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bugs.chromium.org/p/chromium/issues/detail?id=773219#c11</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 22:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>71.177.243.54</title>
      <link>https://beta.shodan.io/host/71.177.243.54</link>
      <description>Ports open: 80, 443, 500</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://beta.shodan.io/host/71.177.243.54</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 22:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make tracking your work easier than ever with Tables</title>
      <link>https://blog.google/technology/area-120/tables/</link>
      <description>Tables, the newest tool from Area 120 by Google, beta launches in the U.S. to help teams easily track and automate work.</description>
      <author> (Tim Gleason

    
      
        General Manager, Tables)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.google/technology/area-120/tables/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 22:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using GitHub Actions in Visual Studio is as easy as right-click and Publish | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/using-github-actions-in-visual-studio-is-as-easy-as-right-click-and-publish/</link>
      <description>Download the latest preview version of Visual Studio and try out the new ability to setup CI/CD to Azure for projects that use GitHub to host your source repository.  With VS 16.8 Preview 3.1, for this feature to show up in Publish dialog,</description>
      <author> (Angelos Petropoulos Product Manager, on the .NET team Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/using-github-actions-in-visual-studio-is-as-easy-as-right-click-and-publish/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 21:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The cop who quit instead of helping to gentrify Atlanta</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/crime-justice/2020/09/the-cop-who-quit-instead-of-helping-to-gentrify-atlanta/</link>
      <description>"It dawned on me that the entire system, the entire thing, was just a shitty mafia system."</description>
      <author> (Laura Thompson)</author>
      <guid>https://www.motherjones.com/crime-justice/2020/09/the-cop-who-quit-instead-of-helping-to-gentrify-atlanta/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 21:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Features in Visual Studio 2019 v16.8 Preview 3.1 | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2019-v16-8-preview-3-1/</link>
      <description>Visual Studio 2019 v16.8 Preview 3.1 brings Git Integration, C++20 conformance, .NET Productivity, and more. Plus, sign-up for Visual Studio Codespaces! </description>
      <author> (Jacqueline Widdis Release Manager, Visual Studio Release Team Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2019-v16-8-preview-3-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 21:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activision says no Call of Duty account hacks have occurred, no details compromised - VG247</title>
      <link>https://www.vg247.com/2020/09/22/activision-call-of-duty-account-hack-response/</link>
      <description>Activision is denying reports that Call of Duty accounts have suffered a major hack.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.vg247.com/2020/09/22/activision-call-of-duty-account-hack-response/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 21:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kk9Fv8m0Ksw</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io/</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kk9Fv8m0Ksw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 21:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commentary: How India's ancient caste system is ruining lives in Silicon Valley | ZDNet</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/commentary-how-indias-ancient-caste-system-is-ruining-lives-in-silicon-valley/</link>
      <description>Over 90% of Indian techies in the US are upper-caste Indians and many of them are allegedly making life a living hell for Dalits, those who are classified as the lowest of the low in India, whose horrifying historical persecution has continued in the cradle of tech.</description>
      <author> (Rajiv Rao)</author>
      <guid>https://www.zdnet.com/article/commentary-how-indias-ancient-caste-system-is-ruining-lives-in-silicon-valley/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 20:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NerdsVote | Register to Vote at Conventions</title>
      <link>https://www.nerdsvote.com/</link>
      <description>NerdsVote links cosplayers, gamers, pop culture fans, and nerds of all kinds to voter registration opportunities.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nerdsvote.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 20:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.0.0-preview5 · microsoft/reverse-proxy</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/reverse-proxy/releases/tag/v1.0.0-preview5</link>
      <description>This release supports .NET Core 3.1 and .NET 5.0.0 RC 1. See Getting Started. The Microsoft.ReverseProxy package is available on NuGet.org.
Major changes and features:

Per-cluster configuration of...</description>
      <author> (microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/reverse-proxy/releases/tag/v1.0.0-preview5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 19:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New for Blazor: Azure Static Web Apps Support -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/09/22/blazor-static-web-apps.aspx</link>
      <description>With Blazor taking the .NET web development world by storm, one of the first announcements during Microsoft's Ignite 2020 developer/IT event was its new support in Azure Static Web Apps.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel09/22/2020)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/09/22/blazor-static-web-apps.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 19:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Disaster Recovery Scenarios for SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Data-Exposed/Hybrid-Disaster-Recovery-Scenarios-for-SQL-Server</link>
      <description>In the conclusion to this two-part series with Allan Hirt, learn how Azure can be used to create disaster recovery solutions for your on premises Microsoft SQL Server instances and databases through t</description>
      <author> (by Marisa Brasile)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Data-Exposed/Hybrid-Disaster-Recovery-Scenarios-for-SQL-Server</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 19:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Ignite</title>
      <link>https://myignite.microsoft.com/sessions/338ab7e7-0c86-47b2-b928-9b93c2503a30</link>
      <description>Microsoft Ignite | Microsoft’s annual gathering of technology leaders and practitioners will be launched as a digital event experience this September.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://myignite.microsoft.com/sessions/338ab7e7-0c86-47b2-b928-9b93c2503a30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Static Web Apps with .NET and Blazor | ASP.NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/azure-static-web-apps-with-blazor/</link>
      <description>Azure Static Web Apps is a service that automatically builds and deploys full stack web apps from a GitHub repository. Azure Static Web Apps consist of a static web frontend, and an Azure Functions based backend. When you create a Static Web Apps resource,</description>
      <author> (Aaron Powell)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/azure-static-web-apps-with-blazor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Ignite</title>
      <link>https://myignite.microsoft.com/sessions/876deac4-3b19-443e-adf7-11c1061a4dbc</link>
      <description>Microsoft Ignite | Microsoft’s annual gathering of technology leaders and practitioners will be launched as a digital event experience this September.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://myignite.microsoft.com/sessions/876deac4-3b19-443e-adf7-11c1061a4dbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC voter ID law written with ‘discriminatory intent,’ says judge who just blocked it</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article238870598.html</link>
      <description>“Racial discrimination and racial polarization have historically pervaded North Carolina’s political climate — and still do,” the judge wrote in her ruling against the new voter ID law.</description>
      <author> (By Rashaan Ayesh)</author>
      <guid>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article238870598.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Ignite</title>
      <link>https://myignite.microsoft.com/sessions/9c81f93e-2a2b-4f1c-91fd-4523a9959045</link>
      <description>Microsoft Ignite | Microsoft’s annual gathering of technology leaders and practitioners will be launched as a digital event experience this September.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://myignite.microsoft.com/sessions/9c81f93e-2a2b-4f1c-91fd-4523a9959045</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Interview Questions Deconstructed: The Knight’s Dialer</title>
      <link>https://alexgolec.dev/google-interview-questions-deconstructed-the-knights-dialer/</link>
      <description>This is the second in a series of posts in which I share my advice for candidates interviewing for tech companies, drawing on my experience as an engineer and interviewer at Google. If you haven’t already, take a look at the introduction to this series. Before I start, a</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alexgolec.dev/google-interview-questions-deconstructed-the-knights-dialer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars</title>
      <link>https://www.xamarinpodcast.com/78</link>
      <description>The Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Sciences - you may know them as the Oscars - built an app using Xamarin and Azure!</description>
      <author> (Xamarin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.xamarinpodcast.com/78</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 17:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox  81.0, See All New Features, Updates and Fixes</title>
      <link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/81.0/releasenotes/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/81.0/releasenotes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 17:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>postprintum/devcomrade</title>
      <link>https://github.com/postprintum/devcomrade#whats-new</link>
      <description>DevComrade - A copy/paste/run productivity improvement utility for developers - postprintum/devcomrade</description>
      <author> (postprintum)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/postprintum/devcomrade#whats-new</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 17:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com: Online Shopping for Electronics, Apparel, Computers, Books, DVDs &amp; more</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202009</link>
      <description>Free delivery on millions of items with Prime. Low prices across earth's biggest selection of books, music, DVDs, electronics, computers, software, apparel &amp; accessories, shoes, jewelry, tools &amp; hardware, housewares, furniture, sporting goods, beauty &amp; personal care, groceries &amp; just about anything else.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202009</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 16:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowerment to the People! What You Need to Know About Black People, Disability, and Accessibility</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Aqw7i9XPkA</link>
      <description>[w/ASL Interpreting]

About one fifth (20%) of the global population lives with disabilities.​ According to the 2017 American Community Survey, 13.6 percent of Black and African Americans have a disability. Further, the unemployment rate for people with disabilities is almost double of other people, and the people with disabilities who are employed have lower earnings, in general.

This means we have an opportunity and a duty to empower Black people with technology. One of the most powerful ways we can do this is to make our messaging accessible—no matter the platform or media.

While many of us have heard that accessibility is important, we seldom hear about how to implement it in our everyday work. Angela will discuss how people in every discipline—including PMs, content writers, designers, engineers, and more—can do so and further amplify the voices of Black people.
---
Angela Hooker is a Senior Accessibility Program Manager at Microsoft, where she's built a center of expertise for accessibility, user experience, and universal design. She's brought her web management, development, design, accessibility, and editorial and content management expertise to the government and private sector for over 20 years.

Angela also advocates for role-based accessibility and believes that teaching people how to incorporate principles of accessibility in their everyday work creates a sustainable program and produces the most accessible user experiences. Angela speaks on and writes about accessibility, disability, user experience, and plain language.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Aqw7i9XPkA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 16:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://two.findanswersnow.net/bsearch.php?q=login%20microsoft</link>
      <description>Ads related to login microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://two.findanswersnow.net/bsearch.php?q=login%20microsoft</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 16:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View PDF files in Firefox or choose another viewer</title>
      <link>https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/view-pdf-files-firefox-or-choose-another-viewer</link>
      <description>You can view PDF files in Firefox using the built-in viewer or with a third-party tool. Learn more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/view-pdf-files-firefox-or-choose-another-viewer</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 16:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>terrajobst/sample-blog-tooling</title>
      <link>https://github.com/terrajobst/sample-blog-tooling/blob/master/.vscode/tasks.json</link>
      <description>Contribute to terrajobst/sample-blog-tooling development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (terrajobst)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/terrajobst/sample-blog-tooling/blob/master/.vscode/tasks.json</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 16:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why does the Disk Cleanup tool's Windows Update Cleanup take so long and consume so much CPU? | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20200922-00/?p=104252</link>
      <description>If you ask the Disk Cleanup tool to clean up Windows Update files, you may find that it takes a long time and consumes a lot of CPU. What the heck is it doing? How hard can deleting files be? The Windows Update Cleanup option is doing more than just deleting files.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20200922-00/?p=104252</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 15:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Anomaly Detection Using Plain SQL</title>
      <link>https://hakibenita.com/sql-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description>Identify Problems Before They Become Disasters</description>
      <author> (Haki Benita)</author>
      <guid>https://hakibenita.com/sql-anomaly-detection</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 14:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Pieces of Advice for Aspiring Web Developers</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V4UYuvegsTg</link>
      <description>Want to become a Web Developer? Here are the five things you should be doing!

Need a structured path for becoming a Web Developer? Check out the Scrimba Career Path! 👇
http://bit.ly/jqqscrimba
_____________________________________________

Newsletter 🗞
Interested in exclusive content and discounts? 🤯 Sign up for the newsletter!
https://www.jamesqquick.com
_____________________________________________

Connect with me 😀
Live streams on Twitch - https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
Follow me on Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Join the 💬 Discord Server 💬 - https://discord.gg/vM2bagU
_____________________________________________

COURSES  💻
Learn how to build Fullstack apps with React and Serverless Functions - https://www.jamesqquick.com/courses/react-and-serverless-fullstack-developmnent
Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code - https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/
Build a Quiz App  - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V4UYuvegsTg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 14:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Helm chart for an ASP.NET Core app: Deploying ASP.NET Core applications to Kubernetes - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/deploying-asp-net-core-applications-to-kubernetes-part-4-creating-a-helm-chart-for-an-aspnetcore-app/</link>
      <description>In this post I show how you can create a Helm chart for an ASP.NET Core application that you can use to deploy your app to Kubernetes.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/deploying-asp-net-core-applications-to-kubernetes-part-4-creating-a-helm-chart-for-an-aspnetcore-app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 13:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dew Drop – September 22, 2020 (#3280)</title>
      <link>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/2020/09/22/dew-drop-september-22-2020-3280/</link>
      <description>About Me</description>
      <author> (Alvin A.)</author>
      <guid>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/2020/09/22/dew-drop-september-22-2020-3280/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 13:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome Web Store payments deprecation</title>
      <link>https://developer.chrome.com/webstore/cws-payments-deprecation</link>
      <description>The Chrome Web Store payments system is now deprecated and will be shut down over the coming months. There are many other ways to monetize your extensions, and if you currently use Chrome Web Store payments, you’ll need to migrate to one of them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developer.chrome.com/webstore/cws-payments-deprecation</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 12:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>» X-COM The Digital Antiquarian</title>
      <link>https://www.filfre.net/2020/09/x-com/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Jimmy Maher)</author>
      <guid>https://www.filfre.net/2020/09/x-com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 12:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>