<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Donate - Transgender Law Center</title>
      <link>https://transgenderlawcenter.org/donate</link>
      <description>To donate by check, please make payable to Transgender Law Center and mail to us at: PO Box 741803, Los Angeles, CA 90074-1803. For questions about donations, contact giving@transgenderlawcenter.org.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://transgenderlawcenter.org/donate</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 23:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>https://srlp.org/donate/</link>
      <description>Thank you for supporting the Sylvia Rivera Law Project. Your gift helps us continue to provide free legal services to meet&amp;#160;survival needs and build community power with transgender people who are l…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://srlp.org/donate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 23:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donate - Casa Ruby</title>
      <link>https://casaruby.org/donate/</link>
      <description>Your donation to Casa Ruby helps support our Center and programs &amp;amp;amp, Limited Financial Assistance to those enrolled in our career and employment services, when they are un-employed or between jobs, and those with extreme financial hardship. We work with individuals of all backgrounds, races and ethnicities, genders and ages, to connect them to Social Services. We continue using your donations to help others in need.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://casaruby.org/donate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 23:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PKC Test-of-Time Award</title>
      <link>https://www.iacr.org/meetings/pkc/test_of_time_award/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.iacr.org/meetings/pkc/test_of_time_award/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 22:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SerenityOS: A remarkable achievement for a small project</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2022/03/31/serenityos/</link>
      <description>Lead dev of modest ground-up Unix-like OS quits job to work on it</description>
      <author> (Liam Proven in Prague)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2022/03/31/serenityos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 22:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Cloud Azure 4.0 Now Generally Available -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/03/31/spring-cloud-azure-4.aspx</link>
      <description>  Microsoft announced that Spring Cloud Azure -- not to be confused with Azure Spring Cloud -- is now generally available in a version 4.0 update.
</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel03/31/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/03/31/spring-cloud-azure-4.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 21:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2022 for Mac Preview 8</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2022-for-mac-preview-8/</link>
      <description>Visual Studio 2022 for Mac 17.0 Preview 8 is now available! In this release, the focus is on addressing top reported issues from prior preview releases and driving forward to a high-quality GA (General Availability) release. This work builds on top of prior previews where we’ve moved the UI of the IDE to fully native macOS UI and migrated the IDE to run on top of .NET 6 (enabling native support of Apple’s M1 (arm64) processor.</description>
      <author> (Jordan Matthiesen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2022-for-mac-preview-8/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 21:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lupinia Studios - I&amp;#39;m a Scam Prevention Expert, and I Got Scammed</title>
      <link>http://www.lupinia.net/writing/tech/scammed.htm</link>
      <description>When discussing scams and social engineering attacks, it&amp;#39;s easy for security experts to imply the victims of these attacks should have known better.  And, as much as we may like to think we&amp;#39;d handle these situations so much better, that&amp;#39;s just not true.</description>
      <author> (Natasha L.)</author>
      <guid>http://www.lupinia.net/writing/tech/scammed.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 21:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landing Page</title>
      <link>https://reg.rainfocus.com/flow/akamai/secsummitanz22/landing/page/page</link>
      <description>Resilience from the Cloud to the Edge

Rapidly advancing application architectures and the shift to a remote working culture have forced drastic changes to how businesses engage their customers, manage their work forces,...Show more</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://reg.rainfocus.com/flow/akamai/secsummitanz22/landing/page/page</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 20:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDC OLED - mitxela.com</title>
      <link>https://mitxela.com/projects/ddc-oled</link>
      <description>The most useless second monitor possible</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mitxela.com/projects/ddc-oled</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 19:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABP Community Talks 2022.3: Domain-Driven Design &amp;amp; the ABP book</title>
      <link>https://kommunity.com/volosoft/events/abp-community-talks-20223-domain-driven-design-the-abp-book-b7d55a7b</link>
      <description>In this episode of the ABP Community Talks, Halil İbrahim Kalkan, Jon Galloway, Lee Richardson and Anto Subash will talk and discuss Domain-Driven Design, the o</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kommunity.com/volosoft/events/abp-community-talks-20223-domain-driven-design-the-abp-book-b7d55a7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 17:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docket for UBIQUITI INC. v. KREBS, 1:22-cv-00352 - CourtListener.com</title>
      <link>https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/63197557/ubiquiti-inc-v-krebs/</link>
      <description>Docket for UBIQUITI INC. v. KREBS, 1:22-cv-00352 — Brought to you by the RECAP
  Initiative and Free Law Project, a non-profit dedicated to creating high
  quality open legal information.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/63197557/ubiquiti-inc-v-krebs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 17:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAF mitigations for Spring4Shell</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/waf-mitigations-sping4shell/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare Managed Ruleset updates for the recent vulnerabilities affecting the Java Spring framework and related software components</description>
      <author> (Michael Tremante)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/waf-mitigations-sping4shell/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lead Application Engineer</title>
      <link>https://www.smartrecruiters.com/Square/743999807242028</link>
      <description>Company Description: Founded in July 2021, TBD is Block&amp;#39;s&amp;#160;newest business unit. Our team is building an open developer platform and primitives to help unlock the next wave of innovation in financial services — which we believe will be decentralized, permissionless, and non-custodial. As such, we will eschew custodial and traditional centralized approaches — and instead, shape Block&amp;#39;s strategy in building for a non-custodial world, embracing the decentralized and democratized nature of crypto. The offerings we build will provide developers, institutions, and individuals with the capabilities needed to access this decentralized future. Our vision is to leverage bitcoin and other blockchain technologies to reinvent the global financial system in an open and permissionless way to further Block&amp;#39;s mission of economic empowerment and financial inclusion for all, with a global focus.

Job Description: TBD is on the mission to build a platform and protocols that enable developers — from startups to established financial institutions — more easily create solutions in the decentralized financial space that further our mission of economic empowerment globally. You will be an essential contributor as we build towards our mission and you will report to the Head of Decentralized Identity in TBD.You will work with all major components and standards specifications - Decentralized Identifiers, Verifiable Credentials, and personal data-stores - to build apps and interfaces that make using these technologies as effortless as possible. You will lead all front-end app development across all target platforms (desktop and mobile), and produce any tooling required to help foster the developer ecosystem. You are comfortable with both independent and small group collaborative development, and will be able to lead an engineering team as our team continues to grow.You Will:* Spend roughly 75% of your time developing implementations of standard components that make up the backbone of TBD&amp;#39;s efforts.
* In the other 25% of your time, you will contribute to TBD&amp;#39;s architecture and guide others in a senior capacity.
* Scale the learning curve on new subject areas across domains and technologies.
* Manage ambiguity with comfort in a shifting and evolving environment.


Qualifications: You Have:* BS in CS, CE, EE, or equivalent practical experience.
* 1+ year of exposure to the major components and standards specifications (Decentralized Identifiers, Verifiable Credentials, and personal datastores).
* 5+ years experience as a lead engineer on large-scale client applications.
* Experience developing elegant app frontends that distill complex data and interactions into simple, intuitive interfaces.
* Some management experience leading engineers.
* Fluent in TypeScript, JavaScript, React, PWA development, and advanced Web platform APIs.
You May Also Have:* Experience with ION and DID-based personal datastores (e.g. Identity Hubs)
* Experience with DIDComms and DID Authentication.
* Basic ability to work with WASM


Additional Information: We’re working to build a more inclusive economy where our customers have equal access to opportunity, and we strive to live by these same values in building our workplace. Block is a proud equal opportunity employer. We work hard to evaluate all employees and job applicants consistently, without regard to race, color, religion, gender, national origin, age, disability, pregnancy, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation, citizenship, or any other legally protected class.&amp;#160;We believe in being fair, and are committed to an inclusive interview experience, including providing reasonable accommodations to disabled applicants throughout the recruitment process. We encourage applicants to share any needed accommodations with their recruiter, who will treat these requests as confidentially as possible.&amp;#160;Want to learn more about what we’re doing to build a workplace that is fair and square? Check out our I+D page.&amp;#160;Additionally, we consider qualified applicants with criminal histories for employment on our team, and always assess candidates on an individualized basis.
PerksWe want you to be well and thrive. Our global benefits package includes:* Healthcare coverage
* Retirement Plans
* Employee Stock Purchase Program
* Wellness perks
* Paid parental leave
* Paid time off
* Learning and Development resources

Block, Inc. (NYSE: SQ) is a global technology company with a focus on financial services. Made up of Square, Cash App, Spiral, TIDAL, and TBD54566975, we build tools to help more people access the economy. Square helps sellers run and grow their businesses with its integrated ecosystem of commerce solutions, business software, and banking services. With Cash App, anyone can easily send, spend, or invest their money in stocks or Bitcoin. Spiral (formerly Square Crypto) builds and funds free, open-source Bitcoin projects. Artists use TIDAL to help them succeed as entrepreneurs and connect more deeply with fans. TBD54566975 is building an open developer platform to make it easier to access Bitcoin and other blockchain technologies without having to go through an institution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.smartrecruiters.com/Square/743999807242028</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar next week: Clean Architecture with RavenDB</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/196865-B/webinar-next-week-clean-architecture-with-ravendb</link>
      <description>Next week I&amp;#39;ll be talking how you can utilize RavenDB to create a clean architecture for your systems. You can register in the following link</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/196865-B/webinar-next-week-clean-architecture-with-ravendb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director, Product Management - Ecosystem and Identity </title>
      <link>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/3592002</link>
      <description>Remote - US / Canada</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/3592002</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Resilience Manager</title>
      <link>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/4087298</link>
      <description>Remote - US</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/4087298</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sr. Incident Responder (CSIRT)</title>
      <link>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/3973446</link>
      <description>Remote - US / Canada</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/3973446</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future-proofing SaltStack</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/future-proofing-saltstack/</link>
      <description>This blogpost chronicles the recent CVEs investigation, our findings, and how we are helping secure Salt now and in the Quantum future</description>
      <author> (Lenka Marekov&amp;#225;)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/future-proofing-saltstack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 13:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 34: Geeking out on .NET with Nick Chapsas</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0034-nickchapsas/</link>
      <description>In this episode, I was thrilled to be joined by Nick Chapsas! If you’re a .NET developer - then his YouTube channel is an absolute must! Given all the amazing topics he covers on his channel - it would have been a shame to just chat with him about a single topic! So we decided to do a few lightning topics instead! Here’s what we geeked out on…
 .NET 6 Minimal API The outdated opinion of some non .</description>
      <author> (Dan Clarke)</author>
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0034-nickchapsas/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 13:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quicksort Algorithm in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-quicksort-algorithm/</link>
      <description>Quicksort is one of the most efficient algorithms that we can use to accomplish our sorting goals. In this article, we discuss how to implement Quicksort in C# as well as analyze its time and space complexity. Let’s start.&amp;#160; What is Quicksort Algorithm? Just like merge sort, quicksort uses the “divide and conquer” strategy to […]</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-quicksort-algorithm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 09:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTTP/2 output processing make over by davidfowl &amp;#183; Pull Request #40925 &amp;#183; dotnet/aspnetcore</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspnetcore/pull/40925</link>
      <description>This changes the HTTP/2&amp;#39;s output processing to be use queues instead of locks (a channel to be precise). We&amp;#39;re manually scheduling the Http2OutputProducer&amp;#39;s intent to write instead of a write opera...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspnetcore/pull/40925</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 07:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Releasing Faster Without Defects: The Automation Game</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/releasing-faster-without-defects-automation-game</link>
      <description>Increasing release frequency creates potential for defects in production and puts a lot of pressure on software testing, struggling to keep up with the pace.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/releasing-faster-without-defects-automation-game</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 06:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running .NET 7 apps on WASI on arm64 Mac</title>
      <link>https://www.strathweb.com/2022/03/running-net-7-apps-on-wasi-on-arm64-mac/</link>
      <description>WASI stands for WebAssembly System Interface, and allows to run WebAssembly code independently of the browsers, as it provides access to operating system features such as file system access or networking. It is highly experimental, but at the same time a tremendously interesting project, and one that has the potential of contributing to a massive paradigm-shift in the industry, making WebAssembly truly ubiquitous.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.strathweb.com/2022/03/running-net-7-apps-on-wasi-on-arm64-mac/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 06:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source .NET MAUI Workshop - Multi-platform apps with C#</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/dotnet/open-source-net-maui-workshop-multi-platform-apps-with-c-nle</link>
      <description>The .NET Foundation helps organize &amp;quot;Presentations in a Box&amp;quot; including workshops, demos,...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/dotnet/open-source-net-maui-workshop-multi-platform-apps-with-c-nle</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 06:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Dagger: a new way to create CI/CD pipelines</title>
      <link>https://dagger.io/blog/public-launch-announcement</link>
      <description>Dagger.io | Blog | Title of post</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dagger.io/blog/public-launch-announcement</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 01:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> How to generate tons of Blog ideas using Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://mjidosblog.blogspot.com/2022/03/how-to-generate-tons-of-blog-ideas_57.html</link>
      <description>Blogging is a great way to stay updated on current events and teach others about what you know. It&amp;#39;s also the ideal way to build your brand....</description>
      <author> (Majid)</author>
      <guid>https://mjidosblog.blogspot.com/2022/03/how-to-generate-tons-of-blog-ideas_57.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lando, WordPress, and ngrok...oh my - Postcards From My Life</title>
      <link>https://blog.calevans.com/2022/03/29/lando-wordpress-and-ngrok-oh-my/</link>
      <description>How to use ngrok to setup a tunnel for a WordPress development environment running in Lando so you can share it with the world.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.calevans.com/2022/03/29/lando-wordpress-and-ngrok-oh-my/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I find Linux gaming important?</title>
      <link>https://akselmo.dev/2022/02/04/Why-I-find-Linux-gaming-important.html</link>
      <description>People who read this mess of a blog may have noticed that I am very Linux-y. This wasn’t actually always the case.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://akselmo.dev/2022/02/04/Why-I-find-Linux-gaming-important.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much time do we have left? - Patrick Zhong</title>
      <link>https://patzhong.com/how-much-time-do-we-have-left/</link>
      <description>I always thought I am a hardworking person, and I should&amp;#39;ve achieved a lot. However, when I reflect on what I have done in the past year, I was often surprised that I did not really accomplish anything! Steve Job famously said, &amp;quot;Your time is limited, so don&amp;#39;t waste it living someone else&amp;#39;s life.&amp;quot; It is</description>
      <author> (patrick)</author>
      <guid>https://patzhong.com/how-much-time-do-we-have-left/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Django Raise an Error for Missing Template Variables - Adam Johnson</title>
      <link>https://adamj.eu/tech/2022/03/30/how-to-make-django-error-for-undefined-template-variables/</link>
      <description>It’s all too easy to forget to pass a variable to your template, or make a typo in a variable name. Unfortunately, it can be quite hard to debug such mistakes, since Django’s default behaviour is to ignore the problem and render an empty string.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://adamj.eu/tech/2022/03/30/how-to-make-django-error-for-undefined-template-variables/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self Learning and Personal Projects</title>
      <link>https://christophers-blog.netlify.app/posts/self-learning-and-personal-projects/</link>
      <description>Self Learning and Personal Projects</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://christophers-blog.netlify.app/posts/self-learning-and-personal-projects/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>