<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Time spent programming is often time well spent - Stan Bright</title>
      <link>https://stanbright.com/time-spent-programming/</link>
      <description>Was the time I spent writing my RSS scripts more than the time I would now spend thinking about the “best” RSS aggregator and reader? Doesn’t matter. I enjoyed writing the scripts. I learned new things and got satisfaction out of seeing them run correctly. I get nothing like that out of comparing apps and services.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stanbright.com/time-spent-programming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;Everyone Gains&amp;quot;: The Pretty Lie of Economics</title>
      <link>https://www.betonit.ai/p/everyone-gains-the-pretty-lie-of</link>
      <description>Home-grown SDB in our sanctuary of candor</description>
      <author> (Bryan Caplan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.betonit.ai/p/everyone-gains-the-pretty-lie-of</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixing slow PostgreSQL queries: How to make a smart optimizer more stupid | OtterTune</title>
      <link>https://bohanzhang.me/assets/blogs/order_by_limit/order_by_limit.html</link>
      <description>You&amp;#39;ve got a slow-running PostgreSQL query, so you run ANALYZE, but what if ANALYZE can&amp;#39;t fix it? </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bohanzhang.me/assets/blogs/order_by_limit/order_by_limit.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an image search engine on Postgres | Tembo</title>
      <link>https://tembo.io/blog/image-search</link>
      <description>Search images with text and existing images using Postgres.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tembo.io/blog/image-search</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solid Cache for Rails and PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://andyatkinson.com/solid-cache-rails-postgresql</link>
      <description>Solid Cache is a relatively new cache framework that’s available as a Ruby gem for Ruby on Rails. In the next major version of Rails, version 8, it’s becoming the default cache backend.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andyatkinson.com/solid-cache-rails-postgresql</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doing Something Once Vs. Doing It Every Day</title>
      <link>https://durmonski.com/life-advice/show-up-every-day/</link>
      <description>When you show up every day. When you don&amp;#39;t stop when others stop, you become unstoppable. Keep this in mind the next time you want to quit.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/durmonski/)</author>
      <guid>https://durmonski.com/life-advice/show-up-every-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Summer I MacGyvered a Smart Bug Repeller and Saved $700</title>
      <link>http://lukedoesthings.com/posts/smart-bug-repeller/</link>
      <description>
&amp;#127909; Video Version Available!
You can watch the video version of this project on YouTube as given at the Tech Lancaster Meetup in July


    
    
    Sometimes, all you need is duct tape.
    
  
As a software guy, hardware hacking has long appealed to me. Until recently I just
never took the plunge past goofing off with an Arduino starter kit.
I like to think it was just a lack of a good use case, maybe it was fear. Regardless, no hardware hacking for me.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://lukedoesthings.com/posts/smart-bug-repeller/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalability works in two directions</title>
      <link>https://eloydegen.com/blog/posts/scalability/</link>
      <description>When talking about scalability in the context of software, it is always about being able to handle more: users, data, network traffic, etcetera.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://eloydegen.com/blog/posts/scalability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>~fpereiro</title>
      <link>https://federicopereiro.com/edge/</link>
      <description>The edge, in cloud computing, is deploying servers in multiple physical locations to serve users that are also distributed geographically. A service that uses edges will serve (say) users in the US with servers in North America, and Indonesian users with servers located in Southeast Asia. The reason for this is simple: the smaller the distance between a server and a user, the smaller the network delays (and the better the user experience).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://federicopereiro.com/edge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress, Hosts, and Hosting</title>
      <link>https://eric.mann.blog/wordpress-hosts-and-hosting/</link>
      <description>After nearly a decade out of WordPress, I visited WordCamp US and met with several hosts. TLDR: the state of WordPress hosting is stale.</description>
      <author> (ericmann)</author>
      <guid>https://eric.mann.blog/wordpress-hosts-and-hosting/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fun driven development</title>
      <link>https://zoriya.dev/posts/fun-driven-dev/</link>
      <description>I use a lot of nerdy tools (linux, nix, river), some tools also have a steep learning curve (vim, dvorak). I also type on a 32 split keyboard I made myself. A lot of developers would say I am wasting time, using tools that have no use or slow me down, and I should stop to ship some products.
I also write code in a lot of different language (21 according to my github stats) and I still do not have a favorite language. Nor do I have a go-to language when I want to make a project quickly. Even on my most important project, Kyoo, multiple languages coexist while most would say a big monolith could be enough.</description>
      <author> (Zoe Roux)</author>
      <guid>https://zoriya.dev/posts/fun-driven-dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Guide to Webscaling</title>
      <link>https://amree.dev/2023/11/26/tiny-guide-to-webscaling/</link>
      <description>Someone on Twitter asked what if Khairul Aming wanted to set up his own website for his sambal? For those who may not know, his product has gained fame and typically sells out quickly once he opens orders. At present, he utilizes Shopee.
From a business standpoint, it’s advisable for him to stay with Shopee. My post is primarily for educational purposes.
Disclaimer: I am not an SRE/DevOps professional, but rather someone eager to share insights that might broaden understanding of web scalability, drawn from my limited experiences. Therefore, there may be inaccuracies, though I hope none too significant.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://amree.dev/2023/11/26/tiny-guide-to-webscaling/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Fryxell</title>
      <link>https://scott-fryxell.github.io/blog/the-white-collar-apocalypse-is-nigh/</link>
      <description>I don&amp;#39;t have a degree, but I have worked in tech two plus decades and I can tell you it&amp;#39;s interesting as all get out to watch the status economy begining it&amp;#39;s downward spiral. Imagine spending the first twenty five years of your life striving to become the kind of person society prioritizes only to graduate into a world where you are the first victim of &amp;quot;The intelligence Age&amp;quot;.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scott-fryxell.github.io/blog/the-white-collar-apocalypse-is-nigh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where are the Microvans?</title>
      <link>https://andrewchilds.com/posts/where-are-the-microvans</link>
      <description>Microvans are the future - we just don&amp;#39;t know it yet.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewchilds.com/posts/where-are-the-microvans</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the limits of Postgres: when does it break? – StepChange</title>
      <link>https://stepchange.work/blog/exploring-the-limits-of-postgres-when-does-it-break</link>
      <description>In this post, we explore the limits of single-node Postgres and what optimizations can extend its usefulness as a primary application database before requiring more advanced scaling solutions.


Monolithic ecommerce app on RDS PostgreSQL

Let&amp;#39;s use a real-world scenario, a monolith web application that uses PostgreSQL as the application database running on AWS RDS. The RDS instance is a 2xlarge.

The resources are:

 * 8 vCPUs
 * 64 GB Memory
 * 20,000 Max I/O operations per second (IOPS)

In ou</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stepchange.work/blog/exploring-the-limits-of-postgres-when-does-it-break</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being Raised by the Internet</title>
      <link>https://jimmyhmiller.github.io/raised</link>
      <description>I grew up relatively poor. I was fortunate enough to have a roof over my head, clean water, electricity, a computer, internet, and cable tv. But food was often harder to come by. This may seem like a contradiction, but when your mom has left to marry her uncle and your dad has schizophrenia, you aren’t really in charge of how the money is spent.</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Miller)</author>
      <guid>https://jimmyhmiller.github.io/raised</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Height WebView from Static HTML in React Native Expo</title>
      <link>https://iwritecodesometimes.net/2024/09/24/dynamic-height-webview-from-static-html-in-react-native-expo/</link>
      <description>Let’s say your app is consuming rich text content from an API. That content is returned via a get request and returns a response that is a plain-text string of HTML content. How would you dis…</description>
      <author> (Published by Joe Meyer)</author>
      <guid>https://iwritecodesometimes.net/2024/09/24/dynamic-height-webview-from-static-html-in-react-native-expo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 21:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redesign Case Study</title>
      <link>https://ishadeed.com/article/redesign-2024/</link>
      <description>A look at how I redesigned my website.</description>
      <author> (Ahmad Shadeed)</author>
      <guid>https://ishadeed.com/article/redesign-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running Docker in an Azure Windows Virtual Machine – Not so fast!</title>
      <link>https://nestenius.se/2024/09/24/running-docker-in-an-azure-windows-virtual-machine-not-so-fast/</link>
      <description>This blog post describes getting Docker up and running inside an Azure Windows Virtual Machine. This might sound like a simple task, but trust me, there are some surprises on the way that took me a day or so to figure out. Background As a trainer for developers, I sometimes provide a training environment in […]</description>
      <author> (webmaster)</author>
      <guid>https://nestenius.se/2024/09/24/running-docker-in-an-azure-windows-virtual-machine-not-so-fast/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 20:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - WinampDesktop/winamp: Iconic media player</title>
      <link>https://github.com/WinampDesktop/winamp</link>
      <description>Iconic media player. Contribute to WinampDesktop/winamp development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (WinampDesktop)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/WinampDesktop/winamp</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenFreeMap</title>
      <link>https://openfreemap.org/</link>
      <description>Open and free custom maps for your website and apps, based on OpenStreetMap.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://openfreemap.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 16:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Receiving GitHub Webhooks When Using the ASP.NET Core Developer Certificate - Steve Gordon - Code with Steve</title>
      <link>https://www.stevejgordon.co.uk/receiving-github-webhooks-when-using-the-aspnetcore-developer-certificate</link>
      <description>In this post, I share how to enable testing GitHub webhooks locally using HTTPS with the self-signed ASP.NET Core developer certificate.</description>
      <author> (Steve Gordon)</author>
      <guid>https://www.stevejgordon.co.uk/receiving-github-webhooks-when-using-the-aspnetcore-developer-certificate</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 12:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between “Promise” and “Observable” in Angular</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/abp-community/difference-between-promise-and-observable-in-angular-aab25c7db105</link>
      <description>In this article, I will mention the differences between Promise and Observable. They have different uses cases and behaviors. Read more…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@alperonline)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/abp-community/difference-between-promise-and-observable-in-angular-aab25c7db105</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core 9 and IAsyncEnumerable - Async Streaming JSON and NDJSON From Blazor WebAssembly</title>
      <link>https://www.tpeczek.com/2024/09/aspnet-core-9-and-iasyncenumerable.html</link>
      <description>This post explores  streaming data asynchronously from Blazor based on async streamed JSON and NDJSON.</description>
      <author> (Tomasz Pęczek)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tpeczek.com/2024/09/aspnet-core-9-and-iasyncenumerable.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Loop Performance in .NET: The Simple Trick of Caching Array Length</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/09/24/collection-performance-looping-over-a-collection-2/</link>
      <description>The post discusses optimizing array iteration in programming by caching the array’s length for performance improvements. This method yields a 1.021x performance boost, particularly beneficial…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/09/24/collection-performance-looping-over-a-collection-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 09:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tune Llama3 405B on AMD MI300x (our journey) - Felafax Blog - Obsidian Publish</title>
      <link>https://publish.obsidian.md/felafax/pages/Tune+Llama3+405B+on+AMD+MI300x+(our+journey)</link>
      <description>Tune Llama3 405B on AMD MI300x (our journey) - Felafax Blog - Powered by Obsidian Publish.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://publish.obsidian.md/felafax/pages/Tune+Llama3+405B+on+AMD+MI300x+(our+journey)</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 06:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics Lab Thermostat</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2989/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2989/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 04:00:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>