<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Framework vs .NET Core (.NET 5+) | Pro Code Guide</title>
      <link>https://procodeguide.com/dotnet/dotnet-framework-vs-dotnet-core/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will learn about the differences between .NET Framework &amp;amp; .NET Core (.NET 5+) i.e. NET Framework vs .NET Core.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://procodeguide.com/dotnet/dotnet-framework-vs-dotnet-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 05:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Last Week in .NET #79] – Space Newts</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2022/01/31/last-week-in-net-79-space-newts/</link>
      <description>Space Newts, a forgotten SDK, and Skynet. Let’s get into it. The .NET SDK is back! on the Github Actions Ubuntu runner. It was removed, and this was widely considered to be a bad idea. &amp;#127939;‍♀️ D…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2022/01/31/last-week-in-net-79-space-newts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 05:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Light Green Light</title>
      <link>https://jamessevedge.com/articles/red-light-green-light/</link>
      <description>I was listening to the Tim Ferriss Show podcast episode #532 with Sheila Heen (Harvard Negotiation Project, co-author of Difficult Conversations: How To Discuss What Matters Most) and a specific story she told during the conversation really resonated with me and I have been thinking alot about it since I heard it. Below is the excerpt of that story in her own words.
 It reminds me, I sometimes tell this story about my eldest son.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jamessevedge.com/articles/red-light-green-light/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Framework Design Guidelines: Conventions, Idioms, and Patterns for Reusable .NET Libraries (paperback) (Addison-Wesley Microsoft Technology Series): Cwalina, Krzysztof, Barton, Jeremy, Abrams, Brad: 9780135896464: Amazon.com: Books</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/dp/0135896460?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202202</link>
      <description>Framework Design Guidelines: Conventions, Idioms, and Patterns for Reusable .NET Libraries (paperback) (Addison-Wesley Microsoft Technology Series) [Cwalina, Krzysztof, Barton, Jeremy, Abrams, Brad] on Amazon.com. *FREE* shipping on qualifying offers. Framework Design Guidelines: Conventions, Idioms, and Patterns for Reusable .NET Libraries (paperback) (Addison-Wesley Microsoft Technology Series)</description>
      <author> (Share                            &amp;lt;Embed&amp;gt;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/dp/0135896460?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202202</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 02:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create microservices with .NET and ASP.NET Core Ep1: Introduction to microservices with .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6dyr13agA-Y</link>
      <description>Microservice applications are composed of small, independently versioned, and scalable customer-focused services that communicate with each other over standa...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6dyr13agA-Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 02:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Philosophy Workstation with NixOS: Installing Firefox, VSCodium, and LaTeX</title>
      <link>https://shen.hong.io/nixos-for-philosophy-installing-firefox-latex-vscodium/</link>
      <description>A NixOS tutorial on creating a Philosophy Workstation with Firefox, VSCodium, and LaTeX.</description>
      <author> (Shen Zhou Hong)</author>
      <guid>https://shen.hong.io/nixos-for-philosophy-installing-firefox-latex-vscodium/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord Holds the Keys to Your Heart</title>
      <link>https://artemis.sh/2022/01/30/discord-holds-the-keys-to-your-heart.html</link>
      <description>A friend of ours has been struggling with RSI. As part of their plans to address this, they decided to create a secondary Discord account to use on their phone, for direct messaging purposes. That way, they could still talk to people from their phone, but wouldn’t be tempted to participate in active discussions in group channels. As part of the signup process, Discord forced them to provide a phone number for account verification. They provided the same phone number they used for their primary Discord account, and in response, Discord locked both accounts, cutting them off from a huge part of their social circle. Discord’s support was unable to unlock the account or provide any information on when it might be unlocked.</description>
      <author> (Artemis Everfree)</author>
      <guid>https://artemis.sh/2022/01/30/discord-holds-the-keys-to-your-heart.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destroy All Values: Designing Deinitialization in Programming Languages</title>
      <link>https://gankra.github.io/blah/deinitialize-me-maybe/</link>
      <description>January 23rd, 2022</description>
      <author> (Aria Beingessner)</author>
      <guid>https://gankra.github.io/blah/deinitialize-me-maybe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruce Lawson&amp;#39;s personal site</title>
      <link>https://brucelawson.co.uk/2022/one-week-left-to-save-the-web/</link>
      <description> &amp;#187; One week left to save the Web!</description>
      <author> (Bruce Lawson)</author>
      <guid>https://brucelawson.co.uk/2022/one-week-left-to-save-the-web/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 lessons from a 5 year Meta-rollercoaster ride</title>
      <link>https://zakelfassi.com/2022/02/01/10-lessons-from-a-5-year-meta-facebook-rollercoaster-ride/</link>
      <description>I joined Facebook (before it went Meta) in 2016. At that time, the company size was just shy of 15,000 employees, which, even at that scale, is much much more manageable than what it is today (the only publicly available number so far is 58K by the end of 2020 – watch out for the company’s earnings Feb 2 as that number can only go up). That is close to a +400% growth, just in employee size.</description>
      <author> (https://zakelfassi.com/author/admin/)</author>
      <guid>https://zakelfassi.com/2022/02/01/10-lessons-from-a-5-year-meta-facebook-rollercoaster-ride/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t trust comments</title>
      <link>https://nns.ee/blog/2022/01/31/dont-trust-comments.html</link>
      <description>And habitually review the third party code you&amp;#39;re using - even when it&amp;#39;s in thestandard library.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nns.ee/blog/2022/01/31/dont-trust-comments.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro to self-hosting. How to get started hosting your applications</title>
      <link>https://georgev.design/blog/intro-to-self-hosting-how-to-get-started-hosting-your-applications</link>
      <description>You want to get into self-hosting but don&amp;#39;t know what that involves? This is the perfect place to start.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgev.design/blog/intro-to-self-hosting-how-to-get-started-hosting-your-applications</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is “Anti-Work?”</title>
      <link>https://blog.alexisdumas.org/2022/01/29/anti-work.html</link>
      <description>1</description>
      <author> (Alexis Purslane)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.alexisdumas.org/2022/01/29/anti-work.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreigners should be allowed to compete on price</title>
      <link>https://tedis.me/posts/negotiation-by-location/</link>
      <description>Thoughts and projects.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tedis.me/posts/negotiation-by-location/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My most meaningful work of 2021 – not falling down</title>
      <link>https://www.xorph.com/nfd/2022/01/04/my-most-meaningful-work-of-2021/</link>
      <description>Last year, in cooperation with many of my friends on a private social network, I took an idea from neighborhood organizations here in Chicago and started a small online-only mutual aid fund. Over twelve months, we distributed more than seven thousand dollars from some friends to others, mostly in increments of $100 USD. I want to be clear that everyone involved in that system was of equal importance to its operation: people have to identify and articulate their need for help in order for donations to have a place to go, and both asking and donating take courage and labor. A number of the people involved made requests at one point and donations at another, which I think illustrates how important the fluidity of a mutual aid project can be. Here are the steps we took to get it running.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.xorph.com/nfd/2022/01/04/my-most-meaningful-work-of-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on six months of fatherhood</title>
      <link>https://jasoncrawford.org/reflections-on-six-months-of-fatherhood</link>
      <description>To be fed from a spoon requires three distinct skills. First, you must open your mouth when the spoon approaches. Second, you must close your mouth around the spoon once it has fully entered the mouth (and not before). Third, you must swallow the food that remains in your mouth after the spoon is withdrawn, rather than spitting it out.

</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jasoncrawford.org/reflections-on-six-months-of-fatherhood</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start paying for internet stuff - Can&amp;#39;s blog</title>
      <link>https://canolcer.com/post/pay-for-internet-stuff/</link>
      <description>A lot of services and products you use on the internet are free. Of course, the companies behind the services need to make money one way or another. Often …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://canolcer.com/post/pay-for-internet-stuff/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaving better paths</title>
      <link>https://www.logikblok.com/leaving-the-path-better/</link>
      <description>Good documentation is useful, great documentation is empowering. We should practice towards great documentation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.logikblok.com/leaving-the-path-better/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Better Turing Machine Tape Model</title>
      <link>https://nickdrozd.github.io/2021/12/31/turing-machine-tape.html</link>
      <description>A Turing machine is a simple type of computer. Its memory consists of a single strip of tape that is divided into discrete cells, each one of which is marked with one of a fixed number of colors. Data is read from and written to the tape by means of a tape head. Turing machine memory is not random-access; the machine head can reach any cell on the tape, but it must move cell by cell to get there. At any given time the tape head is scanning just one cell.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nickdrozd.github.io/2021/12/31/turing-machine-tape.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1751984 - Let&amp;#39;s Encrypt TLS Using ALPN TLS Version and OID</title>
      <link>https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=1751984</link>
      <description>ASSIGNED (aaron) in NSS - CA Certificate Compliance. Last updated 2022-01-31.</description>
      <author> (Aaron Gable)</author>
      <guid>https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=1751984</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Download affected certificate serials for 2022.01.25 TLS-ALPN-01 Incident</title>
      <link>https://letsencrypt.org/tlsalpnrevocation/</link>
      <description>This page hosts the list of certificates affected by the TLS-ALPN-01 Incident. You can find details about this incident in the community forum and on bugzilla.
We have sent notification emails to affected subscribers who have registered a valid email address; if you received an email, you have at least one affected certificate. You may not have received an email if you did not provide an email address when registering your ACME account, if you unsubscribed from Let&amp;amp;rsquo;s Encrypt email notifications previously, or if the email was caught by a spam filter.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://letsencrypt.org/tlsalpnrevocation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello OmniSharp on .NET 6.0!</title>
      <link>https://www.strathweb.com/2022/01/hello-omnisharp-on-net-6-0/</link>
      <description>On December 15, 2021 we released version 1.38.0 of OmniSharp which, for the first time, included .NET 6.0 builds of the OmniSharp server. The related feature branch was maintained for over a year, and previously contained a .NET 5-based variant of OmniSharp, though that one was never released.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.strathweb.com/2022/01/hello-omnisharp-on-net-6-0/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 21:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET R&amp;amp;D Digest (January, 2022)</title>
      <link>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2022/01/31/net-rd-digest-january-2022/</link>
      <description>This issues includes bits of computer science, software development, distributed systems, .NET, Windows, diagnostics, COM and low level performance.</description>
      <author> (Oleg Karasik)</author>
      <guid>https://olegkarasik.wordpress.com/2022/01/31/net-rd-digest-january-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 21:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the new hire who showed up is not the same person we interviewed</title>
      <link>https://www.askamanager.org/2022/01/the-new-hire-who-showed-up-is-not-the-same-person-we-interviewed.html</link>
      <description>A reader writes: This is a situation currently unfolding at my husband&amp;#39;s office so I’m a very amused bystander and thought I’d get your opinion on this</description>
      <author> (www.facebook.com/askamanager)</author>
      <guid>https://www.askamanager.org/2022/01/the-new-hire-who-showed-up-is-not-the-same-person-we-interviewed.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 20:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please make a dumb car – TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2022/01/29/please-make-a-dumb-car/</link>
      <description>Today’s cars are dumb where they should be smart, and smart where they should be dumb. Enough already. Make a car that’s pretty much all dumb and watch it sell — because what automakers are giving people is so bad, they’ll pay more to have less of it. Cars now are like budget smar…</description>
      <author> (Devin Coldewey@techcrunch / 8:02 AM PST•January 29, 2022comment Comment)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2022/01/29/please-make-a-dumb-car/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 19:03:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Array or object JSON deserialization (feat. .NET &amp;amp; System.Text.Json)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gi7GT3yrrc0</link>
      <description>Ah, the joys of integrating with third-party APIs... We always end up having to hammer something to get things working &amp;#129315;.This is a post about one of such si...</description>
      <author> (TechWorld with Nana
  
  
  
    TechWorld with Nana
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gi7GT3yrrc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 19:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Bryan Costanich on .NET 6 IoT - Episode 177</title>
      <link>http://feed.azuredevops.show/net-6-iot-with-bryan-costanich-episode-177</link>
      <description>This week, Jeffrey welcomes Bryan Costanich, Founder of Wilderness Labs and former VP of Xamarin. Bryan talks with us about the state of .NET, the advantages and disadvantages of moving into the embedded space, and how embedded computing is the new revolution. Bryan is also on a mission to leave the world a little better than he found it. &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [2:04] Bryan talks about his background and time at Xamarin, Microsoft, and the origins of Wilderness Labs. [4:16] What is the state of .NET? In the embedded system world, what are the realistic options and future in 2022 and beyond? [8:04] What are both the advantages and disadvantages of moving into the embedded space? [11:04] Bryan discusses how a lot of the advantages of microcontrollers moving to embedded are historical in the sense that you are developing for embedded devices that haven’t changed a lot since the ’70s and ’80s. [12:30] Seventy percent of all security bugs aren’t even an issue in .NET. [15:05] Bryan talks about his intent to make it easier for people to use and to create the ideal experience through Xamarin. [15:41] The next phase of humankind’s technological computing journey is embedded computing. This is the new revolution. [16:45] There are three parts of the IoT market: consumer, commercial, and industrial. [20:23] Bryan talks about how Xamarin’s main products are compromised and where they land on the spectrum. He discusses Azure Sphere and Raspberry Pi. [26:29] What exactly does Bryan develop with? He describes his setup. [31:09] Some fun smart chicken coop talk! [34:42] How does crash reporting work in Xamarin? [36:55] In the core compute module, how does one build the enclosure that it snaps into? [39:11] What is the most common product mix? [39:30] When will Xamarin’s products be released? &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:  — New video podcast!   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!     &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://feed.azuredevops.show/net-6-iot-with-bryan-costanich-episode-177</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 19:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Array or object JSON deserialization (feat. .NET &amp;amp; System.Text.Json)</title>
      <link>https://blog.codingmilitia.com/2022/01/31/array-or-object-deserialization/</link>
      <description>Ah, the joys of integrating with third-party APIs… We always end up having to hammer something to get things working &amp;#129315;. This is a post about one of such situations, resorting to some JSON deserialization trickery (via JsonConverter) to be able to get things working.</description>
      <author> (Jo&amp;#227;o Antunes)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.codingmilitia.com/2022/01/31/array-or-object-deserialization/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 19:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adblocking People and Non-adblocking People Experience a Totally Different Web</title>
      <link>https://imlefthanded.com/2022/adblocking-people-and-non-adblocking-people-experience-a-totally-different-web/</link>
      <description>I’ve just spent the past hour writing a blog post about why on earth certain websites have autoplaying videos that must cost them a fortune in bandwidth. And then it dawned on me. Video ads! …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://imlefthanded.com/2022/adblocking-people-and-non-adblocking-people-experience-a-totally-different-web/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 19:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Discovered Thousands of Open Databases on AWS</title>
      <link>https://infosecwriteups.com/how-i-discovered-thousands-of-open-databases-on-aws-764729aa7f32?gi=ba781482d685</link>
      <description>My journey on finding and reporting databases with sensitive data about Fortune-500 companies, Hospitals, Crypto platforms, Startups during…</description>
      <author> (https://avi-lumelsky.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://infosecwriteups.com/how-i-discovered-thousands-of-open-databases-on-aws-764729aa7f32?gi=ba781482d685</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 17:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - marcominerva/MinimalHelpers.Registration: A lightweight library to automatically register all the Route Endpoints of a Minimal API project.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/marcominerva/MinimalHelpers.Registration</link>
      <description>A lightweight library to automatically register all the Route Endpoints of a Minimal API project. - GitHub - marcominerva/MinimalHelpers.Registration: A lightweight library to automatically registe...</description>
      <author> (marcominerva)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/marcominerva/MinimalHelpers.Registration</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 17:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why does the Windows debugger engine show a bunch of hex digits after one of the DLL names?</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220131-00/?p=106205</link>
      <description>You’re using the Windows debugger engine, say ntsd or windbg, and some DLLs come with hex digits after their names. What’s up with that? contoso_7ffe7d0e0000!GetWidgetName: 00007ffe`7d0e2f50 488bc4     mov   rax,rsp 00007ffe`7d0e2f53 48895808    mov   qword ptr [rax+8],rbx 00007ffe`7d0e2f57 48896810    mov   qword ptr [rax+10h],rbp 00007ffe`7d0e2f5b 48897018    mov   qword ptr [rax+18h],rsi 00007ffe`7d0e2f5f 48897820    mov   qword ptr [rax+20h],rdi 00007ffe`7d0e2f63 4156      push  r14 00007ffe`7d0e2f65 4883ec20    sub   rsp,20h 00007ffe`7d0e2f69 33db      xor   ebx,ebx  If you look more closely,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20220131-00/?p=106205</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory leaks: the forgotten side of web performance</title>
      <link>https://nolanlawson.com/2022/01/05/memory-leaks-the-forgotten-side-of-web-performance/</link>
      <description>I’ve researched and learned enough about client-side memory leaks to know that most web developers aren’t worrying about them too much. If a web app leaks 5 MB on every interaction, but…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nolanlawson.com/2022/01/05/memory-leaks-the-forgotten-side-of-web-performance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If? 2</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2575/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2575/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Server Accelerator (NSA HTTP)</title>
      <link>https://myenterpriselicense.hpe.com/cwp-ui/free-software/NSAHTTP</link>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The HP-UX Network Server Accelerator for HTTP (NSA HTTP) is a networking feature that improves Web server performance by maintaining an in-kernel cache of recently accessed Web pages.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://myenterpriselicense.hpe.com/cwp-ui/free-software/NSAHTTP</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 15:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallelize test cases execution in xUnit - G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/parallelize-test-cases-execution-in-xunit.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to execute test cases in parallel in xUnit tests.</description>
      <author> (G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/parallelize-test-cases-execution-in-xunit.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 15:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Partner Program Now Supports SASE &amp;amp; Zero Trust Managed Services</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/zero-trust-managed-services/</link>
      <description>We’ve been building out the Cloudflare Partner Network for years, working alongside businesses of all sizes and types including our world-wide system integrator partners</description>
      <author> (Matthew Harrell)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/zero-trust-managed-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 14:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How CallerArgumentExpression changes the logging game in C# 10</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MHIheQ2_Yb4</link>
      <description>Check out my courses: https://nickchapsas.comBecome a Patreon and get source code access: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsasHello everybody I&amp;#39;m Nick and in ...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MHIheQ2_Yb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 13:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development With A Dot - Using Generated Methods Instead of Reflection</title>
      <link>https://weblogs.asp.net/ricardoperes/using-generated-methods-instead-of-reflection</link>
      <description>IntroductionIt is a common thing to say that reflection is slow.You will find tons of posts saying this, and I generally tend to agree to them, although in most cases we generally don’t need to care&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#8230;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://weblogs.asp.net/ricardoperes/using-generated-methods-instead-of-reflection</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 13:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I reversed a NodeJS malware and found the author</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@devops-guy/how-i-reversed-a-nodejs-malware-and-found-the-author-7dd9531b389f</link>
      <description>To give a bit of context, I am a Discord admin on a small server about development, and we recently got a report from one of our users that…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@devops-guy)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@devops-guy/how-i-reversed-a-nodejs-malware-and-found-the-author-7dd9531b389f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 12:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with AWS Distro for OpenTelemetry and distributed tracing using .NET. Part 1: Setting up the AWS OTEL Collector</title>
      <link>https://www.mytechramblings.com/posts/getting-started-with-aws-distro-for-otel-and-dotnet-part-1/</link>
      <description>This is a 2 part-series post. In part 1 I’ll be talking about what is the AWS OpenTelemetry Collector and how to set it up for ingesting and exporting traces to AWS X-Ray.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mytechramblings.com/posts/getting-started-with-aws-distro-for-otel-and-dotnet-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 11:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 21: Milly Schmidt — PATHS UNCOVERED</title>
      <link>https://www.pathsuncovered.com/episodes/21-milly-schmidt</link>
      <description>WRITER - FLUTE TEACHER - TUTOR - EDITOR - DEVELOPER - WEB DEV - FRONT END ENGINEER - UX LEAD - TECH INSTRUCTOR - DIRECTOR OF PRODUCT &amp;amp;amp; DESIGN</description>
      <author> (31 Jan
            
            Written By Paths Uncovered)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pathsuncovered.com/episodes/21-milly-schmidt</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 10:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Copy Array Elements to New Array in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-copy-array-elements-to-new-array/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to talk about different ways to copy array and explore the efficiency of each approach with benchmarks.</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-copy-array-elements-to-new-array/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 09:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>291: GitHub Actions All The Things</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/291</link>
      <description>Frank is finally all in on continuous integration and continuous delivery with .NET 6 and he did it all with GitHub actions! </description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/291</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 09:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implement a PWA using Blazor with BFF security and Azure B2C</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2022/01/31/implement-a-pwa-using-blazor-with-bff-security-and-azure-b2c/</link>
      <description>The article shows how to implement a progressive web application (PWA) using Blazor which is secured using the backend for frontend architecture and Azure B2C as the identity provider. Code Setup a…</description>
      <author> (damienbod)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2022/01/31/implement-a-pwa-using-blazor-with-bff-security-and-azure-b2c/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 09:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Tables with EF Core 6</title>
      <link>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2022/01/31/efcoretemporaltables/</link>
      <description>Temporal tables keep changes of updates and deletes with specific tables. This is a feature of SQL Server since SQL Server 2016. Without using this feature from SQL Server, with EF Core often the b…</description>
      <author> (Published by
	Christian Nagel)</author>
      <guid>https://csharp.christiannagel.com/2022/01/31/efcoretemporaltables/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 09:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t forget Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://luttig.substack.com/p/dont-forget-microsoft</link>
      <description>Understanding the behemoth in Redmond teaches us valuable lessons in cloud infrastructure, startup strategy, and the future of software.</description>
      <author> (John Luttig)</author>
      <guid>https://luttig.substack.com/p/dont-forget-microsoft</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 08:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code-Splitting: Get Better Performance When Developing React</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/code-splitting-get-better-performance-developing-react</link>
      <description>This post covers React Suspense and React Lazy, which split code, fetch data and set the order components are rendered—giving you control of your project.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/code-splitting-get-better-performance-developing-react</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 06:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tzdata, the time zone database for RHEL: 2021 update | Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/01/28/tzdata-time-zone-database-rhel-2021-update</link>
      <description>2021 was an eventful year for the Time Zone Database (tzdata) project, with time zone mergers, DST updates, and controversial upstream changes.</description>
      <author> (Patsy Griffin)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/01/28/tzdata-time-zone-database-rhel-2021-update</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 06:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Uno Platform Applications to Azure</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/deploying-uno-platform-applications-to-azure/</link>
      <description>How to create an Azure Static Web App and configure it to pull from your GitHub repository.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/deploying-uno-platform-applications-to-azure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 06:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep your workflow actions up to date using GitHub Dependabot | Visual Studio Geeks</title>
      <link>https://www.visualstudiogeeks.com/github/ensure-your-actions-are-up-to-date</link>
      <description>Keep your workflow actions up to date using GitHub Dependabot</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.visualstudiogeeks.com/github/ensure-your-actions-are-up-to-date</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 06:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F# and WebAssembly</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/tunaxor/f-and-webassembly-n0a</link>
      <description>F# and WebAssembly   When I talk about F# and Web development I tend to speak about Fable...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/tunaxor/f-and-webassembly-n0a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 06:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Apps and the .NET Developer</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/dotnet/power-apps-and-the-net-developer-5e4f</link>
      <description>When you mix Power Apps with .NET - your productivity can go through the roof. So let&amp;#39;s talk about why the .NET developer should know Power Apps.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/dotnet/power-apps-and-the-net-developer-5e4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 06:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>