<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Forums are Moving to Microsoft Q&amp;amp;A</title>
      <link>https://forums.asp.net/t/2175125.aspx?ASP%2BNET%2BForums%2Bare%2BMoving%2Bto%2BMicrosoft%2BQ%2BA=</link>
      <description>We’ve listened to your feedback on how we can enhance the forum experience and bring together all .NET products into one unified platform. We are excited to announce Microsoft Q&amp;amp;amp;A for .NET , in...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://forums.asp.net/t/2175125.aspx?ASP%2BNET%2BForums%2Bare%2BMoving%2Bto%2BMicrosoft%2BQ%2BA=</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legalizing Gay Marriage in Crusader Kings III with Ghidra</title>
      <link>https://waffleironer.medium.com/legalizing-gay-marriage-in-crusader-kings-iii-with-ghidra-2602e6aa8689</link>
      <description>Crusader Kings III is a pretty impressive game. It’s impressive not only for its official content, but also for its extensive modding…</description>
      <author> (https://waffleironer.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://waffleironer.medium.com/legalizing-gay-marriage-in-crusader-kings-iii-with-ghidra-2602e6aa8689</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.3 million Aussies caught in Facebook hack</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/online/social/73-million-australians-affected-by-facebook-personal-data-leak/news-story/a8b266f88b405767f702808851c2a94a</link>
      <description>Back in 2019, the personal information of 533 million Facebook users, including more than 7.3 million Australians – which might include you – was stolen by hackers. Now, cybersecurity experts are warning it’s easier for criminals to sort through the data and use it to steal your identity.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.news.com.au/technology/online/social/73-million-australians-affected-by-facebook-personal-data-leak/news-story/a8b266f88b405767f702808851c2a94a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Storr - Azure Functions Not Loading My Dependencies, What Have I Missed?</title>
      <link>https://adamstorr.azurewebsites.net/blog/azure-functions-not-loading-my-dependencies-what-have-i-missed</link>
      <description>Adam Storr - Powered by coffee!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://adamstorr.azurewebsites.net/blog/azure-functions-not-loading-my-dependencies-what-have-i-missed</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 03:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Coding has been Unified with Backpropagation - LessWrong</title>
      <link>https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/JZZENevaLzLLeC3zn/predictive-coding-has-been-unified-with-backpropagation</link>
      <description>Artificial Neural Networks (ANNs) are based around the backpropagation
algorithm. The backpropagation algorithm allows you to perform gradient descent
on a network of neurons. When we feed training data through an ANNs, we use the
backpropagation algorithm to tell us how the weights should change.

ANNs are good at inference problems. Biological Neural Networks (BNNs) are good
at inference too. ANNs are built out of neurons. BNNs are built out of neurons
too. It makes intuitive sense that ANNs and BNNs might be running similar
algorithms.

There is just one problem: BNNs are physically incapable of running the
backpropagation algorithm.

We do not know quite enough about biology to say it is impossible for BNNs to
run the backpropagation algorithm. However, &amp;quot;a consensus has emerged that the
brain cannot directly implement backprop, since to do so would require
biologically implausible connection rules&amp;quot;[1].

The backpropagation algorithm has three steps.

 1. Flow information forward through a network to compute a prediction.
 2. Compute an error by comparing the prediction to a target value.
 3. Flow the error backward through the network to update the weights.

The backpropagation algorithm requires information to flow forward and backward
along the network. But biological neurons are one-directional. An action
potential goes from the cell body down the axon to the axon terminals to another
cell&amp;#39;s dendrites. An axon potential never travels backward from a cell&amp;#39;s
terminals to its body.



HEBBIAN THEORY
Predictive coding is the idea that BNNs generate a mental model of their
environment and then transmit only the information that deviates from this
model. Predictive coding considers error and surprise to be the same thing.
Hebbian theory is specific mathematical formulation of predictive coding.

Predictive coding is biologically plausible. It operates locally. There are no
separate prediction and training phases which must be synchronized. Most
importantly, it lets</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/JZZENevaLzLLeC3zn/predictive-coding-has-been-unified-with-backpropagation</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - gRPC Performance Improvements</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DkElWa3--8s</link>
      <description>James Newton-King overviews some of the recent gRPC performance improvements in .NET.Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/aspnet-standup-2021-03-16Feat...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DkElWa3--8s</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 23:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Open Source C# standardization | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-open-source-c-standardization-standards/</link>
      <description>The C# standards committee moved its work into Open Source, enabling C# developers worldwide to participate in the standardization effort.</description>
      <author> (Bill Wagner  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-open-source-c-standardization-standards/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 23:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aava.sh</title>
      <link>https://aava.sh/</link>
      <description>aava.sh</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aava.sh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 23:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I made $500k as a part-time tech recruiter</title>
      <link>https://davidsamkim.com/p/how-i-made-500k-as-a-part-time-tech</link>
      <description>Intro From 2017 to 2019, I worked as a full-time engineer and as a part-time recruiter. I made $500k by placing 28 engineers at companies like Snap, Palantir and Betterment. My average fee was ~$30k with a range of $23k-$40k. My split on commission ranged from 30-100%. My recruiting take home was $500,745.</description>
      <author> (David Samuel Kim)</author>
      <guid>https://davidsamkim.com/p/how-i-made-500k-as-a-part-time-tech</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Danger of &amp;quot;Simplicity&amp;quot;</title>
      <link>https://preslav.me/2021/04/05/the-danger-of-simplicity/</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s good to think about simplicity in terms of the tradeoffs we make when we take a particular decision.</description>
      <author> (Preslav Rachev

Apr 5, 2021
• 2 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://preslav.me/2021/04/05/the-danger-of-simplicity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I solved RSI Repetitive Strain Injury</title>
      <link>https://flaviocopes.com/repetive-strain-injury/</link>
      <description>A few years back I went through a miserable period.
My arms, my hands, were a constant source of pain.
I was a computer engineer, typing in a keyboard to make a living, and I was terrified this was the end of my career.
I tried it all. New mouse, new keyboard, fixing the posture, new chair.. nothing worked.
The pain was so bad it didn’t even stop during the night.</description>
      <author> (Flavio Copes)</author>
      <guid>https://flaviocopes.com/repetive-strain-injury/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFS Boot Environments for ARM</title>
      <link>https://vermaden.wordpress.com/2021/04/05/ufs-boot-environments-for-arm/</link>
      <description>Several days ago I introduced UFS Boot Environments that work great on AMD64 (or 64-bit PC if you prefer). I was interested it it will also work on less powerful devices that ZFS is not always the …</description>
      <author> (by vermaden)</author>
      <guid>https://vermaden.wordpress.com/2021/04/05/ufs-boot-environments-for-arm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owning Your Own Data</title>
      <link>https://atthis.link/blog/2021/yourowndata.html</link>
      <description>I do cool things with Computers.</description>
      <author> (Marc)</author>
      <guid>https://atthis.link/blog/2021/yourowndata.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activity is not impact</title>
      <link>https://imwrightshardcode.com/2021/04/activity-is-not-impact/</link>
      <description>Why do writing more code and working more hours fall short of delivering more value? What should engineers be doing?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://imwrightshardcode.com/2021/04/activity-is-not-impact/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Struggle With Probability Theory</title>
      <link>http://mitchgordon.me/math/2021/04/02/probability.html</link>
      <description>There are many circumstances in which uncertainty is warranted.1 Gas temperature measurements, weather forecasts, horse races, coin flips, and clinical trials all have some uncertainty involved. Probability theory is the science that finds commonality among these seemingly disconnected phenomena. We can observe, for example, that the summation of many “repeatable” random events, properly normalized, begins to look like a gaussian distribution (aka the central limit theorem). We can notice common shapes in the histograms of these repeatable experiments, such as “fat-tailed” or “power law” distributions. And if the event is not repeatable, we can at least apply the rules of probability theory to avoid inconsistencies in our thinking (which would allow a savvy adversary to take advantage of us when gambling). Many events are unpredictable to us in practice, either because the laws governing the outcome are not known, or because the laws are known but the observations required are too arduous to make. Sometimes the required observations are too numerous to collect (as in statistical mechanics), and other times the non-linear, chaotic nature of the system necessitates observations that are too precise to be practical. Quantum experiments seem to be inherently unpredictable, although whether this is a fundamental facet of nature is a matter of debate.&amp;#160;↩</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://mitchgordon.me/math/2021/04/02/probability.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I lost 25 pounds lugging my Peloton across the country in the back of my car</title>
      <link>https://www.trevormckendrick.com/essays/how-i-lost-25-pounds-lugging-my-peloton-across-the-country-in-the-back-of-my-car</link>
      <description>I was losing weight but then Covid hit &amp;amp; my gym closed. That left me with only 1 option...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.trevormckendrick.com/essays/how-i-lost-25-pounds-lugging-my-peloton-across-the-country-in-the-back-of-my-car</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to convince your product owner to invest more time in technical tasks</title>
      <link>https://www.ninkovic.dev/blog/2021/how-to-acquire-more-time-for-technical-tasks</link>
      <description>In this post we offer a few tips on how to convince
businesspeople and product owner to invest more time in solving technical tasks</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ninkovic.dev/blog/2021/how-to-acquire-more-time-for-technical-tasks</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History is Repeating Itself and Why You Should Care - Sasank&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://chsasank.github.io/history-repeats-itself-why-care.html</link>
      <description>I get a sense of d&amp;#233;j&amp;#224; vu as I read the news these days. Recent tensions between India, China and the United States harken back to the cold war of 1950s and 60s. The parallels are uncanny: ideologic...</description>
      <author> (Sasank Chilamkurthy)</author>
      <guid>https://chsasank.github.io/history-repeats-itself-why-care.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on (roughly) 750,000 words</title>
      <link>https://ethan.katzenberg.co.uk/posts/750-words/</link>
      <description>In May 2018, I stumbled upon Buster Benson’s site, where he discusses the Morning Pages idea and journaling for 750 words. The key idea is that you journal every day, and must write (at least) 750 words, or around 3 pages. I’d been journaling on and off in a paper journal for a year at that point, generally maxing out at one or two entries a month. Trying to bring a little more rigour to my approach was appealing, so I figured I’d give it a go for a week and see what happens. Two and a half years later, I’m still going strong. 1000 days in, here are my thoughts on what it’s done for me, what I (vaguely) expected to get out of it, and what I’ve learned:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ethan.katzenberg.co.uk/posts/750-words/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning with ML.NET - Object detection with YOLO</title>
      <link>https://rubikscode.net/2021/04/05/machine-learning-with-ml-net-object-detection-with-yolo/</link>
      <description>In this article, we explore object detection, learn how different versions of YOLO function and how you can utilize all that with ML.NET.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rubikscode.net/2021/04/05/machine-learning-with-ml-net-object-detection-with-yolo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 21:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My new AC has built-in Wi-Fi and that brings dilemma into my home automation hacking</title>
      <link>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233857-my-new-ac-has-built-in-wifi-and-that-brings-dilemma-into-my-home-automation-hacking</link>
      <description>5 Apr 2021
	
	 3 mins
	
	 Home Automation, IoT</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233857-my-new-ac-has-built-in-wifi-and-that-brings-dilemma-into-my-home-automation-hacking</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 21:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 371 - Cloud Native Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-371-Cloud-Native-Machine-Learning</link>
      <description>The Azure Podcast</description>
      <author> (Kendall Roden)</author>
      <guid>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-371-Cloud-Native-Machine-Learning</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 21:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to Basics: What Is a Delegate?</title>
      <link>https://hasan-hasanov.com/2021/04/05/what_is_a_delegate/</link>
      <description>One of the hardest things to explain to a beginner developer is delegate. It usually proves to be difficult because this piece of functionality’s use case is not obvious like variables, loops, collections etc.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hasan-hasanov.com/2021/04/05/what_is_a_delegate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 21:04:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - The 12 Factor App</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xRlDuXJ3t08</link>
      <description>The 12 Factor App methodology can help you build better cloud native services. Join Shayne Boyer to learn how the pattern works, and how you can apply it to ...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xRlDuXJ3t08</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 21:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win a free copy of Eggcelerate!</title>
      <link>https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSflWZRMeLEXY1sMY-jPP7udszjvcaf4HCMnK0-76xzs2hzUDg/viewform</link>
      <description>Sign up to win a copy of Eggcelerate! on Steam! The Live Coders is sponsoring 15 free copies of the new PC game that Tim Beaudet just launched!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSflWZRMeLEXY1sMY-jPP7udszjvcaf4HCMnK0-76xzs2hzUDg/viewform</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 21:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing tools I learned from The Economist</title>
      <link>https://builtbywords.substack.com/p/writing-tools-i-learned-from-the</link>
      <description>I learned writing from The Economist. Back home, it wasn’t easy to learn English. No one in my social circle was fluent in the language and I couldn’t afford a private tutor. The best I could do was to create my own syllabus. The kiosk near my house had, to my surprise, the newspaper</description>
      <author> (Ahmed Soliman)</author>
      <guid>https://builtbywords.substack.com/p/writing-tools-i-learned-from-the</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 20:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Open Source C# standardization | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-open-source-c-standardization/</link>
      <description>The C# compilers have been open source since 2014, now in the dotnet/roslyn repository. The dotnet/csharplang split off to provide a dedicate public space for the innovation and evolution of the C# language. Now, dotnet/csharpstandard completes the group, providing a public space for the ongoing work to document the standard for the latest C# language versions.</description>
      <author> (Bill Wagner  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-open-source-c-standardization/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 20:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Social Media monitoring tool with NodeJs, Azure Cosmos DB and Azure Cognitive services</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/building-a-socialmedia-monitoring-tool-with-nodejs/</link>
      <description>This article will discuss about implementing Social Media monitoring tool with NodeJs, Azure Cosmos DB and Azure cognitive services.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/building-a-socialmedia-monitoring-tool-with-nodejs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 19:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Is Testing Its Controversial New Ad Targeting Tech in Millions of Browsers. Here’s What We Know.</title>
      <link>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/03/google-testing-its-controversial-new-ad-targeting-tech-millions-browsers-heres</link>
      <description>Today, Google launched an “origin trial” of Federated Learning of Cohorts (aka FLoC), its experimental new technology for targeting ads. A switch has silently been flipped in millions of instances of Google Chrome: those browsers will begin sorting their users into groups based on behavior, then...</description>
      <author> (Bennett Cyphers)</author>
      <guid>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/03/google-testing-its-controversial-new-ad-targeting-tech-millions-browsers-heres</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 19:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web API CRUD Conventions [5 of 18] | Beginner&amp;#39;s Series to: Web APIs</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mQL5DV4RL1g</link>
      <description>When we’re working with the resources that Web APIs provide to us, there’s usually some common actions that we want to use. In this video, we’ll look at how ...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mQL5DV4RL1g</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 18:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetris in Blazor Part 3: Tetrominos</title>
      <link>https://exceptionnotfound.net/tetris-in-blazor-part-3-tetrominos/</link>
      <description>Four parts each, in different layouts. Let&amp;#39;s build them all!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/exceptionnotfnd/)</author>
      <guid>https://exceptionnotfound.net/tetris-in-blazor-part-3-tetrominos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 17:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ekspert: S&amp;#229;dan finder du sikkert ud af, om du er en af de 600.000 danskere, der har f&amp;#229;et delt data i Facebook-l&amp;#230;k</title>
      <link>https://www.dr.dk/nyheder/indland/ekspert-saadan-finder-du-sikkert-ud-af-om-du-er-en-af-de-600000-danskere-der-har</link>
      <description>P&amp;#229; verdensplan er oplysningerne p&amp;#229; over 500 millioner Facebook-brugere blevet gjort offentlige. </description>
      <author> (Jakob Slyngborg Trolle)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dr.dk/nyheder/indland/ekspert-saadan-finder-du-sikkert-ud-af-om-du-er-en-af-de-600000-danskere-der-har</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 17:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using raw html with isolated CSS in Blazor - G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/using-raw-html-with-isolated-css-in-blazor.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to use raw html fragment with isolated CSS in an ASP.NET Core Blazor component.</description>
      <author> (G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/using-raw-html-with-isolated-css-in-blazor.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 15:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The .NET Docs Show - C# Ask Me Anything &amp;#129327;</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U6cwOzUqjxY</link>
      <description>In this very special episode of The .NET Docs Show, we&amp;#39;re joined by titans of C# Mads Torgersen, Bill Wagner, and Jon Skeet. They&amp;#39;ll answer your burning ques...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U6cwOzUqjxY</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 15:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C++ coroutines: Making the promise itself be the shared state, the outline | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210405-18/?p=105054</link>
      <description>Last time, we got the idea of putting the result holder state directly inside the coroutine state. This time, we’ll set to work on the implementation. A restriction we are placing on our simple_task is that it can be co_awaited only once.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210405-18/?p=105054</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 15:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18-956 Google LLC v. Oracle America, Inc. (04/05/2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/20pdf/18-956_d18f.pdf</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/20pdf/18-956_d18f.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 15:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Profits: Netflix Made Record Profits in 2020, Paid a Tax Rate of Less than 1 Percent</title>
      <link>https://itep.org/pandemic-profits-netflix-made-record-profits-in-2020-paid-a-tax-rate-of-less-than-1-percent/</link>
      <description>Netflix’s “current” federal income tax for 2020 was $24 million, which equals just 0.9 percent of the company’s pretax income for the year. This is another way of saying Netflix paid an effective federal income tax rate of just 0.9 percent in 2020. If the company paid the statutory rate, its tax bill would be $572 million.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://itep.org/pandemic-profits-netflix-made-record-profits-in-2020-paid-a-tax-rate-of-less-than-1-percent/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 14:06:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Five: Azure Communication Services, More!</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-mvp-award-program-blog/friday-five-azure-communication-services-more/ba-p/2235379</link>
      <description>Learn Azure Communication Services Day 14 – Showing Video and Screen Share Content Tom Morgan is a Microsoft Teams Platform developer and Microsoft MVP with more than 10 years of experience in the software development industry. For the last 8 years, Tom has worked at Modality Systems, with responsib...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/680288)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-mvp-award-program-blog/friday-five-azure-communication-services-more/ba-p/2235379</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 13:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Verifiable credentials in ASP.NET Core for decentralized identities using Trinsic</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2021/04/05/creating-verifiable-credentials-in-asp-net-core-for-decentralized-identities-using-trinsic/</link>
      <description>This article shows how verifiable credentials can be created in ASP.NET Core for decentralized identities using the Trinsic platform which is a Self-sovereign identity implementation with APIs to i…</description>
      <author> (damienbod)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2021/04/05/creating-verifiable-credentials-in-asp-net-core-for-decentralized-identities-using-trinsic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 13:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elegant Acceptance Testing in .NET with SpecFlow</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qWEDkHGNhvk</link>
      <description>Check out SpecFlow: http://go.specflow.org/NickChapsasSubscribe: http://bit.ly/ChapsasSubBecome a Patreon and get source code access: https://www.patreon.com...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
    

    
      
    Nick Chapsas
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qWEDkHGNhvk</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 13:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>soywod/himalaya</title>
      <link>https://github.com/soywod/himalaya</link>
      <description>&amp;#128235; Minimalist CLI email client, written in Rust. Contribute to soywod/himalaya development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (soywod)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/soywod/himalaya</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 09:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>248: Satisfying Business Requirements</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/248</link>
      <description>Yes, this is the most boring title ever, but this podcast episode isn&amp;#39;t!</description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/248</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 09:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Blazor Material Navigation Menu - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/creating-blazor-material-navigation-menu/</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s learn how to implement complete responsice Blazor material navigation by using different material components in Blazor WASM app.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/creating-blazor-material-navigation-menu/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 09:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi GPIO C# LED | C# Tutorials Blog</title>
      <link>https://wellsb.com/csharp/iot/raspberry-pi-gpio-csharp-led/</link>
      <description>Did you know you can use C# to control the GPIO pins on your Raspberry Pi? Learn how to write a .NET app to drive an LED with this tutorial.</description>
      <author> (Bradley Wells)</author>
      <guid>https://wellsb.com/csharp/iot/raspberry-pi-gpio-csharp-led/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 07:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET News Roundup - Week of March 29th, 2021 </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2021/04/dotnet-news-roundup-mar29-2021/</link>
      <description>The last week of March was pretty intense in the .NET community, with the release of Project Reunion 0.5, Dapr 1.1, and more. InfoQ examined these and a number of smaller stories in the .NET ecosystem from the week of March 29th, 2021.</description>
      <author> (Arthur Casals
                
            
        Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2021/04/dotnet-news-roundup-mar29-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 07:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-04-05</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/04/app-developer-links-2021-04-05/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/04/app-developer-links-2021-04-05/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 07:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why software engineers should become CEOs</title>
      <link>https://www.tlt21.com/why-software-engineers-should-become-ceos/</link>
      <description>Former software engineers make excellent CEOs, but few of them think they could do it</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tlt21.com/why-software-engineers-should-become-ceos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 07:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook data breach files, v2</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/troyhunt/9a081cea0de6cbc63d93ebc010484eda</link>
      <description>Facebook data breach files, v2. GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/troyhunt/9a081cea0de6cbc63d93ebc010484eda</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 06:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>