<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux and Valve Collaboration - Arch-dev-public</title>
      <link>https://lists.archlinux.org/archives/list/arch-dev-public@lists.archlinux.org/thread/RIZSKIBDSLY4S5J2E2STNP5DH4XZGJMR/</link>
      <description>We are excited to announce that Arch Linux is entering into a direct 
collaboration with Valve. Valve is generously providing backing for two 
critical projects that will have a huge impact on our distribution: a 
build service infrastructure and a secure signing enclave. By supporting 
work on a freelance basis for these topics, Valve enables us to work on 
them without being limited solely by the free time of our volunteers.

This opportunity allows us to address some of the biggest outstanding 
challenges we have been facing for a while. The collaboration will 
speed-up the progress that would otherwise take much longer for us to 
achieve, and will ultimately unblock us from finally pursuing some of 
our planned endeavors. We are incredibly grateful for Valve to make this 
possible and for their explicit commitment to help and support Arch Linux.

These projects will follow our usual development and consensus-building 
workflows. [RFCs] will be created for any wide-ranging changes. 
Discussions on this mailing list as well as issue, milestone and epic 
planning in our GitLab will provide transparency and insight into the 
work. We believe this collaboration will greatly benefit Arch Linux, and 
are looking forward to share further development on this mailing list as 
work progresses.

[RFCs]: https://rfc.archlinux.page/</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lists.archlinux.org/archives/list/arch-dev-public@lists.archlinux.org/thread/RIZSKIBDSLY4S5J2E2STNP5DH4XZGJMR/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 14:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - 2Retr0/GodotOceanWaves: FFT-based ocean-wave rendering, implemented in Godot</title>
      <link>https://github.com/2Retr0/GodotOceanWaves</link>
      <description>FFT-based ocean-wave rendering, implemented in Godot - 2Retr0/GodotOceanWaves</description>
      <author> (2Retr0)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/2Retr0/GodotOceanWaves</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 13:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do You REALLY Need To Write Tests? – Dev Leader Weekly 63</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/09/28/do-you-really-need-to-write-tests-dev-leader-weekly-63/</link>
      <description>Welcome to another issue of Dev Leader Weekly! In this issue, I discuss situations where we may or may not want or need to write tests!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/09/28/do-you-really-need-to-write-tests-dev-leader-weekly-63/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 13:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD Unveils Its First Small Language Model AMD-135M</title>
      <link>https://community.amd.com/t5/ai/amd-unveils-its-first-small-language-model-amd-135m/ba-p/711368</link>
      <description>In the ever-evolving landscape of artificial intelligence, large language models (LLMs) like GPT-4 and Llama&amp;#160;have garnered significant attention for their impressive capabilities in natural language processing and generation. However, small language models (SLMs) are emerging as an essential counter...</description>
      <author> (https://community.amd.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/407864)</author>
      <guid>https://community.amd.com/t5/ai/amd-unveils-its-first-small-language-model-amd-135m/ba-p/711368</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 13:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking It Down: How to Migrate Your Modular Monolith to Microservices</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/breaking-it-down-how-to-migrate-your-modular-monolith-to-microservices</link>
      <description>Transitioning from a modular monolith to microservices can significantly enhance your system&amp;#39;s scalability and your team&amp;#39;s productivity, but it&amp;#39;s a journey that requires careful planning and execution. In this practical guide, I&amp;#39;ll walk you through the key steps of this migration process, from preparing your monolith and selecting the right module to extract, to implementing effective inter-service communication and data migration strategies, all based on real-world experience with .NET applications.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/breaking-it-down-how-to-migrate-your-modular-monolith-to-microservices</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 01:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>double to string conversion in 150 lines of code</title>
      <link>https://vitaut.net/posts/2024/simple-dtoa/</link>
      <description>My previous blog post gained some
attention on Hacker News (discussion), and as someone deeply
interested in floating-point formatting, I couldn’t ignore the following
comment:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vitaut.net/posts/2024/simple-dtoa/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Mobile Networks Work</title>
      <link>https://matduggan.com/how-mobile-networks-work/</link>
      <description>A technical overview of mobile network technology today.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matduggan.com/how-mobile-networks-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Postgres Indexing Went Wrong</title>
      <link>https://blog.bemi.io/indexing/</link>
      <description>It’s important to understand basics of indexing and best practices around them for preventing system downtime.</description>
      <author> (Arjun Lall
                
                    Sep 23, 2024
                        • 5 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.bemi.io/indexing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Drama: From the Sidelines</title>
      <link>https://eric.mann.blog/wordpress-drama-from-the-sidelines/</link>
      <description>Yeah ... the inside track of WordPress is a mess right now. I&amp;#39;m sure we all have opinions, so I figured I should log mine in as well.</description>
      <author> (ericmann)</author>
      <guid>https://eric.mann.blog/wordpress-drama-from-the-sidelines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Types of investor misbehavior | ssaraf</title>
      <link>https://ssaraf.com/misbehavior/</link>
      <description>I recently completed a pre-seed fundraise for Partly [1], and I thought I’d share some of the negative experiences I had with investors. Most people who fail to raise money can’t share all the horror stories - they don’t want to burn bridges. And people who raise money easily (i.e. if they already have traction, or are in a hot area) often don’t see as much misbehavior. It’s folks in the middle that often have the best view of things.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ssaraf.com/misbehavior/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Cole - Localless Development</title>
      <link>http://jeff-cole.com/localless-development/</link>
      <description>I write about building things.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://jeff-cole.com/localless-development/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How iOS Restricts Features by Region: A Look at MobileGestalt and Eligibility</title>
      <link>https://type.cyhsu.xyz/2024/09/ios-feature-regional-lockout/</link>
      <description>Apple is a for-profit that is capable of and responsible for its own decisions of whether and how to comply. On the other hand, users can vote with their wallets. What’s more intriguing to me, though, is how Apple manages this growing set of regional feature restrictions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://type.cyhsu.xyz/2024/09/ios-feature-regional-lockout/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best $4 ever spent</title>
      <link>https://papanotes.com/the-best-4-ever-spent</link>
      <description>Kids get excited about things that are very different from those of adults.You probably remember your kid&amp;#39;s first birthday. The members of ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://papanotes.com/the-best-4-ever-spent</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 22:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.Net in the cloud with OCI</title>
      <link>https://basementprogrammer.com/net-in-the-cloud-with-oci</link>
      <description>Just over a month ago, I joined Oracle, specifically OCI, as a Master Principal Cloud Architect. While Oracle products such as E-Business Suite, Java, and Oracle databases are ubiquitous in the corporate world, Oracle Cloud Infrastructure or OCI is l...</description>
      <author> (https://hashnode.com/@BasementProgrammer)</author>
      <guid>https://basementprogrammer.com/net-in-the-cloud-with-oci</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 21:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>