<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How Crash Bandicoot Hacked The Original Playstation | War Stories | Ars Technica</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=izxXGuVL21o</link>
      <description>For today’s episode of War Stories, Ars Technica sat down with Naughty Dog Co-founder Andy Gavin to talk about the hurdles in bringing the original Crash Bandicoot to gamers around the world. When Andy and his partner Jason Rubin made the decision to bring the action platforming genre into three dimensions, it required living up to their company ethos of “leaving no stone unturned” in the search for memory - even if it meant hacking Sony’s library code. 

Directed and Produced by Sean Dacanay
Edited and Graphics Animated by Jeremy Smolik 

Footage used in the video:
LGR - SGI Indigo2 Computer System Review.mp4 https://youtu.be/ZDxLa6P6exc
Way Of The Warrior Classic 3DO gameplay.mp4 https://youtu.be/JPsnkWqIfaU
Super Mario World Video Walkthrough.mp4 https://youtu.be/j8YFxB6rYIo
Donkey Kong Country Video Walkthrough.mp4 https://youtu.be/whp2Y_MjTXs
[TAS] Donkey Kong Country 101% in 4118 by Tompa.mp4 https://youtu.be/lrBG_9PJJPY
Atari 2600 Longplay Pitfall! (old).mp4 https://youtu.be/pslbO6Fddhw
Sonic The Hedgehog - Full Playthrough No  Commentary.mp4 https://youtu.be/B1FEHo_RcNw
Street Fighter II Genesis - Ken Playthrough 1 3.mp4 https://youtu.be/cKQXc2Xupgs
Mortal Kombat 1 Super Nintendo SNES Very Hard Playthrough Sub-Zero.mp4 https://youtu.be/exR98Lil8eU
Virtua Fighter 1 Arcade - 1CC (Akira   Not MAME)   バーチャファイター 1   버추어 파이터 1.mp4 https://youtu.be/QDbn9lF7k8Y
Galaga - Gameplay Arcade 1981.mp4 https://youtu.be/dvjapcHsqXY
PSX Longplay [040] Twisted Metal 2 World Tour.mp4 https://youtu.be/d6mB8zlx88g
Tomb Raider (PS1) 100% ALL SECRETS Walkthrough Longplay NO COMMENTARY.mp4 https://youtu.be/ECVAdDHDssk
NES Longplay [250] Super Mario Bros (a).mp4 https://youtu.be/7qirrV8w5SQ
SNES Longplay - Super Mario World.mp4 https://youtu.be/Vxg5eOPmzHI
Super Mario 64 - N64 - Full Playthrough No Commentary.mp4 https://youtu.be/Z3G4t6i5PAc
LONGPLAY Commander Keen Episode 1 Marooned on Mars (1990) [MS-DOS].mp4 https://youtu.be/doA3d5_zD1Q
The Incredible Machine (PC) - versión Windows 3.1.mp4 https://youtu.be/O14FIxIF_5E
Crash Bandicoot Commercials 1996-2000.mp4 https://youtu.be/yKXpjkNgY88
SONY PlayStation (1995).mp4 https://youtu.be/xsElYfwkhzE
Arcade Game  I, Robot (1983 Atari) (1 5).mp4 https://youtu.be/EHkwdvfXHJc
Inside NaughtyDog - Crash Warped [Playstation Underground].mp4 https://youtu.be/crh-OFOLOeg
History of 3D in Video Games 1974-1994.mp4 https://youtu.be/hTehcvSgyWI
Jurassic Park Before and After.mp4 https://youtu.be/PgixhKfH1w4
Sonic the Hedgehog 2 Special Stage 7.mp4 https://youtu.be/npalmFeX9ak
PSX Longplay [049] Tekken.mp4 https://youtu.be/n_61oi6WavA
Playstation 299 (E3 1995 Keynote).mp4 https://youtu.be/ExaAYIKsDBI

Connect with Ars Technica:
Visit ArsTechnica.com: http://arstechnica.com
Follow Ars Technica on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/arstechnica
Follow Ars Technica on Google+: https://plus.google.com/+ArsTechnica/videos
Follow Ars Technica on Twitter: https://twitter.com/arstechnica


How Crash Bandicoot Hacked The Original Playstation | War Stories | Ars Technica</description>
      <author> (Ars Technica)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=izxXGuVL21o</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 13:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programmers generate every possible melody in MIDI to prevent lawsuits - MusicTech</title>
      <link>https://www.musictech.net/news/programmers-generate-every-possible-melody-in-midi-to-prevent-lawsuits/</link>
      <description>Damien Riehl, musician, programmer and copyright attorney, teamed up with programmer, Noah Rubin, to find a way to stop musicians getting sued for their music.</description>
      <author> (Sam Willings)</author>
      <guid>https://www.musictech.net/news/programmers-generate-every-possible-melody-in-midi-to-prevent-lawsuits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 12:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Gift Cards | Give the Gift of Secure Passwords | 1Password</title>
      <link>https://1password.com/giftcards/</link>
      <description>Gift a 1Password subscription account, pay with Paypal, Apple Pay, Visa, Mastercard. Redeem a gift code for your account or purchase a code for a friend.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://1password.com/giftcards/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WildML</title>
      <link>http://www.wildml.com/</link>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence, Deep Learning, and NLP</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.wildml.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 09:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 180</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-180/</link>
      <description>If last week was the week where I felt like I was drowning in data that was still being processed, this week was the week where it came to light. Not all of it, mind you, I've still got ginormous volumes I'm disclosing but it certainly was a whole heap</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-180/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 09:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Framework February 2020 Preview of Quality Rollup | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/net-framework-february-2020-preview-of-quality-rollup/</link>
      <description>Today, we are releasing the February 2020 Preview of Quality Rollup Updates for .NET Framework.
Quality and Reliability
This release contains the following quality and reliability improvements.
CLR1  Addresses an issue with rare crashes or deadlocks that could occur if a GC occurs while another thread is running NGen’ed code which makes the initial call into a static method within the same module where one or more parameter types involve type-forwarded value types.</description>
      <author> (Tara OverfieldSoftware Engineer II , .NET ServicingFollow Tara)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/net-framework-february-2020-preview-of-quality-rollup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rider 2020.1 Starts Early Access Program - .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/02/27/rider-2020-1-eap/</link>
      <description>For the first 2020.1 EAP build, we didn’t set our sights on implementing any new big features or changing the world. Instead, we put a lot of effort into polishing and jazzing up the tons of existing features to make … Continue reading →</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/02/27/rider-2020-1-eap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to set up Docker within Windows System for Linux (WSL2) on Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/HowToSetUpDockerWithinWindowsSystemForLinuxWSL2OnWindows10.aspx</link>
      <description>I've written about WSL2 and it's glorious wonders many times. As its release (presumably) grows closer - as of this ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/HowToSetUpDockerWithinWindowsSystemForLinuxWSL2OnWindows10.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Azure Cache for Redis - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/dotnet/net-development/overview-of-azure-cache-for-redis/</link>
      <description>Caching data is one way to improve application performance. In this article, Chandra Kudumla explains a service for caching data found in Azure called Azure Cache for Redis.</description>
      <author> (Chandra Kudumula)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/dotnet/net-development/overview-of-azure-cache-for-redis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper Ultimate 2020.1 Kicks off the Early Access Program! - .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/02/27/resharper-ultimate-2020-1-eap/</link>
      <description>Just an hour ago, we published our first EAP build for ReSharper Ultimate 2020.1. Jump in and preview what’s coming in 2020.1! Since everybody seems interested in performance, let’s start with the performance news. There were tons of changes in … Continue reading →</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/02/27/resharper-ultimate-2020-1-eap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tip 249 - Deploying a Node.js Web App using Visual Studio Code, GitHub Actions and Azure</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/blog/tip249.html</link>
      <description>GitHub Actions gives you the flexibility to build an automated software development lifecycle workflow. You can write individual tasks ("Actions") and combine them to create a custom workflow. Workflows are configurable automated processes that you can set up in your repository to build, test, package, release, or deploy any project on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/blog/tip249.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Observability to .NET Core Apps ASP.NET Blog |</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/observability-asp-net-core-apps/</link>
      <description>Based on customers using .NET Core in different environments, this article explores options for adding observability to .NET Core apps.</description>
      <author> (Francisco BeltraoFollow Francisco)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/observability-asp-net-core-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immutability in DTOs?</title>
      <link>https://jimmybogard.com/immutability-in-dtos/</link>
      <description>Something that comes up every so often is the question of whether or not Data Transfer Objects should be immutable - that is, should our design of the classes and types of a DTO enforce immutability. To answer this question, we first need to look at what purpose a DTO</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Bogard)</author>
      <guid>https://jimmybogard.com/immutability-in-dtos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic UI</title>
      <link>https://semantic-ui.com/</link>
      <description>Semantic empowers designers and developers by creating a shared vocabulary for UI.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://semantic-ui.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 05:52:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why hand washing really could slow down an epidemic</title>
      <link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/why-hand-washing-really-could-slow-down-an-epidemic</link>
      <description>Air travel pattern simulations and reports on travelers' personal hygiene practices show that hand washing really could slow down the spread of disease.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/why-hand-washing-really-could-slow-down-an-epidemic</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 05:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candyman - Official Trailer [HD]</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tlwzuZ9kOQU</link>
      <description>Candyman
In Theaters June 12
https://www.CandymanMovie.com

Don’t say his name. 

This summer, Oscar® winner Jordan Peele unleashes a fresh take on the blood-chilling urban legend that your friend’s older sibling probably told you about at a sleepover: Candyman. Rising filmmaker Nia DaCosta (Little Woods) directs this contemporary incarnation of the cult classic.  

For as long as residents can remember, the housing projects of Chicago’s Cabrini Green neighborhood were terrorized by a word-of-mouth ghost story about a supernatural killer with a hook for a hand, easily summoned by those daring to repeat his name five times into a mirror. In present day, a decade after the last of the Cabrini towers were torn down, visual artist Anthony McCoy (Yahya Abdul-Mateen II; HBO’s Watchmen, Us) and his girlfriend, gallery director Brianna Cartwright (Teyonah Parris; If Beale Street Could Talk, The Photograph), move into a luxury loft condo in Cabrini, now gentrified beyond recognition and inhabited by upwardly mobile millennials.

With Anthony’s painting career on the brink of stalling, a chance encounter with a Cabrini Green old-timer (Colman Domingo; HBO’s Euphoria, Assassination Nation) exposes Anthony to the tragically horrific nature of the true story behind Candyman. Anxious to maintain his status in the Chicago art world, Anthony begins to explore these macabre details in his studio as fresh grist for paintings, unknowingly opening a door to a complex past that unravels his own sanity and unleashes a terrifyingly viral wave of violence that puts him on a collision course with destiny.

Universal Pictures presents, from Metro Goldwyn Mayer Pictures and Jordan Peele and Win Rosenfeld’s Monkeypaw Productions, in association with BRON Creative, Candyman. Candyman is directed by DaCosta, and is produced by Ian Cooper (Us), Rosenfeld and Peele. The screenplay is by Peele &amp; Rosenfeld and DaCosta. The film is based on the 1992 film Candyman, written by Bernard Rose, and the short story “The Forbidden” by Clive Barker. The film’s executive producers are David Kern, Aaron L. Gilbert and Jason Cloth.</description>
      <author> (Universal Pictures)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tlwzuZ9kOQU</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 05:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IoT SVG Idea</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/NickCraver/b4dd3cee429f811d41a4ddb1ccaa7a5a</link>
      <description>IoT SVG Idea. GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/NickCraver/b4dd3cee429f811d41a4ddb1ccaa7a5a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principal Software Engineer in Redmond, Washington, United States | Engineering at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/800721/Principal-Software-Engineer</link>
      <description>Apply for Principal Software Engineer job with Microsoft in Redmond, Washington, United States. Engineering at Microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/800721/Principal-Software-Engineer</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strava Runner Profile | David Ortinau</title>
      <link>https://www.strava.com/athletes/1044152</link>
      <description>David Ortinau is a runner from Wildwood, MO. Join Strava to track your activities, analyze your performance, and follow friends.  Strava members can plan routes, participate in motivating challenges, and join clubs.  Get started by signing up for free.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.strava.com/athletes/1044152</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bern_relief.py</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/wybiral/53b6a0e32bf9a03437f904553707a245</link>
      <description>GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/wybiral/53b6a0e32bf9a03437f904553707a245</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Zero Knowledge: Zero-Knowledge Proofs for Set Membership | ZKProof Standards</title>
      <link>https://zkproof.org/2020/02/27/zkp-set-membership/</link>
      <description>Last year I wrote about why booking too far in advance can be dangerous for your business, and this concept of margin so eloquently captures what I had recognized had been my problem: I was so booked up with clients that I wasn’t leaving any margin for error, growth, planning, or reflection.</description>
      <author> (Dario FioreAll author posts)</author>
      <guid>https://zkproof.org/2020/02/27/zkp-set-membership/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping coronavirus, responsibly</title>
      <link>https://www.esri.com/arcgis-blog/products/product/mapping/mapping-coronavirus-responsibly/</link>
      <description>We live in an amazing time as far as cartography is concerned. Technology allows, and actively supports rapid, democratized mapping. Data, compiled and published in near real-time (if not actual real-time) encourages people to get their hands dirty to see what they can make. Media outlets all rush to provide their audience with fast, visible content. Social media drives sharing of these maps at a breathtaking pace. When you throw in a developing human health story the ingredients are ripe for maps to take centre stage, as they have become with the ongoing coronavirus outbreak. Let’s take a look at how maps can help shape the narrative and, as concern (fear?) grows, how to map the data responsibly.</description>
      <author> (Kenneth Field)</author>
      <guid>https://www.esri.com/arcgis-blog/products/product/mapping/mapping-coronavirus-responsibly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 23:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Attribute Routing in ASP.NET Core 3.0 MVC</title>
      <link>https://exceptionnotfound.net/an-overview-of-attribute-routing-in-asp-net-core-3-0-mvc/</link>
      <description>Let's see how to use the fine-grained control of attribute routing in our ASP.NET Core 3.0 apps.</description>
      <author> (exceptionnotfound)</author>
      <guid>https://exceptionnotfound.net/an-overview-of-attribute-routing-in-asp-net-core-3-0-mvc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 22:34:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Default Keyboard Shortcuts - Visual Studio 2019 for Mac</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/visualstudio/mac/keyboard-shortcuts?view=vsmac-2019</link>
      <description>This article lists the default keyboard shortcuts in Visual Studio for Mac</description>
      <author> (heiligerdankgesang)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/visualstudio/mac/keyboard-shortcuts?view=vsmac-2019</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 22:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math with Bad Drawings: Illuminating the Ideas That Shape Our Reality: Ben Orlin: 9780316509039: Amazon.com: Books</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0316509035/ref=as_li_tl?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202002</link>
      <description>Buy Math with Bad Drawings: Illuminating the Ideas That Shape Our Reality on Amazon.com ✓ FREE SHIPPING on qualified orders</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0316509035/ref=as_li_tl?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202002</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 22:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Feb 25, 2020 - Intro to Kubernetes for ASP.NET Core devs</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V_EszvGJ8O8</link>
      <description>Join members from the ASP.NET teams for our community standup covering great community contributions for ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, and more. 

Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/aspnet-community-standup-2020-02-25</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V_EszvGJ8O8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 22:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t try to sanitize input. Escape output.</title>
      <link>https://benhoyt.com/writings/dont-sanitize-do-escape/</link>
      <description>Why you should escape output correctly, but generally not sanitize user input.</description>
      <author> (Ben Hoyt)</author>
      <guid>https://benhoyt.com/writings/dont-sanitize-do-escape/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 21:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundred year mistakes</title>
      <link>https://ericlippert.com/2020/02/27/hundred-year-mistakes/</link>
      <description>My manager and I got off on a tangent in our most recent one-on-one on the subject of the durability of design mistakes in programming languages. A particular favourite of mine is the worst of the …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ericlippert.com/2020/02/27/hundred-year-mistakes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straffic</title>
      <link>https://straffic.io/updates.php</link>
      <description>Wednesday, Feb 26 2020 21:15, IST</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://straffic.io/updates.php</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:16:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straffic</title>
      <link>https://straffic.io/contact.php</link>
      <description>Let Us Know What We Can Do For You.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://straffic.io/contact.php</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:16:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli Marketing Company Exposes Contacts Database</title>
      <link>https://www.databreachtoday.com/israeli-marketing-company-exposes-contacts-database-a-13785</link>
      <description>An Israeli marketing company left the authentication credentials for a database online, exposing more than 140 GB worth of names, email addresses and phone numbers.</description>
      <author> (Jeremy Kirk)</author>
      <guid>https://www.databreachtoday.com/israeli-marketing-company-exposes-contacts-database-a-13785</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:16:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to create a Dell-Ubuntu Image on your Dell PC</title>
      <link>https://www.dell.com/support/article/en-us/sln265886/how-to-create-a-dell-ubuntu-image-on-your-dell-pc</link>
      <description>This article takes you through creating a Dell system image on your PC if it's using an Ubuntu operating system.</description>
      <author> (Dell US)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dell.com/support/article/en-us/sln265886/how-to-create-a-dell-ubuntu-image-on-your-dell-pc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:15:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hasura raises $9.9M Series A to simplify GraphQL for developers – TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2020/02/26/hasura-raises-9-9m-series-a-to-simplify-graphql-for-developers/</link>
      <description>Hasura, a startup working to solve developer problems around connecting to databases when using the open-source GraphQL tool, announced a $9.9 million Series A investment today. Vertex Ventures US led the round, with participation from SAP.iO Fund and existing investors Nexus Venture Partners and S…</description>
      <author> (Ron Miller@ron_miller / 7:11 am PST • February 26, 2020comment Comment)</author>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2020/02/26/hasura-raises-9-9m-series-a-to-simplify-graphql-for-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:09:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the GOV.UK Design System team changed the input type for numbers - Technology in government</title>
      <link>https://technology.blog.gov.uk/2020/02/24/why-the-gov-uk-design-system-team-changed-the-input-type-for-numbers/</link>
      <description>About digital and technology projects in government.</description>
      <author> (Hanna Laakso, GDS, Frontend Developer)</author>
      <guid>https://technology.blog.gov.uk/2020/02/24/why-the-gov-uk-design-system-team-changed-the-input-type-for-numbers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:09:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incident on 2020-02-27 14:31 UTC</title>
      <link>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/q07bfjh7jf1t</link>
      <description>GitHub's Status Page - Incident on 2020-02-27 14:31 UTC.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.githubstatus.com/incidents/q07bfjh7jf1t</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:09:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A painless self-hosted Git service</title>
      <link>https://gogs.io/</link>
      <description>Gogs is a painless self-hosted Git service.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gogs.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:14:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Encrypt Has Issued a Billion Certificates</title>
      <link>https://letsencrypt.org/2020/02/27/one-billion-certs.html</link>
      <description>We issued our billionth certificate on February 27, 2020. We’re going to use this big round number as an opportunity to reflect on what has changed for us, and for the Internet, leading up to this event. In particular, we want to talk about what has happened since the last time we talked about a big round number of certificates - one hundred million.
One thing that’s different now is that the Web is much more encrypted than it was.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://letsencrypt.org/2020/02/27/one-billion-certs.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showcase of projects built with .net technology - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/</link>
      <description>BuiltWithDot.Net is a community showcase of projects built with .net framework, .net core, xamarin, mono, mono game, unity, or godot. Anyone can submit.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuillJs editor &amp; Image resize proxy tag helpers - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/179/fluxmatix-asp.net-core-taghelpers</link>
      <description>Fluxmatix ASP.NET Core tag helpers is a collection of handy ASPNET Core TagHelpers that I initially created when building BuiltWithDot.Net.

Currently it includes 2 tag helpers:

QuillEditor
This tag helper enables developers to easily add the popular Quill WYSIWYG editor to a form, with model bind…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/179/fluxmatix-asp.net-core-taghelpers</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CppCon 2014: Chandler Carruth "Efficiency with Algorithms, Performance with Data Structures"</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fHNmRkzxHWs</link>
      <description>http://www.cppcon.org
—
Presentation Slides, PDFs, Source Code and other presenter materials are available at: https://github.com/CppCon/CppCon2014
--
Why do you write C++ code? There is a good chance it is in part because of concerns about the performance of your software. Whether they stem from needing to run on every smaller mobile devices, squeezing the last few effects into video game, or because every watt of power in your data center costs too much, C++ programmers throughout the industry have an insatiable desire for writing high performance code.

Unfortunately, even with C++, this can be really challenging. Over the past twenty years processors, memory, software libraries, and even compilers have radically changed what makes C++ code fast. Even measuring the performance of your code can be a daunting task. This talk will dig into how modern processors work, what makes them fast, and how to exploit them effectively with modern C++ code. It will teach you how modern C++ optimizers see your code today, and how that is likely to change in the coming years. It will teach you how to reason better about the performance of your code, and how to write your code so that it performs better. You will even learn some tricks about how to measure the performance of your code.
--
Chandler Carruth leads the Clang team at Google, building better diagnostics, tools, and more. Previously, he worked on several pieces of Google’s distributed build system. He makes guest appearances helping to maintain a few core C++ libraries across Google’s codebase, and is active in the LLVM and Clang open source communities. He received his M.S. and B.S. in Computer Science from Wake Forest University, but disavows all knowledge of the contents of his Master’s thesis. He is regularly found drinking Cherry Coke Zero in the daytime and pontificating over a single malt scotch in the evening.
--
Videos Filmed &amp; Edited by Bash Films: http://www.BashFilms.com</description>
      <author> (CppCon)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fHNmRkzxHWs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Babylon.js 4.1</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@babylonjs/welcome-to-babylon-js-4-1-b855d09d32b</link>
      <description>Our mission is to create one of the most powerful, beautiful, and simple Web rendering engines in the world. Our passion is to make it…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@babylonjs)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@babylonjs/welcome-to-babylon-js-4-1-b855d09d32b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 18:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a Member | Mathematical Association of America</title>
      <link>https://www.maa.org/join</link>
      <description>Choose the membership type:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.maa.org/join</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 16:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/team/livecoders</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/team/livecoders</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 15:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 8 pattern matching - Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2020/02/27/c-8-pattern-matching/</link>
      <description>We explore C# 8's extended pattern matching support and compare it to pattern matching in C# 7.</description>
      <author> (By Tom Deseyn February 27, 2020February 26, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2020/02/27/c-8-pattern-matching/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 15:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tippin.me</title>
      <link>https://tippin.me/@Programazing</link>
      <description>Your digital tip jar, using Lightning Network and Bitcoin.</description>
      <author> (tippin.me)</author>
      <guid>https://tippin.me/@Programazing</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Simpsons in CSS</title>
      <link>https://pattle.github.io/simpsons-in-css/</link>
      <description>The Simpsons in CSS</description>
      <author> (Chris Pattle)</author>
      <guid>https://pattle.github.io/simpsons-in-css/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>