<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Learn .NET - GitHub Copilot (Africa)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HANHdcnE-TQ</link>
      <description>Let's learn about GitHub Copilot and Copilot Chat in this workshop covering AI-powered coding, getting started with Copilot, and prompt engineering for crafting effective commands. Together, we will take a peek into maximizing Copilot efficiency, tips and tricks, frequently asked questions, as well as an intro to Continuous Development Flow with GitHub Copilot for Azure. 

Acknowledgment: This content will be presented by our colleagues in Africa.

Repo: https://github.com/microsoft/mastering-github-copilot-for-dotnet-csharp-developers

Community Links: https://aka.ms/letslearn/dotnet/ghcp

Featuring: Japhlet Nwamu, Someleze Diko, Lebogang Madise

#dotNET #GitHub #Copilot #GitHubCopilot</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HANHdcnE-TQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimal CSS-only blurry image placeholders</title>
      <link>https://leanrada.com/notes/css-only-lqip/</link>
      <description>Here’s a CSS technique that produces blurry image placeholders (LQIPs) without cluttering up your markup — Only a single custom property needed!</description>
      <guid>https://leanrada.com/notes/css-only-lqip/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 50 years of Microsoft | Bill Gates</title>
      <link>https://www.gatesnotes.com/home/home-page-topic/reader/microsoft-original-source-code</link>
      <description>This one piece of code led to a half century of innovation from Microsoft.</description>
      <guid>https://www.gatesnotes.com/home/home-page-topic/reader/microsoft-original-source-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI 2027</title>
      <link>https://ai-2027.com/</link>
      <description>A research-backed AI scenario forecast.
</description>
      <guid>https://ai-2027.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's talk about Tariffs? </title>
      <link>https://novice.media/p/lets-talk-about-tariffs</link>
      <description>The end of free trade, or the beginning of American Renaissance?</description>
      <guid>https://novice.media/p/lets-talk-about-tariffs</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timing Is Everything: Real S&amp;P 500 Returns Across 5, 10, and 20-Year Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.moatmind.com/p/real-sp500-returns-5-10-20-year-windows</link>
      <description>A century-long look at how entry timing shapes real, inflation-adjusted returns—proving that even long-term investing in the S&amp;P 500 can yield wildly different outcomes.</description>
      <guid>https://www.moatmind.com/p/real-sp500-returns-5-10-20-year-windows</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating Azure Durable Function App to Use Durable Task Scheduler: Running Locally</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2025/04/migrating-azure-durable-function-app-to.html</link>
      <description>.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Azure, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2025/04/migrating-azure-durable-function-app-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Scrape</title>
      <link>https://herman.bearblog.dev/the-great-scrape/</link>
      <description>Scraper bots are destroying the commons to feed the machine</description>
      <guid>https://herman.bearblog.dev/the-great-scrape/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - lwthiker/curl-impersonate: curl-impersonate: A special build of curl that can impersonate Chrome &amp; Firefox</title>
      <link>https://github.com/lwthiker/curl-impersonate</link>
      <description>curl-impersonate: A special build of curl that can impersonate Chrome &amp; Firefox - lwthiker/curl-impersonate</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/lwthiker/curl-impersonate</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To the rejected</title>
      <link>https://blog.johnqian.com/college-admissions</link>
      <description>April 2024</description>
      <guid>https://blog.johnqian.com/college-admissions</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Easiest Way to Meditate</title>
      <link>https://shubhamjain.co/2025/04/03/easiest-form-of-meditation/</link>
      <description>
Meditation is great — most of us can agree on that. But like exercise, it’s been overcomplicated. There are just so many forms of it: guided, silent, body scans, vipassana, kriyas. There are apps, videos, retreats, books, and self-proclaimed gurus—everyone’s selling their version.

Its benefits have also been oversold. People are led to believe it’s a one-stop solution for all mental health issues, and at worst, a path to everlasting bliss. Do a week of Vipassana and your mind will be permanently transformed.

I can’t speak for everyone, but that hasn’t been my experience.

Meditation, to me, is just a tool to denoise the brain — and that’s become crucial in an age of constant overstimulation. Denoising helps you tune into the present, improves your focus, helps you identify the negative thought patterns, and also, softens their grip.

## Transcendental Meditation

Once I reframed what meditation *is*—a tool to denoise the brain—I had much more realistic expectations. After experimenting with various techniques, I found one that fits perfectly: Transcendental Meditation.

Don't worry, the name makes it sound advanced, but it’s actually the simplest one I’ve tried.

That said, it’s promoted by an organization that is borderline scammy (trying too hard to sell something), so good info is weirdly hard to find without paying. But the technique itself? Surprisingly easy and effective.

Here's how to do it:

**Just close your eyes and repeat a simple word or mantra &lt;u&gt;in your mind&lt;/u&gt; (like, _om_, _shrim_, or _namah_). It should be pleasant sounding and ideally meaningless. Don’t try to control your thoughts. If your mind drifts, gently return to repeating the mantra.**

That’s it. Sit on a chair, sit cross-legged, or lie down, doesn’t matter. Set a timer for 15–20 minutes, or go by feel. Do it in a park, or at home; in the morning, evening, or at night.

​Everything is up to you. 

## Why it works?

Like I said earlier, meditation is just a way to denoise your brain. Whether you focus on your breath, your body, or a mantra — it’s all aiming for the same outcome.

Repeating a word in your head is especially effective because, oddly enough, **the mind can only focus on one thing at a time**. When you repeat the word, it gently cuts off wandering thoughts. Over time, this starts to clear the mental clutter. Your mind calms down and you become more in tune with the present, and your own thought patterns.

When I practice it, I feel less overwhelmed, more focused, and the urge to doomscroll quiets down. And at night, it’s incredibly helpful for falling asleep.

If meditation is supposed to be a path to everlasting bliss, then I’m probably not on it — and honestly, that’s okay.

---

People have claimed all sorts of things about meditation, but in my experience, it's not necessary to explore the depth of consciousness to be reasonably happy. It’s healthier to approach meditation with more grounded expectations. 

But that's my take.  If you want to transform your mind, you're better off exploring a retreat or something similar.
</description>
      <guid>https://shubhamjain.co/2025/04/03/easiest-form-of-meditation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bikes in the Age of Tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.renehersecycles.com/bikes-in-the-age-of-tariffs/</link>
      <description>Today's post was going to be about a new product we're introducing—but we need to hold off while we recalculate our prices. You've probably seen the news: Virtually all imports into the United States will be subjected to additional, steep import taxes, also called tariffs. The…</description>
      <guid>https://www.renehersecycles.com/bikes-in-the-age-of-tariffs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your LLM Problem Isn't Tooling. It's Effort</title>
      <link>https://tomdekan.com/articles/eval-frameworks</link>
      <description>Getting great LLM output with an LLM-as-a-judge requires more effort, not more tools</description>
      <guid>https://tomdekan.com/articles/eval-frameworks</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I guess some request headers are more trustworthy than others.</title>
      <link>https://macarthur.me/posts/forbidden-request-headers/</link>
      <description>There's a subset of request headers that can't be modified by a spec-compliant user agent. Let's explore why they're useful for determining how and for what purpose a request was triggered. </description>
      <author> (Alex MacArthur)</author>
      <guid>https://macarthur.me/posts/forbidden-request-headers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Overestimate the Importance of Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://en.lutaonan.com/we-overestimate-the-importance-of-intelligence/</link>
      <description>In this era of increasingly powerful AI, one question I've been pondering more often is whether we tend to overvalue intelligence.

Several things sparked ...</description>
      <guid>https://en.lutaonan.com/we-overestimate-the-importance-of-intelligence/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balance</title>
      <link>https://blog.knhash.in/balance/</link>
      <description>
I've been thinking a lot about balance lately. It has been a background thread slowly developing, with three distinct step functions where it rose to the f...</description>
      <guid>https://blog.knhash.in/balance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nix that looks like Bazel</title>
      <link>https://fzakaria.com/2025/04/02/nix-that-looks-like-bazel</link>
      <description>This is an idea 💡 that came from PlanetNix. I did not originate the idea.</description>
      <guid>https://fzakaria.com/2025/04/02/nix-that-looks-like-bazel</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A case against migration files</title>
      <link>https://rcwz.pl/2025-04-03-a-case-against-migration-files/</link>
      <description>I never really understood the popularity of migration files. Sure enough, you need to somehow change schema from version A to version B and using SQL statements is the most straightforward way to do it, but surely, there has to be a better way, right..?</description>
      <guid>https://rcwz.pl/2025-04-03-a-case-against-migration-files/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Wants to Be a Ghibli Character. So, Why Does It Feel So Wrong?</title>
      <link>https://samsimlai.github.io/ghibli-ai-trend</link>
      <description>There’s a peculiar kind of magic in watching Studio Ghibli films. The kind that doesn’t just entertain — it lingers. It coats your soul like the afternoon light in My Neighbor Totoro, or the silent resilience of Princess Mononoke. It makes you want to touch grass, sip tea slowly, notice the wind, and wonder why we ever stopped paying attention to these things in the first place.</description>
      <guid>https://samsimlai.github.io/ghibli-ai-trend</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Journey with Vibe Coding</title>
      <link>https://tildehacker.com/my-journey-with-vibe-coding</link>
      <description>A detailed look at vibe coding from someone who’s been building software before and after the AI revolution</description>
      <guid>https://tildehacker.com/my-journey-with-vibe-coding</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSH is exciting</title>
      <link>https://yoyo-code.com/ssh-is-exciting/</link>
      <description>Matyáš Racek's blog</description>
      <guid>https://yoyo-code.com/ssh-is-exciting/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I'm Going Back to Zathura reader</title>
      <link>https://blog.nimendra.xyz/blog/zathura/</link>
      <description>After trying various readers on Linux, I’m returning to Zathura for its speed, minimal UI.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.nimendra.xyz/blog/zathura/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Your Neural Network Run Faster: An Overview of Optimization Techniques</title>
      <link>https://arikpoz.github.io/posts/2025-03-30-how-to-make-your-neural-network-run-faster-an-overview-of-optimization-techniques/</link>
      <description>Introduction Neural networks are becoming increasingly powerful, but speed remains a crucial factor in real-world applications. Whether you’re running models on the cloud, edge devices, or personal hardware, optimizing them for speed can lead to faster inference, lower latency, and reduced resource consumption.
In this post, we’ll explore various techniques to accelerate neural networks, from model compression to hardware optimizations. This will serve as a foundation for future deep dives into each method.</description>
      <guid>https://arikpoz.github.io/posts/2025-03-30-how-to-make-your-neural-network-run-faster-an-overview-of-optimization-techniques/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An image of an archeologist adventurer who wears a hat and uses a bullwhip</title>
      <link>https://theaiunderwriter.substack.com/p/an-image-of-an-archeologist-adventurer</link>
      <description>There is only one thing worse than being imitated</description>
      <guid>https://theaiunderwriter.substack.com/p/an-image-of-an-archeologist-adventurer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning models don't always say what they think</title>
      <link>https://www.anthropic.com/research/reasoning-models-dont-say-think</link>
      <description>Research from Anthropic on the faithfulness of AI models' Chain-of-Thought</description>
      <guid>https://www.anthropic.com/research/reasoning-models-dont-say-think</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anime.js | JavaScript Animation Engine</title>
      <link>https://animejs.com/</link>
      <description>An fast and versatile JavaScript animation library</description>
      <guid>https://animejs.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenNutrition — Search</title>
      <link>https://www.opennutrition.app/search</link>
      <description>OpenNutrition is a mobile app designed to help you track your macros, receive personalized diet recommendations, and monitor your fitness goals.</description>
      <guid>https://www.opennutrition.app/search</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET AI Community Standup - 🔮 Fortune-Telling with Semantic Kernel</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=MV0ezTU9SA4</link>
      <description>What do your birth date, time, and place say about your future? In Korea, fortune tellers use complex math to create a perpetual calendar—but now, we're giving that tradition a modern .NET twist! 💻✨

Join Bruno and Justin as they summon the powers of Azure OpenAI, Semantic Kernel, and Azure Container Apps dynamic sessions to build an intelligent .NET app that calculates your birth chart and lets an LLM interpret your destiny.

From generating and executing Python code on-the-fly to orchestrating it all with Semantic Kernel, they’ll show live demos, share clever tricks, and spark ideas for your own AI-powered experiences.

Community Links: https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/collections/8xymaztyqqe21r

Featuring: Bruno Capuano (@elbruno), Justin Yoo (@justinchronicle)

#dotnet #AI #SemanticKernel #AzureOpenAI #AzureContainerApps</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=MV0ezTU9SA4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ANY Model with GitHub Copilot &amp; Visual Studio Code! Custom Models are Here!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EeUXWrbMtpM</link>
      <description>Custom models just landed in GitHub Copilot inside of VS Code! This means you can easily connect to Anthropic, OpenAI, Azure AI, Gemini, and more including running custom models inside of Ollama on your own machine! Let's get into it!

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCENTmbKaTphpWV2R2evVz2A/join

👕 Buy some swag! - https://jamesmontemagno.myspreadshop.com/
☕️ Buy me a coffee - https://www.buymeacoffee.com/jamesmontemagno

Follow:
👨‍💻 GitHub: https://github.com/jamesmontemagno
🦜 X: https://x.com/jamesmontemagno
📄 Website: https://www.montemagno.com
📰 Newsletter: https://newsletter.montemagno.com/

Disclaimer: This channel, videos, and streams are created in my spare time and are a product of me... James Montemagno! They are NOT officially affiliated or endorsed by Microsoft (my employer) in any way. Opinions and views are my own.

What is on my hat? It is the CLE clothing logo because I am from Cleveland! Checkout their awesome CLE merch: https://cleclothingco.myshopify.com/

What is that art on my wall? It is an original piece from the French street artist Gregos of La Butte Montmartre: https://www.instagram.com/p/BceZ1oNHiQx/

My Setup:
📷 Canon M50 Mark II - https://amzn.to/3P8R7lp
💡 Nanoleaf Elements Lights - https://amzn.to/3umwJVW
🎙 Blue Spark Microphone - https://amzn.to/3qgtYkq
🎙 Blue Pop Filter - https://amzn.to/3jEWM3r
🤳 Rode Microphone Arm - https://amzn.to/2Z68AlE
🎧 Sony MDR7306 Headphones - https://amzn.to/372jxta
📲 Stream Deck - https://amzn.to/373Uk1n
🖱 MX Master 2S Mouse - https://amzn.to/3d7J2gj
⌨️ Tecware Phantom Keyboard - https://amzn.to/3aUP4y9

Using links I provide I may receive a commission if you buy something which helps support the channel.

#githubcopilot #vscode #visualstudiocode #azureai #ollama #deepseek #anthropic #gemini #github #copilot</description>
      <author> (James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EeUXWrbMtpM</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Community Chatter, Open Source C# and SharpSite</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=VwDmwaHfuW4</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Fritz is working on SharpSite - an open source CMS that has been built on these live streams.  Learn more at https://sharpsite.org</description>
      <author> (Fritz's Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=VwDmwaHfuW4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landscape I’ve seen it before. "When you're bigger," she had merely been sent to a.</title>
      <link>https://chronicles.mad-scientist.club/tales/grepping-logs-remains-terrible/</link>
      <description>Less 52 1984 cared. All one knew where, and of.</description>
      <guid>https://chronicles.mad-scientist.club/tales/grepping-logs-remains-terrible/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoMapper, MediatR and MassTransit go Commercial!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=bNuQ9xOG9eQ</link>
      <description>Get 40% off everything on Dometrain: https://dometrain.com/courses/?coupon_code=EARLYBDAY40&amp;ref=nick-chapsas&amp;promo=youtube
Subscribe to my weekly newsletter: https://nickchapsas.com

Become a Patreon and get special perks: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsas

Hello, everybody. I'm Nick, and in this video, I will talk about MediatR, AutoMapper and MassTransit going commercial. 

Workshops: https://bit.ly/nickworkshops

Don't forget to comment, like and subscribe :)

Social Media:
Follow me on GitHub: https://github.com/Elfocrash
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/nickchapsas
Connect on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick-chapsas

#csharp #dotnet</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=bNuQ9xOG9eQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Maintain a 17 Year Old Thinkpad</title>
      <link>https://pilledtexts.com/why-i-use-a-17-year-old-thinkpad/</link>
      <description>
If a book has been in print for forty years, I can expect it to be in print for another forty years. But, and that is the main difference, if it survives …</description>
      <guid>https://pilledtexts.com/why-i-use-a-17-year-old-thinkpad/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eventing in C#</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=rXtkCXOVxjc</link>
      <description>🎯 Mastering Events and Delegates in C#
In this video, we dive deep into eventing in C# — from the basics to advanced techniques used in real-world enterprise systems.

🔍 What you’ll learn:
✅ Introduction to events and delegates in C#
✅ How to implement eventing in enterprise-level applications
✅ Best practices and advanced patterns for robust event-driven architecture

Whether you're new to C# or looking to sharpen your skills for enterprise development, this video will give you the practical insights and patterns you need.

📌 Chapters: 
0:00 - Introduction
1:45 - What are Events and Delegates in C#
5:30 - Eventing in Enterprise Systems
22:00 - Advanced Eventing Techniques and Best Practices
25:00 - Final Thoughts and Tips

📚 Helpful Resources:
Microsoft Docs - Events and Delegates
https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/csharp/programming-guide/events/

The Standard
https://github.com/hassanhabib/The-Standard

Source Code
https://github.com/hassanhabib/EventingDemo

👍 Like, 💬 comment, and 🔔 subscribe if you find this helpful!
Let me know in the comments how you use eventing in your projects.

#CSharp #Eventing #Delegates #DotNet #EnterpriseArchitecture</description>
      <author> (Hassan Habib)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=rXtkCXOVxjc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - luskaner/ageLANServer: Web Server for AoE 1, 2 and 3 DE supporting LAN multiplayer 100% offline</title>
      <link>https://github.com/luskaner/ageLANServer</link>
      <description>Web Server for AoE 1, 2 and 3 DE supporting LAN multiplayer 100% offline - luskaner/ageLANServer</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/luskaner/ageLANServer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role Based Authorization in ASP .NET Core (using Identity and JWT)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=C82qlYq8aCQ</link>
      <description>In this tutorial we will talk about role based authorization in ASP .NET Core Web API that uses Identity for user management and provides JWT after successful authentication.

In this tutorial I've used the API that was built in my tutorial about JWT/Refresh Token Authentication in ASP .NET Core Web API, feel free to check it out to get the proper understanding about it. In description of this video, you will find the link to the github where I've posted the source code.

JWT Authentication in ASP .NET Core with Refresh Token (.NET 9):
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G6eEPPBIkh8

By the end of this video, you’ll have a fully functional authorization system that ensures only authorized users can access specific resources in your API project based on Role claim in JSON web token.

Support me on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/remigiuszzalewski
Follow me on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/remigiusz-zalewski
Follow me on Medium: https://medium.com/@remigiuszzalewski
Check out my Blog: https://remigiuszzalewski.com
Source code: https://github.com/RemigiuszZalewski/Role-Based-Authorization-In-ASP-.NET-Core</description>
      <author> (Remigiusz Zalewski)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=C82qlYq8aCQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>