<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How Red Hat just quietly, radically transformed enterprise server Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-red-hat-just-quietly-radically-transformed-enterprise-server-linux/</link>
      <description>RHEL 10 becomes the first major enterprise Linux distro to discard traditional packaging and embrace immutable. See how we got here.</description>
      <guid>https://www.zdnet.com/article/how-red-hat-just-quietly-radically-transformed-enterprise-server-linux/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 16:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Researchers Develop ‘Transparent Paper’ as Alternative to Plastics; New Material Is Biodegradable, Can Be Produced with Low Carbon Emissions</title>
      <link>https://japannews.yomiuri.co.jp/science-nature/technology/20250605-259501/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers with the Japan Agency for Marine-Earth Science and Technology (JAMSTEC) and other entities have developed thick sheets of transparent paper using cellulose, a material made from plant biomass.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://japannews.yomiuri.co.jp/science-nature/technology/20250605-259501/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 09:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A year of funded FreeBSD</title>
      <link>https://www.daemonology.net/blog/2025-06-06-A-year-of-funded-FreeBSD.html</link>
      <description>I've been maintaining
FreeBSD on the
Amazon EC2 platform ever since I
first got it booting in 2010, but in
November
2023 I added to my responsibilities the role of FreeBSD release
engineering lead — just in time to announce the availability of
FreeBSD 14.0, although Glen Barber did all the release engineering work for
that release.  While I receive a small amount of funding from
Antithesis and from my
FreeBSD/EC2 Patreon, it
rapidly became clear that my release engineering duties were competing
with — in fact, out-competing — FreeBSD/EC2 for my available
FreeBSD volunteer hours: In addition to my long list of "features to
implement" stagnating, I had increasingly been saying "huh that's weird...
oh well, no time to investigate that now".  In short, by early 2024 I was
becoming increasingly concerned that I was not in a position to be a good
"owner" of the FreeBSD/EC2 platform.</description>
      <guid>https://www.daemonology.net/blog/2025-06-06-A-year-of-funded-FreeBSD.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 09:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Illusion of Vibe Coding: There Are No Shortcuts to Mastery - ShiftMag</title>
      <link>https://shiftmag.dev/the-illusion-of-vibe-coding-5297/</link>
      <description>In the age of AI-assisted development, it’s tempting to believe we’re entering a golden era where human effort in programming becomes obsolete.</description>
      <guid>https://shiftmag.dev/the-illusion-of-vibe-coding-5297/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 02:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Interviews - Recruit better participants</title>
      <link>https://www.userinterviews.com/unsupported-browser</link>
      <description>The fastest &amp; easiest way to recruit high quality participants for any type of user research study. Make better decisions by getting feedback from real users.</description>
      <guid>https://www.userinterviews.com/unsupported-browser</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 02:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbor-Source Heat Pump</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3099/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3099/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 02:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balaji Arumugam</title>
      <link>https://b0a04gl.site/blog/test-loss-is-lying-to-you</link>
      <description>Portfolio of Balaji Arumugam - Senior Developer, Indie Hacker, and AI enthusiast</description>
      <guid>https://b0a04gl.site/blog/test-loss-is-lying-to-you</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Claude in Github: Hype and Reality</title>
      <link>https://www.coryzue.com/writing/claude-github/</link>
      <description>Agents are coming faster than ever and yet are still kind of hard to use?</description>
      <guid>https://www.coryzue.com/writing/claude-github/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we decreased GitLab repo backup times from 48 hours to 41 minutes</title>
      <link>https://about.gitlab.com/blog/2025/06/05/how-we-decreased-gitlab-repo-backup-times-from-48-hours-to-41-minutes/</link>
      <description>Learn how GitLab tracked a performance bottleneck to a 15-year-old Git function and fixed it, leading to enhanced efficiency that supports more robust backup strategies and can reduce risk.</description>
      <guid>https://about.gitlab.com/blog/2025/06/05/how-we-decreased-gitlab-repo-backup-times-from-48-hours-to-41-minutes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing everything I could understand about gradient noise</title>
      <link>https://blog.pkh.me/p/42-sharing-everything-i-could-understand-about-gradient-noise.html</link>
      <description>You've most likely heard about gradient noise through the name Perlin
noise, which refers to one particular implementation with various CPU
optimizations. Because it's an incredible tool for creative work, it's used
virtually everywhere: visual effects, video games, procedural mathematical art,
etc. While getting it right can sometimes be subtle, a "broken" implementation
can still look good or interesting. After all, "it looks fine, and I'm an
artist".</description>
      <guid>https://blog.pkh.me/p/42-sharing-everything-i-could-understand-about-gradient-noise.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> I can’t believe they said that! How to speak difficult truths</title>
      <link>https://blog.engora.com/2025/05/i-cant-believe-they-said-that.html</link>
      <description>Why comedians can say things other people can't</description>
      <guid>https://blog.engora.com/2025/05/i-cant-believe-they-said-that.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have LLMs Finally Mastered Geolocation? - bellingcat</title>
      <link>https://www.bellingcat.com/resources/how-tos/2025/06/06/have-llms-finally-mastered-geolocation/</link>
      <description>We tasked LLMs from OpenAI, Google, Anthropic, Mistral and xAI to geolocate our unpublished holiday snaps. Here's how they did.</description>
      <guid>https://www.bellingcat.com/resources/how-tos/2025/06/06/have-llms-finally-mastered-geolocation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts in the Internet Age: the Power of Email</title>
      <link>https://brianschrader.com/archive/experts-in-the-internet-age-the-power-of-email/</link>
      <description>These days I spend a fair bit of my time emailing libraries in order to get access to research materials for a project I'm working on, and I'd like to share what has become a very typical experience for me and one that I think more people should know about.</description>
      <guid>https://brianschrader.com/archive/experts-in-the-internet-age-the-power-of-email/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Coding: Where it works and where it doesn't</title>
      <link>https://sachin.devicion.com/blog/vibe-coding-where-it-works-and-where-it-does-not</link>
      <description>Vibe coding is a term that was coined by Andrej Karpathy in a tweet and it has been catching fire since then every day.</description>
      <guid>https://sachin.devicion.com/blog/vibe-coding-where-it-works-and-where-it-does-not</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jason Eckert's Website and Blog</title>
      <link>https://jasoneckert.github.io/myblog/powerbook-summer-vacation/</link>
      <description>My personal website and blog</description>
      <guid>https://jasoneckert.github.io/myblog/powerbook-summer-vacation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Resources Are For Caching</title>
      <link>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2025/06/05/mcp-resources</link>
      <description>This is a quick tour of what MCP resources actually are. And more to the point, what MCP is supposed to do (and not supposed to do).</description>
      <guid>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2025/06/05/mcp-resources</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is it hard to evaluate GenAI applications? | Random Walk</title>
      <link>https://andreagao.com/posts/genai-evaluation-challenge/</link>
      <description>TL;DR
If you don’t have time to read the whole article, the following four takeaways are a concise version. You can navigate to the corresponding section in the article for details.

Lack of framework: A GenAI application is not a GenAI foundation model; different frameworks are required to evaluate them. There may be a lack of clarity on the difference between the two tasks.
Unstructured data: The unstructured output of a GenAI application makes evaluation more difficult than a traditional ML system.
Foundation model unpredictability: GenAI foundation model usually introduces extra unpredictability into the evaluation process.
Longer and more costly iteration: GenAI application evaluation is expensive and time consuming, because building evaluation dataset and running tests on GenAI application require more resources.

Introduction
I have spent the last two and a half years listening to what businesses want from GenAI, building GenAI applications, and delivering value from the applications. It has been an interesting journey, as I realized the advent of ChatGPT constitutes a paradigm shift for ML/AI practitioners like me. I started to believe that GenAI would change our lives, similar to personal computers in the 90s or the modern search engine in the 2000s.</description>
      <guid>https://andreagao.com/posts/genai-evaluation-challenge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another Dating App (some ideas)</title>
      <link>https://nandinfinitum.com/posts/yada-ideas/</link>
      <description>Ramblings on a new kind of dating app</description>
      <guid>https://nandinfinitum.com/posts/yada-ideas/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tip: Put your Rails app on a SQL query diet</title>
      <link>https://andyatkinson.com/tip-track-sql-queries-quantity-ruby-rails-postgresql</link>
      <description>Introduction Much of the time taken processing HTTP requests in web apps is SQL queries. To minimize that, we want to avoid unnecessary and duplicate queries, and generally perform as few queries as possible.</description>
      <guid>https://andyatkinson.com/tip-track-sql-queries-quantity-ruby-rails-postgresql</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working on the plumbing in a small web community :: Sacha Chua</title>
      <link>https://sachachua.com/blog/2025/05/working-on-the-plumbing-in-a-small-web-community/</link>
      <description>The IndieWeb Carnival prompt for May is small web
communities. I've been exploring some thoughts on
how a little effort goes a long way to connecting
a community. Sometimes I think of it as working on
the plumbing so that ideas can flow more smoothly.
It feels a little different from the direct
contribution of knowledge or ideas. I also want to
connect with other people who do this kind of
thing.</description>
      <guid>https://sachachua.com/blog/2025/05/working-on-the-plumbing-in-a-small-web-community/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing is fun again (with LLMs)</title>
      <link>https://misfra.me/2025/writing-is-fun-again-with-llms/</link>
      <description>After I started FunnelStory, I just stopped writing. As a founder, you always have a list of ten other things that need to get done, and writing never felt like the most important one. It took up too much time. Ever since I started using LLMs for writing, though, I’ve found a flow that works. It’s becoming fun, and I’m now writing more.</description>
      <guid>https://misfra.me/2025/writing-is-fun-again-with-llms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A bored engineer's personal website</title>
      <link>https://elianrieza.dev/posts/lessons-from-a-FAT-god</link>
      <description>A place to ramble about my electrical engineering classes, personal hardware projects and research notes.</description>
      <guid>https://elianrieza.dev/posts/lessons-from-a-FAT-god</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly efficient matrix transpose in Mojo 🔥</title>
      <link>https://veitner.bearblog.dev/highly-efficient-matrix-transpose-in-mojo/</link>
      <description>In this blogpost I will step by step show you how to implement a highly efficient transpose kernel for the  architecture using Mojo.
The best kernel archive...</description>
      <guid>https://veitner.bearblog.dev/highly-efficient-matrix-transpose-in-mojo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>