<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Old Books Smell So Good?</title>
      <link>https://scienceswitch.com/2023/08/19/why-do-old-books-smell-so-good/</link>
      <description>The distinctive scent of old books comes from volatile organic compounds released as the materials decay over time. Scientists analyze these chemical clues to reveal secrets about a historical tome…</description>
      <author> (Author: ScienceSwitch)</author>
      <guid>https://scienceswitch.com/2023/08/19/why-do-old-books-smell-so-good/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - leejet/stable-diffusion.cpp: Stable Diffusion in pure C/C++</title>
      <link>https://github.com/leejet/stable-diffusion.cpp</link>
      <description>Stable Diffusion in pure C/C++. Contribute to leejet/stable-diffusion.cpp development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (leejet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/leejet/stable-diffusion.cpp</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 23:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hahaha we live in hell</title>
      <link>https://cohost.org/cathoderaydude/post/2521077-hahaha-we-live-in-he</link>
      <description>sitting in my car in a Seattle parking lot. there&amp;#39;s a knock on my window. it&amp;#39;s an old lady, who asks me &amp;quot;how do we pay for parking?&amp;quot;

----------------------------------------

she&amp;#39;s taking her husband to the hospital to see his doctor, but there&amp;#39;s a massive road project that has cut off access for months, no end in sight, so she&amp;#39;s parked a few blocks away. almost every parking lot in town removed their pay stations years ago. she has a smartphone but no idea how to handle this situation.

she never would have figured it out. her words, and I don&amp;#39;t doubt her.

the lot has three signs hung up with instructions on how to pay, because every single lot in town supports one to five different competing parking lot apps. there&amp;#39;s one sign that says you can use Park Mobile, and gives a lot ID, and then on another wall there&amp;#39;s a sign that says you can use PayByPhone, with a different lot ID, and then there&amp;#39;s a huge sign with a QR code that encourages you to Scan Here To Park, as if it&amp;#39;s the official primary method for doing so. It is not, it&amp;#39;s just another app.

I&amp;#39;ve scanned these before and gotten an &amp;quot;Instant App.&amp;quot; I figure this is minimal friction for this person, so I suggest she do so. she pulls up a QR Scanner app - either because she&amp;#39;s been bamboozled into believing that&amp;#39;s the only way to get QR support, or because her particular Android phone actually does not have it built into the camera for God knows what reason; I didn&amp;#39;t have time to figure out which.

at first she struggles to figure out how to change cameras, but this turns out to be only because she&amp;#39;s used to every camera app opening with the front facing selected by default; it has actually selected the rear camera, so I help her get it aimed right, and it goes bleep, and then... pops up an ad. i have to stop her before she hits open on whatever sludge is trying to put itself on her device

then we get a screen with 30 different elements on it describing different qualities of the QR code. the most prominent is a &amp;quot;Search The Web&amp;quot; button, which would have dumped the scanned URL into Google for some reason and produced irrelevant results; i have to direct her to tap the tiny blue link.

that link opens Instant App. Google play prints a huge permissions message; I direct her to accept it. it installs a 16mb app; so what was the point of Instant here, exactly?

well, that&amp;#39;s moot anyway, because as soon as it opens, it asks for permission, and then simply installs the normal version of the app, 24mb.

we get into that. it asks for the street address of the lot. I have never seen this information printed on any parking lot in my life. it suggests several &amp;quot;nearby&amp;quot; options; they are actually half a mile away.

unable to figure this conundrum out even for myself, i sigh and walk her through installing Park Mobile, which I know works. i help her find the lot ID. it asks for duration. she picks two hours. it asks for payment. she gets out her CC and types in the info.

proceeding to checkout, it then... selects google pay. even though she just put in a CC. she hits proceed, and i go &amp;quot;is that the right card?&amp;quot; and she double takes and goes &amp;quot;...no.&amp;quot; i maybe just saved this woman from losing $30 in overdrafts.

I direct her to tap the payment options field. nothing. i sigh. &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m sorry, it looks like you have to tap that tiny pencil icon in the CORNER of the field.&amp;quot; yep. finally she&amp;#39;s able to select her credit card. she hits proceed.

it now pops up the duration selector again. what???? why????? it&amp;#39;s back at the default of 1 hour, and she tries to pick two again, but it just won&amp;#39;t do it. I happen to know this UI pretty well, so I know that if parking time was actually limited to 1 hour, it wouldn&amp;#39;t show the option at all. This is just completely glitched out.

with no other options, she just picks one hour, and successfully pays. we both breathe a sigh of relief, and I advise her that if she needs more time, she should be able to just tap a button in the app to extend her parking. I really hope it actually works like I described.

throughout all this we had to grant Location permissions at least three times, and each time you have to decide between three options, none of which are &amp;quot;Yes.&amp;quot; the one you want is &amp;quot;while the app is open&amp;quot; but there is no way to know this, and nobody alive has ever picked either of the other options. nobody would.

i have struggled to write an ending to this post three times. words genuinely fail me.</description>
      <author> (https://cohost.org/cathoderaydude)</author>
      <guid>https://cohost.org/cathoderaydude/post/2521077-hahaha-we-live-in-he</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 22:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So, your friend has a startup idea, huh?</title>
      <link>https://kevinlestarge.com/2023/08/14/so-your-friend-has-a-startup-idea-huh/</link>
      <description>The Scenario If you are a software engineer, then the following scenario inevitably happens to you: Your friend (or relative, neighbor, acquaintance, etc) learns you are a software engineer. She te…</description>
      <author> (Kevin LeStarge)</author>
      <guid>https://kevinlestarge.com/2023/08/14/so-your-friend-has-a-startup-idea-huh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precision and Recall are just filtered accuracies</title>
      <link>https://shubhanshu.com/blog/accuracy-precision-recall.html#accuracy-precision-recall?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</link>
      <description>In this post I will show how precision and recall are related to accuracy and how they can be thought of as filtered versions of accuracy. Accuracy&amp;#182;Accuracy is a fundamental concept in evaluating every day systems. In simple terms, accuracy is defined as proportion of times the predictions of our system matched the true outcome (assuming the true outcome exists). For this post lets follow the scikit-learn convention and define y_true</description>
      <author> (https://shubhanshu.com/blog/author/shubhanshu-mishra.html)</author>
      <guid>https://shubhanshu.com/blog/accuracy-precision-recall.html#accuracy-precision-recall?utm_source=hnblogs.substack.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a USB Mute Button for Online Meetings - ClickedyClick</title>
      <link>https://gergely.imreh.net/blog/2023/08/making-a-usb-mute-button-for-online-meetings/</link>
      <description>Since Google Meet teases us to add a USB device to controll calls, let&amp;#39;s learn how to teach an Arduino clone to act like a phone mute button, and thus ultimately being capable to act like an infinite variety of peripheral devices.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/gergely.imreh)</author>
      <guid>https://gergely.imreh.net/blog/2023/08/making-a-usb-mute-button-for-online-meetings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s build a website using XML!</title>
      <link>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2023/08/lets-build-a-website-using-xml/</link>
      <description>It is 2023. XHTML is dead and buried. HTML is a &amp;quot;living standard&amp;quot; with billions of users. So what kind of idiot would want to build a website using XML? Me. I am that idiot. Last year, I launched a &amp;quot;web page&amp;quot; which didn&amp;#39;t use HTML. Called, appropriately enough, &amp;quot;YOU DON&amp;#39;T NEED HTML!&amp;quot; That (ab)used [...]</description>
      <author> (https://shkspr.mobi/blog/author/admin/)</author>
      <guid>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2023/08/lets-build-a-website-using-xml/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Conference Organisers Everywhere… – Arun Raghavan</title>
      <link>https://arunraghavan.net/2023/08/to-conference-organisers-everywhere/</link>
      <description>(well, not exactly everywhere …)</description>
      <author> (Arun)</author>
      <guid>https://arunraghavan.net/2023/08/to-conference-organisers-everywhere/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ninx | Blog</title>
      <link>https://ninx.xyz/blog/dont-be-yourself</link>
      <description>Added on 1/8/2023, Written by Lubwama Abdul Muswawir</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ninx.xyz/blog/dont-be-yourself</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Visual Database Query Plans from a CLI</title>
      <link>https://davidgomes.com/analyzing-visual-query-plans-from-a-cli/</link>
      <description>tl;dr: we’ve created new SQL commands ( SHOW PROFILE UI, EXPLAIN UI and SHOW PLAN UI) that allow developers to more easily visualize their SingleStoreDB query plans. It’s the little things!

I recently tried to define Database Developer Experience, which is where I’ve been spending most of</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidgomes.com/analyzing-visual-query-plans-from-a-cli/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scourge of 00UB | Gavin D. Howard</title>
      <link>https://gavinhoward.com/2023/08/the-scourge-of-00ub/</link>
      <description>Compiler authors claim that the possibility of UB is a license to kill. They are not James Bond.</description>
      <author> (Compiler Author vs. Language User)</author>
      <guid>https://gavinhoward.com/2023/08/the-scourge-of-00ub/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Matters</title>
      <link>https://martinrue.com/nothing-matters/</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s far too easy to be passive and experience life as the default, but it&amp;#39;s clear to me that it works the other way around.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martinrue.com/nothing-matters/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2022 17.7 with .NET and C++ Development Features, Performance Improvements, and More </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/08/visual-studio-2022/</link>
      <description>Visual Studio 2022 17.7 is now generally available. It brings plenty of features and improvements to create a high-level developer experience, based on community feedback. There are new features within .NET and C++ development as well as these ones that improve overall performance. The latest version is available for download.</description>
      <author> (Robert Krzaczyński
                
            
            
        Software EngineerFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/08/visual-studio-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 18:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Chaos Testing? #shorts #microservices</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=NNNfED-9G7Q</link>
      <description>What is Chaos Testing? #shortsSupport me on Patreon to access the source code:https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawandLet us connect:&amp;#127757;  My website  - https://m...</description>
      <author> (SoftwaretestingbyMKT
  
  
  
    SoftwaretestingbyMKT
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=NNNfED-9G7Q</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 17:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful UI Controls for .NET MAUI with Telerik UI</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DzD0ucPldeM</link>
      <description>Becky is joined by Sam Basu from Progress to show off the latest controls in Telerik UI for .NET MAUI! See how to build beautiful apps with their lovely cont...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=DzD0ucPldeM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 12:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testcontainers For Easy Integration Testing In .NET #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=nDx0NqFoOoY</link>
      <description>&amp;#128204; Check out my Pragmatic Clean Architecture course: https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/pragmatic-clean-architecture&amp;#128640; Join 770+ engineers in my  Patreon commun...</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=nDx0NqFoOoY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 12:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Solve the HTTP Error 500.31 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/aspnetcore-solve-http-error-500-31-failed-to-load-runtime-error/</link>
      <description>This article explores how to diagnose and solve the HTTP Error 500.31 - Failed to Load ASP.NET Core Runtime Error</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/aspnetcore-solve-http-error-500-31-failed-to-load-runtime-error/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 09:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Architecture | Communication patterns inside a Modular-Monolith</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XdpNXGqny9c</link>
      <description>0:00 Introduction1:28 Async communication3:30 RabbitMq as message broker6:10 Types of Exchanges7:05 RabbitMq setup9:41 Vertical slices setup12:34 How it all ...</description>
      <author> (Learnit Training
  
  
  
    Learnit Training
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XdpNXGqny9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 08:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 11 (Complete C# Quick Reference) • Ben Bowen&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://benbowen.blog/post/two_decades_of_csharp_vii/</link>
      <description>Ben Bowen&amp;#39;s Software Blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://benbowen.blog/post/two_decades_of_csharp_vii/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 05:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Smart Home - Part 13 Wall Mounted Dashboards | LINQ to Fail</title>
      <link>https://www.aaron-powell.com/posts/2023-08-19-building-a-smart-home---part-13-wall-mounted-dashboards/</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s take our smart home to the next level with a wall mounted dashboard!</description>
      <author> (Aaron Powell)</author>
      <guid>https://www.aaron-powell.com/posts/2023-08-19-building-a-smart-home---part-13-wall-mounted-dashboards/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Rate Limiting Use Cases In .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/advanced-rate-limiting-use-cases-in-dotnet</link>
      <description> Rate limiting is about restricting the number of requests to your application. It&amp;#39;s usually applied within a specific time window or based on some other criteria.
Rate limiting is practical for a few reasons: - Improves security - Guards against DDoS attacks - Prevents overloading of application servers - Reduces costs by preventing unnecessary resource consumption
But you need to know how to implement it correctly, or you could grind your system to a halt.
In this week&amp;#39;s newsletter I&amp;#39;ll teach you: - How to rate limit users by IP address - How to rate limit users by their identity - How to apply rate limiting on the reverse proxy
So let&amp;#39;s dive in.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/advanced-rate-limiting-use-cases-in-dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 01:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>