<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Three major networks devoted a full five minutes to Afghanistan in 2020 – Responsible Statecraft</title>
      <link>https://responsiblestatecraft.org/2021/08/20/three-major-networks-devoted-a-full-five-minutes-to-afghanistan-in-2020/</link>
      <description>It should be no surprise then, that Americans are shocked at the images of violence and the grim political situation on the ground today.</description>
      <author> (Written by 
Jim Lobe 







 Share	


 Copy	

 Print)</author>
      <guid>https://responsiblestatecraft.org/2021/08/20/three-major-networks-devoted-a-full-five-minutes-to-afghanistan-in-2020/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 23:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I switched from macOS to Linux after 15 years of Apple</title>
      <link>https://markosaric.com/linux/</link>
      <description>After using Macs for fifteen years, I switched to Linux as my main operating system and I’m enjoying it. Here’s an introduction to Linux that may help you too.</description>
      <author> (By Marko Saric)</author>
      <guid>https://markosaric.com/linux/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 23:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why we are in a speculative bubble</title>
      <link>https://huijzer.xyz/posts/bubble/</link>
      <description>The news is full of headlines such as &amp;quot;Why The Global Economy is Recovering Faster Than Expected&amp;quot; (Harvard Business Review, October 2020). and &amp;quot;Dutch Economy Grows Again, Second Corona Low is Over&amp;quot; (NOS, August 2021 (in Dutch)). It completely baffles me how these articles overlook a simple explanation from Warren Buffet and Charlie Munger: we are in a massive speculative bubble.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://huijzer.xyz/posts/bubble/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great hackers are fearless - Blog by Amir Bolous</title>
      <link>https://amirbolous.com/posts/hackers/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve realized that being a world-class engineer or hacker (whatever that means) is as much about virtues such as honesty, integrity, and bravery as it is about raw-intellect.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://amirbolous.com/posts/hackers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lenovo IdeaPad Flex 5</title>
      <link>https://taoofmac.com/space/blog/2021/08/26/1400</link>
      <description>This is going to be another non-Apple post, but for a good reason: As I wrote about the other day, my lovely, svelte and ultralight E111 die...</description>
      <author> (Rui Carmo)</author>
      <guid>https://taoofmac.com/space/blog/2021/08/26/1400</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s not about the rock | Blog of Christian Felde</title>
      <link>https://blog.cfelde.com/2021/08/its-not-about-the-rock/</link>
      <description>A few days ago someone allegedly paid $1.3 million for a rock. It’s not even a real rock, or a picture of a real rock. And the underlying rock contract doesn’t even follow the NFT standard, as that was established in 2018, after this contract was deployed. But it’s not about the rock, and we’re… Continue reading It’s not about the rock</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cfelde.com/2021/08/its-not-about-the-rock/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Observed Deaths</title>
      <link>https://mcculley.github.io/VisualizingObservedDeaths/</link>
      <description>This is a visualization, using polar coordinates, of the total observed deaths for every week using data published by
            
                CDC
            .</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mcculley.github.io/VisualizingObservedDeaths/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Clock: Solar &amp;#183; James Wilson</title>
      <link>https://jmw.name/projects/linear-clock/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jmw.name/projects/linear-clock/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregatable Distributed Key Generation</title>
      <link>https://www.benthamsgaze.org/2021/03/24/aggregatable-distributed-key-generation/</link>
      <description>We present our work on designing an aggregatable distributed key generation algorithm, which will appear at Eurocrypt 2021.&amp;#160; This is joint work with Kobi Gurkan, Philipp Jovanovic, Mary Maller, Sarah Meiklejohn, Gilad Stern, and Alin Tomescu.
What is a Distributed Key Generation Algorithm?
Ever he</description>
      <author> (Sarah Meiklejohn)</author>
      <guid>https://www.benthamsgaze.org/2021/03/24/aggregatable-distributed-key-generation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brit says sorry after waving around nonce patent and leaning on sites to cough up</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2021/08/26/datawing_csp_patent_claims/</link>
      <description>Using that CSP 2.0 feature? You may have received a worrying missive</description>
      <author> (Gareth Corfield
            Thu&amp;#160;26&amp;#160;Aug&amp;#160;2021 // 11:23&amp;#160;UTC)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2021/08/26/datawing_csp_patent_claims/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 21:05:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are hyperlinks blue? | The Mozilla Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/deep-dives/why-are-hyperlinks-blue/</link>
      <description>The internet has ingrained itself into every aspect of our lives, but there’s one aspect of the digital world that I bet you take for granted. Did you ev</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.mozilla.org/en/internet-culture/deep-dives/why-are-hyperlinks-blue/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 20:06:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>there is no such thing as a “glibc based alpine image” – Ariadne&amp;#39;s Space</title>
      <link>https://ariadne.space/2021/08/26/there-is-no-such-thing-as-a-glibc-based-alpine-image/</link>
      <description>For whatever reason, the alpine-glibc project is apparently being used in production.&amp;#160; Worse yet, some are led to believe that Alpine officially supports or at least approves of its usage.&amp;#160; For the reasons I am about to outline, we don’t.&amp;#160; I have also proposed an update to Alpine which will block the installation of the glibc packages produced by the alpine-glibc project, and have referred acceptance of that update to the TSC to determine if we actually want to put our foot down or not.&amp;#160; I have additionally suggested that the TSC may wish to have the Alpine Council reach out to the alpine-glibc project to find a solution which appropriately communicates that the project is not supported in any way by Alpine.&amp;#160; It should be hopefully clear that there is no such thing as a “glibc based alpine image” because Alpine does not use glibc, it uses musl.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ariadne.space/2021/08/26/there-is-no-such-thing-as-a-glibc-based-alpine-image/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 19:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot Security Study: &amp;#39;Developers Should Remain Awake&amp;#39; in View of 40% Bad Code Rate -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/08/26/github-copilot-security.aspx</link>
      <description>&amp;#39;Developers should remain vigilant (&amp;#39;awake&amp;#39;) when using Copilot as a co-pilot.&amp;#39;</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel08/26/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/08/26/github-copilot-security.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 19:06:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent changes to Western Digital’s budget SSD may lower speeds by up to 50%</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/08/silent-changes-to-western-digitals-budget-ssd-may-lower-speeds-by-up-to-50/</link>
      <description>Most people wouldn&amp;#39;t notice most of the time, but that doesn&amp;#39;t make it OK.</description>
      <author> (Andrew Cunningham
    -  8/26/2021, 3:30 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/08/silent-changes-to-western-digitals-budget-ssd-may-lower-speeds-by-up-to-50/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 18:06:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Dean Guida on the Future of .NET Components - Episode 154</title>
      <link>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/dean-guida-on-the-future-of-net-components-episode-154</link>
      <description>Joining Jeffrey this week is the CEO and founder of Infragistics, Dean Guida! Infragistics is the world leader in user interface development tools and experts in User-Centered Design; empowering you to build and style immersive user experiences and rich data visualization in line with business applications across all platforms. &amp;amp;nbsp; Dean Guida shares his insights on the future of .NET components; lessons he has learned having run a software company for over 30 years; his top recommendations when it comes to managing software teams, DevOps toolchains, preparing for the release of .NET 6, server-side vs. Web Assembly, what .NET developers should be doing today for full system testing, and more! He also gives advice to aspiring entrepreneurial software engineers, an overview of Infragistics’ tools, and what to be looking out for as a software developer today. &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [:14] About The Azure DevOps Podcast, Clear Measure, and Jeffrey’s offer to speak at virtual user groups. [1:24] Jeffrey is looking to hire an apprentice! If you, or anyone you know, loves to code and wants to pursue software engineering, apply today! [2:13] Be sure to check out the new video podcast, Architect Tips. [2:17] About today’s episode with Dean Guida. [2:25] Jeffrey welcomes Dean to the show. [2:33] What got Dean into software development, the journey of his career, and how he came to create his company, Infragistics. [5:01] How many engineers do they have on staff at Infragistics? [5:09] Dean’s insights on managing software teams. [6:08] Dean’s perspective on cutting the scope vs. shifting the date. [7:25] Dean’s DevOps toolchain of choice. [8:25] Dean’s opinion on the adoption of GitHub Actions, Azure Pipelines, and Team City. [9:28] Dean’s vision for the .NET 6 release and his team’s strategy regarding it. [12:57] Dean’s recommended path for the teams where developers are asked to lay things out and do not have a designer. [14:00] Do most developers just need applications that are completely unique or should they be attaching themselves to certain UI framework and worrying about customization less? [15:58] Why Blazor is going to work so much better with .NET 6 than it has with .NET 5? [16:30] Dean’s take on server-side and Web Assembly. [17:22] A word from Azure DevOps Podcast’s sponsor: Clear Measure. [17:53] What would it take for web applications developers to make Blazor their framework of choice? [19:22] What should .NET developers be doing today for full system testing when they need to go top-down, through the user interface? [22:00] Dean’s vision for the intersection of Digital Workforce and application developers. [26:12] The tech stack behind Slingshot that puts it ahead of .NET 6 and MAUI. [27:28] Is MAUI going to have a huge refactoring or are there gaps in MAUI that Slingshot can fill? [29:08] About the current public preview of Slingshot on Infragistics of components for MAUI. [29:28] Dean’s take on whether developers will begin to create C# smartphone apps on .NET 6 if they haven’t before? [30:40] Having run a software company for over 30 years, Dean shares some of the important lessons he has learned and gives advice to aspiring software engineers. [33:09] Jeffrey thanks Dean for joining the podcast! &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:  — New video podcast!   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!  — Click here to download the .NET DevOps for Azure ebook!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!                  &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/dean-guida-on-the-future-of-net-components-episode-154</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 18:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux in a Pixel Shader - A RISC-V Emulator for VRChat</title>
      <link>https://blog.pimaker.at/texts/rvc1/</link>
      <description>Linux in a Pixel Shader - A RISC-V Emulator for VRChat</description>
      <author> (_pi_)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.pimaker.at/texts/rvc1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 17:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Combat Playtest 04SEP21</title>
      <link>https://forum.ageofascent.com/t/team-combat-playtest-04sep21/943</link>
      <description>Hey everyone,  We will be giving you more detail in the next few days on this upcoming playtest.  Look forward to seeing you there!  Best,  The AoA Team</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://forum.ageofascent.com/t/team-combat-playtest-04sep21/943</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 17:06:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s new in C# 10.0 - C# Guide</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/csharp/whats-new/csharp-10?WT.mc_id=onedevquestion-c9-dotnet6</link>
      <description>Get an overview of the new features available in C# 10.0.</description>
      <author> (BillWagner)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/csharp/whats-new/csharp-10?WT.mc_id=onedevquestion-c9-dotnet6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 16:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysts: Google to pay Apple $15 billion to remain default Safari search engine in 2021</title>
      <link>https://9to5mac.com/2021/08/25/analysts-google-to-pay-apple-15-billion-to-remain-default-safari-search-engine-in-2021/</link>
      <description>It’s long been known that Google pays Apple a hefty sum every year to ensure that it remains the default search engine on iPhone, iPad, and Mac. Now, a new report from analysts at Bernstein suggests that the payment from Google to Apple may reach $15 billion in 2021, up from $10 billion in 2020. […]</description>
      <author> (Chance Miller)</author>
      <guid>https://9to5mac.com/2021/08/25/analysts-google-to-pay-apple-15-billion-to-remain-default-safari-search-engine-in-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 16:05:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaner, more elegant, and harder to recognize</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20050114-00/?p=36693</link>
      <description>It appears that some people interpreted the title of one of my rants from many months ago, “Cleaner, more elegant, and wrong”, to be a reference to exceptions in general. (See bibliography reference [35]; observe that the citer even changed the title of my article for me!)  The title of the article was a reference to a specific code snippet that I copied from a book,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20050114-00/?p=36693</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:53:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaner, more elegant, and wrong</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20040422-00/?p=39683</link>
      <description>Just because you can’t see the error path doesn’t mean it doesn’t exist.  Here’s a snippet from a book on C# programming, taken from the chapter on how great exceptions are.  try {  AccessDatabase accessDb = new AccessDatabase();  accessDb.GenerateDatabase(); } catch (Exception e) {  // Inspect caught exception } public void GenerateDatabase() {  CreatePhysicalDatabase();</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20040422-00/?p=39683</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:53:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error Handling — Problem Overview</title>
      <link>https://go.googlesource.com/proposal/+/master/design/go2draft-error-handling-overview.md</link>
      <description>Russ CoxAugust 27, 2018</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://go.googlesource.com/proposal/+/master/design/go2draft-error-handling-overview.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:34:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic Governance - Law Project</title>
      <link>https://www.arcticgovernance.org/</link>
      <description>Arctic Governance Welcome to the online referral portal for professionals in law and government of the Arctic Governance. Get the right assistance with all legal matters and find the right information for public and personal matters. LEARN MORE 1000 + Trusted Clients $ 1000 Recovered for our clients 1 % […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.arcticgovernance.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In C#, how do I get the descriptive text for an HRESULT?</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210826-00/?p=105609</link>
      <description>Suppose your C# code manages to find in its hands a COM HRESULT value. How do you convert that to a descriptive string? One idea is to p/invoke to the Format&amp;#173;Message function, but that’s awfully cumbersome. Maybe we can live off the land.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210826-00/?p=105609</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pin, Unpin, and why Rust needs them</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/pin-and-unpin-in-rust/</link>
      <description>Using async Rust libraries is usually easy. It&amp;#39;s just like using normal Rust code, with a little async or .await here and there. But writing your own async libraries can be hard.</description>
      <author> (Adam Chalmers)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/pin-and-unpin-in-rust/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converting PFX format to PEM via OpenSSL programmatically</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/194625-C/converting-pfx-format-to-pem-via-openssl-programmatically?Key=37b4adff-89e1-4cb4-9553-a0fe80544dd3</link>
      <description>I run into a task that I needed to do in Go, given a PFX file, I needed to get a tls.X509KeyPair from that. However, Go doesn’t have support for PFX. RavenDB...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/194625-C/converting-pfx-format-to-pem-via-openssl-programmatically?Key=37b4adff-89e1-4cb4-9553-a0fe80544dd3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>r/ThatsInsane - almost all of the top subreddits are moderated by the same people</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ThatsInsane/comments/pbloje/almost_all_of_the_top_subreddits_are_moderated_by/</link>
      <description>12,576 votes and 1,122 comments so far on Reddit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/ThatsInsane/comments/pbloje/almost_all_of_the_top_subreddits_are_moderated_by/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:05:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSMC hikes chip prices up to 20% amid supply shortage</title>
      <link>https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Tech/Semiconductors/TSMC-hikes-chip-prices-up-to-20-amid-supply-shortage</link>
      <description>Taiwanese company faces earnings pressure with plans for overseas plants</description>
      <author> (YU NAKAMURA, Nikkei staff writer)</author>
      <guid>https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Tech/Semiconductors/TSMC-hikes-chip-prices-up-to-20-amid-supply-shortage</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:05:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valneva and Pfizer Announce Initiation of Phase 2 Study for Lyme Disease Vaccine Candidate</title>
      <link>https://www.pfizer.com/news/press-release/press-release-detail/valneva-and-pfizer-announce-initiation-phase-2-study-lyme</link>
      <description>Saint-Herblain (France) and New York, NY, March 8, 2021 – Valneva SE (“Valneva”), a specialty vaccine company focused on prevention of diseases with major unmet needs, and Pfizer Inc. (NYSE: PFE) today announced initiation of study VLA15-221. The VLA15-221 study builds on previous positive Phase 2 studies, incorporates new dose regimens and is anticipated to be the final Phase 2 study readout before a decision to progress into pivotal Phase 3 studies.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pfizer.com/news/press-release/press-release-detail/valneva-and-pfizer-announce-initiation-phase-2-study-lyme</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 14:06:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iiSM.org</title>
      <link>https://iism.org/article/why-are-ceos-failing-software-engineers-56</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iism.org/article/why-are-ceos-failing-software-engineers-56</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 12:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web cookie requests and red tape to be scrapped in post-Brexit data revolution</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2021/08/25/web-cookie-requests-red-tape-scrapped-post-brexit-data-revolution/#Echobox=1629958035</link>
      <description>Government set to overhaul key parts of the EU&amp;#39;s data laws under proposals to turbocharge the UK&amp;#39;s digital economy</description>
      <author> (By
Harry Yorke, 

Whitehall Editor



25 August 2021 • 9:30pm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2021/08/25/web-cookie-requests-red-tape-scrapped-post-brexit-data-revolution/#Echobox=1629958035</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 12:05:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor DataGrid Meets Blazor Report Viewer</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/blazor-datagrid-meets-blazor-report-viewer</link>
      <description>We have combined two great tools to show how they can work together. Let users adapt the dataset through Blazor UI Grid and base reports on that same dataset</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/blazor-datagrid-meets-blazor-report-viewer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 08:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Breach Release - Indianapolis, IN , Fort Wayne, IN, and Nashville, TN</title>
      <link>https://www.imavex.com/breach-information/</link>
      <description>Contact Imavex. Imavex has 3 locations in the midwest servicing Indianapolis, IN, Fort Wayne, IN and Nashville, TN.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.imavex.com/breach-information/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 07:06:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-08-26</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/08/app-developer-links-2021-08-26/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/08/app-developer-links-2021-08-26/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 07:06:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Testers Add Value</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-testers-add-value</link>
      <description>If we have to do testing (and we do) then we should be turning it into something that our users will actually find valuable. Here’s how.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-testers-add-value</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:06:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sort of Permutation</title>
      <link>https://kevlinhenney.medium.com/a-sort-of-permutation-768c1a7e029b</link>
      <description>Practical lessons in the impractical permutation sort</description>
      <author> (https://kevlinhenney.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://kevlinhenney.medium.com/a-sort-of-permutation-768c1a7e029b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It looks like you’re using Visual Studio. Would you like help?</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/it-looks-like-youre-using-visual-studio-would-you-like-help/</link>
      <description>We launched a new feature in Visual Studio 2022 Preview 2 that shows tips and tricks during Visual Studio updates/installation.</description>
      <author> (Misty Hays)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/it-looks-like-youre-using-visual-studio-would-you-like-help/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My MacBook Pro had over 10,000 USD in repairs</title>
      <link>https://pqvst.com/2021/08/24/my-macbook-pro/</link>
      <description>I treat my MacBook Pro laptop very well. It barely has a scratch and it’s never had any accidental drops or damage. Even so, my 4 years of owning it has resulted in:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pqvst.com/2021/08/24/my-macbook-pro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy birthday – 30 Years of Linux | Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://ubuntu.com/blog/happy-birthday-30-years-of-linux</link>
      <description>Won’t be big Thirty years ago today, Linus Torvalds announced his free operating system to the world. As with many of the world’s greatest, Linux had humble beginnings as a very small pet project. The GNU was working on an ambitious free, public domain operating system but the project had been delayed, and enthusiasts were  […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ubuntu.com/blog/happy-birthday-30-years-of-linux</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Tests With ASP.NET Core, XUnit, and Playwright</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/end-to-end-test-with-aspnet-core-xunit-and-playwright</link>
      <description>Write end-to-end tests for ASP.NET Core apps using XUnit and Playwright</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/end-to-end-test-with-aspnet-core-xunit-and-playwright</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:05:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Released: Microsoft.Data.SqlClient 4.0 Preview 1</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server/released-microsoft-data-sqlclient-4-0-preview-1/ba-p/2685322</link>
      <description>Microsoft.Data.SqlClient 4.0 Preview 1 has been released. This release contains improvements and updates to the Microsoft.Data.SqlClient data provider for SQL Server. Our plan is to provide GA releases twice a year with two preview releases in between. This cadence should provide time for feedback a...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/343280)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server/released-microsoft-data-sqlclient-4-0-preview-1/ba-p/2685322</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:05:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tip 330 - How to use Azure API Management from VS Code</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/blog/tip330.html</link>
      <description>When you expose an API that other people use, you want full control over who uses it and how they use it. You can use Azure API Management (opens new window) for that. You import API definitions into Azure API Management and create a facade API that users communicate with. This allows you to create products (opens new window) for your API, and monitor and manage API usage and access with policies (opens new window). API Management also enables you to manage versions (opens new window) of your API. It also allows you to design the API methods (opens new window) and documentation that you expose, so that it works for your users, regardless of what the original API looks like. And you can run API Management in several usage tiers (opens new window), including a consumption tier, which is billed per execution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://microsoft.github.io/AzureTipsAndTricks/blog/tip330.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play with Proxy in Azure Function App</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/play-with-proxy-in-azure-function-app/ba-p/2614677</link>
      <description>&amp;#160; Proxy in Azure Function App&amp;#160;is often used for&amp;#160;specifying endpoints on your function app that are implemented by another resource. You can use these proxies to break a large API into multiple function apps (as in a microservice architecture), while still presenting a single API surface for clients....</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/1074444)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/play-with-proxy-in-azure-function-app/ba-p/2614677</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:05:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get A Property Name From a .NET Lambda Expression</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/get-a-property-name-from-a-dotnet-lambda-expression</link>
      <description>Learn how to use .NET lambda expressions to retrieve a PropertyInfo and property name.</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/get-a-property-name-from-a-dotnet-lambda-expression</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:05:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stripping Times from Dates in C#</title>
      <link>https://www.stevefenton.co.uk/2021/08/stripping-times-from-dates-in-c/</link>
      <description>This is a surprisingly common problem in C#, where you need to take a DateTime and strip off the “time” bit to leave you with a representation of a day. Currently, you can do it by creating a new DateTime and passing only the parts you want to keep, like year, month, and day.</description>
      <author> (Steve Fenton)</author>
      <guid>https://www.stevefenton.co.uk/2021/08/stripping-times-from-dates-in-c/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Techniques for Communicating Between Services</title>
      <link>https://ardalis.com/comparing-techniques-communicating-between-services/</link>
      <description>There are several typical ways for two services (or microservices) to communicate with one another at runtime. Compare the various techniques and patterns, and their individual pros and cons.</description>
      <author> (Ardalis)</author>
      <guid>https://ardalis.com/comparing-techniques-communicating-between-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:05:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks! vNext</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1754</link>
      <description>.NET Rocks! is a weekly talk show for anyone interested in programming on the Microsoft .NET platform. The shows range from introductory information to hardcore geekiness.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1754</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 05:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My dead dad’s journal: How I finally met a man I knew for my entire life</title>
      <link>https://www.seanblanda.com/my-dead-dads-journal-how-i-finally-met-a-man-i-knew-for-my-entire-life/</link>
      <description>For some reason, when my brother told me our dad was dead, I immediately went and listened to my voicemails. He left me silly voicemails often and I wanted to hear his voice. I came across the last voicemail he ever left me, a month before. This one wasn’t</description>
      <author> (Sean Blanda)</author>
      <guid>https://www.seanblanda.com/my-dead-dads-journal-how-i-finally-met-a-man-i-knew-for-my-entire-life/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The All-Seeing &amp;quot;i&amp;quot;: Apple Just Declared War on Your Privacy</title>
      <link>https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/all-seeing-i</link>
      <description>“Under His Eye,” she says. The right farewell. “Under His Eye,” I reply, and she gives a little nod.</description>
      <author> (Edward Snowden)</author>
      <guid>https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/all-seeing-i</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:06:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiku, Inc. has hired an existing contributor to work on Haiku full-time!</title>
      <link>https://www.haiku-os.org/news/2021-08-25_hiring_waddlesplash/</link>
      <description>Haiku, Inc. is proud to announce that we have hired existing contributor waddlesplash to work on general Haiku improvement full-time. The contract was signed on Monday, August 23, 2021 and waddlesplash plans to start work tomorrow.
In the past Haiku, …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.haiku-os.org/news/2021-08-25_hiring_waddlesplash/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:06:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure SDK: Goodbye QnA Maker, Hello AI &amp;#39;Question Answering&amp;#39; -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/08/25/azure-sdk-aug21.aspx</link>
      <description>The regular monthly update to Microsoft&amp;#39;s Azure SDK improves Cognitive Services text analytics, specifically with a new Question Answering SDK that supplants QnA Maker.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel08/25/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/08/25/azure-sdk-aug21.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 01:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Login | Microsoft Careers</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/i/us/en/job/1120170/Senior-Program-Manager</link>
      <description>This site uses cookies for analytics, personalized content and ads. By continuing to browse this site, you agree to this use.
          Learn more
         .</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/i/us/en/job/1120170/Senior-Program-Manager</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My experience dealing with Microsoft in the old Windows Phone times</title>
      <link>https://blog.kulman.sk/dealing-with-microsoft-in-wp-times/</link>
      <description>This summer marks exactly a decade since I started doing mobile apps development. My first mobile app was called MyTVShows and was released to the Windows Phone Store in summer of 2011.
The app solved a practical problem for me, keeping track of new episodes. I later rewrote the app as TvTime which was one of my most successful Windows Phone apps.

  
  
  


My times of doing Windows Phone development are long over as the platform has been dead for many years but this reminded me of all the struggles I had to deal with when interacting with the local Microsoft branch.
Disclaimer: Microsoft is a huge company so my experience is hopefully not the general experience of everyone from those times, people on all the local branches are different.
Windows Phone app competitions
In 2012 the Czech Microsoft started a competition giving every developer a Nokia Lumia 800 for publishing 3 apps to the Windows Phone Store.
The problem was the quality of those apps did not matter at all. The goal was to increases the number of the apps as much as possible, probably reaching some arbitrary number set by Redmond.

  
  
  


The Czech Windows Phone Store was flooded by crappy apps created only because of this competition, not having any real value for the user. I remember an app with one input and one button doing some kind of number conversion.
Microsoft just wanted to bump the app numbers count by any means necessary to be able to compare the Windows Phone Store to other mobile app stores.
This also reminded me that Microsoft was really bad at competitions overall, another example was destroying DVLUP after purchasing Nokia.</description>
      <author> (Igor Kulman)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.kulman.sk/dealing-with-microsoft-in-wp-times/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I use attrs instead of pydantic</title>
      <link>https://threeofwands.com/why-i-use-attrs-instead-of-pydantic/</link>
      <description>This post is an account of why I prefer using the attrs library over Pydantic. I&amp;#39;m writing it since I am often asked this question and I want to have something concrete to link to.</description>
      <author> (Tin
                    
                        More posts)</author>
      <guid>https://threeofwands.com/why-i-use-attrs-instead-of-pydantic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptography Engineer</title>
      <link>https://boards.greenhouse.io/o1labs/jobs/4023646004</link>
      <description>Remote</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://boards.greenhouse.io/o1labs/jobs/4023646004</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomadism, Mobility and Risk — Travel Writer Shaun Busuttil</title>
      <link>https://www.shaunbusuttil.com/academic-writing/2021/8/18/digital-nomadism-mobility-and-risk</link>
      <description>This article analyses the global mobility patterns of digital nomads through a Beckian model of risk. It argues that digital nomads use mobility as a hedge against the precarious (and risky) employment relations they often find themselves in. At the same time, however, these same mobility practices </description>
      <author> (Shaun Busuttil)</author>
      <guid>https://www.shaunbusuttil.com/academic-writing/2021/8/18/digital-nomadism-mobility-and-risk</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of the Desk Setup</title>
      <link>https://www.arun.is/blog/desk-setup</link>
      <description>What are the principles underlying the ideal desk setup? How do we balance great design with modern technology? Let’s plunge into my desk setup and my philosophy behind it.</description>
      <author> (Arun Venkatesan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.arun.is/blog/desk-setup</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking a closer look at lodash&amp;#39;s chain</title>
      <link>https://www.maartenhus.nl/blog/lodash-chain-vs-native-methods/</link>
      <description>Comparing lodash&amp;#39;s chain method versus the native methods of Array in JavaScript, and see how chain works under the hood.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.maartenhus.nl/blog/lodash-chain-vs-native-methods/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absurdest Academia (A ‘Darkest Dungeon’ Parody)</title>
      <link>https://bastian.rieck.me/blog/posts/2021/absurdest_academia/</link>
      <description>Staying in academia requires, among other things, a healthy dose of
humour. Its is therefore not surprising that many academical aspects are
likened to more whimsical pursuits. The great Matt Might,
for instance, has a roaringly funny series of posts, describing both the
nine kinds of students you will meet in the
classroom and
the types of reviewers you will face
in terms of characters from the game Team Fortress 2.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bastian.rieck.me/blog/posts/2021/absurdest_academia/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>