<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear Reactor Explainer | Lorenzo Venneri</title>
      <link>https://lvenneri.com/nuclear_reactor_explainer</link>
      <description>Harnessing the stored energy of heavy elements</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lvenneri.com/nuclear_reactor_explainer</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Next Bottleneck — Ethan Lalakea Alter</title>
      <link>https://www.ethanalter.com/blog/the-next-bottleneck</link>
      <description>Current and future bottlenecks, and of course, “AI”</description>
      <author> (Feb 22
            
            Written By Ethan A)</author>
      <guid>https://www.ethanalter.com/blog/the-next-bottleneck</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Learn Nix, Part 49: nix-direnv is a huge quality of life improvement</title>
      <link>https://ianthehenry.com/posts/how-to-learn-nix/nix-direnv/</link>
      <description>The reason I discovered an ancient blog post the other day was that I had something new to say about Nix for the first time in over two years.
The thing I want to say is this: nix-direnv is great. It fixes roughly every problem that I’ve had with nix-shell, and does so in a much nicer way than my previous ad-hoc solutions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ianthehenry.com/posts/how-to-learn-nix/nix-direnv/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &amp;#39;Pro&amp;#39; Paradox and The Allure of Style Over Substance</title>
      <link>https://simone.org/pro-paradox/</link>
      <description>When style trumps substance and size trumps user interest.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://simone.org/pro-paradox/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things I Used to Care About</title>
      <link>https://uptointerpretation.com/posts/things-i-used-to-care-about/</link>
      <description>Do you ever look back and marvel at how much fashion has changed? In 2016 all the cool kids were wearing selvedge jeans, Clarks desert boots or maybe Stan Smith sneakers. Oh and they were writing ES6 with React classes, CSS in JS and Redux. Y’know, the cool front-end dev kids. Now it’s all kids wearing light-washed high-waisted bell-bottom (!) jeans with some chunky sneakers, writing Solid with Tailwind and TypeScript.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://uptointerpretation.com/posts/things-i-used-to-care-about/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from my third year running a SaaS - Max Rozen</title>
      <link>https://maxrozen.com/lessons-from-my-third-year-running-a-saas</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve run this business for three years now, and I&amp;#39;m only just now starting to *get it*.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://maxrozen.com/lessons-from-my-third-year-running-a-saas</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Only Productivity Framework You Need – Monica Lim</title>
      <link>https://monicalim.co/?p=1103</link>
      <description>A mantra for some, a tattoo for others, mise-en-place literally means “put in place” in French. It is the art of prepping and arranging the ingredients and the tools before starting to cook. It’s how chefs survive and thrive in the kitchen. And it is one of the most effective productivity frameworks I’ve tried.</description>
      <author> (Name *)</author>
      <guid>https://monicalim.co/?p=1103</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The value of a PhD</title>
      <link>https://andrewpwheeler.com/2021/03/22/the-value-of-a-phd/</link>
      <description>For my current work as a data scientist, I spend most of my time writing SQL queries, generating some sort of predictive model on that data using python, and automating those data pipelines using a…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewpwheeler.com/2021/03/22/the-value-of-a-phd/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>formats</title>
      <link>https://jon.work/research/formats/</link>
      <description>Homepage of Jon Secchis</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jon.work/research/formats/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESP32 based voice assistant with wake word – Tristam</title>
      <link>https://tristam.ie/2024/1026/</link>
      <description>Last year (2023) was Home Assistant’s Year of the Voice so I thought there’d be no better way to start 2024 than by building my own Home Assistant powered smart speaker.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tristam.ie/2024/1026/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>foojay – 12 Lessons Learned From Doing The 1BRC Challenge</title>
      <link>https://foojay.io/today/12-lessons-learned-from-doing-the-one-billion-row-challenge/</link>
      <description>How fast can you process a 1 billion rows text file in Java? That&amp;#39;s the challenge that many Java developers tried to solve in January 2024.</description>
      <author> (Anthony Goubard)</author>
      <guid>https://foojay.io/today/12-lessons-learned-from-doing-the-one-billion-row-challenge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Motion Capture for Autonomous Drones</title>
      <link>https://joshuabird.com/blog/post/mocap-drones</link>
      <description>$20 system for room-scale millimeter level precision motion capture</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joshuabird.com/blog/post/mocap-drones</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Register Minimal APIs in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/automatically-register-minimal-apis-in-aspnetcore</link>
      <description>In ASP.NET Core applications using Minimal APIs, registering each API endpoint with app.MapGet, app.MapPost, etc. can introduce repetitive code. Today, I&amp;#39;ll show you how to automatically register your Minimal APIs with a simple abstraction.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/automatically-register-minimal-apis-in-aspnetcore</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers, Your Job Is Not To Write Code / Matt Hogg FYI</title>
      <link>https://matthogg.fyi/developers-your-job-is-not-to-write-code/</link>
      <description>The advice I&amp;#39;ve consistently given to developers who want to grow might seem counter-intuitive, but it&amp;#39;s always held true for me—the first step to being a great developer is recognizing that your job is not to write code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matthogg.fyi/developers-your-job-is-not-to-write-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The pitfalls of pure rationality</title>
      <link>https://bbu87.blogspot.com/2024/02/the-pitfalls-of-pure-rationality.html</link>
      <description>Being rational with regards to the surrounding natural and physical world is undeniably good for our survival. We learn the effects of touch...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bbu87.blogspot.com/2024/02/the-pitfalls-of-pure-rationality.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The trouble with transaction.atomic &amp;#183; David Seddon</title>
      <link>https://seddonym.me/2020/11/19/trouble-atomic/</link>
      <description>Something about Django has bothered me for some time. It’s the context manager at the heart of its API for handling
database transactions: django.db.transaction.atomic. It offers a neat design to help us write robust code, but also
plenty of opportunity to write programs that are not as robust as they appear. Before we look into why, here’s a
refresher on transaction.atomic.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://seddonym.me/2020/11/19/trouble-atomic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forms of life, forms of mind | Dr. Michael Levin | Some thoughts on memory, goals, and universal hacking</title>
      <link>https://thoughtforms.life/some-thoughts-on-memory-goals-and-universal-hacking/</link>
      <description>A transcript on some thoughts on memory, goals, universal hacking, and the evolution of agents.</description>
      <author> (Mike Levin)</author>
      <guid>https://thoughtforms.life/some-thoughts-on-memory-goals-and-universal-hacking/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Benzle&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://kylebenzle.com/airpure.html</link>
      <description>Big Pure has us by the balls as air pollution has become
              the world’s single biggest environmental health risk, linked to
              around 7 million deaths in 2012 according to a recent World Health
              Organisation (WHO) report. The new data further reveals a stronger
              link between, indoor and outdoor air pollution exposure and
              cardiovascular diseases, such as strokes and ischemic heart
              disease, as well as between air pollution and cancer. The role of
              air pollution in the development of respiratory diseases,
              including acute respiratory infections and chronic pulmonary
              diseases, is well known. While both indoor and outdoor pollution
              affect health, recent statistics on the impact of household indoor
              pollutants is alarming.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kylebenzle.com/airpure.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cycles all way down</title>
      <link>https://coredumped.dev/2024/02/23/cycles-all-way-down/</link>
      <description>A while ago while working on Rust-based Emacs, I was loading a new elisp file and hit a stack overflow. Digging deeper I found the issue in trying to print a cyclic list (where the tail of the list points back to previous element). I knew this was a possibility, and that at some point I would have to handle cycles.
So I quickly implemented a version of Floyd’s cycle detection algorithm (visualized here).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://coredumped.dev/2024/02/23/cycles-all-way-down/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You need more than p-values</title>
      <link>https://www.alexmolas.com/2024/02/22/ab-tests.html</link>
      <description>Explore the critical considerations and potential pitfalls of relying solely on A/B testing in making business decisions. While A/B testing is a valuable tool, this post challenges the assumption of exchangeability between past and future data, emphasizing the dynamic nature of the business environment. I propose two solutions (1) validating the exchangeability assumption through holdback groups and (2) advocating for a holistic decision-making approach that goes beyond statistical tests. Executives are urged not to blindly trust p-values, emphasizing the importance of intuition, market understanding, and forecasting in shaping successful business strategies. In conclusion, the post encourages a balanced approach, combining statistical rigor with real-world insights for effective decision-making.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.alexmolas.com/2024/02/22/ab-tests.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do literally anything - Aaron Francis</title>
      <link>https://aaronfrancis.com/2024/do-literally-anything</link>
      <description>Feeling overwhelmed? Don&amp;#39;t know where to start? Do literally anything.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aaronfrancis.com/2024/do-literally-anything</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a List of Nearly Every Minecraft Player</title>
      <link>https://matdoes.dev/minecraft-uuids</link>
      <description>I’ve recently been engaging in some tomfoolery to acquire a list of 51 million Minecraft: Java Edition player UUIDs (out of ~61 million total existing UUIDs).
This blog post will explain exactly what I did to make this list.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matdoes.dev/minecraft-uuids</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a deep learning rig | part-1</title>
      <link>https://samsja.github.io/blogs/rig/part_1/</link>
      <description>Blog post of Samsja</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://samsja.github.io/blogs/rig/part_1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OK-Robot: What Really Matters in Integrating Open-Knowledge Models for Robotics</title>
      <link>https://ok-robot.github.io/</link>
      <description>OK-Robot is an open framework for zero-shot, natural language pick-and-drop system in arbitrary homes.</description>
      <author> (*: Equal contributions, †: Equal advising)</author>
      <guid>https://ok-robot.github.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 22:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform 5.0: Elevate Your Cross-Platform .NET Development with .NET 8 | .NET Conf 2023</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EgftgnNz-lA</link>
      <description>.NET ecosystem prides itself on all the options it provides to developers. The open-source Uno Platform is yet another option you have to create cross-platfo...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=EgftgnNz-lA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Visual Studio Code for .NET MAUI Development</title>
      <link>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/02/24/using-visual-studio-code-for-dotnet-maui-development/</link>
      <description>In August 2023, Microsoft made an official announcement regarding the retirement of Visual Studio for Mac, scheduled to take place by August 31, 2024 (in another 6 months), as stated in a blog post…</description>
      <author> (By Vijay Anand E G)</author>
      <guid>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/02/24/using-visual-studio-code-for-dotnet-maui-development/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - google/gemma.cpp: lightweight, standalone C++ inference engine for Google&amp;#39;s Gemma models.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/google/gemma.cpp</link>
      <description>lightweight, standalone C++ inference engine for Google&amp;#39;s Gemma models. - google/gemma.cpp</description>
      <author> (google)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/google/gemma.cpp</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond A*: Better Planning with Transformers via Search Dynamics Bootstrapping</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2402.14083</link>
      <description>While Transformers have enabled tremendous progress in various application settings, such architectures still lag behind traditional symbolic planners for solving complex decision making tasks. In this work, we demonstrate how to train Transformers to solve complex planning tasks and present Searchformer, a Transformer model that optimally solves previously unseen Sokoban puzzles 93.7% of the time, while using up to 26.8% fewer search steps than standard $A^*$ search. Searchformer is an encoder-decoder Transformer model trained to predict the search dynamics of $A^*$. This model is then fine-tuned via expert iterations to perform fewer search steps than $A^*$ search while still generating an optimal plan. In our training method, $A^*$&amp;#39;s search dynamics are expressed as a token sequence outlining when task states are added and removed into the search tree during symbolic planning. In our ablation studies on maze navigation, we find that Searchformer significantly outperforms baselines that predict the optimal plan directly with a 5-10$	imes$ smaller model size and a 10$	imes$ smaller training dataset. We also demonstrate how Searchformer scales to larger and more complex decision making tasks like Sokoban with improved percentage of solved tasks and shortened search dynamics.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 21 Feb 2024])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2402.14083</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 14 years in the industry, I still find programming difficult</title>
      <link>https://www.piglei.com/articles/en-programming-is-still-hard-after-14-years/</link>
      <description>piglei&amp;#39;s blog</description>
      <author> (piglei,piglei2007@gmail.com)</author>
      <guid>https://www.piglei.com/articles/en-programming-is-still-hard-after-14-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 19:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrutor vs Autofac in C#: What You Need To Know</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/02/23/scrutor-vs-autofac-in-c-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <description>Scrutor vs Autofac in C#! Which one comes out on top between these two solutions for dependency injection in dotnet? See how each are used with code examples!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/02/23/scrutor-vs-autofac-in-c-what-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gotcha: Be careful how you shut down your dispatcher queues - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240223-00/?p=109438</link>
      <description>The dispatcher queue thread isn&amp;#39;t useful after it has shut down, so don&amp;#39;t try anything.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240223-00/?p=109438</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel Processor Instability Causing Oodle Decompression Failures</title>
      <link>https://www.radgametools.com/oodleintel.htm</link>
      <description>RAD Game Tools&amp;#39; web page. RAD makes Bink
Video, the Telemetry Performance Visualization System, and Oodle Data Compression - all popular video game middleware.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.radgametools.com/oodleintel.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Billion Row Challenge (1BRC) - Step-by-step from 71s to 1.7s</title>
      <link>https://questdb.io/blog/billion-row-challenge-step-by-step/</link>
      <description>I took part in the Billion Row Challenge. Enjoy a deep, step-by-step summary of how you get from a Parallel Java Streams implementation that takes 71 seconds to a super-optimized version that takes 1.7 seconds. Example code and walkthroughs included!</description>
      <author> (QuestDB)</author>
      <guid>https://questdb.io/blog/billion-row-challenge-step-by-step/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 17:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cecilifier - Learn Mono.Cecil by example</title>
      <link>https://cecilifier.me/</link>
      <description>Cecilifier is a tool aiming to make learning using Mono.Cecil easier by taking code snippets and generating Cecil APIs calls that creates an assembly equivalent to the compiled code snippet. It may also help you to learn more about MSIL (also known simply as IL).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cecilifier.me/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT vs. Advent of Code 2023 Day 22: Sand Slabs</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Yd3emlhHl2E</link>
      <description>Can ChatGPT and its Code interpreter solve a programming puzzle resembling Jenga? Let&amp;#39;s see!</description>
      <author> (Martin Zikmund
  
  
  
    Martin Zikmund
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Yd3emlhHl2E</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 14:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commits &amp;#183; sigma0-xyz/zkbitcoin</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sigma0-xyz/zkbitcoin/commits/v0.1.0</link>
      <description>zkBitcoin: zero-knowledge proofs on Bitcoin! Contribute to sigma0-xyz/zkbitcoin development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (sigma0-xyz)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sigma0-xyz/zkbitcoin/commits/v0.1.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 13:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZK Mini Summit &amp;#183; Luma</title>
      <link>https://lu.ma/ZKMiniSummit_Denver</link>
      <description>The ZK Mini Summit &amp;#128640; is gearing up to be a thrilling ride &amp;#127775;. We’ll dive deep into the innovative universe of zero-knowledge proofs (ZKPs) &amp;#129504;&amp;#128171;&amp;#160;From a whimsical zero-knowledge proofs...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lu.ma/ZKMiniSummit_Denver</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 13:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>v0.1.0 &amp;#183; sigma0-xyz/zkbitcoin &amp;#183; Discussion #44</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sigma0-xyz/zkbitcoin/discussions/44</link>
      <description>Hey &amp;#128075; This is our first release &amp;#127881; What&amp;#39;s Changed (since we came out of stealth &amp;#129399;) ci: run bitcoin core regtest node for tests by @xJonathanLEI in #17 Keepalive with Fibonacci Backoff, fault toleran...</description>
      <author> (sigma0-xyz)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sigma0-xyz/zkbitcoin/discussions/44</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 13:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Scrum and is Scrum good for startups? — todo.space blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.todo.space/2019/03/04/what-is-scrum-in-agile-and-is-scrum-good-for-startups/</link>
      <description>TLDR: No, it&amp;#39;s not lean, it&amp;#39;s not agile, and, therefore, it is very expensive, therefore, not good for startups.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.todo.space/2019/03/04/what-is-scrum-in-agile-and-is-scrum-good-for-startups/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nanoFramework: Unleashing the Power of C# in Embedded Systems and IoT with Jos&amp;#233; Sim&amp;#245;es</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=G1WOQKT6pgg</link>
      <description>Avalonia XPF This episode of The Modern .NET Show is supported, in part, by Avalonia XPF, a binary-compatible cross-platform fork of WPF, enables WPF apps to...</description>
      <author> (The No-Frauds Club
  
  
  
    The No-Frauds Club
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=G1WOQKT6pgg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Bloat in 2024</title>
      <link>https://tonsky.me/blog/js-bloat/</link>
      <description>What is the average size of JavaScript code downloaded per website? Fuck around and find out!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/nikitonsky)</author>
      <guid>https://tonsky.me/blog/js-bloat/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Oliver&amp;#39;s World</title>
      <link>https://blog.markoliver.website/Recording-Video-From-A-Nintendo-Switch</link>
      <description>Posted: 23/02/2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.markoliver.website/Recording-Video-From-A-Nintendo-Switch</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup Topic - Assessing your app&amp;#39;s Azure readiness</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=lhoNVsxRIP4</link>
      <description>Mike Rousos joins us for an update on Azure Migrate Application and Code Assessment, and how you can use it to check your scan your application&amp;#39;s .NET source...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=lhoNVsxRIP4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 08:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDXL Lightning - by fal.ai</title>
      <link>https://fastsdxl.ai/</link>
      <description>Lightning fast SDXL API demo by fal.ai</description>
      <author> (fal.ai)</author>
      <guid>https://fastsdxl.ai/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 08:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IA responsable y mecanismos de protecci&amp;#243;n</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Z4PVYfXSFuw</link>
      <description>Trataremos el tema de moda la IA con un experto en la materia como lo es Matias Cordero para adentrarnos en la IA responsable y mecanismos de protecci&amp;#243;n.Beco...</description>
      <author> (Javier Su&amp;#225;rez
  
  
  
    Javier Su&amp;#225;rez
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Z4PVYfXSFuw</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 07:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Modular Monoliths: The Goldilocks Architecture</title>
      <link>https://ardalis.com/introducing-modular-monoliths-goldilocks-architecture/</link>
      <description>This article introduces the concept of Modular Monoliths, an architectural approach that combines the simplicity of monolithic applications with the flexibility of microservices, offering a balanced solution for software development. It outlines the key characteristics, advantages, and suitable scenarios for adopting this Goldilocks architecture, providing a pragmatic path for developers and architects aiming for maintainability, simplicity, and scalability in their projects.</description>
      <author> (Ardalis)</author>
      <guid>https://ardalis.com/introducing-modular-monoliths-goldilocks-architecture/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 06:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Active Local NuGet Server</title>
      <link>https://ardalis.com/active-local-nuget-server/</link>
      <description>As I&amp;#39;m writing this the Internet is out. When that happens, it makes it very difficult to work on development projects that have NuGet dependencies, especially when it comes to adding anything new to a project. A local NuGet server that kept up-to-date with my commonly used packages would be helpful right now.</description>
      <author> (Ardalis)</author>
      <guid>https://ardalis.com/active-local-nuget-server/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 06:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing TypeScript 5.4 RC - TypeScript</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-5-4-rc/</link>
      <description>Today we’re excited to announce our Release Candidate of TypeScript 5.4! Between now and the stable release of TypeScript 5.4, we expect no further changes apart from critical bug fixes. To get started using the RC, you can get it through NuGet,</description>
      <author> (Daniel Rosenwasser)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-5-4-rc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 06:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimal APIs vs Controller APIs: SerializerOptions.WriteIndented = true</title>
      <link>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2024/02/minimal-apis-vs-controller-apis.html</link>
      <description>Another thing added in ASP.NET Core / .NET 7.0 (yeah, I know it&amp;#39;s been a   while since it was released), is the &amp;quot;ConfigureHttpJsonOptions&amp;quot; e...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jeremybytes.blogspot.com/2024/02/minimal-apis-vs-controller-apis.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 06:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The case for an application-level tracing API in .NET</title>
      <link>https://nblumhardt.com/2024/02/tracing-with-message-templates/</link>
      <description>If you want to record a log event from your application in .NET, you can do that today without a lot of noise or ceremony using Microsoft.Extensions.Logging:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nblumhardt.com/2024/02/tracing-with-message-templates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 06:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET API Middleware for common functionality [Pt 5] | Back-end Web Development w/ .NET for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2QvUwxcHCBc</link>
      <description>This video covers implementing common behavior for ASP.NET Core APIs using middlewares. Middlewares are a piece of code that can run before and after each re...</description>
      <author> (@ventoshe)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2QvUwxcHCBc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure API Center and ASP.NET Web API Integration: A Developer&amp;#39;s Guide | .NET Conf 2023</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=o4gMJfee4iA</link>
      <description>In a rapidly evolving digital landscape, the use of APIs is becoming increasingly popular. One key tool that has emerged as a game-changer is the ability to ...</description>
      <author> (@acodersjourney
          
        
        
        
        3 months ago)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=o4gMJfee4iA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Teams Toolkit in Visual Studio - Teams</title>
      <link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoftteams/platform/toolkit/toolkit-v4/install-teams-toolkit-vs?pivots=visual-studio-v17-7</link>
      <description>Learn about installation of Teams Toolkit of different versions in Visual Studio, and marketplace.</description>
      <author> (zyxiaoyuer)</author>
      <guid>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoftteams/platform/toolkit/toolkit-v4/install-teams-toolkit-vs?pivots=visual-studio-v17-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 04:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>