<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cockpit-project.org/</link>
      <description>Cockpit makes it easy to administer your GNU/Linux servers via a web browser.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cockpit-project.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 09:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers looking for mRNA were ridiculed by colleagues. Luckily, that didn’t stop them. - Macleans.ca</title>
      <link>https://www.macleans.ca/society/science/scientists-mrna-covid-vaccines/</link>
      <description>Sixty years ago, the scientists who were pioneering the technology that would make today&amp;#39;s COVID-19 vaccines possible were mocked and dismissed</description>
      <author> (By Christina Frangou
								
								 February 18, 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://www.macleans.ca/society/science/scientists-mrna-covid-vaccines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 09:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Json.NET - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/167/json.net</link>
      <description>JsonNET is a popular high-performance JSON framework for .NET. Over 100 million downloads. Used by Visual Studio, .NET, ASPNET, SignalR, Windows Azure. Most popular .NET open source library. Most downloaded nuget library.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/167/json.net</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 08:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceberger</title>
      <link>https://joshdata.me/iceberger.html</link>
      <description>Draw an iceberg and see how it will float.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joshdata.me/iceberger.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 06:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YoutubeExplode - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/230/youtubeexplode</link>
      <description>YoutubeExplode is a library that provides an interface to query metadata of YouTube videos, playlists and channels, as well as to resolve and download video streams and closed caption tracks. Behind a layer of abstraction, the library parses raw page content and uses reverse-engineered AJAX request…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/230/youtubeexplode</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 05:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Griddy | Griddy Update: Why energy prices were sky high this week | Texas Energy</title>
      <link>https://www.griddy.com/post/griddy-update-why-energy-prices-were-sky-high-this-week</link>
      <description>The market is supposed to set the prices, not political appointees.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.griddy.com/post/griddy-update-why-energy-prices-were-sky-high-this-week</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 05:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NameResolutionPal.Unix enabled async name resolution by gfoidl &amp;#183; Pull Request #34633 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/34633</link>
      <description>Fixes #33378
Also

added basic tests in System.Net.NameResolution.Pal.Tests
same order of methods as in the Windows-Pal


Edit: this issue is fixed.
Marking this PR as draft, as there is some bug a...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/34633</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 04:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GetAddrInfoExA function (ws2tcpip.h) - Win32 apps</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/win32/api/ws2tcpip/nf-ws2tcpip-getaddrinfoexa</link>
      <description>Provides protocol-independent name resolution with additional parameters to qualify which namespace providers should handle the request.</description>
      <author> (stevewhims)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/win32/api/ws2tcpip/nf-ws2tcpip-getaddrinfoexa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 04:05:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modified Dns.GetHostAddressesAsync to be truly async by JeffCyr &amp;#183; Pull Request #26850 &amp;#183; dotnet/corefx</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/corefx/pull/26850</link>
      <description>PR for issue dotnet/runtime#17224 (originally: https://github.com/dotnet/corefx/issues/8371)
Modified Dns.GetHostAddressesAsync to use GetAddrInfoEx when supported.</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/corefx/pull/26850</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 04:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>getaddrinfo_a(3) - Linux man page</title>
      <link>https://linux.die.net/man/3/getaddrinfo_a</link>
      <description>The getaddrinfo_a() function performs the same task as getaddrinfo(3), but allows multiple name look-ups to be performed asynchronously, with optional ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://linux.die.net/man/3/getaddrinfo_a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 04:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swati Mohan, Indian-American scientist who led charge to land Nasa rover on Mars, was inspired by Star Trek as a kid</title>
      <link>https://www.indiatoday.in/science/story/swati-mohan-indian-american-scientist-of-nasa-mars-rover-perseverance-1770795-2021-02-19</link>
      <description>When Nasa landed its Mars rover Perseverance on the Martian surface, it was an Indian-American handling the controls and landing system. Swati Mohan spearheaded the attitude control and landing system of the Perseverance rover that navigated a particularly difficult touchdown.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.indiatoday.in/science/story/swati-mohan-indian-american-scientist-of-nasa-mars-rover-perseverance-1770795-2021-02-19</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 03:05:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Euphoria, a New Trans-Focused App Backed by Chelsea Clinton, Others</title>
      <link>https://www.builtinaustin.com/2021/02/17/euphoria-raises-250k-robbi-katherine-anthony</link>
      <description>Euphoria aims to empower transgender people through every facet of their lives, providing tools for everything from financial planning to health tracking.&amp;#160;</description>
      <author> (by Ellen Glover
          February 17, 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://www.builtinaustin.com/2021/02/17/euphoria-raises-250k-robbi-katherine-anthony</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 03:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Expert: Rust at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Ask-the-Expert/Ask-the-Expert-Rust-at-Microsoft</link>
      <description>You may have heard developers talking about the Rust programming language, but maybe you&amp;#39;re not sure what it&amp;#39;s all about. In this session, Ryan Levick and Nell Shamrell-Harrington will talk through wh</description>
      <author> (by melaniemckenna)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Ask-the-Expert/Ask-the-Expert-Rust-at-Microsoft</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 01:05:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Maze Weekly #65 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-65/</link>
      <description>Cold weather, excellent for staying at home and learning new stuff. As winter is kicking in around the globe (at least the Northern hemisphere) we’re gearing up and going through many excellent articles that our fellow bloggers have written. .NET 6 preview 1 is already available for testing so make sure you jump on the […]</description>
      <author> (Vladimir Pecanac)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-65/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 01:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Jeff Fritz on Blazor Webassembly Architecture - Episode 127</title>
      <link>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/is-blazor-ready-for-prime-time-episode-127</link>
      <description>Jeff Fritz is joining the podcast today! This is his second guest appearance. He&amp;amp;nbsp; is an experienced developer, technical educator and PM on the .NET team at Microsoft. He founded The Live Coders team on Twitch, and regularly livestreams builds of websites and fun applications. You can follow Jeff for more .NET, .NET Core and Visual Studio content on Twitch and Twitter at @csharpfritz. &amp;amp;nbsp; In this episode, Jeff talks about what you’re missing out when it comes to Blazor web assembly and Blazor server side. Jeff has been getting a lot of skeptical comments lately on whether this .net application is ready for the real deal, and he shares his opinions for what it&amp;#39;s most useful for. He also has a live project that you can check out and beta test! Listen in as Jeff talks deployment and the future of where this application is headed.&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;amp;nbsp; &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [:38] Be sure to visit  for past episodes and show notes. [1:00] About The Azure DevOps Podcast, Clear Measure, and Jeffrey’s offer to speak at virtual user groups. [1:20] Clear Measure is hiring! Be sure to check out the link in the show notes. [1:30] About Jeffrey’s newest podcast, Architect Tips! [1:59] About today’s episode with return guest, Jeff Fritz! [2:35] Jeffrey welcomes Jeff back on to the podcast. [3:15] Jeff shares what he’s currently up to and why he’s currently obsessed with live streaming.&amp;amp;nbsp; [6:45] Both Jeffery and Jeff can’t wait to get back to live conferences when this is all over.&amp;amp;nbsp; [7:45] Jeff kid’s are currently doing online school and they’re missing the social interactions.&amp;amp;nbsp; [8:45] Is .Net Blazor really ready for primetime?&amp;amp;nbsp; [10:35] Nothing is an overnight success. Let’s give Blazor some breathing room to see how it matures.&amp;amp;nbsp; [11:20] Jeff shares some of the fun things he’s been doing with Blazor.&amp;amp;nbsp; P12:55] What’s the difference between the web assembly version vs. the server version, and when should you be using which?&amp;amp;nbsp; [14:40] What makes Blazor different from other .Net apps?&amp;amp;nbsp; [18:05] How do successfully connect and deploy this application? [24:00] A word from Azure DevOps Podcast’s sponsor: Clear Measure. [24:40] Do we need to be thinking about containers when it comes to Blazor? Jeff argues it’s even simpler than that.&amp;amp;nbsp; [27:05] Jeff breaks down the compatibility level of Blazor web assembly.&amp;amp;nbsp; [28:05] Blazor web assembly not compatible with your particular use case? You can convert it on server side for more flexibility.&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;amp;nbsp; [29:35] Jeff shares some of the projects he’s currently working on.&amp;amp;nbsp; [33:05] Listener challenge! Test out Jeff’s project.&amp;amp;nbsp; [37:30] We have a whole generation of web developers that have grown up on ‘web for everything’. However, as an industry, we’re slowly going back to native client applications.&amp;amp;nbsp; [39:30] Jeffrey shares what excites him about Blazor the most.&amp;amp;nbsp; [41:25] Jeffrey thanks James for joining the podcast. &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:  — New video podcast!   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!  — Click here to download the .NET DevOps for Azure ebook!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!    Twitch:  Twitter:   &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/is-blazor-ready-for-prime-time-episode-127</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Azure from your phone with the Azure mobile app | Azure Friday</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Managing-Azure-from-your-phone-with-the-Azure-mobile-app</link>
      <description>Ilse Terrazas Ortega joins Scott Hanselman to show you how to take advantage of the Azure mobile app to monitor and manage your Azure environment. </description>
      <author> (by Scott Hanselman, Rob Caron)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Managing-Azure-from-your-phone-with-the-Azure-mobile-app</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 01:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFTS Inc., Data Security Issue – Awwd</title>
      <link>https://awwd.com/impact/emergency-information/afts-inc-security-issue/</link>
      <description>Alderwood Water &amp;amp; Wastewater District (the District) was informed that a vendor called Automatic Funds Transfer Services, Inc. (AFTS) was the victim of a ransomware attack. The District contracts with AFTS to handle utility billing and the processing of paper check payments. There is no direct threat to the District’s network as a result of this incident.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://awwd.com/impact/emergency-information/afts-inc-security-issue/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 01:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brave Browser leaks your Tor / Onion service requests through DNS.</title>
      <link>https://ramble.pw/f/privacy/2387/brave-browser-leaks-your-tor-onion-service-requests-through</link>
      <description>Edit: (Since this is gaining traction elsewhere.) I&amp;#39;m not trying to shit on Brave. I&amp;#39;m just wanting to help protect end-users who may use Brave for it&amp;#39;s Tor feature to do stuff over Tor that should only be done with the actual Tor browser. If you&amp;#39;re using Brave you probably use it because you expect a certain level of privacy/anonymity. Piping .onion requests through DNS where your ISP or DNS provider can see that you made a request for an .onion site defeats that purpose.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ramble.pw/f/privacy/2387/brave-browser-leaks-your-tor-onion-service-requests-through</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding “reversed” callstacks in Visual Studio and Perfview with async/await code</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/criteo-engineering/understanding-reversed-callstacks-in-visual-studio-and-perfview-with-async-await-code-11ebe5769332</link>
      <description>This post explains why profilers like Visual Studio could display “reversed” callstacks when dealing with async/await code.</description>
      <author> (https://chnasarre.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/criteo-engineering/understanding-reversed-callstacks-in-visual-studio-and-perfview-with-async-await-code-11ebe5769332</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptology ePrint Archive: Report 2020/1533</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2020/1533</link>
      <description>On  the  Security  of  Homomorphic  Encryption  on  Approximate  Numbers</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://eprint.iacr.org/2020/1533</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:07:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against Agile</title>
      <link>https://alvaroduran.com/essays/against-agile/</link>
      <description>The widespread methodology for software development has backfired, swallowed by the bad management it tried to eradicate.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alvaroduran.com/essays/against-agile/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:07:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When a Solution Is Right In Front of You</title>
      <link>https://rauljordan.com/2021/02/18/when-a-solution-is-right-in-front-of-your-eyes.html</link>
      <description>We had a crazy week debugging one of the trickiest issues we’ve seen in our software. This post showcases how we went down a rabbit hole of information only to conclude a resolution was far easier than we thought.</description>
      <author> (Raul Jordan)</author>
      <guid>https://rauljordan.com/2021/02/18/when-a-solution-is-right-in-front-of-your-eyes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:07:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silence</title>
      <link>https://martinrue.com/silence/</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s be honest, silence is not usually considered an exciting subject. Despite Depeche Mode&amp;#39;s ironic effort to convince us, the idea that we should enjoy silence seems like a stretch. So why am I writing about it?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martinrue.com/silence/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:07:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why do software engineers struggle to write “chunks” function?</title>
      <link>https://shekhargulati.com/2021/02/18/why-do-software-engineers-struggle-to-write-chunks-function/</link>
      <description>In the last couple of years, I took close to two hundred interviews. These interviews range from Java engineers with two years of experience to architects holding more than fifteen years of experie…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shekhargulati.com/2021/02/18/why-do-software-engineers-struggle-to-write-chunks-function/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:07:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open source projects should run office hours</title>
      <link>https://simonwillison.net/2021/Feb/19/office-hours/</link>
      <description>Back in December I decided to try something new for my Datasette open source project: Datasette Office Hours. The idea is simple: anyone can book a 25 minute conversation with …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://simonwillison.net/2021/Feb/19/office-hours/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:07:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to know if you&amp;#39;re interviewing at a product-led company</title>
      <link>https://andrewskotzko.com/how-to-know-if-youre-interviewing-at-a-product-led-company/</link>
      <description>Think of this as &amp;quot;The Mom Test&amp;quot; but applied to product / design / engineering job interviews.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewskotzko.com/how-to-know-if-youre-interviewing-at-a-product-led-company/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:07:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to manage your manager</title>
      <link>https://bdickason.com/posts/manage-your-manager/</link>
      <description>Become a great Product Manager.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bdickason.com/posts/manage-your-manager/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:07:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lemme | with Music original sound - Kd97</title>
      <link>https://www.tiktok.com/@kd_k97/video/6930020014519061766?_d=secCgYIASAHKAESMgow0BDuI7CyD8Mvv4773WrKQsU%2B74oJlmtYYT0KvRyUquDj8a6r%2FIb6qn1palWnEVcAGgA%3D&amp;language=fr&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;share_item_id=6930020014519061766&amp;share_link_id=EF1284F7-0227-40C2-A857-97B05F5D6D6C&amp;timestamp=1613772332&amp;u_code=0</link>
      <description>Kd97 (@kd_k97) has created a short video on TikTok with music original sound. | Lemme</description>
      <author> (kd_k97Kd97 &amp;#183; Il y a 2 j)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiktok.com/@kd_k97/video/6930020014519061766?_d=secCgYIASAHKAESMgow0BDuI7CyD8Mvv4773WrKQsU%2B74oJlmtYYT0KvRyUquDj8a6r%2FIb6qn1palWnEVcAGgA%3D&amp;language=fr&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;share_item_id=6930020014519061766&amp;share_link_id=EF1284F7-0227-40C2-A857-97B05F5D6D6C&amp;timestamp=1613772332&amp;u_code=0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:07:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CliWrap - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/231/cliwrap</link>
      <description>CliWrap is a library that makes it easier to interact with command line interfaces. It provides a convenient wrapper around the target executable, allowing you to pass execution parameters and read the resulting output. The library can also handle errors reported by the underlying process, allows c…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/231/cliwrap</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 22:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reply to @marknorton14 @charlihasnotallent7 @cr7xxxjw @sharifhashiva @raiden_r2d2</title>
      <link>https://www.tiktok.com/@kd_k97/video/6930038227977997573?language=fr&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;share_item_id=6930038227977997573&amp;share_link_id=2EDBBD4D-BF33-4A36-85A9-EA3B5DFED945&amp;timestamp=1613771929&amp;u_code=0</link>
      <description>Kd97 (@kd_k97) has created a short video on TikTok with music original sound. | Reply to @marknorton14 @charlihasnotallent7 @cr7xxxjw @sharifhashiva @raiden_r2d2</description>
      <author> (kd_k97Kd97 &amp;#183; Il y a 2 j)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiktok.com/@kd_k97/video/6930038227977997573?language=fr&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;share_item_id=6930038227977997573&amp;share_link_id=2EDBBD4D-BF33-4A36-85A9-EA3B5DFED945&amp;timestamp=1613771929&amp;u_code=0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 22:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotnet/versionsweeper</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/versionsweeper</link>
      <description>&amp;#127919; LTS (or current) versions - GitHub Action that will run as a scheduled CRON job. Ideally, once every few months or as often as necessary to align with .NET version updates. - dotnet/versionsweeper</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/versionsweeper</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 22:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[mono] Implement public hot reload API by lambdageek &amp;#183; Pull Request #48380 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/48380</link>
      <description>Also add ApplyUpdateSdb that takes byte[] arguments for use with
mono/debugger-libs as its awkward to call a ROS method from the debugger.
Contributes to #45689
This is the mono counterpart of #48366</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/48380</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 21:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s New in EF Core 6.0 Preview 1 -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/efcore6-preview1.aspx</link>
      <description>The Entity Framework Core 6 dev team shipped Preview 1 this week, headed toward a debut with the larger, unifying .NET 6 umbrella platform in November.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel02/19/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/efcore6-preview1.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 21:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add hot reload apply changes API: AssemblyExtensions.ApplyUpdate by mikem8361 &amp;#183; Pull Request #48366 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/48366</link>
      <description>Issue: #45689
Currently Windows only: there will be another PR to enable this API on Linux/MacOS.
The Hot reload API will fail if debugging or if the module isn&amp;#39;t editable.</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/48366</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 21:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the .NET Foundation Speakers Directory</title>
      <link>https://dotnetfoundation.org/blog/2021/02/19/blog/posts/announcing-the-dot-net-foundation-speakers-directory</link>
      <description>This is your .NET Foundation!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetfoundation.org/blog/2021/02/19/blog/posts/announcing-the-dot-net-foundation-speakers-directory</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 21:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn TV</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/tv/?WT.mc_id=twitter-0000-learntv</link>
      <description>AI Show Live: Build Responsible AI using Error Analysis toolkit</description>
      <author> (brstegge)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/tv/?WT.mc_id=twitter-0000-learntv</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build smaller, faster, and more secure desktop applications with a web frontend | Tauri Studio</title>
      <link>https://tauri.studio/en/</link>
      <description>Tauri is a framework for building tiny, blazing fast binaries for all major desktop platforms. Developers can integrate any front-end framework that compiles to HTML, JS and CSS for building their user interface.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tauri.studio/en/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 19:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shoddy Science Behind Emotional Recognition Tech</title>
      <link>https://onezero.medium.com/the-shoddy-science-behind-emotional-recognition-tech-2e847fc526a0</link>
      <description>People’s facial expressions line up with their emotions less than half the time</description>
      <author> (https://dave.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://onezero.medium.com/the-shoddy-science-behind-emotional-recognition-tech-2e847fc526a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 18:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#187; Ultima VIII (or, How to Destroy a Gaming Franchise in One Easy Step) The Digital Antiquarian</title>
      <link>https://www.filfre.net/2021/02/ultima-viii-or-how-to-destroy-a-gaming-franchise-in-one-easy-step/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Jimmy Maher)</author>
      <guid>https://www.filfre.net/2021/02/ultima-viii-or-how-to-destroy-a-gaming-franchise-in-one-easy-step/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 18:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Outdated Answers project</title>
      <link>https://meta.stackoverflow.com/questions/405302/introducing-outdated-answers-project?cb=1</link>
      <description>In our blog post last month on our Community &amp;amp;amp; Public Platform strategy &amp;amp;amp; roadmap for Q1 2021, we announced an initiative to address outdated answers on Stack Overflow. Today, I&amp;#39;ll give you...</description>
      <author> (MakotoMakoto
        
            94.9k104104 gold badges671671 silver badges10071007 bronze badges)</author>
      <guid>https://meta.stackoverflow.com/questions/405302/introducing-outdated-answers-project?cb=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 18:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WUG: (Ne)Zn&amp;#225;m&amp;#233; vlastnosti Azure Storage (online)</title>
      <link>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233851-ne-zname-vlastnosti-azure-storage</link>
      <description>19 Feb 2021
	
	 1 mins
	
	 Presentations &amp;amp; Speaking</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tabsoverspaces.com/233851-ne-zname-vlastnosti-azure-storage</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 17:06:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Virtual ML.NET Community Conference 2021: Call for Speakers/Papers</title>
      <link>https://sessionize.com/the-virtual-ml-net-community-conference-9022/</link>
      <description>On May 7th, The Virtual ML.NET Community Conference will kick off with 2 days of sessions on all things ML.NET, and we want to see you there!&amp;#160;Come and...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sessionize.com/the-virtual-ml-net-community-conference-9022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 17:06:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiscordChatExporter - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/232/discordchatexporter</link>
      <description>DiscordChatExporter can be used to export message history from a Discord channel to a file. It works for both direct message chats and guild chats, supports markdown, message grouping, embeds, attachments, mentions, reactions and other features. It works with both user and bot tokens, supports mult…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/232/discordchatexporter</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 17:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Miss My Bar - Recreate Your Favorite Bar&amp;#39;s Atmosphere</title>
      <link>http://imissmybar.com/</link>
      <description>A modern digital artifact recreating the atmosphere of our favorite local bars to keep us company while it’s safe to visit them again. An initiative by Maverick Monterrey.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://imissmybar.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 16:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How can I prevent a Windows Runtime WebView from loading any content beyond the initial request and its redirects? | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210219-00/?p=104881</link>
      <description>Last time, we configured a Windows Runtime WebView control so that it loaded content only from the initial request, and all other requests were blocked. However, we found that this meant that if the original request resulted in a redirect, we blocked the redirect.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210219-00/?p=104881</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 15:06:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How NASA Designed a Helicopter That Could Fly Autonomously on Mars - IEEE Spectrum</title>
      <link>https://spectrum.ieee.org/automaton/aerospace/robotic-exploration/nasa-designed-perseverance-helicopter-rover-fly-autonomously-mars</link>
      <description>Tucked under the belly of the Perseverance rover that will be landing on Mars in just a few days is a little helicopter called Ingenuity. Its body is the size of a box of tissues, slung underneath a pair of 1.2m carbon fiber rotors on top of four spindly legs. It weighs just 1.8kg, but the importance of its mission is massive. If everything goes according to plan, Ingenuity will become the first aircraft to fly on Mars.</description>
      <author> (By Evan Ackerman)</author>
      <guid>https://spectrum.ieee.org/automaton/aerospace/robotic-exploration/nasa-designed-perseverance-helicopter-rover-fly-autonomously-mars</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 15:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“I will slaughter you” | daniel.haxx.se</title>
      <link>https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2021/02/19/i-will-slaughter-you/</link>
      <description>You might know that I’ve posted funny emails I’ve received on my blog several times in the past. The kind of emails people send me when they experience problems with some device they own (like a car) and they contact me because my email address happens to be visible somewhere.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2021/02/19/i-will-slaughter-you/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 14:07:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET sites - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/168/asp.net-sites-the-good-the-bad-the-downright-ugly</link>
      <description>I am planning a number of web projects and have a background and experience in C#, MSSQL and ASP.NET so .NET was the prime candidate for the technology I would use. I was very curious to see what kind of websites were being developed using ASP.NET as I wanted to be sure I was in good company. So I …</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/168/asp.net-sites-the-good-the-bad-the-downright-ugly</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 12:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bliki: MonolithFirst</title>
      <link>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/MonolithFirst.html</link>
      <description>Going directly to a microservices architecture is risky, so consider building a monolithic system first. Split to microservices when, and if, you need it.</description>
      <author> (Martin Fowler)</author>
      <guid>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/MonolithFirst.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 12:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using HPKE to Encrypt Request Payloads</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/using-hpke-to-encrypt-request-payloads/</link>
      <description>Allowing users to securely log parts of the request that match firewall rules while making it impossible for anyone else to decrypt.</description>
      <author> (Miguel de Moura)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/using-hpke-to-encrypt-request-payloads/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 12:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 70 - Picking the Right Azure Resources with Barry Luijbregts</title>
      <link>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-70-picking-the-right-azure-resources-with-barry-luijbregts/</link>
      <description>In this episode of the .NET Core Podcast we chatted with Barry Luijbregts (aka Azure Barry) about the many different Azure resources and how to pick the &amp;amp;quot;best&amp;amp;quot; ones for your project</description>
      <author> (RJJ Software)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetcore.show/episode-70-picking-the-right-azure-resources-with-barry-luijbregts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 11:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gleam v0.14 released! – Gleam</title>
      <link>https://gleam.run/news/gleam-v0.14-released/</link>
      <description>The Gleam programming language</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gleam.run/news/gleam-v0.14-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 11:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vertical Farming Does Not Save Space</title>
      <link>https://www.lowtechmagazine.com/2021/02/vertical-farming-ecosystem-services.html</link>
      <description>If the electricity for a vertical farm is supplied by solar panels, the energy production takes up at least as much space as the vertical farm saves. Urban agriculture in vertical, indoor “farms” is on the rise. Electric lights allow the crops to be grown in layers above each other year-round. Proponents argue that growers can save a lot of agricultural land in this way. Additional advantages are that less energy is needed to transport food (most people live in a city) and that less water and pesticides are required. Which crops? The vertical farms that have been commercially active for several years all focus on the same crops. These are agricultural products with a high water content, such as...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lowtechmagazine.com/2021/02/vertical-farming-ecosystem-services.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 11:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>