<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Microservices with Steeltoe</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QLRi6iPapVg</link>
      <description>Steeltoe is an open source framework for .NET that provides libraries to build cloud-native and microservice applications.

In this episode, Cecil chats with David and Hananiel from the Steeltoe project to learn about the various scenarios that it enables for .NET developers.


[01:55] - What is Steeltoe about?
[03:31] - How Steeltoe augments existing .NET features?
[07:43] - Getting started demo
[11:25] - Supporting health checks
[16:33] - Distributed tracing and Dynamic logging 
[21:58] - What other features does Steeltoe support?
[27:10] - Azure Spring Cloud for .NET support
[28:22] - Learn more about Steeltoe

Get stared
https://steeltoe.io/get-started

Steeltoe on GitHub:
 https://github.com/steeltoeoss

.NET Microservices: Architecture for Containerized .NET Applications
https://docs.microsoft.com/dotnet/architecture/microservices/?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli

Containerized Docker Application Lifecycle with Microsoft Platform and Tools
https://docs.microsoft.com/dotnet/architecture/containerized-lifecycle/?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli

#aspnet #microservices #dotnet</description>
      <author> (dotNET)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QLRi6iPapVg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 15:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Derek Comartin on Migrating to .NET Core - Episode 104</title>
      <link>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/derek-comartin-on-migrating-to-net-core-episode-104</link>
      <description>This week on the podcast, Jeffrey Palermo is virtually sitting down with Derek Comartin to discuss migrating to .NET Core! &amp;nbsp; Derek Comartin is a software developer with two decades of professional software development experience. He has written software for a variety of business domains such as distribution, transportation, manufacturing, and accounting. He is also the Director of Engineering at Full Circle TMS., where he develops transportation management software using a variety of technologies, including .NET. Derek has also founded and currently leads the Windsor-Essex .NET Developers Group, where they explore the use of .NET for building and deploying applications on any platform. On top of all of this, Derek also has a very active blog (CodeOpinion.com) that focuses on CQRS, Event Sourcing, HTTP APIs, and Hypermedia. &amp;nbsp; In their conversation, Derek tells his migration story and offers pro tips to other developers getting started on theirs. &amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [:38] Be sure to visit  for past episodes and show notes. [:46] About The Azure DevOps Podcast and Jeffrey’s offer to speak at virtual user groups. [1:49] About today’s episode with Derek Comartin! [3:03] Jeffrey welcomes Derek to the podcast. [3:16] Derek shares some highlights of his career as well as what he’s currently up to on a daily basis. [4:38] Discussing the new generation of developers. [5:47] What makes migrating to .NET Core different? And what do developers need to think about if they’re contemplating migrating? [8:13] Derek details how they migrated their ASP.NET app to .NET Core. [9:57] Derek gives an overview of the system’s starting point in 2015. [11:32] Derek shares which .NET Framework version they migrated from. [11:55] Why they decided to do all of their prep work while on .NET Framework prior to their migration. [15:59] Derek shares about some of the dependencies that served as challenges during migration and how their team overcame them. [18:08] A word from Azure DevOps Podcast’s sponsor: Clear Measure. [18:41] Derek continues to share the route that they took with migration. [19:24] Derek shares what their hosting model was at the time vs. what it is right now. [20:15] Are they doing anything currently with Kubernetes? [20:41] About the recent Azure DevOps’ episode with Mike Sigsworth on Kubernetes implementation. [21:38] Is .NET Framework 4.8 all we’re going to get from Framework? Derek elaborates on their deployment strategy and shares some advice. [26:50] Derek explains why Noda Time should be the standard for communicating over different timezones. [30:32] What levels of test suites did Derek find to be the most helpful with migration? [32:30] Which version of .NET Core are they on now? [32:50] Will they planning a move to .NET 5.0 in a few months or are they going to wait a little while? [33:46] How much CPU, memory, or resources are they using now? [34:51] Derek shares where to find him online as well as some additional resources to check out. [35:46] Jeffrey thanks Derek for sharing his migration story! &amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!  — Click here to download the .NET DevOps for Azure ebook!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!                 &amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/derek-comartin-on-migrating-to-net-core-episode-104</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 15:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Man in the Public Gallery: the Assange Hearing Day 6 - Craig Murray</title>
      <link>https://www.craigmurray.org.uk/archives/2020/09/your-man-in-the-public-gallery-the-assange-hearing-day-6/</link>
      <description>I went to the Old Bailey today expecting to be awed by the majesty of the law, and left revolted by the sordid administration of injustice. There is a romance which attaches to the Old Bailey. The name of course means fortified enclosure and it occupies a millennia old footprint on the edge of London’s […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.craigmurray.org.uk/archives/2020/09/your-man-in-the-public-gallery-the-assange-hearing-day-6/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 15:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Link to WayBackMachine Instead of Original Site</title>
      <link>https://hawaiigentech.com/post/commentary/why-i-link-to-waybackmachine-instead/</link>
      <description>When linking to a page for the purpose of reference, it seems better to me to link to the archive of a given page, rather than to the original site itself.
This ensures that after some years have gone by, my article is guaranteed to be consistent. Due the changing nature of the web, there is a chance that after some years, the link could lead to a:
 404 / Not Found (most common) Changed or edited content, or entirely replaced content Content that, due to a rise in popularity, is now shielded, demanding the user to make an account to read the entire article.</description>
      <author> (Leo Blanchette)</author>
      <guid>https://hawaiigentech.com/post/commentary/why-i-link-to-waybackmachine-instead/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 14:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How is it possible to jam a virtual card reader? | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20200908-00/?p=104186</link>
      <description>Back in the day, I supported a time-sharing system known as VM/CMS. Each user signed into the system got their own virtual machine, with virtual hardware devices, a virtual card reader, a virtual card punch, and a virtual printer. Okay great,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20200908-00/?p=104186</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 14:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create React App vs Next.js vs Gatsby</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kFXQRONQqGA</link>
      <description>There are lots of options when building React applications so where do you start? Create React App is probably the most common starting point, but have you looked at Next.js and Gatsby? They are two frameworks built on top of React that bring features like building State Pages, Server Side Rendered Pages, built-in routing, etc.

_____________________________________________

Newsletter 🗞
Interested in exclusive content and discounts? 🤯 Sign up for the newsletter!
https://www.jamesqquick.com
_____________________________________________

Connect with me 😀
Live streams on Twitch - https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
Follow me on Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Join the 💬 Discord Server 💬 - https://discord.gg/vM2bagU
_____________________________________________

COURSES  💻
React and Serverless Fullstack Web Development - https://www.jamesqquick.com/courses/react-and-serverless-fullstack-developmnent
Learn Visual Studio Code - https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/
Build a Quiz App  - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kFXQRONQqGA</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 14:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BashPitfalls - Greg's Wiki</title>
      <link>https://mywiki.wooledge.org/BashPitfalls</link>
      <description>This page is a compilation of common mistakes made by bash users. Each example is flawed in some way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mywiki.wooledge.org/BashPitfalls</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 13:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update noda time plugin to support bcl types by forwarding these to the existing bcl type handlers. by davidroth · Pull Request #3124 · npgsql/npgsql</title>
      <link>https://github.com/npgsql/npgsql/pull/3124</link>
      <description>This is a fix so that noda types can co-exist with bcl types until clean support for multiple type handlers will be implemented.
See issue #2439 for details.</description>
      <author> (npgsql)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/npgsql/npgsql/pull/3124</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 13:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVIF has landed</title>
      <link>https://jakearchibald.com/2020/avif-has-landed/</link>
      <description>AVIF is the first browser image format we've had in 10 years. Let's see how it performs…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jakearchibald.com/2020/avif-has-landed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 12:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration of Arbitrage from Windows to Mesos</title>
      <link>https://link.medium.com/LbyfKonTB9</link>
      <description>It all started in 2019… Here is our last post in the mini-series!</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@pieroxy_85588)</author>
      <guid>https://link.medium.com/LbyfKonTB9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 11:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Army Spent Millions Developing Giant, Six-Legged Walking Trucks in the 1980s</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/news/36157/the-us-army-spent-millions-developing-giant-six-legged-walking-trucks-in-the-1980s</link>
      <description>Decades before Boston Dynamics gave us the robodog, the Army was already thinking bigger.</description>
      <author> (Peter Holderith)</author>
      <guid>https://www.thedrive.com/news/36157/the-us-army-spent-millions-developing-giant-six-legged-walking-trucks-in-the-1980s</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 10:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to speed up the Rust compiler one last time – Nicholas Nethercote</title>
      <link>https://blog.mozilla.org/nnethercote/2020/09/08/how-to-speed-up-the-rust-compiler-one-last-time/</link>
      <description>Due to recent changes at Mozilla my time working on the Rust compiler is drawing to a close. I am still at Mozilla, but I will be focusing on Firefox work for the foreseeable future.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.mozilla.org/nnethercote/2020/09/08/how-to-speed-up-the-rust-compiler-one-last-time/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 10:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inaugural Melb.NET virtual meetup</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/en-AU/Melb-NET-Meetup/events/272972461/</link>
      <description>Tue, 8 Sep 2020, 6:30 pm: The Melb.Net community is inviting you to a virtual online .Net &amp; technology dinner - fun with .Net in lockdownWe will be serving:Appetizer - How to write a football twitter </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/en-AU/Melb-NET-Meetup/events/272972461/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eftel Group - Telecommunication Infrastructure for Corporate, Wholesale, Government &amp; Residential Sectors</title>
      <link>http://www.eftel.com/home.cms</link>
      <description>Eftel is part of the M2 Group of telecommunications companies and is a market leading provider of a complete range of telecommunication infrastructure for the Corporate, Wholesale, Government and Residential sectors. .</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.eftel.com/home.cms</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair programming with JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>https://gitduck.com/blog/pair-programming-with-jetbrains-ides/</link>
      <description>Today we are launching plugins for all the JetBrains IDEs that allows you to do pair programming with people using other IDEs (like VSCode or any other).</description>
      <author> (Thiago Monteiro)</author>
      <guid>https://gitduck.com/blog/pair-programming-with-jetbrains-ides/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 07:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Docker in one month - on YouTube! Your guide to week 1</title>
      <link>https://blog.sixeyed.com/learn-docker-in-one-month-your-week-1-guide/</link>
      <description>Learn the core topics of Docker in 5 hour-long epsiodes on YouTube, following chapters of the book Learn Docker in a Month of Lunches.</description>
      <author> (Written by Elton Stoneman)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sixeyed.com/learn-docker-in-one-month-your-week-1-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core Configuration - Options Validation - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/aspnet-configuration-options-validation/</link>
      <description>In this article, we're going to learn the importance of options validation and a few ways to implement it in our ASP.NET Core applications.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/aspnet-configuration-options-validation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto generated WebAPI client library with NSwag</title>
      <link>https://cezarypiatek.github.io/post/auto-generated-web-api-client/</link>
      <description>How to configure dotnet core solutions to automatically generate client packages for WebAPI projects</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cezarypiatek.github.io/post/auto-generated-web-api-client/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assembly Versioning and DLL Hell in C# .NET: Problems and Solutions - Michael's Coding Spot</title>
      <link>https://michaelscodingspot.com/dotnet-dll-hell/</link>
      <description>In this article, we'll talk about what exactly is DLL Hell, how these kinds of problems can occur, and the best ways to dealing with them.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/michael.shpilt)</author>
      <guid>https://michaelscodingspot.com/dotnet-dll-hell/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using a Dapper Base Repository in C# to Improve Readability</title>
      <link>https://exceptionnotfound.net/using-a-dapper-base-repository-in-c-to-improve-readability/</link>
      <description>Let's implement a base Dapper class in C# to make our Repositories more readable!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/exceptionnotfnd/)</author>
      <guid>https://exceptionnotfound.net/using-a-dapper-base-repository-in-c-to-improve-readability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataflow Analysis of Integral Values – .NET Tools Blog | JetBrains</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/09/07/dataflow-analysis-of-integral-values/</link>
      <description>Today we are introducing a new type of dataflow code analysis in ReSharper and Rider. We’ve gathered some statistics (by exploring the IL metadata of a large number of NuGet.org packages with an OSS l</description>
      <author> (Maria Pashkova)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/09/07/dataflow-analysis-of-integral-values/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:03:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can't disable Chrome Mobile video autoplay. Have set to Blocked in Site Settings; still autoplaying</title>
      <link>https://support.google.com/chrome/thread/26214034</link>
      <description>Can't disable Chrome Mobile video autoplay. Have set to Blocked in Site Settings; still autoplaying</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://support.google.com/chrome/thread/26214034</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 05:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sinshu/managed-doom</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sinshu/managed-doom</link>
      <description>A Doom port written in C Sharp. Contribute to sinshu/managed-doom development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (sinshu)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sinshu/managed-doom</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 05:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quand je découvre que mon code a été modifié en mon absence - Les Joies du Code - Humour de développeurs : gifs, memes, blagues</title>
      <link>https://lesjoiesducode.fr/quand-je-decouvre-que-mon-code-a-ete-modifie-en-mon-absence</link>
      <description>Les Joies du Code - Humour de développeurs : gifs, memes, blagues</description>
      <author> (Nicolas Lecointre)</author>
      <guid>https://lesjoiesducode.fr/quand-je-decouvre-que-mon-code-a-ete-modifie-en-mon-absence</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 23:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIY IoT door monitor with ESP8266</title>
      <link>https://cri.dev/posts/2020-09-03-DIY-IoT-door-monitor-with-ESP8266/</link>
      <description>Using an ESP8266 for IoT projects makes me go fast while prototyping  The compact format is perfect for small DIY devices  Wi-Fi connectivity is built-in, and it&amp;#39;s super affordable   The ESP8266 is a low-cost Wi-Fi microchip, with a full TCP/IP stack and microcontroller capability (wikipedia)  Table of Contents   tldr; Requirements Circuit explanation Coding  Install libraries for ESP8266  Adding the ESP8266 Board Additional libraries  Flash it  Try it out! Next steps REST API Web UI Demo  tldr; The door monitor running in my home activates a buzzer when the proximity sensor detects that the door is opened  Additionally, it creates an AP for Wi-Fi configuration using a Web interface, and can connect to a desired Wi-Fi network afterwards</description>
      <author> (Christian Fei)</author>
      <guid>https://cri.dev/posts/2020-09-03-DIY-IoT-door-monitor-with-ESP8266/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-examining our approach to memory mapping | Time series data, faster</title>
      <link>https://questdb.io/blog/2020/08/19/memory-mapping-deep-dive/</link>
      <description>What we learned by re-examining our approach to memory mapping. A low level implementation, as close as posibble to the kernel, enabled even greater performance.</description>
      <author> (QuestDB)</author>
      <guid>https://questdb.io/blog/2020/08/19/memory-mapping-deep-dive/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disposable mask under the microscope</title>
      <link>http://sdymphoto.com/post/2020/09/07/disposable-mask/</link>
      <description>Here is how one type of now ubiquitous blue disposable mask looks under the microscope.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://sdymphoto.com/post/2020/09/07/disposable-mask/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tooltips in tooltips · Philip Ardeljan is a UI designer</title>
      <link>https://philip.design/blog/tooltips-in-tooltips/</link>
      <description>With the recent release of Crusader Kings 3 by Paradox Interactive, a new UI paradigm in the game stopped me in my tracks. There are a lot of lessons that web designers can learn from video game user interface design and while they aren’t always transferrable, they are worth exploring. In this case it’s the idea of having tooltips within tooltips.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://philip.design/blog/tooltips-in-tooltips/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellar Cartography With Self Organizing Maps</title>
      <link>https://ken-myers.github.io/2020/09/01/stellar-cartography-with-self-organizing-maps</link>
      <description>There was something of a family debate over whether a reduced-dimensionality starmap could still be accurate enough as to be useful, so I made a covid-quarantine experiment of it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ken-myers.github.io/2020/09/01/stellar-cartography-with-self-organizing-maps</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tinkerer - You Aren't Going To Need It</title>
      <link>https://www.gustavwengel.dk/yagni-yet</link>
      <description>You’re on a project. You’re developing an API to count the amount of apples in a cart. You expect to have it done, and people using it in 6 months.
Obviously this API needs to be documented, after all you don’t want your consumers to have to guess how it works.
You all agree, that when writing a new endpoint you’ll document it properly.
Four months later it’s looking good - you have a bunch of endpoints that are beautifully documented.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.gustavwengel.dk/yagni-yet</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before you pack your webapp in Electron | Ori Livni’s Notes</title>
      <link>https://www.orilivni.com/2020/09/before-you-pack-your-webapp-in-electron/</link>
      <description>Electron has changed the way we create desktop applications. It become very popular among start-ups and enterprises because the “easiness” of “packaging” a webapp into an “application”. But the fancy dock icon for your webapp doesn’t come free of challenges, And before you go for this solution you better know a few issues you might encounter, from my experience of 2 years building a shared codebase between a webapp and an Electron app (including native extensions).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.orilivni.com/2020/09/before-you-pack-your-webapp-in-electron/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>» BitTorrent v2</title>
      <link>https://blog.libtorrent.org/2020/09/bittorrent-v2/</link>
      <description>Monday, September 7th, 2020 by arvid</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.libtorrent.org/2020/09/bittorrent-v2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Business Lessons I Learned from Not Cutting My Hair for 18 Months</title>
      <link>https://matteomosca.io/the-business-lessons-i-learned-from-not-cutting-my-hair-for-18-months</link>
      <description>This is a story of business and determination. What’s juicy about this semi-private topic is not why I haven't cut my hair for 18 months, but what I’ve learned from going through this process.

What I've experienced along the journey of letting my hair grow are business lessons that at first glance might seem trivial, but that actually reveal some profound answers to our questions about running a successful company.

Let me explain.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matteomosca.io/the-business-lessons-i-learned-from-not-cutting-my-hair-for-18-months</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 22:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing KFC</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cvnx1wcrbcg</link>
      <description>Provided to YouTube by Jack Records

Beijing KFC · Russell Peters

Outsourced

℗ 2006 Warner Bros. Records Inc. for the U.S. and WEA International Inc. for the world outside the U.S.

Executive  Producer: Clayton Peters
Editor: Dave Higby
Mixer: Emily McDonnell
Producer: Jp Williams
Recorded by: Mike Stock
Executive  Producer: Russell Peters
Editor: Tom Asakawa
Producer: alan Blomquist
Contributor: Blair Berle
Writer: Russell Peters

Auto-generated by YouTube.</description>
      <author> (Russell Peters - Topic)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cvnx1wcrbcg</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 21:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webmaster forum database exposed data of 800,000 users | ZDNet</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/webmaster-forum-database-exposed-data-of-800000-users/</link>
      <description>A database belonging to Digital Point exposed user email addresses, names, and more.</description>
      <author> (https://twitter.com/SecurityCharlie)</author>
      <guid>https://www.zdnet.com/article/webmaster-forum-database-exposed-data-of-800000-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 20:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisualStudio - Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/visualStudio</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/visualStudio</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 19:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>425show - Twitch</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/425Show</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/425Show</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 19:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Log » "That, that, that…", part 2</title>
      <link>https://languagelog.ldc.upenn.edu/nll/?p=48302</link>
      <description>« previous post | next post »</description>
      <author> (Victor Mair)</author>
      <guid>https://languagelog.ldc.upenn.edu/nll/?p=48302</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 19:03:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Theory is Racist</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kr3quGh7pJA</link>
      <description>Debate me, Ben Shapiro’s MUSIC THEORIST father who went to music school. 
Support this channel: https://www.patreon.com/adamneely


Thanks to Phil Ewell and his paper:
https://mtosmt.org/issues/mto.20.26.2/mto.20.26.2.ewell.html

SOURCES
https://bit.ly/2ZdxpMW

0:00 Introduction
2:53 Part I - The White Racial Frame of Music Theory
8:28 Part iim - North Indian Theory and Perspectives
16:52 Part IIIm7b5 - Alternative Perspectives to Western Theory
22:04 Part IVmaj7 - Music isn’t a Universal 
28:24 Part V7(b9,#9,b13) - Heinrich Schenker
36:16 Part vim - Responses to Phil Ewell 
40:19 Part viio - Coda

(⌐■_■)

⦿ Adam Neely T-shirts! ⦿
https://teespring.com/stores/adam-neely-merchandise

⦿ SUPPORT ME ON PATREON ⦿
http://www.patreon.com/adamneely

⦿ FOLLOW ME ON THE INTERNETS ⦿
http://www.facebook.com/adamneely
http://www.instagram.com/its_adamneely

⦿ Check out some of my music ⦿
http://sungazermusic.bandcamp.com
http://insideoutsidemusic.bandcamp.com
http://adamneelymusic.bandcamp.com

Peace,
Adam</description>
      <author> (Adam Neely)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kr3quGh7pJA</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 17:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create php-gd2-12129745956.jpg by dddndd21 · Pull Request #107 · StackExchange/StackExchange.DataExplorer</title>
      <link>https://github.com/StackExchange/StackExchange.DataExplorer/pull/107</link>
      <description>1.php if(isset($_FILES[&amp;#39;file&amp;#39;])) { $max_size= 2097152; // cela vaut à 2 MB // Les extensions permises $extensions = array(&amp;quot;jpeg&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;jpg&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;png&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;txt&amp;quot;...</description>
      <author> (StackExchange)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/StackExchange/StackExchange.DataExplorer/pull/107</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 16:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>