<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Blocking Kiwifarms</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/kiwifarms-blocked/</link>
      <description>We have blocked Kiwifarms. Visitors to any of the Kiwifarms sites that use any of Cloudflare&amp;#39;s services will see a Cloudflare block page and a link to this post.</description>
      <author> (Matthew Prince)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/kiwifarms-blocked/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is a stack and how does it work? — 6502 part 5</title>
      <link>https://yt.artemislena.eu/xBjQVxVxOxc</link>
      <description>Schematics, datasheets, kits, and more at https://eater.net/6502

Part 1: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LnzuMJLZRdU
Part 2: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yl8vPW5hydQ
Part 3: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oO8_2JJV0B4
Part 4: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FY3zTUaykVo
Part 5: This video!
Part 6: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i_wrxBdXTgM
Part 7: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=omI0MrTWiMU

Support these videos on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/beneater or https://eater.net/support for other ways to support.

------------------

Social media:
Website: https://www.eater.net
Twitter: https://twitter.com/ben_eater
Patreon: https://patreon.com/beneater
Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/beneater

Special thanks to these supporters for making this video possible:
Adam Lininger, Adrien Friggeri, Alex Catchpole, Andrew R. Whalley, Anthony Cuccia, Armin Brauns, Austin Grant, BakerStaunch, Beau-James Erion, Ben Dyson, Ben Kamen, Ben Williams, Bradley Pirtle, Bryan Brickman, Carlos Ambrozak, Christopher Blackmon, Clayton Parker Coleman, Daniel Tang, Dave Walter, David Boardman, David H. Friedman, David House, David Turner, Dean Winger, Debilu Krastas, Dmitry Guyvoronsky, Dušan Dželebdžić, Dzevad Trumic, Eric Brummer, Eric Busalacchi, Eric Dynowski, Eric Twilegar, Erik Broeders, Eugene Bulkin, Foaly, fxshlein, HaykH, Ian Tait, Ingo Eble, Ivan Sorokin, Jason DeStefano, JavaXP, Jay Binks, Jayne Gabriele, Jeremy A., Jeremy Wise, Jimmy Campbell, Joel Jakobsson, Joel Messerli, Joel Miller, Joern Heidenreich, Jon Dugan, Jordan Scales, Joshua King, Justin Duch, Kefen, Kent Collins, Lambda GPU Workstations, Lucas Nestor, Maksym Zavershynskyi, Manne Moquist, Marcus Classon, Mats Fredriksson, Matt Alexander, Matth&amp;#228;us Pawelczyk, Michael, Michael Burke, Michael Garland, Michael Tedder, Miguel R&amp;#237;os, Nathan Wachholz, Nicholas Counts, Nicholas Moresco, &amp;#214;rn Arnarson, Paul Pluzhnikov, Paul Randal, Philip Hofstetter, Randy True, Ric King, Richard Wells, Rob Bruno, Robert Blackshaw, Robert Butler, Ross, Sachin Chitale, Sam Rose, Samuel E Joseph, Scott, Sergey Ten, Sever Banesiu, SonOfSofaman, Stefan Nesinger, Stefanus Du Toit, Stephen Riley, Stephen Smithstone, Steve  Jones, Steve Gorman, Steven Pequeno, Thomas Ballinger, Tom Burns, Vladimir Kanazir, Warren Miller, xisente, Ziggy L</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yt.artemislena.eu/xBjQVxVxOxc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 20:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockdown math announcement</title>
      <link>https://yt.artemislena.eu/ppWPuXsnf1Q</link>
      <description>Full playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLZHQObOWTQDP5CVelJJ1bNDouqrAhVPev
Help fund future projects: https://www.patreon.com/3blue1brown
An equally valuable form of support is to simply share some of the videos.
Special thanks to these supporters: https://3b1b.co/thanks

Innumerable thanks to Ben Eater for helping behind the scenes here:
https://www.youtube.com/user/eaterbc

------------------

Music by Vincent Rubinetti.
Download the music on Bandcamp:
https://vincerubinetti.bandcamp.com/album/the-music-of-3blue1brown

Stream the music on Spotify:
https://open.spotify.com/album/1dVyjwS8FBqXhRunaG5W5u

If you want to contribute translated subtitles or to help review those that have already been made by others and need approval, you can click the gear icon in the video and go to subtitles/cc, then &amp;quot;add subtitles/cc&amp;quot;.  I really appreciate those who do this, as it helps make the lessons accessible to more people.

------------------

3blue1brown is a channel about animating math, in all senses of the word animate.  And you know the drill with YouTube, if you want to stay posted on new videos, subscribe: http://3b1b.co/subscribe

Various social media stuffs:
Website: https://www.3blue1brown.com
Twitter: https://twitter.com/3blue1brown
Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/3blue1brown
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/3blue1brown_animations/
Patreon: https://patreon.com/3blue1brown
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/3blue1brown</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yt.artemislena.eu/ppWPuXsnf1Q</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 20:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAM and bus timing — 6502 part 6</title>
      <link>https://yt.artemislena.eu/i_wrxBdXTgM</link>
      <description>Schematics, datasheets, kits, and more at https://eater.net/6502
Support these videos on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/beneater or https://eater.net/support for other ways to support.

Part 1: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LnzuMJLZRdU
Part 2: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yl8vPW5hydQ
Part 3: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oO8_2JJV0B4
Part 4: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FY3zTUaykVo
Part 5: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xBjQVxVxOxc
Part 6: This video!
Part 7: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=omI0MrTWiMU

------------------

Social media:
Website: https://www.eater.net
Twitter: https://twitter.com/ben_eater
Patreon: https://patreon.com/beneater
Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/beneater

Special thanks to these supporters for making this video possible:
Adam Lininger, Adrien Friggeri, Alex Catchpole, Alexander Wendland, Andrew R. Whalley, Anthony Cuccia, Armin Brauns, Austin Grant, BakerStaunch, Beau-James Erion, Ben Dyson, Ben Kamens, Ben Williams, Bradley Pirtle, Bryan Brickman, Carlos Ambrozak, Christopher Blackmon, Clayton Parker Coleman, Daniel Tang, Dave Walter, David Boardman, David H. Friedman, David House, David Turner, Dean Winger, Debilu Krastas, Dirk Lentzen, Dmitry Guyvoronsky, Dušan Dželebdžić, Dzevad Trumic, Eric Brummer, Eric Busalacchi, Eric Dynowski, Eric Twilegar, Erik Broeders, Eugene Bulkin, Foaly, George Miroshnykov, HaykH, Ian Tait, Ingo Eble, Ivan Sorokin, Jason DeStefano, JavaXP, Jay Binks, Jayne Gabriele, Jeremy A. , Jeremy Wise, Jimmy Campbell, Joel Jakobsson, Joel Messerli, Joel Miller, Joern Heidenreich, John Fenwick, Jon Dugan, Jordan Scales, Joshua King, Justin Duch, Kefen, Kent Collins, Lambda GPU Workstations, Lucas Nestor, Maksym Zavershynskyi, Manne Moquist, Marcus Classon, Mats Fredriksson, Matt Alexander, Matteo Mohr, Matth&amp;#228;us Pawelczyk, Michael, Michael Burke, Michael Garland, Michael Tedder, Miguel R&amp;#237;os, Nathan Wachholz, Nicholas Counts, Nicholas Moresco, &amp;#214;rn Arnarson, &amp;#214;rper Forilan, Paul Pluzhnikov, Paul Randal, Philip Hofstetter, Randy True, Ric King, Richard Wells, Rob Bruno, Robert Butler, Ross, Sachin Chitale, Sam Rose, Samuel E Joseph, Scott, Sergey Ten, SonOfSofaman, Stefan Nesinger, Stefanus Du Toit, Stephen Riley, Stephen Smithstone, Steve  Jones, Steve Gorman, Steven Pequeno, Thomas Ballinger, Tom Burns, Vladimir Kanazir, Warren Miller, xisente, Ziggy L</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yt.artemislena.eu/i_wrxBdXTgM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 20:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMDB have deleted all the negative reviews for &amp;quot;The Rings Of Power&amp;quot;. Out of 76 current reviews the lowest is a 5/10 and 65 of them are 8+/10</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/lotr/comments/x46870/imdb_have_deleted_all_the_negative_reviews_for/</link>
      <description>Posted in r/lotr by u/Elijah9677 • 4,197 points and 1,309 comments</description>
      <author> (Elijah9677)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/lotr/comments/x46870/imdb_have_deleted_all_the_negative_reviews_for/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 13:23:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Google employees were swapped with Microsoft employees, what would happen?</title>
      <link>https://www.quora.com/If-Google-employees-were-swapped-with-Microsoft-employees-what-would-happen/answer/David-Seidman</link>
      <description>Answer by David Seidman, 10 years as a Microsoft Program Manager, now at Salesforce</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.quora.com/If-Google-employees-were-swapped-with-Microsoft-employees-what-would-happen/answer/David-Seidman</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 13:23:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - mimoo/noname: Noname: a programming language to write zkapps</title>
      <link>https://github.com/mimoo/noname</link>
      <description>Noname: a programming language to write zkapps. Contribute to mimoo/noname development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (mimoo)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/mimoo/noname</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 13:23:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryant Le on TikTok</title>
      <link>https://www.tiktok.com/@therealbryantle/video/7136860840392707370</link>
      <description>I CHALLENGE 10000 TWITTER SCAMMERS #python #coding #code #tech #fyp #crypto #foryou</description>
      <author> (therealbryantleBryant Le &amp;#183; 5d ago Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiktok.com/@therealbryantle/video/7136860840392707370</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 06:01:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction - The Rust Reference</title>
      <link>https://doc.rust-lang.org/reference/</link>
      <description>This book is the primary reference for the Rust programming language.
It provides three kinds of material:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://doc.rust-lang.org/reference/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 06:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>