<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>The pain points of C# source generators</title>
      <link>https://turnerj.com/blog/the-pain-points-of-csharp-source-generators</link>
      <description>With great power can come great pain points...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://turnerj.com/blog/the-pain-points-of-csharp-source-generators</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 09:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gregory Szorc&amp;#39;s Digital Home | Surprisingly Slow</title>
      <link>https://gregoryszorc.com/blog/2021/04/06/surprisingly-slow/</link>
      <description>I have an affinity for performance optimization and making software as
efficient as possible. Over the years, I&amp;#39;ve encountered specific instances
and common patterns that make software or computers slow. In this post,
I&amp;#39;ll shine a spotlight on some of them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gregoryszorc.com/blog/2021/04/06/surprisingly-slow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 09:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How We Bootstrapped a $1M ARR Email Client</title>
      <link>https://missiveapp.com/blog/how-we-built-1m-arr-email-client</link>
      <description>Five years ago, we launched Missive, an innovative but somewhat hard-to-define email client to the world. Fast-forward to last week when we reached **US$1M** in annual recurring revenue (ARR). This is the story of how we did it.</description>
      <author> (by Philippe
            April 6th, 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://missiveapp.com/blog/how-we-built-1m-arr-email-client</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 08:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core in .NET 6 - Part 04 - DynamicComponent in Blazor</title>
      <link>https://asp.net-hacker.rocks/2021/04/06/aspnetcore6-04-dynamiccomponent.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/juergen.gutsch)</author>
      <guid>https://asp.net-hacker.rocks/2021/04/06/aspnetcore6-04-dynamiccomponent.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 07:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing your $Profile | PowerShell Team</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/optimizing-your-profile/</link>
      <description>Optimizing your $Profile Your PowerShell Profile allows you to customize your PowerShell session and runs at startup. Complex profiles can cause a significant delay in the startup of PowerShell as it is a script that needs to be executed before the prompt first shows up.</description>
      <author> (Steve Lee  Principal Software Engineer Manager, PowerShell Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/optimizing-your-profile/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 06:06:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Azure Data Architecture Map</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-developer-community-blog/the-azure-data-architecture-map/ba-p/2251943</link>
      <description>Hi, &amp;#160; I&amp;#39;m excited to announce this new map and I&amp;#39;m happy to see the great success (beyond expectations) of this map series. With nearly 300K views, these maps even gave birth to a more exhaustive book. &amp;#160; FYI, here are all the maps of the series:  The OpenID Connect (OIDC) Architecture Map The Azure ...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/277009)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-developer-community-blog/the-azure-data-architecture-map/ba-p/2251943</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 06:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t Code Tired | Watch All My Courses For Free This April</title>
      <link>http://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Watch-All-My-Courses-For-Free-This-April</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t Code Tired - Jason Roberts on Software Development and .NET -</description>
      <author> (Jason)</author>
      <guid>http://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Watch-All-My-Courses-For-Free-This-April</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 06:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unparalleled Genius of John von Neumann</title>
      <link>https://www.cantorsparadise.com/the-unparalleled-genius-of-john-von-neumann-791bb9f42a2d</link>
      <description>“Most mathematicians prove what they can, von Neumann proves what he wants”</description>
      <author> (https://jorgenveisdal.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cantorsparadise.com/the-unparalleled-genius-of-john-von-neumann-791bb9f42a2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 06:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Episode: A Journey to .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/dotnet/on-net-episode-a-journey-to-net-maui-40l6</link>
      <description>.NET MAUI is the evolution of Xamarin.Forms and a major aspect of the upcoming .NET 6 release.  In th...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/dotnet/on-net-episode-a-journey-to-net-maui-40l6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 06:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C++ coroutines: Making the promise itself be the shared state, the outline | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210405-00/?p=105054</link>
      <description>Last time, we got the idea of putting the result holder state directly inside the coroutine state. This time, we’ll set to work on the implementation. A restriction we are placing on our simple_task is that it can be co_awaited only once.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210405-00/?p=105054</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 05:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t Be &amp;quot;That Guy&amp;quot; - Scott Kelby&amp;#39;s Photoshop Insider</title>
      <link>https://scottkelby.com/dont-be-that-guy/</link>
      <description>Or “that gal.” Last week my buddy got a new M1 powered MacBook Air. His first new computer for his personal (non-work) use since 2012, and he was really excited about it. He shared a shot of the packaging on social, noted it was his first new one in 9 years, and simply said, “Time […]</description>
      <author> (Scott Kelby)</author>
      <guid>https://scottkelby.com/dont-be-that-guy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 05:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Azure Static Web Apps CLI</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/introducing-the-azure-static-web-apps-cli/ba-p/2257581?WT.mc_id=twitter-0000-azureadvocates</link>
      <description>&amp;#160; &amp;#160; Azure Static Web Apps seamlessly integrates globally distributed hosting for your static content, serverless APIs powered by Azure Functions, as well as features like authentication, custom routing, and route-based authorization. &amp;#160; With the new Static Web Apps CLI, you can now run your entire fu...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/185703)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure/introducing-the-azure-static-web-apps-cli/ba-p/2257581?WT.mc_id=twitter-0000-azureadvocates</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 05:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Facebook Phone Numbers Are Now Searchable in Have I Been Pwned</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/the-facebook-phone-numbers-are-now-searchable-in-have-i-been-pwned/#comment-5332905964</link>
      <description>The headline is pretty self-explanatory so in the interest of time, let me just jump directly into the details of how this all works. There&amp;#39;s been huge interest in this incident, and I&amp;#39;ve seen near-unprecedented traffic to Have I Been Pwned (HIBP) over the last couple of days, let me</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/the-facebook-phone-numbers-are-now-searchable-in-have-i-been-pwned/#comment-5332905964</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 03:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Really Caused Facebook&amp;#39;s 500M-User Data Leak?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/facebook-data-leak-500-million-users-phone-numbers/</link>
      <description>The company&amp;#39;s explanations have been confusing and inconsistent, but there are finally some answers.</description>
      <author> (Lily Hay Newman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wired.com/story/facebook-data-leak-500-million-users-phone-numbers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 03:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All C++20 core language features with examples</title>
      <link>https://oleksandrkvl.github.io/2021/04/02/cpp-20-overview.html</link>
      <description>Introduction</description>
      <author> (Oleksandr Koval)</author>
      <guid>https://oleksandrkvl.github.io/2021/04/02/cpp-20-overview.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 02:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal Adds Payments—With a Privacy-Focused Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/signal-mobilecoin-payments-messaging-cryptocurrency/</link>
      <description>The encrypted messaging app is integrating support for MobileCoin in a bid to keep up with the features offered by its more mainstream rivals.</description>
      <author> (Andy Greenberg)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wired.com/story/signal-mobilecoin-payments-messaging-cryptocurrency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 02:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Richard Campbell on the History of .NET - Episode 133</title>
      <link>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/richard-campbell-on-the-history-of-net-episode-133</link>
      <description>In this episode, Jeffrey and Richard are jumping into part-two of their two-part conversation! If you haven’t caught the previous episode, “Richard Campbell on the Humanitarian Toolbox — Episode 132,” be sure to tune into that first before diving into this one! &amp;amp;nbsp; Richard Campbell is an entrepreneur, advisor, and rabid podcaster. He&amp;#39;s also a Microsoft regional director, the co-host of .NET Rocks, host of the RunAs Radio, and is a consultant and advisor for a number of successful technology firms. Additionally, Richard is the founder of Humanitarian Toolbox, an organization designed to let developers around the world donate their skills to disaster relief organizations by building open-source software. &amp;amp;nbsp; In their last conversation together, Richard spoke about his organization, Humanitarian Toolbox, and their most recent exciting endeavor: the Two Weeks Ready project. In today’s conversation, Richard speaks all about his new project to write a book compiling the history of .NET! He shares why this project is important to him, what it will serve as an important resource to developers new and old to the field, key pieces and insights into the history of .NET, and his predictions on the future of .NET, A.I., automation, and more! &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [:38] Be sure to visit  for past episodes and show notes. [:50] About The Azure DevOps Podcast, Clear Measure, and Jeffrey’s offer to speak at virtual user groups. [1:14] About Jeffrey’s newest podcast, Architect Tips! [1:18] About part-two of the two-part series with Richard Campbell. [1:50] About Richard’s newest project: a book on the history of .NET and how the origin of how he got started with it. [5:28] Richard retells the beginnings of how he approached the history of .NET project. [8:27] The challenges of writing this book and what he hopes to accomplish by writing it. [11:06] What Richard sees as the story and themes of .NET. [12:35] Richard speaks about .NET’s pivot away from a focus on Windows into cross-platform, opensource, Cloud execution; as well as what he sees .NET 5 aiming towards. [16:50] The advantages and disadvantages to upgrading to .NET 5. [18:55] The latest state of power apps and the emergence of a new generation of domain expert developers. [22:24] A word from Azure DevOps Podcast’s sponsor: Clear Measure. [22:56] Discussing the development of automation in the industry. [26:24] Richard’s predictions on the future of augmented reality. [29:00] Jeffrey and Richard speak about how one of the visionaries of .NET, Brian Harry, is focusing his attention on A.I. currently, and what this could mean. [32:08] Why developers need to become proficient in IoT to move A.I. forward. [33:21] Is .NET being maintained because of the developer pool and eventually other things are going to win out? Or, is .NET continuing to grow, strengthen, and are others are going to get “squeezed out” because of it? [37:19] What computing devices does Richard have in his bag and office? [42:24] Jeffrey thanks Richard for joining the podcast! &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:  — New video podcast!   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!  — Click here to download the .NET DevOps for Azure ebook!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!     — Part-One of the Conversation!          — Richard’s Blog   &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/richard-campbell-on-the-history-of-net-episode-133</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy and Rob&amp;#39;s Book</title>
      <link>https://book.troyhunt.com/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://book.troyhunt.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I’m Writing a Book with Rob Conery, and It’s Gonna Be Awesome</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/im-writing-a-book-with-rob-conery-and-its-gonna-be-awesome/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been chatting about this in some of my recent weekly videos and I thought it was finally time to sit down and write the blog post. So, this is a blog post about a book about blog posts. Gotcha, makes sense. It all began when Rob Conery reached out</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/im-writing-a-book-with-rob-conery-and-its-gonna-be-awesome/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic tabstops - a better way to indent and align code</title>
      <link>https://nickgravgaard.com/elastic-tabstops/</link>
      <description>Elastic tabstops - a better way to indent and align code</description>
      <author> (Nick Gravgaard)</author>
      <guid>https://nickgravgaard.com/elastic-tabstops/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Previews Its Own Build of OpenJDK -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/04/06/microsoft-openjdk.aspx</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;a new no-cost long-term supported distribution and Microsoft&amp;#39;s new way to collaborate and contribute to the Java ecosystem.&amp;#39;</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel04/06/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/04/06/microsoft-openjdk.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your E-Mail Validation Logic is Wrong</title>
      <link>https://www.netmeister.org/blog/email.html</link>
      <description>Nope,
you don&amp;#39;t know how to validate an email address. Even
if you think you&amp;#39;d get the domain part right,
fuggeddabout the local part. Seriously.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.netmeister.org/blog/email.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dumping user data from cheap tablets in minutes</title>
      <link>https://blog.m1t.re/posts/klipad-dump/</link>
      <description>Published on 2021-04-06</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.m1t.re/posts/klipad-dump/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Three Un’s of Successful Founders</title>
      <link>https://kellblog.com/2021/04/04/the-three-uns-of-successful-founders/</link>
      <description>I’ve worked with scores of founders and companies over the years and I’ve come to make bright-line distinction between founders and managers.&amp;#160; Let me demonstrate it with a story. One da…</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://kellblog.com/2021/04/04/the-three-uns-of-successful-founders/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portable Internet Behavior Bond</title>
      <link>https://andrewbadr.com/log/29/portable-internet-behavior-bond/</link>
      <description>Makers of free apps, including apps with a free plan or trial period, are forced to spend an inordinate amount of time fighting abuse of their services. Twitter has to fight spam bots, multiplayer games deal with cheaters, dev platforms have people scamming CPU time, anything that touches email needs rules and rate limits—the list goes on. This tiresome work is an endless game of cat-and-mouse, and uses time and money that would ideally be spent on improving features for real users.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewbadr.com/log/29/portable-internet-behavior-bond/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assembling An Atomic Brain?</title>
      <link>https://muircheartblog.wpcomstaging.com/2021/04/06/assembling-an-atomic-brain/</link>
      <description>As so neatly lampooned by xkcd, physicists have a reputation for being just a little reductionist at times. It’s a well-deserved critique in many cases — some sub-fields of our subject …</description>
      <author> (Author: Philip Moriarty)</author>
      <guid>https://muircheartblog.wpcomstaging.com/2021/04/06/assembling-an-atomic-brain/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Non-standard Ways to Fix N+1 Queries in Rails </title>
      <link>https://pawelurbanek.com/rails-n-1-queries</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m not sure if the world needed another post about N+1 queries in Ruby on Rails. To make up for the cliche topic, I&amp;#39;ll describe less common solutions to this problem. Read on if you want to learn how to reduce the number of cascading N+1 SQL queries without using includes or additional table join operations.</description>
      <author> (Paweł Urbanek)</author>
      <guid>https://pawelurbanek.com/rails-n-1-queries</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Use My Free Azure Credit &amp;#128184;</title>
      <link>https://www.thesamosborne.com/posts/how-i-use-my-free-azure-credit/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has a program for all engineer employees to get some free Azure credit to play with. Having been with Microsoft for two summer internships I have accumulated two separate accounts with $150 of credit/month each. Growing up pinching pennies, I am not one to let anything free go to waste, so for the past couple years I have been using my Azure credit for some fun stuff.
1. NextCloud Personal Cloud Storage   NextCloud is super cool if you haven’t heard of it.</description>
      <author> (Sam Osborne)</author>
      <guid>https://www.thesamosborne.com/posts/how-i-use-my-free-azure-credit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Preview of Microsoft Build of OpenJDK | Java at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/announcing-preview-of-microsoft-build-of-openjdk/</link>
      <description>Today we are excited to announce the preview of the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK, a new no-cost Long-Term Support (LTS) distribution of OpenJDK that is open source and available for free for anyone to deploy anywhere. It includes binaries for Java 11,</description>
      <author> (Bruno Borges  Principal Program Manager, Java Engineering Group Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/announcing-preview-of-microsoft-build-of-openjdk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 22:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://whitepaper.zama.ai/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://whitepaper.zama.ai/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 22:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fastest, Safest PNG Decoder in the World</title>
      <link>https://nigeltao.github.io/blog/2021/fastest-safest-png-decoder.html</link>
      <description>Summary: Wuffs’ PNG image decoder is memory-safe but can also clock between
1.22x and 2.75x faster than libpng, the widely used open source C
implementation. It’s also faster than the libspng, lodepng and stb_image
C libraries as well as the most popular Go and Rust PNG libraries. High
performance is achieved by SIMD-acceleration, 8-byte wide input and copies when
bit-twiddling and zlib-decompressing the entire image all-at-once (into one
large intermediate buffer) instead of one row at a time (into smaller,
re-usable buffers). All-at-once requires more intermediate memory but allows
substantially more of the image to be decoded in the zlib-decompressor’s
fastest code paths.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nigeltao.github.io/blog/2021/fastest-safest-png-decoder.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 22:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Sponsors Community</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sponsors/community</link>
      <description>Find new open source contributors to support.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sponsors/community</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 21:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming is hard</title>
      <link>https://dorinlazar.ro/2021-02-programming-is-hard/</link>
      <description>Most beginners in programming eventually end up with the same ingratiating message: „Programming is easy, everyone can do it”, with some threatening message that people doing the gatekeeping should stop doing that. I’m here to tell you that that is not true. Programming is hard, programming is not for everyone, and for the time being everyone might be able to do it, but most definitely most should not. Like most of the empty, shallow, positive messages coming with an automatic defense against refute, in this case talking about this gatekeeping thing that simply doesn’t happen.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dorinlazar.ro/2021-02-programming-is-hard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 21:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help us test payments in Signal</title>
      <link>https://signal.org/blog/help-us-test-payments-in-signal/</link>
      <description>The latest Signal betas are rolling out today. Inside, you’ll find performance enhancements, a slew of bug fixes, improvements to the mute settings, and if you’re in the United Kingdom, you’ll see support for Signal Payments – a new feature that enables you to send and receive privacy focused pay...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://signal.org/blog/help-us-test-payments-in-signal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 20:04:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AsynkronIT/protoactor-dotnet</title>
      <link>https://github.com/AsynkronIT/protoactor-dotnet/blob/dev/src/Proto.Actor/Utils/TypedDictionary.cs#L11</link>
      <description>Proto Actor - Ultra fast distributed actors for Go, C# and Java/Kotlin - AsynkronIT/protoactor-dotnet</description>
      <author> (AsynkronIT)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/AsynkronIT/protoactor-dotnet/blob/dev/src/Proto.Actor/Utils/TypedDictionary.cs#L11</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 20:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eliminating Data Races in Firefox – A Technical Report – Mozilla Hacks - the Web developer blog</title>
      <link>https://hacks.mozilla.org/2021/04/eliminating-data-races-in-firefox-a-technical-report/</link>
      <description>We successfully deployed ThreadSanitizer in the Firefox project to eliminate data races in our remaining C/C++ components. In the process, we found several impactful bugs and can safely say that data races are often underestimated in terms of their impact on program correctness.</description>
      <author> (@mozdeco)</author>
      <guid>https://hacks.mozilla.org/2021/04/eliminating-data-races-in-firefox-a-technical-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 20:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Refused to Become an FBI Informant, and the Government Put Me on the No Fly List</title>
      <link>https://www.aclu.org/news/national-security/i-refused-to-become-an-fbi-informant-and-the-government-put-me-on-the-no-fly-list/</link>
      <description>With the help of the ACLU, I’m bringing a lawsuit to challenge the government’s actions.</description>
      <author> (Ahmad Chebli)</author>
      <guid>https://www.aclu.org/news/national-security/i-refused-to-become-an-fbi-informant-and-the-government-put-me-on-the-no-fly-list/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 20:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET April 2021 Updates – 5.0.5 | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/net-april-2021-updates/</link>
      <description>Today, we are releasing the .NET April 2021 Updates. These updates contains reliability and other non-security improvements. See the individual release notes for details on updated packages. You can download 5.0.5 versions for Windows, macOS, and Linux, for x86, x64, Arm32,</description>
      <author> (Rahul Bhandari  Software Engineer, .NET Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/net-april-2021-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 19:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debugging, Workbench, Raspberry Pi Guidance Highlight VS Code Update -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/04/06/vscode-1-55.aspx</link>
      <description>The latest update to Microsoft&amp;#39;s open source-based, cross-platform code editor features better debugging, many Workbench improvements and new guidance for Raspberry Pi installations.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel04/06/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/04/06/vscode-1-55.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 19:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 5 NuGet Restore Failures on Linux distributions using NSS or ca-certificates | The NuGet Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/nuget/net-5-nuget-restore-failures-on-linux-distributions-using-nss-or-ca-certificates/</link>
      <description>We will be releasing updated builds of NuGet this week to accommodate NuGet restore failures on Linux distributions. The failures are observed when updated versions of the NSS or ca-certificates packages are installed.</description>
      <author> (Jon Douglas  Senior Program Manager, NuGet Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/nuget/net-5-nuget-restore-failures-on-linux-distributions-using-nss-or-ca-certificates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 19:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Degree Should You Pursue to Get a Job in Tech?</title>
      <link>https://codesubmit.io/blog/which-degree-for-a-job-in-tech/</link>
      <description>Whether you’re a high school student trying to figure out which career path to take or someone looking for a career switch, this post lists the various tech careers and the educational routes available to break into tech.</description>
      <author> (Tracy Phillips)</author>
      <guid>https://codesubmit.io/blog/which-degree-for-a-job-in-tech/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 19:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laying Out Pages | Web Browser Engineering</title>
      <link>https://browser.engineering/layout.html</link>
      <description>So far, layout has been a linear process that handles open tags and and close tags independently. But web pages are trees, and look like them: borders and backgrounds visually nest inside one another. To support that, this chapter switches to tree-based layout, where the tree of elements is transformed into a tree of layout objects for the visual elements of the page. In the process, we’ll make our web pages more colorful with backgrounds.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://browser.engineering/layout.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 19:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Toolbox Live - What&amp;#39;s New in VS for Mac?</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lluU4C3Xvdg</link>
      <description>Time to hit that update button Mac users! Join the VS for Mac team in this live show, where we&amp;#39;ll showcase both new and familiar features in VS for Mac.Featu...</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Visual Studio
  
  
    

    
      
    Microsoft Visual Studio
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lluU4C3Xvdg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 19:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MNWITQvvMYU</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io/</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
    

    
      
    .NET Foundation
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MNWITQvvMYU</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 19:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Development with Azure Service Bus</title>
      <link>https://jimmybogard.com/local-development-with-azure-service-bus/</link>
      <description>For teams new to Azure Service Bus, one of the first questions you have to answer is &amp;quot;how do I develop against this?&amp;quot; And it turns out the answer isn&amp;#39;t that straightforward - because it&amp;#39;s currently impossible to run Azure Service Bus outside of Azure. There&amp;#39;s no install. There&amp;#39;s no</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Bogard)</author>
      <guid>https://jimmybogard.com/local-development-with-azure-service-bus/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 19:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Features Every Developer Must Know in C# 9.0</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/syncfusion/4-features-every-developer-must-know-in-c-9-0-3m4g</link>
      <description>This blog explains about the features such as init-only setters, pattern matching and more that every developer must know in the C# 9.0 version.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/syncfusion/4-features-every-developer-must-know-in-c-9-0-3m4g</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 18:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Got Into Computers AppDev Edition</title>
      <link>https://blog.lhotka.net/2021/04/05/How-I-Got-Into-Computers-AppDev-Edition</link>
      <description>This is another in a series about how I got into computers and how my career has unfolded.</description>
      <author> (Rockford Lhotka)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.lhotka.net/2021/04/05/How-I-Got-Into-Computers-AppDev-Edition</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 17:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accessing Dapr secrets building block using Dapr .NET SDK</title>
      <link>https://laurentkempe.com/2021/04/06/accessing-dapr-secrets-building-block-using-dapr-dotnet-sdk/</link>
      <description>In all previous posts, we were looking at the Dapr service invocation building block. We have seen how to expose and call HTTP and gRPC services using it. In this post, we will see how Dapr ease devel</description>
      <author> (Laurent Kemp&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://laurentkempe.com/2021/04/06/accessing-dapr-secrets-building-block-using-dapr-dotnet-sdk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 17:05:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please don’t make me go back: Some of the reasons I hope work from home continues and I never have to return to an office — Ryan Mercer&amp;#39;s Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanmercer.com/ryansthoughts/2021/4/6/some-of-the-reasons-i-hope-work-from-home-continues-and-i-never-have-to-return-to-an-office</link>
      <description>I just hope my employer continues to allow me to work remotely.   Working from home I:    Have been exceeding production for the past year    Don&amp;#39;t have to share a keyboard/mouse/desk with another shift (gross).    Do not spend an hour a day(+/- 10 minutes) driving, and save all the money associated</description>
      <author> (by Ryan Mercer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.ryanmercer.com/ryansthoughts/2021/4/6/some-of-the-reasons-i-hope-work-from-home-continues-and-i-never-have-to-return-to-an-office</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 16:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Standup is a Waste of Time | Build the Stage</title>
      <link>https://buildthestage.com/the-daily-standup-is-a-waste-of-time/</link>
      <description>Daily standups feel like a waste of time. I will teach you two new techniques the will make every minute count.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://buildthestage.com/the-daily-standup-is-a-waste-of-time/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 16:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Things I Hate About PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://rbranson.medium.com/10-things-i-hate-about-postgresql-20dbab8c2791</link>
      <description>Over the last few years, the software development community’s love affair with the popular open-source relational database  has reached a…</description>
      <author> (https://rbranson.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://rbranson.medium.com/10-things-i-hate-about-postgresql-20dbab8c2791</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 16:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C++ coroutines: Building a result holder for movable types | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210406-00/?p=105057</link>
      <description>One of the pieces we need for the simple_promise we use to construct a coroutine is what we have been calling the “result holder”. This is basically a variant that starts out empty, and can atomically transition to holding either the result of a successful coroutine,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210406-00/?p=105057</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 16:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Web API routes [6 of 18] | Beginner&amp;#39;s Series to: Web APIs</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i8iICilTuAs</link>
      <description>What address to do we use to access our Web API resources? How do we know which action method will be called to process a request? In this video, we’ll get t...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i8iICilTuAs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 15:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ll Finish It This Week&amp;quot; And Other Lies</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2103.16574</link>
      <description>A small group of postdocs, graduate students, and undergraduates
inadvertently formed a longitudinal study contrasting expected productivity
levels with actual productivity levels. Over the last nine months, our group
self-reported 559 tasks, dates, and completion times -- expected and actual.
Here, I show which types of tasks we are the worst at completing in the
originally planned amount of time (spoiler: coding and writing tasks), whether
more senior researchers have more accurate expectations (spoiler: not much),
and whether our expectations improve with time (spoiler: only a little).</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 30 Mar 2021])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2103.16574</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 15:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Django 3.2 released | Weblog</title>
      <link>https://www.djangoproject.com/weblog/2021/apr/06/django-32-released/</link>
      <description>Posted by Carlton Gibson on April 6, 2021</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.djangoproject.com/weblog/2021/apr/06/django-32-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 15:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiency of the winsorized and trimmed Harrell-Davis quantile estimators</title>
      <link>https://aakinshin.net/posts/wthdqe-efficiency/</link>
      <description>A set of simulation studies that calculate the efficiency of the winsorized and trimmed Harrell-Davis quantile estimator for different distributions</description>
      <author> (Andrey Akinshin)</author>
      <guid>https://aakinshin.net/posts/wthdqe-efficiency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 14:05:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked phone number of Mark Zuckerberg reveals he is on Signal</title>
      <link>https://www.indiatoday.in/technology/news/story/leaked-phone-number-of-mark-zuckerberg-reveals-he-is-on-signal-1787396-2021-04-05</link>
      <description>Zuckerberg&amp;#39;s phone number was among the leaked data of 533 million Facebook users. A security researcher confirmed that Zuckerberg uses Signal app.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.indiatoday.in/technology/news/story/leaked-phone-number-of-mark-zuckerberg-reveals-he-is-on-signal-1787396-2021-04-05</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 14:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WPO-Foundation/webpagetest-github-action</title>
      <link>https://github.com/WPO-Foundation/webpagetest-github-action</link>
      <description>Automatically test code changes in WebPageTest and enforce performance budgets - WPO-Foundation/webpagetest-github-action</description>
      <author> (WPO-Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/WPO-Foundation/webpagetest-github-action</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 14:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core in Action, Second Edition is available now!</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/my-new-book-aspnetcore-in-action-2e-is-available-now/</link>
      <description>My new book, ASP.NET Core in Action, Second Edition is available now. In this post I describe what&amp;#39;s changed since the first version and why.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/my-new-book-aspnetcore-in-action-2e-is-available-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 13:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking GitHub Private Pages for $35k</title>
      <link>https://robertchen.cc/blog/2021/04/03/github-pages-xss</link>
      <description>Abusing CRLF, cache poisoning, and other misconfigurations for a no-interaction XSS against GitHub Private Pages.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robertchen.cc/blog/2021/04/03/github-pages-xss</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 12:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Now Own the Coinhive Domain. Here&amp;#39;s How I&amp;#39;m Fighting Cryptojacking and Doing Good Things with Content Security Policies.</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/i-now-own-the-coinhive-domain-heres-how-im-fighting-cryptojacking-and-doing-good-things-with-content-security-policies/#comment-5332033276</link>
      <description>If you&amp;#39;ve landed on this page because you saw a strange message on a completely different website then followed a link to here, drop a note to the site owner and let them know what happened. If, on the other hand, you&amp;#39;re on this page because you&amp;#39;re interested in reading</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/i-now-own-the-coinhive-domain-heres-how-im-fighting-cryptojacking-and-doing-good-things-with-content-security-policies/#comment-5332033276</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 12:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 9 pattern matching - Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2021/04/06/c-9-pattern-matching/</link>
      <description>Discover new features for pattern matching in C# 9, including support for combining patterns in both if and switch, nesting patterns, and more.</description>
      <author> (By Tom Deseyn April 6, 2021April 5, 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2021/04/06/c-9-pattern-matching/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 12:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>