<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Stripe Login | Sign in to the Stripe Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://dashboard.stripe.com/settings/billing/automatic</link>
      <description>Sign in to the Stripe Dashboard to manage business payments and operations in your account. Manage payments and refunds, respond to disputes and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dashboard.stripe.com/settings/billing/automatic</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 02:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map of Reddit</title>
      <link>https://anvaka.github.io/map-of-reddit/</link>
      <description>This website shows a map of reddit. Each dot is a subreddit. Two dots within the same cluster are usually close to each other if multiple users frequently leave comments on both subreddits</description>
      <author> (Andrei Kashcha)</author>
      <guid>https://anvaka.github.io/map-of-reddit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 01:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret detection needs to be free, even for private repositories</title>
      <link>https://www.arnica.io/blog/secret-detection-needs-to-be-free-even-for-private-repositories</link>
      <description>Secrets can grant access to data, impact production operations, access third party systems down the software supply chain, and introduce a reputational risk. They can be found in source code, production and CI/CD logs, Docker images, Slack channels, or even on a random shared file. Given how powerful secrets are, it is critical that developer security tools provide secret detection for free across public and private repos.</description>
      <author> (Nir ValtmanMay 12, 2022)</author>
      <guid>https://www.arnica.io/blog/secret-detection-needs-to-be-free-even-for-private-repositories</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 01:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Process Isolation in Firefox 100 – Mozilla Hacks - the Web developer blog</title>
      <link>https://hacks.mozilla.org/2022/05/improved-process-isolation-in-firefox-100/</link>
      <description>Firefox uses a multi-process model for additional security and stability while browsing. Web Content is rendered in separate processes.</description>
      <author> (By
                                        Gian-Carlo Pascutto)</author>
      <guid>https://hacks.mozilla.org/2022/05/improved-process-isolation-in-firefox-100/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 01:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New European strategy for a Better Internet for Kids</title>
      <link>https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/QANDA_22_2826</link>
      <description>New European strategy for a Better Internet for Kids – Questions and Answers</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/QANDA_22_2826</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fhur</title>
      <link>https://fhur.me/posts/theres-no-such-thing-as-a-one-line-change</link>
      <description>fhur&amp;#39;s blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fhur.me/posts/theres-no-such-thing-as-a-one-line-change</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Down a Phishing Attempt | LINQ to Fail</title>
      <link>https://www.aaron-powell.com/posts/2022-05-10-breaking-down-a-phishing-attempt/</link>
      <description>A look at a phishing attempt on me today</description>
      <author> (Aaron Powell)</author>
      <guid>https://www.aaron-powell.com/posts/2022-05-10-breaking-down-a-phishing-attempt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations, you are human!</title>
      <link>http://www.riching.space/2022/05/11/congratulations-you-are-human.html</link>
      <description>Hi, human being. 50 - 70 millennia ago, your great ancestors invented speech. 5 millennia ago, your other ancestors invented writing. That’s the only reason why me and you can communicate through this text right now. Although this communication is one sided, I still find it to be a miracle. I am writing this text on April 10th, 2022, you are reading it sometime in the future. If there’s one thing we can say about humans and why we are so successful as a species, is that we are great at communicating. That’s our superpower.</description>
      <author> (Rich Pavlovskiy)</author>
      <guid>http://www.riching.space/2022/05/11/congratulations-you-are-human.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Farmer&amp;#39;s Fable: Free as in Lunch - Taylor Pearson</title>
      <link>https://taylorpearson.me/interestingtimes/the-farmers-fable/</link>
      <description>Today, I’d like to tell you a little&amp;#160;story about a farmer named Bill. If you’re not into farming, it just so happens that Bill discovers one of the most important principles in investing and decision-making in this story, so there’s also that. Anyway, back to Bill. Bill grows crops. In a good season, Bill harvests... [Read more]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://taylorpearson.me/interestingtimes/the-farmers-fable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I improved myself in 2014</title>
      <link>https://nanxiao.me/en/how-i-improved-myself-in-2014/</link>
      <description>I graduated from school in&amp;#160;2008, and my first job is an embedded software engineer. After working for more than&amp;#160;2&amp;#160;years, I joined in another traditional telecommunication company (let me use&amp;#160;A&amp;#160;to stand for it). Fast forward to&amp;#160;2014, the business of&amp;#160;A&amp;#160;company seemed stagnated for a while: more and more people began to use&amp;#160;OTT applications&amp;#160;from the second decade of&amp;#160;21th&amp;#160;century, and it was a big hurt to telecommunication companies like&amp;#160;A. Though I still had salary increase every year, the amount can be ignored. But the good thing is&amp;#160;A&amp;#160;company has good work-life-balance culture. Besides that, my daily work is: a) Add new trivial features for one system which is written in&amp;#160;C&amp;#160;and run on&amp;#160;Solaris 10. b) Answer technical questions which support engineers don&amp;#39;t know about. Since I had been very familiar with the stuff I was in charge of, I knew I could not absorb new knowledge from&amp;#160;A&amp;#160;company, so I did following things to improve myself in&amp;#160;2014: (1) Read English technical articles. Yes, before&amp;#160;2014, I had mostly used Chinese key words to search related technical posts and read them. After switching to English, I am exposed to another world which has plentiful resource for me to explore. (2) Write English blog. I realised that if I just write Chinese articles, only the people who know Chinese can understand them. But if I record my thoughts in English, the people around the world can read them. Believe it or not, my current employer even referred one of my blog post before I became its employee. (3) Learn git. A&amp;#160;company still used&amp;#160;svn&amp;#160;in&amp;#160;2014, and it was enough for our development procedure. But I knew&amp;#160;git&amp;#160;is the trend. I still remember I read&amp;#160;Pro git&amp;#160;and practised the commands from the book in a server;&amp;#160;Pro git&amp;#160;is the best tutorial of&amp;#160;git&amp;#160;until now. (4) Study Go. Go&amp;#160;became popular in&amp;#160;2014, and the market for&amp;#160;C&amp;#160;developer began to shrink. The reason for me to learn&amp;#160;Go&amp;#160;is simple: hope to secure my future career. I even spent lot of time in trying to run&amp;#160;Go&amp;#160;on&amp;#160;Solaris, but no success. The irony is until this year (2022), I am still a full-time&amp;#160;C&amp;#160;developer and never got a&amp;#160;Go&amp;#160;job. On top of the above things, I also did others: wrote some&amp;#160;DTrace&amp;#160;tutorials in Chinese, joined some&amp;#160;IRC&amp;#160;chat rooms to learn English, etc. All in all, I learnt a lot of new things in&amp;#160;2014. Not every software engineer can work in leading companies which have advanced technologies and did cool things, but everyone can improve himself/herself by self-learning. Hope my story can give others inspiration.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nanxiao.me/en/how-i-improved-myself-in-2014/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lost 4-Dimensional Rotation</title>
      <link>https://rhsimplex.github.io/2022/05/09/lost-4D-rotation/</link>
      <description>Update: r/math discussion Occasionally, an article about the Fourth Dimension pops up on Hacker News. For instance, The Fourth dimension: Toward a geometry of higher reality (1984) submitted Febr</description>
      <author> (Ryan Henderson)</author>
      <guid>https://rhsimplex.github.io/2022/05/09/lost-4D-rotation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandits for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://eugeneyan.com/writing/bandits/</link>
      <description>Industry examples, exploration strategies, warm-starting, off-policy evaluation, and more.</description>
      <author> (https://eugeneyan.com/about/)</author>
      <guid>https://eugeneyan.com/writing/bandits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feedback on “Soul &amp;gt; Features”</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2022/05/12/feedback-on-soul-features/</link>
      <description>I’ve gotten some feedback on the whole idea that software should have a soul, and I’d like to share it with you. Daily Email List reader Chris (shared with permission) said: I’ve …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2022/05/12/feedback-on-soul-features/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Works as Currently Designed</title>
      <link>https://pxlnv.com/blog/works-as-currently-designed/</link>
      <description>I am beginning to think the ways I use AirPlay, which seem entirely normal to me, are exotic outliers heretofore untested by Apple’s engineers because its promise does not match my experience. Here are the two ways I most frequently use AirPlay through my Apple TV: I want to listen to music on my living […]</description>
      <author> (Nick Heer)</author>
      <guid>https://pxlnv.com/blog/works-as-currently-designed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Johnny Decimal system</title>
      <link>https://dsebastien.net/blog/2022-04-29-johnny-decimal</link>
      <description>Discover the Johnny Decimal system and organize anything with grace.</description>
      <author> (https://dsebastien.net)</author>
      <guid>https://dsebastien.net/blog/2022-04-29-johnny-decimal</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Open Source libraries are missing documentation</title>
      <link>https://blog.sandromaglione.com/techblog/why-open-source-library-is-missing-documentation</link>
      <description>Open Source is fun and rewarding, but if you want your work to bring any value you need documentation. Why many library are missing it?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sandromaglione.com/techblog/why-open-source-library-is-missing-documentation</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Potential Merits of an Itemized OS</title>
      <link>https://alexanderobenauer.com/articles/os/1/</link>
      <description>Does an itemized personal computing user environment have the potential to be a new medium in which software could “actually change the thought patterns of an entire civilization” (Kay, 1989)?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alexanderobenauer.com/articles/os/1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>koaning.io: Enjoy the Silence</title>
      <link>https://koaning.io/posts/enjoy-the-silence/</link>
      <description>GridSearch is Not Enough: Part 7</description>
      <author> (Author
      Affiliation
      
        
          
            Vincent Warmerdam)</author>
      <guid>https://koaning.io/posts/enjoy-the-silence/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Programming Principles</title>
      <link>https://lucapette.me/writing/my-programming-principles/</link>
      <description>What guides me after 20 years of writing code for a living</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lucapette.me/writing/my-programming-principles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate By Population</title>
      <link>https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1N4xCSR5NgoQykK_nQhkbdGd2WzLISD_t-DmUbfTFPfs/edit#gid=123145369</link>
      <description>NST01

table with row headers in column A and column headers in rows 3 through 4. (leading dots indicate sub-parts)
Table 1. Annual Estimates of the Resident Population for the United States, Regions, States, and Puerto Rico: April 1, 2010 to July 1, 2019
Geographic Area,April 1, 2010,Population ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1N4xCSR5NgoQykK_nQhkbdGd2WzLISD_t-DmUbfTFPfs/edit#gid=123145369</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 22:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical bruteforce of AES-1024 military grade encryption</title>
      <link>https://research.kudelskisecurity.com/2022/05/11/practical-bruteforce-of-aes-1024-military-grade-encryption/</link>
      <description>I recently presented work on the analysis of a file encryption solution that claimed to implement “AES-1024 military grade encryption”. Spoiler alert: I did not break AES, and this work…</description>
      <author> (sylvain)</author>
      <guid>https://research.kudelskisecurity.com/2022/05/11/practical-bruteforce-of-aes-1024-military-grade-encryption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Azure Cosmos DB Journey to .NET 6</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/the-azure-cosmos-db-journey-to-net-6/</link>
      <description>Azure Cosmos DB is a fully-managed, multi-tenant, distributed, shared-nothing, horizontally scalable database that provides planet-scale NoSQL capabilities offering APIs for Apache Cassandra, MongoDB, Gremlin, Tables, and the Core (SQL) APIs . A core component of the Azure Cosmos DB service is the API Gateway that handles request parsing and routing across all supported APIs.</description>
      <author> (Vinod S)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/the-azure-cosmos-db-journey-to-net-6/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>teenage engineering</title>
      <link>https://teenage.engineering/</link>
      <description>louder, thinner and 100 times better.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://teenage.engineering/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 22:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generalist Agent</title>
      <link>https://www.deepmind.com/publications/a-generalist-agent</link>
      <description>Inspired by progress in large-scale language modelling, we apply a similar approach towards building a single generalist agent beyond the realm of text outputs. The agent, which we refer to as Gato, works as a multi-modal, multi-task, multi-embodiment generalist policy. The same network with the same weights can play Atari, caption images, chat, stack blocks with a real robot arm and much more, deciding based on its context whether to output text, joint torques, button presses, or other tokens. In this report we describe the model and the data, and document the current capabilities of Gato.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.deepmind.com/publications/a-generalist-agent</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 21:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuckDB - Friendlier SQL with DuckDB</title>
      <link>https://duckdb.org/2022/05/04/friendlier-sql.html</link>
      <description>2022-05-04Alex Monahan</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://duckdb.org/2022/05/04/friendlier-sql.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 21:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - alufers/mitmproxy2swagger: Automagically reverse-engineer REST APIs via capturing traffic</title>
      <link>https://github.com/alufers/mitmproxy2swagger</link>
      <description>Automagically reverse-engineer REST APIs via capturing traffic - GitHub - alufers/mitmproxy2swagger: Automagically reverse-engineer REST APIs via capturing traffic</description>
      <author> (alufers)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/alufers/mitmproxy2swagger</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 20:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Other Kind of Staff Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://earthly.dev/blog/line-staff/</link>
      <description>Let’s talk about a career in tech, but not the usual boring stuff about salary or how to pass the interview process at the place with the most over...</description>
      <author> (Adam Gordon Bell)</author>
      <guid>https://earthly.dev/blog/line-staff/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 20:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2022 17.2 Goes GA, Faces Update Issues -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/05/12/vs-2022-17-2.aspx</link>
      <description>  Visual Studio 2022 17.2 reached General Availability status this week, but some users outside the U.S. soon encountered download update issues.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel05/12/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/05/12/vs-2022-17-2.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 19:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: Web Forms Is No Silverlight -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/05/12/web-forms-silverlight.aspx</link>
      <description>The death of Web Forms has been greatly exaggerated.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel05/12/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/05/12/web-forms-silverlight.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 19:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting up an Azure Virtual Machine as Azure DevOps build agent</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/setting-up-an-azure-vm-devops-build-agent/</link>
      <description>This post is about how we can setup as Azure Virtual Machine as Azure DevOps build agent. Recently I had to provision one virtual machine as Azure DevOps build agent. First we need to create an Azure Virtual machine. I created one with default configuration values.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/setting-up-an-azure-vm-devops-build-agent/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 19:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia takes first step toward open source Linux GPU drivers</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2022/05/nvidia-takes-first-step-toward-open-source-linux-gpu-drivers/</link>
      <description>Both Intel and AMD have maintained mostly open source Linux drivers for years.</description>
      <author> (Andrew Cunningham
    -  5/12/2022, 9:58 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2022/05/nvidia-takes-first-step-toward-open-source-linux-gpu-drivers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 18:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take your first steps with F# - Learn</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/paths/fsharp-first-steps/</link>
      <description>F# is an open-source, cross-platform programming language that makes it easy to write succinct, performant, robust, and practical code. It&amp;#39;s a general-purpose language that enables you to create many different types of applications like Web API, Desktop, IoT, Gaming and more.</description>
      <author> (softchris)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/paths/fsharp-first-steps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Miss Heroku&amp;#39;s DevEx</title>
      <link>https://christine.website/blog/heroku-devex-2022-05-12</link>
      <description>I Miss Heroku&amp;#39;s DevEx - Xe&amp;#39;s Blog</description>
      <author> (Xe Iaso)</author>
      <guid>https://christine.website/blog/heroku-devex-2022-05-12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get rid of gerrymandering: the math is surprising</title>
      <link>https://demodexio.substack.com/p/how-to-get-rid-of-gerrymandering</link>
      <description>Gerrymandering distorts the will of the people, but the basic math of geographic representation makes it difficult to get rid of, unless we get rid of representation for geographic districts.</description>
      <author> (Lawrence Krubner)</author>
      <guid>https://demodexio.substack.com/p/how-to-get-rid-of-gerrymandering</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 14:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EU Commission is planning automatic CSAM scanning of your  private communication – or total surveillance in the name of child protection.</title>
      <link>https://tutanota.com/blog/posts/eu-surveillance-csam/</link>
      <description>This would be the worst surveillance apparatus outside of China, and completely disproportionate.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tutanota.com/blog/posts/eu-surveillance-csam/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Pub/Sub: Programmable MQTT-based Messaging</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/announcing-pubsub-programmable-mqtt-messaging/</link>
      <description>Announcing the beta of Cloudflare Pub/Sub, our programmable, serverless message broker built on the open MQTT messaging standard</description>
      <author> (Matt Silverlock)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/announcing-pubsub-programmable-mqtt-messaging/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regular Expression Improvements in .NET 7</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/regular-expression-improvements-in-dotnet-7/</link>
      <description>System.Text.RegularExpressions has improved significantly in .NET 7. In this post, we&amp;#39;ll deep-dive into many of its exciting improvements.</description>
      <author> (Stephen T)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/regular-expression-improvements-in-dotnet-7/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 13:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Important notice for all customers | BitPrime</title>
      <link>https://www.bitprime.co.nz/important-notice-for-all-customers/</link>
      <description>Important Notice For All CustomersAs you may have noticed over the last 48 hours, trading on the BitPrime retail website has been suspended. Since then, a maintenance notice has been up on our website.This pause in trading is due to liquidity issues combined with extreme market volatility, which has increased over the last 48 hours.You ... Read more</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bitprime.co.nz/important-notice-for-all-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 12:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World&amp;#39;s Best FPV Drone Shot? (Extreme Mountain Biking)</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/13OtZFWdhwQ</link>
      <description>This is a drone shot like you&amp;#39;ve never seen before. Nicholi Rogatkin takes the @Dutch Drone Gods to the most epic urban mountain bike race in the world with ...</description>
      <author> (AuthenTech - Ben Schmanke
  
  
  
    AuthenTech - Ben Schmanke)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/13OtZFWdhwQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 10:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What backs a currency? Terra Luna drops nearly 100% - Economics - Intercoin</title>
      <link>https://community.intercoin.org/t/what-backs-a-currency-terra-luna-drops-nearly-100/2518</link>
      <description>I think this shows why having sound reserves matters. Whether it’s China’s Evergrande or Tether or Luna, people are relying on some assets to back the currency. But what happens when those assets themselves become less in demand (say, because the central bank raises interest rates?) Or if we find out (as in the case of Lehman Brothers) that the third party auditors cannot be trusted?    Intercoin should be different as it can be “backed by” the community currencies themselves, ie the goods and s...</description>
      <author> (EGreg)</author>
      <guid>https://community.intercoin.org/t/what-backs-a-currency-terra-luna-drops-nearly-100/2518</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 09:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone Number Validation in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://jamilhallal.blogspot.com/2022/05/phone-number-validation-in-javascript.html</link>
      <description>Step by step guide to develop JavaScript methods to check for valid phone numbers</description>
      <author> (Jamil Hallal)</author>
      <guid>https://jamilhallal.blogspot.com/2022/05/phone-number-validation-in-javascript.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 09:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Convert JSON to XML or XML to JSON in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-convert-json-to-xml-or-xml-to-json/</link>
      <description>Demonstrate how to convert JSON to XML back and forth using System.Text.Json and Newtonsoft.Json with detail explanation and examples</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-convert-json-to-xml-or-xml-to-json/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 09:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deno.js in production. Key takeaways.</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@sdesalas/deno-js-in-production-main-takeaways-247a2fd2d198</link>
      <description>TL/DR: The hot new JavaScript runtime by Ryan Dahl is sleek, powerful and easy to use. Most importantly, it is TypeScript native with a…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@sdesalas)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@sdesalas/deno-js-in-production-main-takeaways-247a2fd2d198</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 06:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure and Organize .NET Projects with Rider | The .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/05/11/structure-and-organize-net-projects-with-rider/</link>
      <description>Whether you’re starting out with a new project or refactoring a mature codebase, good folder and file organization makes your life less stressful. Having a good structure for your project creates an a</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2022/05/11/structure-and-organize-net-projects-with-rider/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Program - AusCERT Cyber Security Conference</title>
      <link>https://conference.auscert.org.au/program/</link>
      <description>9:00am</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://conference.auscert.org.au/program/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 06:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Modeling - Anemic Models</title>
      <link>https://ardalis.com/domain-modeling-anemic-models/</link>
      <description>When building a domain model, proper object-oriented design and encapsulation should be applied as much as possible. Some teams choose to intentionally create anemic models with little encapsulation, which can lead to problems.</description>
      <author> (Ardalis)</author>
      <guid>https://ardalis.com/domain-modeling-anemic-models/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 06:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to hash passwords and when not to</title>
      <link>https://advancedweb.hu/how-to-hash-passwords-and-when-not-to/</link>
      <description>What is entropy and how it changes how to store and transmit passwords</description>
      <author> (Tam&amp;#225;s Sallai)</author>
      <guid>https://advancedweb.hu/how-to-hash-passwords-and-when-not-to/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 06:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quic.cs</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/davidfowl/b7c28c87dd523686450ef98b73c6171d</link>
      <description>GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/davidfowl/b7c28c87dd523686450ef98b73c6171d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# Method to Check if a Number is Prime</title>
      <link>https://jamilhallal.blogspot.com/2022/05/c-method-to-check-if-number-is-prime.html</link>
      <description>The Best C# method to check if a number is a prime</description>
      <author> (Jamil Hallal)</author>
      <guid>https://jamilhallal.blogspot.com/2022/05/c-method-to-check-if-number-is-prime.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 05:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuring the Diagnostics Port for dotnet monitor</title>
      <link>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/configuring-the-diagnostics-port-for-dotnet-monitor</link>
      <description>So I have been working on the dotnet-monitor tool team since inception and ...</description>
      <author> (Mark Downie)</author>
      <guid>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/configuring-the-diagnostics-port-for-dotnet-monitor</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 05:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report a problem with Visual Studio - Visual Studio (Windows)</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/visualstudio/ide/how-to-report-a-problem-with-visual-studio</link>
      <description>Find out how to report a problem with Visual Studio</description>
      <author> (madskristensen)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/visualstudio/ide/how-to-report-a-problem-with-visual-studio</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 05:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Chrome 99 expands Certificate Transparency, breaking all MitM dev tools</title>
      <link>https://httptoolkit.tech/blog/chrome-android-certificate-transparency/</link>
      <description>Certificate transparency is superb improvement to HTTPS certificate security on the web that&amp;#39;s great for users and businesses, but on…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://httptoolkit.tech/blog/chrome-android-certificate-transparency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 05:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>