<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Building a swipe card jukebox using a Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://helen.blog/2019/12/building-a-swipe-card-jukebox-using-a-raspberry-pi/</link>
      <description>You know how everybody hates on recipe blogs that start posts with stories even though a) it’s good for copyright and b) stories can tell you a lot of things about humans and the why and how of their food, well if that’s you then you’re going to hate this tech recipe! Or you’ve already scrolled past this.</description>
      <author> (helen)</author>
      <guid>https://helen.blog/2019/12/building-a-swipe-card-jukebox-using-a-raspberry-pi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 05:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watchfinder tool | NOMOS Glashütte</title>
      <link>https://nomos-glashuette.com/en/watchfinder-377?o=9&amp;cf=4%7C11%7C40</link>
      <description>Automatic or manual? With a date or world time function? A classic white dial or something more colorful? Find the perfect mechanical watch for you today.
</description>
      <author> (NOMOS Glashütte)</author>
      <guid>https://nomos-glashuette.com/en/watchfinder-377?o=9&amp;cf=4%7C11%7C40</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 05:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MakerDAO gets stress tested as ETH price plummets</title>
      <link>https://messari.io/article/makerdao-gets-stress-tested-as-eth-price-plummets</link>
      <description>In the midst of extreme market-wide turmoil, MakerDAO is facing one of its biggest challenges to date. The main form of collateral in the system, Ether, has dropped over 30% in a 24-hour timeframe marking one of the worst days in its short history. This has triggered an unprecedented wave of liquidations as loans quickly became undercollateralized.

Source: Dune Analytic. Scripts created by Teo Leibowitz.

Normally when the price drops causing a position to fall below the 150% required collateralization ratio, third-party liquidation bots known as Keepers can bid Dai for the underlying collateral in return for a small fee. This ensures the system remains whole and the debt is fully paid back. However, things became complicated today as the Ethereum network became congested leading to oracle’s price updates not going through with the gas price they chose.

This means Maker was not receiving the correct price of ETH needed to ensure proper liquidations. At one point the price feeds were showing $166 while the real price was 15% lower.  Not only did this affect oracles, but Keepers likely did not have their bots configured to bid up gas prices meaning the collateral bids were also not going through, allowing some lucky liquidators to escape with collateral for free. This put the system in a $4 million deficit since collateral was leaving the system without any debt being paid back.

Why it matters
The value in stablecoins like Dai lies in the fact they can be redeemed for their underlying collateral. In circumstances such as this, when there isn’t adequate collateral to back the asset, it can break the system unless otherwise remedied. To prevent this, MakerDAO has a Debt Auction mechanism where the protocol can inflate the supply of MKR in order to make up for the losses. This amount to a system-wide bailout where MKR holders shoulder the burden by way of dilution in order to keep the network functioning.
Another worst-case option being considered is an Emergency Shutdown. This would unwind the whole system returning collateral to Vault owners first and then to Dai holders who would be at risk of receiving a haircut. If this were to occur, it would likely erode faith in the idea of crypto-collateralized stablecoins, damaging one of the most essential components of Open Finance.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://messari.io/article/makerdao-gets-stress-tested-as-eth-price-plummets</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 04:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://curiositystream.com/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://curiositystream.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 02:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Gettysburg</title>
      <link>https://mrgettysburg.com/</link>
      <description>LEGI, INTELLEXI, ET CONDEMNAVI LEFT CENTER RIGHT</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mrgettysburg.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft announces change to its board of directors</title>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/microsoft-announces-change-to-its-board-of-directors-301023293.html</link>
      <description>/PRNewswire/ -- Microsoft Corp. today announced that Co-Founder and Technology Advisor Bill Gates stepped down from the company's Board of Directors to...</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Corporation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/microsoft-announces-change-to-its-board-of-directors-301023293.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comcast accidentally published 200,000 “unlisted” phone numbers</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/03/comcast-accidentally-published-200000-unlisted-phone-numbers/</link>
      <description>Comcast made the same mistake once before and had to pay $33 million.</description>
      <author> (Jon Brodkin
    -  3/11/2020, 2:26 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/03/comcast-accidentally-published-200000-unlisted-phone-numbers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com: Lopbraa Piranha Plants Cannibal Flower Style Plush Slippers Loafer with Pipe Pot Holder for Adults Teens (Piranha Plants): Toys &amp; Games</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/Lopbraa-Piranha-Plants-Cannibal-Slippers/dp/B07R65V452/ref=as_li_ss_tl?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202003</link>
      <description>Amazon.com: Lopbraa Piranha Plants Cannibal Flower Style Plush Slippers Loafer with Pipe Pot Holder for Adults Teens (Piranha Plants): Toys &amp; Games</description>
      <author> (by










Lopbraa)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/Lopbraa-Piranha-Plants-Cannibal-Slippers/dp/B07R65V452/ref=as_li_ss_tl?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202003</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 23:07:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm Now Running Remote Workshops</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/im-now-running-remote-workshops/</link>
      <description>Almost 2 and a half years ago to the day, I left the corporate world. It's funny looking back on it because on the one hand, 2 and a half years isn't that long but on the other hand, it was a lifetime ago; my life is totally different today</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/im-now-running-remote-workshops/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDC Porto 2020</title>
      <link>https://ndcporto.com/</link>
      <description>NDC Porto 2020 is a 4-day online event with workshops 21-22 April followed by a 2 day conference 23-24 April.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ndcporto.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 23:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDC Copenhagen 2020</title>
      <link>https://ndccopenhagen.com/</link>
      <description>NDC Copenhagen, 1-3 April 2020 DGI-byen, Copenhagen, Denmark. NDC Copenhagen is a conference for Software Developers. The conference consists of 2 days of pre-conference workshops followed by 1 day of conference talks. NDC Mini Copenhagen is an event for software developers that covers: .NET, Architecture,Cloud, Cross-Platform, DevOps, Functional Programming, JavaScript, Machine Learning, Microservices, Microsoft, Security, Testing, ToolsWeb, Work Skills and more. NDC Copenhagen, 1-3 April 2020 - DGI-byen, Copenhagen, Denmark.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ndccopenhagen.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 23:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check out the lineup of GDC 2020 virtual talks and awards you can stream next week!</title>
      <link>https://gdconf.com/news/check-out-lineup-gdc-2020-virtual-talks-and-awards-you-can-stream-next-week</link>
      <description>Just a quick reminder that while GDC is no longer happening next week in San Francisco, organizers invite you to watch livestreams of the awards and some of the talks planned for GDC 2020! </description>
      <author> (By Staff | March 13, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://gdconf.com/news/check-out-lineup-gdc-2020-virtual-talks-and-awards-you-can-stream-next-week</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 22:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy your own video collaboration app in five minutes or less</title>
      <link>https://www.twilio.com/blog/open-source-video-apps-reactjs-ios-android</link>
      <description>Get a head start on your video app development with three new Twilio open sourced video collaboration applications for iOS, Android, and ReactJS for the Web.</description>
      <author> (By Aaron Alaniz
      2020-03-12)</author>
      <guid>https://www.twilio.com/blog/open-source-video-apps-reactjs-ios-android</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 22:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation's Nerds Wake Up In Utopia Where Everyone Stays Inside, Sports Are Canceled, Social Interaction Forbidden</title>
      <link>https://babylonbee.com/news/nations-nerds-wake-up-in-utopia-where-everyone-stays-inside-sports-canceled-social-interaction-forbidden</link>
      <description>U.S.&amp;mdash;The nation&amp;#39;s nerds woke up in a utopia this morning, one where everyone stays inside, sporting events are being canceled, and all social interaction is forbidden.All types of nerds, from social introverts to hardcore PC gamers,&amp;nbsp;welcomed the dawn of this new era, privately from their own homes.&amp;quot;I have been waiting my whole life for this &amp;hellip;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://babylonbee.com/news/nations-nerds-wake-up-in-utopia-where-everyone-stays-inside-sports-canceled-social-interaction-forbidden</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 21:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soloslides - Play a slideshow of your Google Photos</title>
      <link>https://soloslides.app/</link>
      <description>Soloslides is an iOS app that connects to Google Photos and plays simple slideshows on your iPad or iPhone. It can play directly on your Smart TV.</description>
      <author> (Screenthink)</author>
      <guid>https://soloslides.app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 19:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A's from "Building your first Blazor App"</title>
      <link>https://community.devexpress.com/blogs/aspnet/archive/2020/03/06/q-amp-a-39-s-from-quot-building-your-first-blazor-app-quot.aspx</link>
      <description>JavaScript, HTML 5, ASP.NET, DevExpress, ASP.NET MVC &amp; WebForms, and News - Mehul Harry's DevExpress blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://community.devexpress.com/blogs/aspnet/archive/2020/03/06/q-amp-a-39-s-from-quot-building-your-first-blazor-app-quot.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 19:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's behind the hype about Blazor? - Stack Overflow Blog</title>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.blog/2020/02/26/whats-behind-the-hype-about-blazor/?hss_channel=tw-4083531</link>
      <description>Blazor is a new client-side UI framework from the ASP.NET team. Its big selling point is the ability to write rich web UI experiences using HTML, CSS, and C# instead of JavaScript—something a lot of developers have been dreaming of.</description>
      <author> (Chris Sainty)</author>
      <guid>https://stackoverflow.blog/2020/02/26/whats-behind-the-hype-about-blazor/?hss_channel=tw-4083531</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 19:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EdDSA, Ed25519, Ed25519-IETF, Ed25519ph, Ed25519ctx, HashEdDSA, PureEdDSA, WTF?</title>
      <link>https://cryptologie.net/article/497/eddsa-ed25519-ed25519-ietf-ed25519ph-ed25519ctx-hasheddsa-pureeddsa-wtf/</link>
      <description>The Edwards-curve Digital Signature Algorithm (EdDSA)
You've heard of EdDSA right? The shiny and new signature scheme (well new, it's been here since 2008, wake up).
Since its inception, EdDSA has evolved quite a lot, and some amount of standardization process has happened to it. It's even doomed to be adopted by the NIST in FIPS 186-5!
First, some definition:

EdDSA stands for Edwards-curve Digit ...</description>
      <author> (david wong)</author>
      <guid>https://cryptologie.net/article/497/eddsa-ed25519-ed25519-ietf-ed25519ph-ed25519ctx-hasheddsa-pureeddsa-wtf/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 19:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Web API + Entity Framework Core : Installing Swagger/OpenAPI - EP10</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S_ocVXMMbSA</link>
      <description>Hey Yo,

Please subscribe here - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCetyodKOWGk5H6FoKoFnkZw
Like our page - https://www.facebook.com/curiousdrive/
Follow us on - https://twitter.com/curious_drive
Talk to us on - https://www.twitch.tv/curiousdrive
Follow us on - https://www.instagram.com/curiousdrive/

Find code here...
https://github.com/CuriousDrive/BookStores

In this ASP.NET #WebAPI #EntityFramework Core tutorial, I am going through steps on how you can install and use #Swagger/#OpenAPI.

Content - 
1. UseSwagger()
2. AddSwaggerGen()
3. SwaggerDoc()
4. UseSwaggerUI()
5. SwaggerEndpoint()
6. Using Swagger UI 



Happy Coding!!</description>
      <author> (Curious Drive)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S_ocVXMMbSA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 18:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTTP Desync Attacks: Request Smuggling Reborn</title>
      <link>https://portswigger.net/research/http-desync-attacks-request-smuggling-reborn</link>
      <description>HTTP Desync Attacks: Request Smuggling Reborn</description>
      <author> (James Kettle
        
            @albinowax)</author>
      <guid>https://portswigger.net/research/http-desync-attacks-request-smuggling-reborn</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 17:36:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is HTTP request smuggling? Tutorial &amp; Examples | Web Security Academy</title>
      <link>https://portswigger.net/web-security/request-smuggling</link>
      <description>In this section, we'll explain HTTP request smuggling attacks and describe how common request smuggling vulnerabilities can arise. What is HTTP request ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://portswigger.net/web-security/request-smuggling</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 17:23:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slack disclosed on HackerOne: Mass account takeovers using HTTP...</title>
      <link>https://hackerone.com/reports/737140</link>
      <description>This researcher exploited an HTTP Request Smuggling bug on a Slack asset to perform a CL.TE-based hijack onto neighboring customer requests. This hijack forced the victim into an open-redirect that forwarded the victim onto the researcher's collaborator client with slack domain cookies. The posted cookies in the customer request on the collaborator client contained the customer's secret session...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hackerone.com/reports/737140</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 17:19:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Invalidate Azure Key Vault Secrets</title>
      <link>https://background-jobs.arcus-azure.net/features/security/auto-invalidate-secrets</link>
      <description>Background job development in Azure with a breeze</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://background-jobs.arcus-azure.net/features/security/auto-invalidate-secrets</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 17:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomasz Łakomy</title>
      <link>https://egghead.io/instructors/tomasz-lakomy</link>
      <description>Senior Frontend Engineer at OLX Group. His interests include React, Svelte, cypress, VR, app performance and... jQuery, which he still thinks is the best library ever.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://egghead.io/instructors/tomasz-lakomy</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows PowerShell for Developers</title>
      <link>http://shop.oreilly.com/product/0636920024491.do</link>
      <description>Want to perform programming tasks better, faster, simpler, and make them repeatable? Take a deep dive into Windows PowerShell and discover what this distributed automation platform can do. Whether you’re a .NET developer or IT pro, this...</description>
      <author> (Douglas Finke)</author>
      <guid>http://shop.oreilly.com/product/0636920024491.do</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Human Experience – The story of computing is the story of humanity.™</title>
      <link>https://computingthehumanexperience.com/</link>
      <description>The story of computing is the story of humanity: this is a story of ambition, invention, creativity, vision, avarice, and serendipity, powered by a refusal to accept the limits of our bodies and our minds. Computing: The Human Experience is a transmedia project that explores the science of computing, examines the connections among computing, individuals, and society, and contemplates the future, taking us on a journey of what it means to be human in the face of a technology that can amplify us, diminish us, and perhaps even replace us.</description>
      <author> (Herbert Simon)</author>
      <guid>https://computingthehumanexperience.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DotNet 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.eventbrite.es/e/entradas-dotnet-2020-90785926149</link>
      <description>Vuelve el evento técnico de desarrollo más importante de España.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.eventbrite.es/e/entradas-dotnet-2020-90785926149</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Em Lazer-Walker</title>
      <link>https://lazerwalker.com/</link>
      <description>I make experimental games, interactive art, and software tools. I thrive at the intersection of HCI
                    and game design; most of my work uses nontraditional interfaces tospark intellectual curiosity about
                    the wider world. By day, I work as a developer advocate at Microsoft.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lazerwalker.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft To Do</title>
      <link>https://to-do.microsoft.com/</link>
      <description>Microsoft To Do</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://to-do.microsoft.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Difference Between API Gateways and Service Mesh - Cloud Native Computing Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2020/03/06/the-difference-between-api-gateways-and-service-mesh/</link>
      <description>Guest post originally published on Kong’s blog by Marco Palladino, co-founder and CTO, Kong Why API Management and Service Mesh are Complementary Patterns for Different Use Cases Note: The goal...</description>
      <author> (By cncf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2020/03/06/the-difference-between-api-gateways-and-service-mesh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researching the optimal; implementing the practical</title>
      <link>https://dfinke.github.io/</link>
      <description>Contact Doug with your automation needs email finked@hotmail.com</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dfinke.github.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Garden of Earthly Delights - Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Garden_of_Earthly_Delights</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Garden_of_Earthly_Delights</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DotNet 2020, el mayor evento de .NET de España</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnet2020.com/</link>
      <description>DotNet 2020  es la conferencia de desarrolladores centrada en las últimas tendencias, con ponentes internacionales especializados en el desarrollo web, arquitectura de software, Inteligencia Artificial, Machine Learning, Blockchain, Javascript, Xamarin, equipos y colaboración</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnet2020.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About service meshes - Azure Kubernetes Service</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/aks/servicemesh-about</link>
      <description>Obtain an overview of service meshes, their architecture and capabilities, and what criteria you should consider when selecting one to deploy.</description>
      <author> (paulbouwer)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/aks/servicemesh-about</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When You Do (and Don't Need) a Service Mesh - The New Stack</title>
      <link>https://thenewstack.io/when-you-do-and-dont-need-a-service-mesh/</link>
      <description>A decision tree for determining if, and when, you will need a service mesh.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thenewstack.io/when-you-do-and-dont-need-a-service-mesh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This PIN Can Be Easily Guessed</title>
      <link>https://this-pin-can-be-easily-guessed.github.io/</link>
      <description>A comprehensive study of user-chosen 4- and 6-digit smartphone unlock PINs.</description>
      <author> (Philipp Markert, Daniel V. Bailey, Maximilian Golla, Markus Duermuth, and Adam J. Aviv)</author>
      <guid>https://this-pin-can-be-easily-guessed.github.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 14:07:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure API for FHIR(r) | Microsoft Azure</title>
      <link>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/azure-api-for-fhir/</link>
      <description>Azure API for FHIR® is a fully managed, open standards–based API for health data. Create new systems of engagement that drive actionable intelligence.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/azure-api-for-fhir/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 14:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo NES FamiCom Creator - Computerphile</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/EbL9OFlxwV8</link>
      <description>Bring Donkey Kong home! - The unenviable task given to Masayuki Uemura by Nintendo bosses in the early '80s. Unimpressed by Atari's 2600 they set out to bring a true videogame arcade experience into the home.

Many thanks to The National Videogame Museum in Sheffield UK for setting up this interview: http://bit.ly/C_NVM 

Thanks also to Akinori Nakamura for interpreting for us. 

See the full (almost) un-edited interview here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zYeDqmV_W1k 

https://www.facebook.com/computerphile
https://twitter.com/computer_phile

This video was filmed and edited by Sean Riley.

Computer Science at the University of Nottingham: https://bit.ly/nottscomputer

Computerphile is a sister project to Brady Haran's Numberphile. More at http://www.bradyharan.com</description>
      <author> (Computerphile)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/EbL9OFlxwV8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 13:59:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Uncensored Library – Reporters without borders</title>
      <link>https://uncensoredlibrary.com/en</link>
      <description>I support The Uncensored Library and the fight for press freedom. #TruthFindsAWay</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://uncensoredlibrary.com/en</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 13:57:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Acadia Nights: Episode 2 - Wild-Eyed Southern Boys</title>
      <link>https://www.twitch.tv/scratticus</link>
      <description>Twitch is the world's leading video platform and community for gamers.</description>
      <author> (Scratticus)</author>
      <guid>https://www.twitch.tv/scratticus</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 12:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conference Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.ndcconferences.com/conference-update/</link>
      <description>The health and safety of our community is our first priority. As a result of the global COVID-19 virus situation we are transforming our upcoming 2020 events to online. We know an online event can’t fully replace an in-person event, but we are working hard to ensure our online</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ndcconferences.com/conference-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 12:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Vacancy Has Been Detected</title>
      <link>https://kellysutton.com/2019/06/19/a-vacancy-has-been-detected.html</link>
      <description>College was a superlative time in my life. I made lifelong friends, had many opportunities, and even started a little business.</description>
      <author> (http://kellysutton.com)</author>
      <guid>https://kellysutton.com/2019/06/19/a-vacancy-has-been-detected.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 12:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Kernel Teaching — The Linux Kernel documentation</title>
      <link>https://linux-kernel-labs.github.io/refs/heads/master/index.html</link>
      <description>This is a collection of lectures and labs Linux kernel topics. The
lectures focus on theoretical and Linux kernel exploration.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://linux-kernel-labs.github.io/refs/heads/master/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 11:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 182</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-182/</link>
      <description>Geez, where do you even begin given how the world has turned just in the last week? I spend a good quarter hour at the start of this video talking about what I'll be doing, namely getting on with business and running a bunch of public workshops remotely in conjunction</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-182/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 11:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double Your Productivity</title>
      <link>https://www.doubleyourproductivity.io/</link>
      <description>It doesn’t have to be this way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.doubleyourproductivity.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 10:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Postman Mock Call Logs - Postman Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.postman.com/2020/03/11/introducing-postman-mock-call-logs/</link>
      <description>With the most recent release of Postman, we introduced call logging to ensure that mock servers generated from Postman collections are more useful. Prior to this release, you could publish a mock server from any… Continue reading "Introducing Postman Mock Call Logs"...</description>
      <author> (Author: Kin Lane)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.postman.com/2020/03/11/introducing-postman-mock-call-logs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 06:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing the title without JavaScript</title>
      <link>http://apeoholic.se/blazor/2020/03/11/ChangeTitle.html</link>
      <description>Blazor is a fantastic way to develop interactive sites without the use of JavaScript.But that is not always entirely true, in some cases, you do need JavaScr...</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Engstr&amp;#246;m)</author>
      <guid>http://apeoholic.se/blazor/2020/03/11/ChangeTitle.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Guide to Arrow Functions in ES6</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/the-guide-to-arrow-functions-in-es6</link>
      <description>Learn more about a powerful feature of ES6: arrow functions. See how we can have better, more concise, and more powerful functions in JavaScript. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/the-guide-to-arrow-functions-in-es6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Containers Basics: Providing Persistent Storage to Containers</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/itops-talk-blog/containers-basics-providing-persistent-storage-to-containers/ba-p/1200050</link>
      <description>One of the main differences you will notice when comparing containers with Virtual Machines (VMs) is that containers use an ephemeral storage by default. What that means is that containers use what we call as “scratch space” and this data is not persisted.   The VMs are associated with a virtual dis...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/26192)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/itops-talk-blog/containers-basics-providing-persistent-storage-to-containers/ba-p/1200050</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 06:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core Session Storage Strategies - DZone Web Dev</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aspnet-core-session-storage-strategies</link>
      <description>In this article, we discuss how to set up NCache Session Provider for ASP.NET Core applications in order to overcome issues caused by sticky sessions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dzone.com/articles/aspnet-core-session-storage-strategies</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 06:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Dotnet Gitignore File</title>
      <link>https://blog.vijay.name/2020/03/microsoft-dotnet-gitignore-file/</link>
      <description>dotnet now has inbuilt functionality to create gitignore files and it's great!</description>
      <author> (விஜய் கணேஷ் - Vijay Ganesh)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.vijay.name/2020/03/microsoft-dotnet-gitignore-file/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 06:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to SSH into a Windows 10 Machine from Linux OR Windows OR anywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/HowToSSHIntoAWindows10MachineFromLinuxORWindowsORAnywhere.aspx</link>
      <description>I've been shushing all over the place lately. I SSH into Linux from Windows using the built-in OpenSSH Client that ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/HowToSSHIntoAWindows10MachineFromLinuxORWindowsORAnywhere.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 06:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>