<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How to use dig</title>
      <link>https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/12/04/how-to-use-dig/</link>
      <description>How to use dig</description>
      <author> (Julia Evans)</author>
      <guid>https://jvns.ca/blog/2021/12/04/how-to-use-dig/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 03:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Starting Word in WORDLE</title>
      <link>https://bert.org/2021/11/24/the-best-starting-word-in-wordle/</link>
      <description>Have you played WORDLE yet? It’s a clever word game that’s basically Mastermind with 5-letter words.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bert.org/2021/11/24/the-best-starting-word-in-wordle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Knowledge Management organization</title>
      <link>https://dsebastien.net/blog/2021-12-03-personal-knowledge-management-organization</link>
      <description>In this post, I dissect my Personal Knowledge Management system.</description>
      <author> (https://dsebastien.net)</author>
      <guid>https://dsebastien.net/blog/2021-12-03-personal-knowledge-management-organization</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On courage</title>
      <link>https://carltheperson.com/posts/on-courage/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://carltheperson.com/posts/on-courage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is infinite token approval safe?</title>
      <link>https://thomasvilhena.com/2021/12/is-infinite-approval-safe</link>
      <description>Is has become common  practice for DeFi protocols to use infinite token allowance approval to improve end users experience. From the user’s perspective it’s indeed very convenient and even appealing, once they grant a dapp (decentralized app) infinite allowance they will be able to interact with such dapp mostly using single transactions instead of having to perform a token spending approval transaction prior to every interaction with the dapp.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thomasvilhena.com/2021/12/is-infinite-approval-safe</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>klog retrospective</title>
      <link>https://www.jotaen.net/9rRZQ/klog-retrospective/</link>
      <description>One year into my open-source time tracking project</description>
      <author> (Jan Heuermann)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jotaen.net/9rRZQ/klog-retrospective/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Zero-knowledge proofs through simple examples</title>
      <link>https://blog.goodaudience.com/understanding-zero-knowledge-proofs-through-simple-examples-df673f796d99</link>
      <description>I recently listened to this ZKFM podcast, which gave illustrative examples that clearly explained key concepts on zero knowledge proofs. I…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@nicolezhu)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.goodaudience.com/understanding-zero-knowledge-proofs-through-simple-examples-df673f796d99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 23:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com: ECHOGEAR 3 Monitor Desk Stand for Screens Up to 27&amp;quot; - Triple Desk Mount with Lock Down Clamp to Eliminate Screen Wobble - Adjust Tilt, Orientation &amp;amp; Swivel of Each Monitor Without Tools : Electronics</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/dp/B079NNC2YQ/?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202112</link>
      <description>Amazon.com: ECHOGEAR 3 Monitor Desk Stand for Screens Up to 27&amp;quot; - Triple Desk Mount with Lock Down Clamp to Eliminate Screen Wobble - Adjust Tilt, Orientation &amp;amp; Swivel of Each Monitor Without Tools : Electronics</description>
      <author> (ECHOGEAR)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/dp/B079NNC2YQ/?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202112</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing AI for Killer Instinct</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9yydYjQ1GLg</link>
      <description>In this 2016 GDC session, Derek Neal and Bruce Hayles, two of the key developers behind Killer Instinct&amp;#39;s Shadow system, use the system as a case study in ho...</description>
      <author> (GDC
  
  
  
    GDC
  






    •
  
  
    
      167K views
    
      4 years ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9yydYjQ1GLg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 21:44:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains launches cross-platform UI framework for Kotlin</title>
      <link>https://www.infoworld.com/article/3643392/jetbrains-launches-cross-platform-ui-framework-for-kotlin.html</link>
      <description>Compose Multiplatform 1.0 allows developers to build user interfaces for the desktop, Android, and web from a single codebase.</description>
      <author> (Paul Krill)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoworld.com/article/3643392/jetbrains-launches-cross-platform-ui-framework-for-kotlin.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 21:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Guacamole™</title>
      <link>https://guacamole.apache.org/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://guacamole.apache.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 21:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The One with .NET after Saint Nick – Codecamp</title>
      <link>https://codecamp.ro/e-conferences/the-one-with-net-after-saint-nick/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://codecamp.ro/e-conferences/the-one-with-net-after-saint-nick/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 20:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - fastify/busboy: A streaming parser for HTML form data for node.js</title>
      <link>https://github.com/fastify/busboy</link>
      <description>A streaming parser for HTML form data for node.js. Contribute to fastify/busboy development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (fastify)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/fastify/busboy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 19:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading from .NET Framework to .NET 6</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cOHXt_0VDRI</link>
      <description>https://aka.ms/dotNETConf2021-GetdotNET6Learn how to bring your .NET Framework apps forward to .NET 6 to take advantage of the latest performance improvement...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •
  
  
    
      24K views
    
      3 weeks ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cOHXt_0VDRI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=channel%2FUCiaZbznpWV1o-KLxj8zqR6A</link>
      <description>Enjoy the videos and music you love, upload original content, and share it all with friends, family, and the world on YouTube.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=channel%2FUCiaZbznpWV1o-KLxj8zqR6A</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - haampie/libtree: ldd as a tree with an option to bundle dependencies into a single folder</title>
      <link>https://github.com/haampie/libtree</link>
      <description>ldd as a tree with an option to bundle dependencies into a single folder - GitHub - haampie/libtree: ldd as a tree with an option to bundle dependencies into a single folder</description>
      <author> (haampie)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/haampie/libtree</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 15:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An alarming trend in K-12 math education: a guest post and an open letter</title>
      <link>https://scottaaronson.blog/?p=6146</link>
      <description>Today, I’m turning over Shtetl-Optimized to an extremely important guest post by theoretical computer scientists Boaz Barak of Harvard and Edith Cohen of Google (cross-posted on the windows o…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scottaaronson.blog/?p=6146</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 15:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 UI/UX Tips &amp;amp; Tricks</title>
      <link>https://akcium.gumroad.com/l/ui-ux-tips</link>
      <description>What this book is about?For the whole year, I&amp;#39;ve been tweeting and collecting UI/UX tips. I end up with more than 120+ of them.Not all of them are good, some are controversial, some are opinionated.So I removed the worse and compiled the rest in 100 tips that I put in a few categories. Almost every tip has an illustration, as well as a description. Apart from that, I tried to provide some external resources that are related to the tip or that provide some proof. In total there are more than 50+ additional links complementing this book.&amp;#128073; You can download a free preview hereWho is this book for?Basically for everyone interested in user interfaces.It might be especially useful for developers, founders and aspiring designers.What&amp;#39;s inside?Exactly 100 UI/UX tips. Every tip takes exactly 1 page, so they are concise and easy to digest because almost all of them are illustrated.A few examples are in the gallery above.What do other people say?“Learning UI can be tricking, but seeing and understanding tips like these can help you level up, I enjoyed reading this book, lots of wisdom that took me years to learn here.”— Adrian Twarog (@adrian_twarog)&amp;quot;This book is seriously impressive. It features tons of high quality, actionable UI/UX tips with visual &amp;quot;do&amp;#39;s and don&amp;#39;ts&amp;quot; to help you design and build awesome applications - even if you&amp;#39;re not a designer yourself. Victor has packaged everything together neatly without any fluff, so I highly recommend picking up this book to level up your practical design skills.&amp;quot;— Mads Brodt (@madsbrodt)&amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ve been following Victor for quite a while and remember him posting all these UI/UX tips. What I can say is that you don&amp;#39;t need a design degree to make decent interfaces. Especially if you are bootstrapped founder and don&amp;#39;t have money for a designer. This book might help you much with that.&amp;quot;— Simon H&amp;#248;iberg (@SimonHoiberg)&amp;quot;What I liked about this book is that it&amp;#39;s easy to read. I&amp;#39;m a Frontend Engineer and sometimes it takes ages for me to make UI looks good. Among these tips, I found quite a few that I hadn&amp;#39;t thought about earlier.&amp;quot;— Dimitri Ivashchuk (@DivDev_)What is the option with a spreadsheet?Since most of the tips were published on Twitter, people left some comments agreeing or disagreeing with every tip. Sometimes they might have provided a better solution or an interesting idea.Plus, not all of the tips are in this book, I didn&amp;#39;t include some of them.The spreadsheet is a .xlsx file that contains ~120 links to my tips.Apart from this, I&amp;#39;ve included big threads, that are dedicated to a specific topic, e.g. validation of sign-up forms. One thread has about 50+ curated links related to designing different UI controls, that got more than 10K likes.For every tweet, I&amp;#39;ve also put the number of likes and retweets, which might be an indirect cue of how good it is. Or a least popular.This is how it looks like &amp;#128071;What is the option with a review?Besides tweeting UI/UX tips, I also did quite a few UI/UX reviews in different formats. At first, I made them for free, but then I realized that it takes quite a lot of time and effort to make them. After I got some positive reviews, I decided that I need to charge some money. Well, it will increase the quality of the review after all.So a review is basically a Loom video, usually ~30-50 minutes long, where I go through your interface and try to point out all the mistakes I see. Before I do this, I go through the interface myself.In some cases, the UI already looks good enough, so I got nothing much to add. In this case, I&amp;#39;ll either try to go deeper or just make a refund. You can also send me a message with your site upfront so that I check it and say if I&amp;#39;m able to help or not.How will I get the review?There is a .txt file with my email and Twitter. You should send me a link to your site or design or whatever you need to review, and I&amp;#39;ll record a video within a few days.You can send me your site upfront on Twitter: https://twitter.com/vponamariov.UI/UX Review testimonialsFree Review Threads</description>
      <author> (ByVictor)</author>
      <guid>https://akcium.gumroad.com/l/ui-ux-tips</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 14:54:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t Make My Mistakes: Common Infrastructure Errors I&amp;#39;ve Made</title>
      <link>https://matduggan.com/mistakes/</link>
      <description>One surreal experience as my career has progressed is the intense feeling of deja vu you get hit with during meetings. From time to time, someone will mention something and you&amp;#39;ll flash back to the same meeting you had about this a few jobs ago. A decision was made then,</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matduggan.com/mistakes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 14:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Advent Calendar - .NET Advent Calendar 2021, Day 4</title>
      <link>https://dotnet.christmas/2021/4</link>
      <description>One blog post every day until Christmas.</description>
      <author> (Dustin Moris Gorski)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnet.christmas/2021/4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 14:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webb</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2550/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2550/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 05:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>