<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Why You Need This:  The Jet KVM - Take Control of ANY PC!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ZhruWAaHcgg</link>
      <description>Dave explains and demos the JetKVM.  Free Sample of my Book on the Spectrum: https://amzn.to/3zBinWM
Dave Cutler Interview: https://youtu.be/xi1Lq79mLeE

Watch ShopTalk on Dave's Attic: https://www.youtube.com/@davepl

Follow me on X: https://x.com/davepl1968
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/davepl</description>
      <author> (Dave's Garage)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ZhruWAaHcgg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 20:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor Community Standup - Updates in .NET 10 Preview 3</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=8kCNWe0Bi8s</link>
      <description>Join us to check out all the new Blazor features in .NET 10 Preview 3.

Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/blazor-standup-20250408

Featuring: Jon Galloway, Javier Calvarro Nelson

#dotnet #aspnetcore #blazor</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=8kCNWe0Bi8s</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 20:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In retrospect, DevOps was a bad idea.</title>
      <link>https://rethinkingsoftware.substack.com/p/in-retrospect-devops-was-a-bad-idea</link>
      <description>We need to talk about DevOps.</description>
      <guid>https://rethinkingsoftware.substack.com/p/in-retrospect-devops-was-a-bad-idea</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Finally Adds Native Python Support to CUDA</title>
      <link>https://thenewstack.io/nvidia-finally-adds-native-python-support-to-cuda/</link>
      <description>For years, NVIDIA’s CUDA software toolkit for GPUs didn't have native Python support. But that’s now changed.</description>
      <guid>https://thenewstack.io/nvidia-finally-adds-native-python-support-to-cuda/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 50 years of Microsoft | Bill Gates</title>
      <link>https://www.gatesnotes.com/meet-bill/source-code/reader/microsoft-original-source-code</link>
      <description>This one piece of code led to a half century of innovation from Microsoft.</description>
      <guid>https://www.gatesnotes.com/meet-bill/source-code/reader/microsoft-original-source-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I stopped using AI code editors · Luciano Nooijen</title>
      <link>https://lucianonooijen.com/blog/why-i-stopped-using-ai-code-editors/</link>
      <description>In the past I used AI code editors for all of my programming, but I stopped using it and recommend others to consider this as well</description>
      <guid>https://lucianonooijen.com/blog/why-i-stopped-using-ai-code-editors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So You Want To Pick A Topic For Your Next Conference Talk?</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=PzyUHYr5ukA</link>
      <description>Are you sitting on valuable knowledge but paralyzed by the fear of public speaking? Does imposter syndrome hold you back from sharing your unique perspective with the world? This video is your roadmap to overcoming those obstacles and finding your authentic speaking voice.

Hi, I'm James, a storytelling technologist who's spoken at over 30 conferences worldwide. In this video, I'll show you why your unique combination of passions, experiences, and hobbies is the perfect foundation for an impactful talk that only YOU can give.

What You'll Learn:
- Why jumping on tech hype trains often leads to inauthentic presentations
- How to identify your unique speaking sweet spot at the intersection of passion and experience
- Why being a beginner can actually be your greatest advantage
- A practical framework for brainstorming talk ideas that resonate with audiences
- How to infuse your presentations with personal touches (like my pizza obsession!)

Every single person watching has something valuable to share with the world. Let me show you how to discover what that is and take your first steps toward the stage.

🔗 FREE DOWNLOAD: Grab my PDF guide on the five most important things when planning a conference talk: https://speak.jameseastham.co.uk/

👉 Stay tuned for the next video in this series where I'll cover talk planning strategies!</description>
      <author> (James Eastham)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=PzyUHYr5ukA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - antiwork/gumroad</title>
      <link>https://github.com/antiwork/gumroad</link>
      <description>Contribute to antiwork/gumroad development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/antiwork/gumroad</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Rust 1.86.0 | Rust Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2025/04/03/Rust-1.86.0.html</link>
      <description>Empowering everyone to build reliable and efficient software.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2025/04/03/Rust-1.86.0.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bored of it</title>
      <link>https://paulrobertlloyd.com/2025/087/a1/bored/</link>
      <description>Please, make it stop.</description>
      <guid>https://paulrobertlloyd.com/2025/087/a1/bored/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First look at the YARP Container - A simple Nginx alternative</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=xf-lu_cjSmU</link>
      <description>Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Get the source code here: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic



Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=xf-lu_cjSmU</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I migrated my Mastodon account to micro.blog</title>
      <link>https://msicc.net/migrating-my-mastodon-account-micro-blog/</link>
      <description>Migrating from Mastodon to micro.blog while keeping your Fediverse connections can be seamless. Here’s how I did it.</description>
      <guid>https://msicc.net/migrating-my-mastodon-account-micro-blog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Code to Cloud in 15 Minutes: Jason Taylor's Expert Insights And The Clean Architecture Template</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Zdi4rM32t1I</link>
      <description>RJJ Software's Software Development Service This episode of The Modern .NET Show is supported, in part, by RJJ Software's Podcasting Services, whether your company is looking to elevate its UK operations or reshape its US strategy, we can provide tailored solutions that exceed expectations.

 Show Notes "So I've been focused on the code to cloud journey, I like to call it, for the template. And two years ago, my goal was to provide a solution that could take you from code to cloud in 45 minutes or less. So I wanted it to be "file new project" to deploy a solution on Azure—because that's where my main focus is—within 45 minutes."— Jason Taylor

 Welcome friends to The Modern .NET Show; the premier .NET podcast, focusing entirely on the knowledge, tools, and frameworks that all .NET developers should have in their toolbox. We are the go-to podcast for .NET developers worldwide, and I am your host: Jamie "GaProgMan" Taylor.

 In this episode, Jason Taylor (no relation) joined us to talk about his journey from Classic ASP to .NET and Azure. He also discusses clean architecture’s maintainability, and his open-source Clean Architecture Solution template for ASP .NET Core, along with strategies for learning new frameworks and dealing with complexity.

 "Right now the template supports PostgreSQL, SQLite, and SQL Server. If you want to support MySQL, it's relatively easy to do because there's already a Bicep module or a Terraform module that you can go in and use it. So I went from 45 minutes to now I can get things up and running in like, I don't know, two minutes of effort and 15 minutes of waiting around while I make my coffee"— Jason Taylor

 Along the way, we talk about some of the complexities involved with creating a template which supports multiple different frontend technologies and .NET Aspire (which was news to me when we recorded), all the while maintaining the goal of being the simplest approach for enterprise development with Clean Architecture.

 Anyway, without further ado, let's sit back, open up a terminal, type in `dotnet new podcast` and we'll dive into the core of Modern .NET.

 Supporting the Show If you find this episode useful in any way, please consider supporting the show by either leaving a review (check our review page for ways to do that), sharing the episode with a friend or colleague, buying the host a coffee, or considering becoming a Patron of the show.

 Full Show Notes The full show notes, including links to some of the things we discussed and a full transcription of this episode, can be found at:  https://dotnetcore.show/season-7/from-code-to-cloud-in-15-minutes-jason-taylors-expert-insights-and-the-clean-architecture-template/

 Jason's Links:  Jason's Clean Architecture repo on GitHub Jason's Northwind Traders with Clean Architecture repo on Github Connect with Jason Jason's RapidBlazor repo on GitHub  Other Links:   C# DevKit for Visual Studio Code  Code, Coffee, and Clever Debugging: Leslie Richardson's Microsoft Journey and the C# Dev Kit in Visual Studio Code with Leslie Richardson  dotnet scaffold devcontainers  .NET Aspire  Azure Developer CLI GitHub CLI Obsidian  Supporting the show:  Leave a rating or review Buy the show a coffee Become a patron  Getting in Touch:  Via the contact page Joining the Discord  Remember to rate and review the show on  Apple Podcasts, Podchaser, or wherever you find your podcasts, this will help the show's audience grow. Or you can just share the show with a friend.

 And don't forget to reach out via our Contact page. We're very interested in your opinion of the show, so please get in touch.

 You can support the show by making a monthly donation on the show's Patreon page at: https://www.patreon.com/TheDotNetCorePodcast.

 Music created by Mono Memory Music, licensed to RJJ Software for use in The Modern .NET Show</description>
      <author> (Jamie Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Zdi4rM32t1I</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agnishom Chattopadhyay | the steam deck is not evil and thats why I like it</title>
      <link>https://isomorphism.xyz/blog/2024/steam-deck/</link>
      <description>in an era where tech giants increasingly control our digital experiences, the Steam Deck stands as a beacon of user freedom</description>
      <guid>https://isomorphism.xyz/blog/2024/steam-deck/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Developer Skills in the AI Age: Leveraging Experience for Better Results • Manuel Kießling</title>
      <link>https://manuel.kiessling.net/2025/03/31/how-seasoned-developers-can-achieve-great-results-with-ai-coding-agents/</link>
      <description>How time-tested software engineering practices amplify the effectiveness of AI coding assistants.</description>
      <guid>https://manuel.kiessling.net/2025/03/31/how-seasoned-developers-can-achieve-great-results-with-ai-coding-agents/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Slow Collapse of Critical Thinking in OSINT due to AI</title>
      <link>https://www.dutchosintguy.com/post/the-slow-collapse-of-critical-thinking-in-osint-due-to-ai</link>
      <description>OSINT used to be a thinking game. Now it’s becoming a trusting game and that should terrify you.I’ve seen it firsthand, analysts running solid investigations, then slowly shifting more and more of the thinking to GenAI tools. At first, it’s small. You use ChatGPT to summarise a document or translate a foreign post. Then it’s helping draft your reports. Then it’s generating leads. And eventually, you’re not thinking as critically as you used to. You’re verifying less, questioning less, relying mo</description>
      <author> (Nico Dekens | dutch_osintguy)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dutchosintguy.com/post/the-slow-collapse-of-critical-thinking-in-osint-due-to-ai</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Learn .NET - GitHub Copilot (Africa)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HANHdcnE-TQ</link>
      <description>Let's learn about GitHub Copilot and Copilot Chat in this workshop covering AI-powered coding, getting started with Copilot, and prompt engineering for crafting effective commands. Together, we will take a peek into maximizing Copilot efficiency, tips and tricks, frequently asked questions, as well as an intro to Continuous Development Flow with GitHub Copilot for Azure. 

Acknowledgment: This content will be presented by our colleagues in Africa.

Repo: https://github.com/microsoft/mastering-github-copilot-for-dotnet-csharp-developers

Community Links: https://aka.ms/letslearn/dotnet/ghcp

Featuring: Japhlet Nwamu, Someleze Diko, Lebogang Madise

#dotNET #GitHub #Copilot #GitHubCopilot</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=HANHdcnE-TQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimal CSS-only blurry image placeholders</title>
      <link>https://leanrada.com/notes/css-only-lqip/</link>
      <description>Here’s a CSS technique that produces blurry image placeholders (LQIPs) without cluttering up your markup — Only a single custom property needed!</description>
      <guid>https://leanrada.com/notes/css-only-lqip/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 50 years of Microsoft | Bill Gates</title>
      <link>https://www.gatesnotes.com/home/home-page-topic/reader/microsoft-original-source-code</link>
      <description>This one piece of code led to a half century of innovation from Microsoft.</description>
      <guid>https://www.gatesnotes.com/home/home-page-topic/reader/microsoft-original-source-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI 2027</title>
      <link>https://ai-2027.com/</link>
      <description>A research-backed AI scenario forecast.
</description>
      <guid>https://ai-2027.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's talk about Tariffs? </title>
      <link>https://novice.media/p/lets-talk-about-tariffs</link>
      <description>The end of free trade, or the beginning of American Renaissance?</description>
      <guid>https://novice.media/p/lets-talk-about-tariffs</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timing Is Everything: Real S&amp;P 500 Returns Across 5, 10, and 20-Year Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.moatmind.com/p/real-sp500-returns-5-10-20-year-windows</link>
      <description>A century-long look at how entry timing shapes real, inflation-adjusted returns—proving that even long-term investing in the S&amp;P 500 can yield wildly different outcomes.</description>
      <guid>https://www.moatmind.com/p/real-sp500-returns-5-10-20-year-windows</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating Azure Durable Function App to Use Durable Task Scheduler: Running Locally</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2025/04/migrating-azure-durable-function-app-to.html</link>
      <description>.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Azure, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2025/04/migrating-azure-durable-function-app-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Scrape</title>
      <link>https://herman.bearblog.dev/the-great-scrape/</link>
      <description>Scraper bots are destroying the commons to feed the machine</description>
      <guid>https://herman.bearblog.dev/the-great-scrape/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - lwthiker/curl-impersonate: curl-impersonate: A special build of curl that can impersonate Chrome &amp; Firefox</title>
      <link>https://github.com/lwthiker/curl-impersonate</link>
      <description>curl-impersonate: A special build of curl that can impersonate Chrome &amp; Firefox - lwthiker/curl-impersonate</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/lwthiker/curl-impersonate</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To the rejected</title>
      <link>https://blog.johnqian.com/college-admissions</link>
      <description>April 2024</description>
      <guid>https://blog.johnqian.com/college-admissions</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Easiest Way to Meditate</title>
      <link>https://shubhamjain.co/2025/04/03/easiest-form-of-meditation/</link>
      <description>
Meditation is great — most of us can agree on that. But like exercise, it’s been overcomplicated. There are just so many forms of it: guided, silent, body scans, vipassana, kriyas. There are apps, videos, retreats, books, and self-proclaimed gurus—everyone’s selling their version.

Its benefits have also been oversold. People are led to believe it’s a one-stop solution for all mental health issues, and at worst, a path to everlasting bliss. Do a week of Vipassana and your mind will be permanently transformed.

I can’t speak for everyone, but that hasn’t been my experience.

Meditation, to me, is just a tool to denoise the brain — and that’s become crucial in an age of constant overstimulation. Denoising helps you tune into the present, improves your focus, helps you identify the negative thought patterns, and also, softens their grip.

## Transcendental Meditation

Once I reframed what meditation *is*—a tool to denoise the brain—I had much more realistic expectations. After experimenting with various techniques, I found one that fits perfectly: Transcendental Meditation.

Don't worry, the name makes it sound advanced, but it’s actually the simplest one I’ve tried.

That said, it’s promoted by an organization that is borderline scammy (trying too hard to sell something), so good info is weirdly hard to find without paying. But the technique itself? Surprisingly easy and effective.

Here's how to do it:

**Just close your eyes and repeat a simple word or mantra &lt;u&gt;in your mind&lt;/u&gt; (like, _om_, _shrim_, or _namah_). It should be pleasant sounding and ideally meaningless. Don’t try to control your thoughts. If your mind drifts, gently return to repeating the mantra.**

That’s it. Sit on a chair, sit cross-legged, or lie down, doesn’t matter. Set a timer for 15–20 minutes, or go by feel. Do it in a park, or at home; in the morning, evening, or at night.

​Everything is up to you. 

## Why it works?

Like I said earlier, meditation is just a way to denoise your brain. Whether you focus on your breath, your body, or a mantra — it’s all aiming for the same outcome.

Repeating a word in your head is especially effective because, oddly enough, **the mind can only focus on one thing at a time**. When you repeat the word, it gently cuts off wandering thoughts. Over time, this starts to clear the mental clutter. Your mind calms down and you become more in tune with the present, and your own thought patterns.

When I practice it, I feel less overwhelmed, more focused, and the urge to doomscroll quiets down. And at night, it’s incredibly helpful for falling asleep.

If meditation is supposed to be a path to everlasting bliss, then I’m probably not on it — and honestly, that’s okay.

---

People have claimed all sorts of things about meditation, but in my experience, it's not necessary to explore the depth of consciousness to be reasonably happy. It’s healthier to approach meditation with more grounded expectations. 

But that's my take.  If you want to transform your mind, you're better off exploring a retreat or something similar.
</description>
      <guid>https://shubhamjain.co/2025/04/03/easiest-form-of-meditation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bikes in the Age of Tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.renehersecycles.com/bikes-in-the-age-of-tariffs/</link>
      <description>Today's post was going to be about a new product we're introducing—but we need to hold off while we recalculate our prices. You've probably seen the news: Virtually all imports into the United States will be subjected to additional, steep import taxes, also called tariffs. The…</description>
      <guid>https://www.renehersecycles.com/bikes-in-the-age-of-tariffs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your LLM Problem Isn't Tooling. It's Effort</title>
      <link>https://tomdekan.com/articles/eval-frameworks</link>
      <description>Getting great LLM output with an LLM-as-a-judge requires more effort, not more tools</description>
      <guid>https://tomdekan.com/articles/eval-frameworks</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I guess some request headers are more trustworthy than others.</title>
      <link>https://macarthur.me/posts/forbidden-request-headers/</link>
      <description>There's a subset of request headers that can't be modified by a spec-compliant user agent. Let's explore why they're useful for determining how and for what purpose a request was triggered. </description>
      <author> (Alex MacArthur)</author>
      <guid>https://macarthur.me/posts/forbidden-request-headers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Overestimate the Importance of Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://en.lutaonan.com/we-overestimate-the-importance-of-intelligence/</link>
      <description>In this era of increasingly powerful AI, one question I've been pondering more often is whether we tend to overvalue intelligence.

Several things sparked ...</description>
      <guid>https://en.lutaonan.com/we-overestimate-the-importance-of-intelligence/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balance</title>
      <link>https://blog.knhash.in/balance/</link>
      <description>
I've been thinking a lot about balance lately. It has been a background thread slowly developing, with three distinct step functions where it rose to the f...</description>
      <guid>https://blog.knhash.in/balance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nix that looks like Bazel</title>
      <link>https://fzakaria.com/2025/04/02/nix-that-looks-like-bazel</link>
      <description>This is an idea 💡 that came from PlanetNix. I did not originate the idea.</description>
      <guid>https://fzakaria.com/2025/04/02/nix-that-looks-like-bazel</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A case against migration files</title>
      <link>https://rcwz.pl/2025-04-03-a-case-against-migration-files/</link>
      <description>I never really understood the popularity of migration files. Sure enough, you need to somehow change schema from version A to version B and using SQL statements is the most straightforward way to do it, but surely, there has to be a better way, right..?</description>
      <guid>https://rcwz.pl/2025-04-03-a-case-against-migration-files/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Wants to Be a Ghibli Character. So, Why Does It Feel So Wrong?</title>
      <link>https://samsimlai.github.io/ghibli-ai-trend</link>
      <description>There’s a peculiar kind of magic in watching Studio Ghibli films. The kind that doesn’t just entertain — it lingers. It coats your soul like the afternoon light in My Neighbor Totoro, or the silent resilience of Princess Mononoke. It makes you want to touch grass, sip tea slowly, notice the wind, and wonder why we ever stopped paying attention to these things in the first place.</description>
      <guid>https://samsimlai.github.io/ghibli-ai-trend</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Journey with Vibe Coding</title>
      <link>https://tildehacker.com/my-journey-with-vibe-coding</link>
      <description>A detailed look at vibe coding from someone who’s been building software before and after the AI revolution</description>
      <guid>https://tildehacker.com/my-journey-with-vibe-coding</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSH is exciting</title>
      <link>https://yoyo-code.com/ssh-is-exciting/</link>
      <description>Matyáš Racek's blog</description>
      <guid>https://yoyo-code.com/ssh-is-exciting/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I'm Going Back to Zathura reader</title>
      <link>https://blog.nimendra.xyz/blog/zathura/</link>
      <description>After trying various readers on Linux, I’m returning to Zathura for its speed, minimal UI.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.nimendra.xyz/blog/zathura/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Your Neural Network Run Faster: An Overview of Optimization Techniques</title>
      <link>https://arikpoz.github.io/posts/2025-03-30-how-to-make-your-neural-network-run-faster-an-overview-of-optimization-techniques/</link>
      <description>Introduction Neural networks are becoming increasingly powerful, but speed remains a crucial factor in real-world applications. Whether you’re running models on the cloud, edge devices, or personal hardware, optimizing them for speed can lead to faster inference, lower latency, and reduced resource consumption.
In this post, we’ll explore various techniques to accelerate neural networks, from model compression to hardware optimizations. This will serve as a foundation for future deep dives into each method.</description>
      <guid>https://arikpoz.github.io/posts/2025-03-30-how-to-make-your-neural-network-run-faster-an-overview-of-optimization-techniques/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An image of an archeologist adventurer who wears a hat and uses a bullwhip</title>
      <link>https://theaiunderwriter.substack.com/p/an-image-of-an-archeologist-adventurer</link>
      <description>There is only one thing worse than being imitated</description>
      <guid>https://theaiunderwriter.substack.com/p/an-image-of-an-archeologist-adventurer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>