<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Factorio Is The Best Technical Interview We Have</title>
      <link>https://erikmcclure.com/blog/factorio-is-best-interview-we-have/</link>
      <description>There&amp;#39;s been a lot of hand-wringing over The Technical Interview lately. Many people realize that inverting a binary tree on a whiteboard has basically zero correlation to whether or not someone is actually a good software developer. The most effective programming test anyone&amp;#39;s come up with is still Fizzbuzz. One consequence of this has been an increased emphasis on Open Source Contributions, but it turns out these aren&amp;#39;t a very good metric either, because most people don&amp;#39;t have that kind of time.</description>
      <author> (Erik McClure)</author>
      <guid>https://erikmcclure.com/blog/factorio-is-best-interview-we-have/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 20:08:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video by Hannah Joy Gebresilassie</title>
      <link>https://bibliogram.art/tv/CM2-GWCHTIz/</link>
      <description>Capitol officers arrested Rep. Park Cannon for knocking on the Governor’s door trying to watch @govkemp sign voter suppression bill SB202 into law. We #STANDWITHPARK @parkcannon58 @itsericathomas</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bibliogram.art/tv/CM2-GWCHTIz/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 20:08:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/P9Pv5IdinMU</link>
      <description>Using Source Generators for Fun (and maybe profit) - with Jason Bock</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/P9Pv5IdinMU</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 20:08:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla - Los Angeles</title>
      <link>https://www.evgo.com/tesla-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>How to Charge with EVgo?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.evgo.com/tesla-los-angeles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 19:13:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Recognize, Prevent, and Manage Burnout</title>
      <link>https://www.pluralsight.com/courses/recognize-prevent-manage-burn-out</link>
      <description>This course teaches you what burnout is and how to prevent and recover from it. </description>
      <author> (Barry Luijbregts)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pluralsight.com/courses/recognize-prevent-manage-burn-out</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 19:11:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Heart</title>
      <link>https://open.spotify.com/track/1GG9V5AeKwgT4OFkAD6Buj?si=N0TwFj2ZQ4mho66fZ-rZdQ</link>
      <description>Brian Aspey &amp;#183; Song &amp;#183; 2021</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://open.spotify.com/track/1GG9V5AeKwgT4OFkAD6Buj?si=N0TwFj2ZQ4mho66fZ-rZdQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 19:11:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sufjan Stevens &amp;quot;Concerning the UFO Sighting Near Highland, Illinois&amp;quot; Sheet Music in G Major - Download &amp;amp; Print</title>
      <link>https://www.musicnotes.com/sheetmusic/mtd.asp?ppn=MN0064242</link>
      <description>Print and download Concerning the UFO Sighting Near Highland, Illinois sheet music by Sufjan Stevens. Sheet music arranged for Piano/Vocal/Guitar, and Singer Pro in G Major.</description>
      <author> (Stevens, Sufjan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.musicnotes.com/sheetmusic/mtd.asp?ppn=MN0064242</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 19:11:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT Encounters of the Third Kind</title>
      <link>https://igor-blue.github.io/2021/03/24/apt1.html</link>
      <description>A few weeks ago an ordinary security assessment turned into an incident response whirlwind. It was definitely a first for me, and I was kindly granted permission to outline the events in this blog post. This investigation started scary but turned out be quite fun, and I hope reading it will be informative to you too.  I&amp;#39;ll be back to posting about my hardware research soon.     How it started   What hell is this?   The NFS Server   2nd malicious binary   Further forensics   Eureka Moment   The GOlang thingy   How the kernel got patched? and why not the golang app?   What we have so far   Q&amp;amp;A   How it started Twice a year I am hired to do security assessments for a specific client. We have been working together for several years, and I had a pretty good understanding of their network and what to look for.  This time my POC, Klaus, asked me to focus on privacy issues and GDPR compliance. However, he asked me to first look at their cluster of reverse gateways / load balancers:    I had some prior knowledge of these gateways, but decided to start by creating my own test environment first. The gateways run a custom Linux stack: basically a monolithic compiled kernel (without any modules), and a static GOlang application on top. The 100+ machines have no internal storage, but rather boot from an external USB media that has the kernel and the application. The GOlang app serves in two capacities: an init replacement and the reverse gateway software. During initialization it mounts /proc, /sys, devfs and so on, then mounts an NFS share hardcoded in the app. The NFS share contains the app&amp;#39;s configuration, TLS certificates, blacklist data and a few more. It starts listening on 443, filters incoming communication and passes valid requests on different services in the production segment.    I set up a self contained test environment, and spent a day in black box examination. Having found nothing much I suggested we move on to looking at the production network, but Klaus insisted I continue with the gateways. Specifically he wanted to know if I could develop a methodology for testing if an attacker has gained access to the gateways and is trying to access PII (Personally Identifiable Information) from within the decrypted HTTP stream.  I couldn&amp;#39;t SSH into the host (no SSH), so I figured we will have to add some kind of instrumentation to the GO app. Klaus still insisted I start by looking at the traffic before (red) and after the GW (green), and gave me access to a mirrored port on both sides so I could capture traffic to a standalone laptop he prepared for me and I could access through an LTE modem but was not allowed to upload data from:    The problem I faced now was how to find out what HTTPS traffic corresponded to requests with embedded PII. One possible avenue was to try and correlate the encrypted traffic with the decrypted HTTP traffic. This proved impossible using timing alone. However, unspecting the decoded traffic I noticed the GW app adds an &amp;#39;X-Orig-Connection&amp;#39; with the four-tuple of the TLS connection! Yay!    I wrote a small python program to scan the port 80 traffic capture and create a mapping from each four-tuple TLS connection to a boolean - True for connection with PII and False for all others: 10.4.254.254,443,[Redacted],43404,376106847.319,False 10.4.254.254,443,[Redacted],52064,376106856.146,False 10.4.254.254,443,[Redacted],40946,376106856.295,False 10.4.254.254,443,[Redacted],48366,376106856.593,False 10.4.254.254,443,[Redacted],48362,376106856.623,True 10.4.254.254,443,[Redacted],45872,376106856.645,False 10.4.254.254,443,[Redacted],40124,376106856.675,False  ...   With this in mind I could now extract the data from the PCAPs and do some correlations. After a few long hours getting scapy to actually parse timestamps consistently enough for comparisons, I had a list of connection timing information correlated with PII. A few more fun hours with Excel and I got histogram graphs of time vs count of packets. Everything looked normal for the HTTP traffic, although I expected more of a normal distribution than the power-low type thingy I got. Port 443 initially looked the same, and I got the normal distribution I expected. But when filtering for PII something was seriously wrong. The distribution was skewed and shifted to longer time frames. And there was nothing similar on the port 80 end.    My only explanation was that something was wrong with my testing setup (the blue bars) vs. the real live setup (the orange bars). I wrote on our slack channel &amp;#39;I think my setup is sh*t, can anyone resend me the config files?&amp;#39;, but this was already very late at night, and no one responded. Having a slight OCD I couldn’t let this go. To my rescue came another security? feature of the GWs: Thet restarted daily, staggered one by one, with about 10 minutes between hosts. This means that every ten minutes or so one of them would reboot, and thus reload it’s configuration files over NFS. And since I could see the NFS traffic through the port mirror I had access to, I recokoned I could get the production configuration files from the NFS capture (bottom dotted blue line in the diagram before).  So to cut a long story short I found the NFS read reply packet, and got the data I need. But … why the hack is eof 77685??? Come on people, its 3:34AM!  What&amp;#39;s more, the actual data was 77685 bytes, exactly 8192 bytes more then the ‘Read length’. The entropy for that data was pretty uniform, suggesting it was encrypted. The file I had was definitely not encrypted.    Histogram of extra 8192 bytes:    When I mounted the NFS export myself I got a normal EOF value of 1!    What hell is this?  Comparing the capture from my testing machine with the one from the port mirror I saw something else weird:    For other NFS open requests (on all of my test system captures and for other files in the production system) we get:    Spot the difference?  The open id: string became open-id:. Was I dealing with some corrupt packet? But the exact same problem reappeared the next time blacklist.db was send over the wire by another GW host.  Time to look at the kernel source code:    The “open id” string is hardcoded. What&amp;#39;s up?  After a good night sleep and no beer this time I repeated the experiment and convincing myself I was not hullucinating I decided to compare the source code of the exact kernel version with the kernel binary I got.  What I expected to see was this (from nfs4xdr.c):  static inline void encode_openhdr(struct xdr_stream *xdr, const struct nfs_openargs *arg) {     __be32 *p;  /*  * opcode 4, seqid 4, share_access 4, share_deny 4, clientid 8, ownerlen 4,  * owner 4 = 32  */     encode_nfs4_seqid(xdr, arg-&amp;gt;seqid);     encode_share_access(xdr, arg-&amp;gt;share_access);     p = reserve_space(xdr, 36);     p = xdr_encode_hyper(p, arg-&amp;gt;clientid);     *p++ = cpu_to_be32(24);     p = xdr_encode_opaque_fixed(p, &amp;quot;open id:&amp;quot;, 8);     *p++ = cpu_to_be32(arg-&amp;gt;server-&amp;gt;s_dev);     *p++ = cpu_to_be32(arg-&amp;gt;id.uniquifier);     xdr_encode_hyper(p, arg-&amp;gt;id.create_time); }   Running binwalk -e -M bzImage I got the internal ELF image, and opened it in IDA. Of course I didn’t have any symbols, but I got nfs4_xdr_enc_open() from /proc/kallsyms, and from there to encode_open() which led me to encode_openhdr(). With some help from hex-rays I got code that looked very similiar, but with one key difference:  static inline void encode_openhdr(struct xdr_stream *xdr, const struct nfs_openargs *arg) {     ...     p = xdr_encode_opaque_fixed(p, unknown_func(&amp;quot;open id:&amp;quot;, arg), 8);     ... }   The function unknown_func was pretty long and complicated but eventually sometimes decided to replace the space between &amp;#39;open&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;id&amp;#39; with a hyphen.  Does the NFS server care? Apparently this string it is some opaque client identifier that is ignored by the NFS server, so no one would see the difference. That is unless they were trying to extract something from an NFS stream, and obviously this was not a likely scenario. OK, back to the weird &amp;#39;eof&amp;#39; thingy from the NFS server.  The NFS Server  The server was running the &amp;#39;NFS-ganesha-3.3&amp;#39; package. This is a very modular user-space NFS server that is implemented as a series of loadable modules called FASLs. For example support for files on the regular filesystem is implemented through a module called libfsalvfs.so. Having verified all the files on disk had the same SHA1 as the distro package, I decided to dump the process memory. I didn&amp;#39;t have any tools on the host, so I used GDB which helpfully was already there. Unexpectadly GDB was suddenly killed, the file I specified as output got erased, and the nfs server process restarted.  I took the dump again but there was nothing special there!  I was pretty suspicious at this time, and wanted to recover the original dump file from the first dump. Fortunately for me I was dumping the file to the laptop, again over NFS. The file had been deleted, but I managed to recover it from the disk on that server.  2nd malicious binary  The memory dump was truncated, but had a corrupt version of NFS-ganesha inside. There were two libfsalvfs.so libraries loaded: the original one and an injected SO file with the same name. The injected file was clearly malicious. The main binary was patched in a few places, and the  function table into libfsalvfs.so as replaced with the alternate libfsalvfs.so. The alternate file was compiled from NFS-ganesha sources, but modified to include new and improved (wink wink) functionality.  The most intersiting of the new functionality were two separate implementations of covert channels.  The first one we encountered already:     When an open request comes in with &amp;#39;open-id&amp;#39; instead of &amp;#39;open id&amp;#39;, the file handle is marked. This is change is opaque to the NFS server, so unpatched servers just ignore it and nothing much happens.   For infiltrated NFS server, when the file handle opened this way is read, the NFS server appends the last block with a payload coming from the malware&amp;#39;s runtime storage, and the &amp;#39;eof&amp;#39; on-the-wire value is changed to be the new total size. An unpatched kernel (which shouldn’t really happen, since it marked the file in the first place) will just ignore the extra bytes. The EOF value is used as a bool, e.g. checked for 0 or not and not a specific value, so having a large integer values doesn’t change anything in the flow of an unmodified kernel.   The second covert channel is used for command and control, and is implemented in the VFS code as a fake directory.  Any writes to /&amp;lt;export&amp;gt;/.snapshot/meta/&amp;lt;cmdid&amp;gt; are handled by the malware code and not passed on to the FS. They are pseudo-files that implement commands through read and write operations.  The malware implemented the following commands:    1701 - self destruct   1702 - set auto self destruct time   1703 - run shell command   1704 - load SO file from buffer specified in command   1706 - get basic system description   1707 - get network connections   170A - upgrade to new SO file   74201 - put buffer in memory dict by ID   74202 - get buffer from memory dict by ID   74650 - put a payload in memory for the first covert channel   74651 - arm the first covert channel   74652 - disarm the first covert channel   For example cp payload.so /mnt/server/.snapshot/meta/1704 will load the SO file in the NFS ganesha process on the target server, and echo 1616580589 &amp;gt; /mnt/server/.snapshot/meta/1702 will set an autodestruct time. Reading this file will retrieve the time.  The self destruct command (0x1701) is very interesting - it sends a UDP broadcast on port 41701 with a random payload of size 321 bytes, and then restarts a clean NFS-ganesha. I guess this is some kind of network signalling.  It appears the malware has a watchdog that iterates over all /proc/&amp;lt;pid&amp;gt;/fd/* links every 25ms, and if a link is open to /proc/&amp;lt;malware pid&amp;gt;/maps or /proc/&amp;lt;malware pid&amp;gt;/smaps or  /proc/&amp;lt;malware pid&amp;gt;/mem it:    kills the offending process,   deletes any writeable file handle it had opened (before it was killed) in /proc/&amp;lt;pid&amp;gt;/fd/, first trying to wipe it,   calls the self destruct command (0x1701).   Further forensics Lets go back to that awful Saturday I triggered the self-destruct. Having a faint understanding I triggered something (that being before I reversed the devil) I asked Klaus to disconnect all the network connections to the outer world and we started taking memory dumps of whatever we could, storing them all on the laptop. In hindsight we destroyed quiet a bit of evidence by triggering more self destructs in other subnets, but I think the self destruct signal has already gone out to the bad guys through a different peace of malware that I later partially recovered, and probably &amp;quot;heard&amp;quot; the UDP distress signal (that&amp;#39;s what is was called in the binary, not my naming).  After getting all the forensics the client insisted on reconnecting his systems to the web, they were &amp;quot;losing money&amp;quot;. I switched from forensics to reversing.  In the process, while inspecting the malicious libfsalvfs.so I discovered the commands I mentioned above, and discovered a &amp;quot;feature&amp;quot; that helped me fill more paces of the puzzle.  Reversing malware you always find some feeble attempt to obfuscate string using XOR or RC4, or just scrambling the letter ordering. In this case I pretty quickly found a function I called get_obfuscated_string(buffer, string_id). The difference however, was that this one was just horrendous, practically irreversible:    It had like a billion nested switches:    I think they let some intern fresh out of college write that one. It seems the complete list of strings used by the tool are encoded inside in a tree of nested switches, with a variable length encoding, e.g. in one branch the 2nd level might have 3 bits and in another it might have 5 and in a third only a single bit. Some kind of prefix tree if I remember anything from Uni.  Eventually I managed to write code to just brute force the function: #include &amp;lt;stdio.h&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;stdlib.h&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;sys/mman.h&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;sys/types.h&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;sys/stat.h&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;fcntl.h&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;unistd.h&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;string&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;set&amp;gt;  int main(int argc, char* argv[]) { 	// error handling code omitted 	const char* filename = (argc &amp;gt; 1) ? argv[1] : &amp;quot;reconstructed.elf&amp;quot;; 	unsigned long offset = (argc &amp;gt; 1) ? strtol(argv[2], NULL, 16) : 0x22a0;  	int fd = open(filename, O_RDONLY); 	struct stat stbuf; 	fstat(fd, &amp;amp;stbuf); 	const char* addr = (char*)mmap(NULL, stbuf.st_size, PROT_READ | PROT_EXEC, MAP_PRIVATE, fd, 0); 	close(fd); 	const char* base = addr + offset;  	typedef int (*entry_t)(char* outbuf, int id); 	entry_t entry = (entry_t)base; 	std::set&amp;lt;std::string&amp;gt; found; 	char buffer[1024]; 	 	for(long bits = 1; bits &amp;lt; 64; ++ bits) { 		bool any_new = false; 		for(long id = (bits == 1) ? 0 : (1 &amp;lt;&amp;lt; (bits - 1)); id &amp;lt; (1&amp;lt;&amp;lt;bits); ++ id) { 			int status = entry(buffer, id); 			if(status == 0) 				continue; 			if(found.find(buffer) != found.end()) 				continue; 			found.insert(buffer); 			printf(&amp;quot;Got &amp;#39;%s&amp;#39;! [0x%x]
&amp;quot;, buffer, id); 			any_new = true; 		} 		if(!any_new) 			break; 	}  	return 0; }   This first binary had the following strings (I am keeping 3 to myself as they have client related info):  &amp;#39;/proc/self/mem&amp;#39;,  &amp;#39;/proc/self/maps&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/cwd&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/environ&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/fd/%d&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/fdinfo/%d&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/limits&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/cgroup&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/exe&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/cmdline&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/mounts&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/smaps&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/self/stat&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/mem&amp;#39;,  &amp;#39;/proc/%d/maps&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/cwd&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/environ&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/fd/%d&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/fdinfo/%d&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/limits&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/cgroup&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/exe&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/cmdline&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/mounts&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/smaps&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/%d/stat&amp;#39;,         &amp;#39;nfs&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;nfs4&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;tmpfs&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;devtmpfs&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;procfs&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;sysfs&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;WSL2&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/os-release&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/passwd&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/lsb-release&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/debian_version&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/redhat-release&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/home/%s/.ssh&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/var/log/wtmp&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/var/log/syslog&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/var/log/auth.log&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/var/log/cron.log&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/var/log/syslog.log&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/netplan/*.yaml&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/yp.conf&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/var/yp/binding/&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/krb5.conf&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/var/kerberos/krb5kdc/kdc.conf&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/var/log/ganesha.log&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/ganesha/ganesha.conf&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/ganesha/exports&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/exports&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Error: init failed&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;DELL&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/usr/lib/x86_64-linux-gnu/libnfs.so.4&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/tmp/.Test-unix/.fa76c5adb8c04239ff3034106842773b&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Error: config missing&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Error: sysdep missing&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Running&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;LOG&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/usr/lib/x86_64-linux-gnu/ganesha/libfsalvfs.so&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;none&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/sudoers&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/net/tcp&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/proc/net/udp&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;/etc/selinux/config&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;libdl.so.2&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;libc-&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;.so&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;cluster-config&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;recovery-signal&amp;#39;,   Eureka Moment Staring endlessly at this weird function I thought to myself: maybe I can look for code that is structured like this in all the dumps we obtained. We have all those block of mov byte ptr [rdi+?], &amp;#39;?&amp;#39;:    So lets look for blocks of code that are highly dense with these opcodes:  import sys  with open(sys.argv[1], &amp;#39;rb&amp;#39;) as f:     data = f.read()  STATE=None for i in range(len(data) - 6):     if ord(data[i]) == 0xc6 and ord(data[i + 1]) == 0x47:         if STATE and (STATE[0] + STATE[1] + 0x40) &amp;gt;= i:             STATE[1] = i - STATE[0]             STATE[2] += 1         else:             if STATE and STATE[2] &amp;gt;= 20:                 print(&amp;#39;Found region at 0x%x - 0x%x&amp;#39; % (STATE[0], STATE[0] + STATE[1]))             STATE = [i, 4, 1]    And I found them. Oh I did. Some adjustment even led to a version for ARM systems:    The GOlang thingy  I finally found the payload that was sent over to the GW machines. It had 2 stages: the first was the 8192 buffer loaded through the first covert channel. The kernel was modified to inject this buffer into the GOlang application and hook it. This will get fairly technical, but I enjoyed it and so will you:     First note that in the Golang stdlib an HTTP connection can be read through the net/http.(connReader).Read function. The calls are made through a io.Reader interface, so the calls are made through a virtual table, and the call locations cannot be statically identified.   the kernel inject begins by allocating a bunch of RWX memory immediately after the GOlang binary - let&amp;#39;s call it the trampoline area, and it will include two types of generated trampoline functions,   Next the ELF symbol table was used to find the &amp;#39;net/http.(*connReader).Read&amp;#39; symbol,   What we’ll call the 1st trampoline function (code below) is copied to the trampoline area, patching the area marked with HERE with the first 9 bytes of net/http.(*connReader).Read   mprotect(net_http_connReader_read &amp;amp; ~0xfff, 8192, PROT_EXEC | PROT_READ | PROT_WRITE)   modified the beginning of net/http.(*connReader).Read to a near jump into the trampoline - using 5 bytes of the 9 original used by &amp;#39;move rcx, fs:….&amp;#39; that are the preamble to function.   First trampoline function      pop     rax                  pop     rcx      push    rcx      push    rax      mov     r11, cs:qword_&amp;lt;relocated&amp;gt;      mov     rdi, rcx      call    qword ptr [r11+8]      pop     rax      pop     rcx      push    rcx      mov     rcx, fs:0FFFFFFFFFFFFFFF8h &amp;lt;---- HERE      cmp     rsp, [rcx+10h]      jmp     rax      When the trampoline is called (from the new near jump in the beginning of net/http.(*connReader).Read) it examines the stack to locate the return address, and checks if a second type of trampoline we&amp;#39;ll refer to as the return trampoline has already been allocated for the return address for the function,   If not it allocates a new trampoline per call location of net/http.(*connReader).Read from the code below, replacing 123456789ABCDEFh with the absolute address of a function in the malware,   GOlang uses memory for all function argument passing, so immediately after the virtual function call to Read() there will always be a 5 byte mov     reg, [rsp+?] to load Read()&amp;#39;s result into a register. This mov instruction is copied into the first db 5 dup(0) area,   those same 5 bytes are then replacing with a near jump to the 2nd trampoline   the 2nd db 5 dup(0) are filled with a relative near jmp back to the original code patch site.         mov     rax, 123456789ABCDEFh     mov     rdi, rsp     call    rax     db 5 dup(0)     db 5 dup(0)                 This way eventually all the net/http.(*connReader).Read call sites are patched to call a function immediatly after net/http.(*connReader).Read virtual call returns. This lets the malicous code inspect the decoded HTTP packet.  On initialization the 1st stage malware also loads the hefty 2nd stage through the 2nd covert channel, and passes each buffer received from the patch on net/http.(*connReader).Read to it for inspection. The data collected is collected and compressed by the malware and stored back to the NFS server (the 2nd covert channel which bypasses read ACLs on NFS).  Before this case I did not think there was any nice way to hook random GO binaries, this technique is pretty cool.  Unfortunatly I cannot discuss what the 2nd payload actually as it will reveal stuff my employer isn&amp;#39;t ready for yet.  How the kernel got patched? and why not the golang app? The golang app is built inside the CI/CD network segment. This segment can only be accessed through monitored jump hosts with MFA. Each day, the CI/CD pipline clones the source code from the GIT server, builds it, and automatically tests it in a pre-production segment. Once tested it gets digitally signed and uploaded to the NFS server. The running app self updates, checking the digital signature beforehand.  The kernel, on the other hand, is manually built by the guy responsible for it on his own laptop. He then digitally signs it and stores it on a server where it is used by the CI/CD pipeline. Fortunatly for us a commented out line in a script in the CI/CD pipline (a line that was not commented out in the GIT!) did not delete old versions of the kernel and we know which versions were tampered with.  We noticed a 3 month gap about 5 month ago, and it corresponded with the guy moving the kernel build from a Linux laptop to a new Windows laptop with a VirtualBox VM in it for compiling the kernel. It looks as if it took the attackers three months to gain access back into the box and into the VM build.  What we have so far  We found a bunch of malware sitting in the network collecting PII information from incoming HTTPS connection after they are decoded in a GOlang app. The data is exfiltrated through the malware network and eventually is sent to the bad guys. We have more info but I am still working on it, expect another blog post in the future with more details, samples, etc’.  Q&amp;amp;A          Q: What was the initial access vector?      A: We have a pretty good idea, but I cannot publish it yet (RD and stuff). Stay tuned!           Q: Why didn&amp;#39;t you upload anything to VT yet?      A: A few reasons:            I need to make sure no client info is in the binaries - some of the binaries have hardcoded strings that cannot be shared       All of the binaries I have have been reconstructed from memory dumps, so are not in their original form. Does anyone know how to upload partial dumps into VT?                Q: It there a security vulnerability in GO? in the Kernel?      A: Defenitly not! this is just an obnoxious attacker doing what obnoxious attacker do. I might even say the complexity of the stuff means they don’t have a 0day for this platform.           Q: What about YARA rules, C2 address, etc&amp;#39;?      A: Wait for it, there is a lot more coming!           Q: Why did you publish instead of collecting more?      A: To quote the client &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t care who else they are attacking. I just want them off my lawn!&amp;quot;, and he thinks publishing will prevent them from returning to THIS network.     Hopefully what we publish next time will get them off other people’s lawns.           Q: Any Windows malware?      A: Definitly, including what we believe is an EDR bypass. Still working on it.           Q: Any zero days?      A: Maybe …           Q: Who are these bad guys you keep refering to?      A: No clue. Didn’t find anything similiar published. There is now sure way to make anything except unsubstantiated guesses, and I won’t do that.      To be continued.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://igor-blue.github.io/2021/03/24/apt1.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 18:08:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fix typo by ramtinak &amp;#183; Pull Request #1298 &amp;#183; microsoft/dotnet</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/dotnet/pull/1298/files</link>
      <description />
      <author> (microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/dotnet/pull/1298/files</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 17:08:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Your Boss Could Do Your Job, You’re More Likely to Be Happy at Work</title>
      <link>https://hbr.org/2016/12/if-your-boss-could-do-your-job-youre-more-likely-to-be-happy-at-work</link>
      <description>Technical competence matters for managers.</description>
      <author> (by 
			
					Benjamin Artz,
					Amanda Goodall,
						 and 
					Andrew J. Oswald)</author>
      <guid>https://hbr.org/2016/12/if-your-boss-could-do-your-job-youre-more-likely-to-be-happy-at-work</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 17:08:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to implement a hash table (in C)</title>
      <link>https://benhoyt.com/writings/hash-table-in-c/</link>
      <description>An explanation of how to implement a simple hash table data structure, with code and examples in the C programming language.</description>
      <author> (Ben Hoyt)</author>
      <guid>https://benhoyt.com/writings/hash-table-in-c/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 17:08:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&amp;#39;s unusual move to shut down an active counterterrorism operation being conducted by a Western democracy</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/03/26/1021318/google-security-shut-down-counter-terrorist-us-ally/</link>
      <description>A decision to shut down exploits being used by &amp;quot;friendly&amp;quot; hackers has caused controversy inside the company&amp;#39;s security teams.</description>
      <author> (by Patrick Howell O&amp;#39;Neill archive page)</author>
      <guid>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/03/26/1021318/google-security-shut-down-counter-terrorist-us-ally/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 16:09:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Maze Weekly #70 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-70/</link>
      <description>Issue #70 of the Code Maze weekly. Check out the articles we’ve selected for you this week and enjoy the read. .NET and C# Getting Started with the Roslyn APIs: Writing Code with Code [www.stevejgordon.co.uk] Roslyn is one of the less explored and niche areas of .NET. Steve Gordon shows us how to get started […]</description>
      <author> (Vladimir Pecanac)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-70/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 15:08:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a task completion source for a C++ coroutine: Failing to produce a result | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210326-00/?p=105009</link>
      <description>So far, we’ve been working on building a result_holder that can hold any type of result. But what about errors? Because maybe you have code that’s waiting for a result, and the code that’s supposed to produce the result realizes that it messed up and wants to say,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210326-00/?p=105009</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 15:08:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a phone book: Part I</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/193473-B/building-a-phone-book-part-i?Key=cb5fdbac-f19d-411c-a81d-e3ff5c8e3f7b</link>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I asked you to rate an interview question that we had sent to candidates. The idea is to build a persistent phone book, with the idea t...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/193473-B/building-a-phone-book-part-i?Key=cb5fdbac-f19d-411c-a81d-e3ff5c8e3f7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 15:08:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji under the hood</title>
      <link>https://tonsky.me/blog/emoji/</link>
      <description>Detailed look into all the machinery involved in rendering Emoji</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/nikitonsky)</author>
      <guid>https://tonsky.me/blog/emoji/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 14:08:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Super Bot Fight Mode</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/super-bot-fight-mode/</link>
      <description>Beginning immediately, any Cloudflare user with a Pro or Business site can take new action against bots. We’ve added advanced features in the dashboard and some exciting updates to analytics.</description>
      <author> (Ben Solomon)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/super-bot-fight-mode/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 13:08:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make the Web Faster! - PHINUG 2021.04</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p9PGjX8PcdM</link>
      <description>This session is run by the Philippine .NET Users Group (https://meetup.com/phinug​​) that hosts meetups in Manila, Philippines.Meetup link: https://www.meetu...</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
    

    
      
    .NET Foundation
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p9PGjX8PcdM</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 11:08:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Git Hooks To Automate Your Workflow - CodeWithStu</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4QQdLDm1vLM</link>
      <description>Git is a powerful version control system, but often we need to ensure certain patterns and practises are followed. Some of these workflows can be automated w...</description>
      <author> (NDC Conferences
  
  
    

    
      
    NDC Conferences
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4QQdLDm1vLM</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 11:08:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hammster/windows-terminal-shaders</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Hammster/windows-terminal-shaders</link>
      <description>(Hopefully) a small collection of terminal shaders - Hammster/windows-terminal-shaders</description>
      <author> (Hammster)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Hammster/windows-terminal-shaders</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 11:08:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duende Software Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.duendesoftware.com/posts/20210326_bff/</link>
      <description>We help companies using .NET to build identity and access control solutions for modern applications.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.duendesoftware.com/posts/20210326_bff/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 11:08:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Drivers Cooperative</title>
      <link>https://www.drivers.coop/</link>
      <description>We are a driver-owned ridehailing cooperative in New York City.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.drivers.coop/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 11:08:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#39;WeLeakInfo&amp;#39; Site: UK Police Arrest 21 Alleged Users</title>
      <link>https://www.bankinfosecurity.com/uk-police-arrest-21-weleakinfo-users-in-cyber-crackdown-a-15666</link>
      <description>Britain&amp;#39;s National Crime Agency says 21 individuals have been arrested on suspicion of purchasing personally identifiable information from the WLeakInfo website.</description>
      <author> (Prajeet Nair)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bankinfosecurity.com/uk-police-arrest-21-weleakinfo-users-in-cyber-crackdown-a-15666</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 10:09:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia&amp;#39;s voting bill makes water an illegal substance</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/georgias-voting-bill-makes-water-an-illegal-substance/vi-BB1eYBfx</link>
      <description>Veteran Democratic strategist James Carville reacts to the bill just signed into law in Georgia that restricts access to voters and even makes it a crime to give food or water to people waiting in line to vote.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/georgias-voting-bill-makes-water-an-illegal-substance/vi-BB1eYBfx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 09:08:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Windows Terminal made better with the Command Palette plus Multiple Actions in one Command</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/the-windows-terminal-made-better-with-the-command-palette-plus-multiple-actions-in-one-command</link>
      <description>I thought I knew everything about the open source Windows Terminal and then I ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/the-windows-terminal-made-better-with-the-command-palette-plus-multiple-actions-in-one-command</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 09:08:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>permission.site</title>
      <link>https://permission.site/</link>
      <description>Async Clipboard API</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://permission.site/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 09:08:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polaris</title>
      <link>https://www.xamarinpodcast.com/89</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s another customer story - and on this podcast hear about an amazing app developed by Polaris that pairs with snowmobiles, motorcycles, off-road, and other powersports vehicles.</description>
      <author> (Xamarin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.xamarinpodcast.com/89</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 09:08:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>String.Concat Method (System)</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/api/system.string.concat?view=net-5.0#System_String_Concat_System_ReadOnlySpan_System_Char__System_ReadOnlySpan_System_Char__System_ReadOnlySpan_System_Char__</link>
      <description>Concatenates one or more instances of String, or the String representations of the values of one or more instances of Object. </description>
      <author> (dotnet-bot)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/api/system.string.concat?view=net-5.0#System_String_Concat_System_ReadOnlySpan_System_Char__System_ReadOnlySpan_System_Char__System_ReadOnlySpan_System_Char__</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 07:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-03-26</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/03/app-developer-links-2021-03-26/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/03/app-developer-links-2021-03-26/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 07:08:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjust, Save and Restore Webcam Properties With CamProps</title>
      <link>https://weblogs.asp.net/rweigelt/adjust-save-and-restore-webcam-properties-with-camprops</link>
      <description>In recent months, I wrote a few articles that hinted that I was developing a webcam-related utility (here, here, here and here). About two weeks ago, I released it to my colleagues who liked it and&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#8230;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://weblogs.asp.net/rweigelt/adjust-save-and-restore-webcam-properties-with-camprops</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 06:09:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Our First Microservice | The Xamarin Show</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/Building-Our-First-Microservice--The-Xamarin-Show</link>
      <description>This week, James is joined by Nish Anil who is here to walk us through building our very first Microservice for our mobile apps with .NET, ASP.NET Core, Docker, Kubernetes, and more! He shows how to s</description>
      <author> (by James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/Building-Our-First-Microservice--The-Xamarin-Show</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 06:09:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Readable JavaScript: A Tale of Two Experts</title>
      <link>https://alistapart.com/article/human-readable-javascript/</link>
      <description>JavaScript gives us many ways to do things, but deciding which way can be tricky. Laurie Barth gives us a story of two experts who solve this problem in different ways, giving some insight into how…</description>
      <author> (About the Author)</author>
      <guid>https://alistapart.com/article/human-readable-javascript/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 06:09:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choices in Desktop Development</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Choices-in-Desktop-Development</link>
      <description>The desktop is here to stay. Sam Basu reviews how you can take advantage of the latest in .NET technologies and still build the apps your customers demand.  </description>
      <author> (by Robert Green)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Choices-in-Desktop-Development</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 06:09:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Rust 1.51.0 | Rust Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2021/03/25/Rust-1.51.0.html</link>
      <description>Empowering everyone to build reliable and efficient software.</description>
      <author> (Mar. 25, 2021 &amp;#183; The Rust Release Team)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2021/03/25/Rust-1.51.0.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 05:09:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamics 365 Finance and operations - Architecture - Pradeep Loganathan</title>
      <link>https://pradeeploganathan.com/dynamics/dynamics-365-finance-and-operations-architecture/</link>
      <description>This post describes the conceptual architecture of D365 and the cloud deployment architecture. We also look at Devops practices on D365 to use CI/CD pipelines.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/pradeepl/)</author>
      <guid>https://pradeeploganathan.com/dynamics/dynamics-365-finance-and-operations-architecture/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 05:09:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs Interview - 2/18/1981</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DbfejwP1d3c</link>
      <description>An interview with Steve Jobs filmed on 2/18/1981 about the future of Apple, Computers, the Home &amp;amp; Personal computer markets, video games, and more.</description>
      <author> (btm0815ma
  
  
    

    
      
    btm0815ma
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DbfejwP1d3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 03:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a full-text search engine in 150 lines of Python code &amp;#183; Bart de Goede</title>
      <link>https://bart.degoe.de/building-a-full-text-search-engine-150-lines-of-code/</link>
      <description>Full-text search is everywhere. From finding a book on Scribd, a movie on Netflix, toilet paper on Amazon, or anything else on the web through Google (like [how to do your job as a software engineer](https://localghost.dev/2019/09/everything-i-googled-in-a-week-as-a-professional-software-engineer/)), you&amp;#39;ve searched vast amounts of unstructured data multiple times today. What&amp;#39;s even more amazing, is that you&amp;#39;ve even though you searched millions (or [billions](https://www.worldwidewebsize.com/)) of records, you got a response in milliseconds. In this post, we are going to build a basic full-text search engine that can search across millions of documents and rank them according to their relevance to the query in milliseconds, in less than 150 lines of code!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bart.degoe.de/building-a-full-text-search-engine-150-lines-of-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 02:08:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 370 - What the Hack</title>
      <link>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-370-What-the-Hack</link>
      <description>March 25, 2021</description>
      <author> (Cynthia Kreng)</author>
      <guid>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-370-What-the-Hack</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 01:08:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/5NqXBFn9v20</link>
      <description>NDC Manchester 2021 - LIVE!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/5NqXBFn9v20</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 01:08:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Hat statement about Richard Stallman’s return to the Free Software Foundation board</title>
      <link>https://www.redhat.com/en/blog/red-hat-statement-about-richard-stallmans-return-free-software-foundation-board</link>
      <description>Red Hat is a long-time donor and contributor to projects stewarded by the Free Software Foundation (FSF), with hundreds of contributors and millions of lines of code contributed. Considering the circumstances of Richard Stallman’s original resignation in 2019, Red Hat was appalled to learn that he had rejoined the FSF board of directors.</description>
      <author> (Red Hat)</author>
      <guid>https://www.redhat.com/en/blog/red-hat-statement-about-richard-stallmans-return-free-software-foundation-board</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 01:08:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/5NqXBFn9v20&amp;t=15659s</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/5NqXBFn9v20&amp;t=15659s</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 01:08:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Success Mysticism - Christopher Butler</title>
      <link>https://www.chrbutler.com/success-mysticism</link>
      <description>Few things make me sadder than the now predictable moment at which a successful person creates a sellable mysticism out of their good luck and privilege.</description>
      <author> (— Christopher Butler, Dec 31, 2020, Durham, NC)</author>
      <guid>https://www.chrbutler.com/success-mysticism</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:09:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing: Funds for Open Source.</title>
      <link>https://blog.opencollective.com/funds-for-open-source/</link>
      <description>Helping companies invest in open source projects because we want open source creators to have a good livelihood and work sustainably, which is critical to the health of the whole ecosystem.</description>
      <author> (Alyssa Wright)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.opencollective.com/funds-for-open-source/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:09:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid, widespread, and preferential increase of SARS-CoV-2 B.1.1.7 variant in Houston, TX, revealed by 8,857 genome sequences</title>
      <link>https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2021.03.16.21253753v1</link>
      <description>Genetic variants of the SARS-CoV-2 virus have become of great interest worldwide because they have the potential to detrimentally alter the course of the SARS-CoV-2 pandemic, and disease in individual patients. We recently sequenced 20,453 SARS-CoV-2 genomes from patients with COVID-19 disease in metropolitan Houston (population 7 million), dating from March 2020 to early February 2021. We discovered that all major variants of concern or interest are circulating in the region. To follow up on this discovery, we analyzed 8,857 genome sequences from patients in eight Houston Methodist hospitals dispersed throughout the metroplex diagnosed from January 1, 2021 to March 7, 2021. This sample represents 94% of Houston Methodist cases and 4.8% of all reported cases in metropolitan Houston during this period. We discovered rapid, widespread, and preferential increase of the SARS-CoV-2 UK B.1.1.7 throughout the region. The estimated case doubling time in the Houston area is 6.9 days. None of the 648 UK B.1.1.7 samples identified had the E484K change in spike protein that can cause decreased recognition by antibodies.

### Competing Interest Statement

The authors have declared no competing interest.

### Funding Statement

The research was supported by the Houston Methodist Academic Institute Infectious Diseases Fund and many generous Houston philanthropists. James Davis was funded in whole or in part with Federal funds from the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, National Institutes of Health, Department of Health and Human Services, under Contract No. 75N93019C00076.

### Author Declarations

I confirm all relevant ethical guidelines have been followed, and any necessary IRB and/or ethics committee approvals have been obtained.

Yes

The details of the IRB/oversight body that provided approval or exemption for the research described are given below:

This work was approved by the Houston Methodist Research institutional review board (IRB1010-0199).

All necessary patient/participant consent has been obtained and the appropriate institutional forms have been archived.

Yes

I understand that all clinical trials and any other prospective interventional studies must be registered with an ICMJE-approved registry, such as ClinicalTrials.gov. I confirm that any such study reported in the manuscript has been registered and the trial registration ID is provided (note: if posting a prospective study registered retrospectively, please provide a statement in the trial ID field explaining why the study was not registered in advance).

Yes

I have followed all appropriate research reporting guidelines and uploaded the relevant EQUATOR Network research reporting checklist(s) and other pertinent material as supplementary files, if applicable.

Yes

Genome data used in this study have been deposited to GISAID.</description>
      <author> (James M. Musser)</author>
      <guid>https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2021.03.16.21253753v1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:09:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I learned promoting my first side project as an engineer</title>
      <link>https://javierfuent.es/blog/Lessons-promoting-side-project/</link>
      <description>Lessons from showing the world clipplayground.co</description>
      <author> (Javier Fuentes Alonso)</author>
      <guid>https://javierfuent.es/blog/Lessons-promoting-side-project/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:09:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The six principles of lifestyle businesses</title>
      <link>https://blog.alexmaccaw.com/the-six-principles-of-lifestyle-businesses/</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s talk about what makes a great lifestyle business.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.alexmaccaw.com/the-six-principles-of-lifestyle-businesses/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:09:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dodyg/practical-aspnetcore</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dodyg/practical-aspnetcore/tree/net5.0/projects/net6/map-action</link>
      <description>Practical samples of ASP.NET Core 2.1, 2.2, 3.1, and 5.0 projects you can use. Readme contains explanations on all projects. - dodyg/practical-aspnetcore</description>
      <author> (dodyg)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dodyg/practical-aspnetcore/tree/net5.0/projects/net6/map-action</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:09:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracking the front page of the New York Times</title>
      <link>https://blog.tjcx.me/p/tracking-front-page-new-york-times</link>
      <description>Part 2 of my New York Times investigation, where I take a close look at what kinds of articles make it to the front page.</description>
      <author> (Tom)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.tjcx.me/p/tracking-front-page-new-york-times</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:09:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You are sharing your downloads with your Antivirus Company</title>
      <link>https://blog.runtux.com/posts/2021/03/23/</link>
      <description>I recently have provided a customer with a link to a firewall image
(using the Turris MOX router with a variant of OpenWRT) hosted on my
own webserver. The image included keys material for an OpenVPN
connection. The image file was in a hidden directory on my projects
webserver. I monitored closely if there would be any downloads besides
the one I expected from my customer.</description>
      <author> (Ralf Schlatterbeck)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.runtux.com/posts/2021/03/23/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:09:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most requested features for online food delivery</title>
      <link>https://ma.ttias.ch/the-most-requested-features-for-online-food-delivery.html</link>
      <description>My main occupation for the past few years has been building ecommerce platforms for large Food Delivery businesses. Unsurprisingly they usually request very similar functionality. What is surprising, is that there are no ecommerce Systems that offer those features out of the box. Here is a list of them:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ma.ttias.ch/the-most-requested-features-for-online-food-delivery.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:09:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve performance of DateTime.UtcNow on Windows by GrabYourPitchforks &amp;#183; Pull Request #50263 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/50263</link>
      <description>Follow-up to #44771. Builds atop work done in #45479 and #46690.
Resolves #13091.
This PR is based on a series of conversations @tarekgh and I have had recently with regard to short-circuiting our ...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/50263</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:08:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jessica Walter, ‘Arrested Development’ and ‘Archer’ Star, Dies at 80</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/jessica-walter-dead-arrested-development-archer-1234938246/</link>
      <description>Jessica Walter, an Emmy-winning actress known for her work as the stalker in Clint Eastwood’s “Play Misty for Me,” and for the TV series “Arrested Development” and &amp;amp;#8…</description>
      <author> (Carmel Dagan)</author>
      <guid>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/jessica-walter-dead-arrested-development-archer-1234938246/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:08:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this ship still stuck?</title>
      <link>https://istheshipstillstuck.com/</link>
      <description>You know that ship, the one possibly still stuck in the canal. Is it still there? Find out that, and really only that, at this website.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://istheshipstillstuck.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:07:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outside In: The Innovation Stack with Jim McKelvey | Hanselminutes with Scott Hanselman</title>
      <link>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/jim-mckelvey-lWoc4vNg</link>
      <description>In this special episode of Hanselminutes, Scott shares a discussion with Jim McKelvey, a glassblower and also the co-founder of Square! This conversation was previously published as a episode of Microsoft&amp;#39;s internal interview series &amp;quot;Outside In.&amp;quot; Jim&amp;#39;s team and our friends at Microsoft have encouraged us to share the episode where we discuss innovation and entrepreneurship.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/jim-mckelvey-lWoc4vNg</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:07:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raft does not Guarantee Liveness in the face of Network Faults</title>
      <link>https://decentralizedthoughts.github.io/2020-12-12-raft-liveness-full-omission/</link>
      <description>Last month, Cloudflare published a postmortem of a recent 6-hour outage caused by a partial switch failure which left etcd unavailable as it was unable to establish a stable leader. This outage has understandably led to discussion online about exactly what liveness guarantees are provided by the Raft consensus algorithm...</description>
      <author> (Decentralized Thinkers)</author>
      <guid>https://decentralizedthoughts.github.io/2020-12-12-raft-liveness-full-omission/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:07:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A &amp;quot;Better C&amp;quot; Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://zserge.com/posts/better-c-benchmark/</link>
      <description>An unusual benchmark for programming languages, designed to replace C. Unlike many other benchmarks, this one measures developer productivity and performance.</description>
      <author> (Serge Zaitsev)</author>
      <guid>https://zserge.com/posts/better-c-benchmark/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 22:08:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/ddopWp7mFVk</link>
      <description>Apple MacBook M1 for .NET and Xamarin Developers: First Look</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/ddopWp7mFVk</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 22:08:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loop alignment in .NET 6 | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/loop-alignment-in-net-6/</link>
      <description>When writing a software, developers try their best to maximize the performance they can get from the code they have baked into the product. Often, there are various tools available to the developers to find that last change they can squeeze into their code to make their software run faster.</description>
      <author> (Kunal Pathak  Senior Software Engineer, .NET Runtime Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/loop-alignment-in-net-6/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 22:08:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/ddopWp7mFVk&amp;list=PLfbOp004UaYWWOZFZ585BCeRvTduLt9Fm&amp;index=1</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/ddopWp7mFVk&amp;list=PLfbOp004UaYWWOZFZ585BCeRvTduLt9Fm&amp;index=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 22:08:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossil: Fossil Chat</title>
      <link>https://www.fossil-scm.org/home/doc/trunk/www/chat.md</link>
      <description>As of version 2.14,
Fossil supports a developer chatroom feature.  The chatroom provides an
ephemeral discussion venue for insiders.  Design goals include:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.fossil-scm.org/home/doc/trunk/www/chat.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 22:08:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebAssembly-Powered FM Synthesizer</title>
      <link>https://notes.ameo.design/fm.html</link>
      <description>An 8-operator, polyphonic FM synthesizer running completely in the web browser via Rust compiled to WebAssembly with SIMD acceleration. A demo from the larger web synth platform I&amp;#39;m building.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.ameo.design/fm.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:08:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phones and Apps Reduce Your Ability to Focus Even When They Don’t Distract You &amp;#183; Next Level Productivity Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.rize.io/blog/phones-and-apps-reduce-your-ability-to-focus-even-when-they-dont-distract-you</link>
      <description>The mere presence of your phone or apps like Gmail, Slack, and iMessage can decrease your ability to focus even when they don&amp;#39;t actually distract you.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.rize.io/blog/phones-and-apps-reduce-your-ability-to-focus-even-when-they-dont-distract-you</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:08:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why All My Servers Have an 8GB Empty File</title>
      <link>https://brianschrader.com/archive/why-all-my-servers-have-an-8gb-empty-file/</link>
      <description>Last night I was listening to the latest Under the Radar, where Marco Arment dove into nerdy detail about his recent Overcast server issues. The discussion was great, and you should listen to it, but Marco&amp;#39;s recent server troubles were pretty similar to my own server issues from last year, and so I figured I&amp;#39;d share my life-hack solution for anyone out there with the same problem.</description>
      <author> (by Brian Schrader)</author>
      <guid>https://brianschrader.com/archive/why-all-my-servers-have-an-8gb-empty-file/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:08:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Cloud Native Patterns for .NET Developers</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PDdHa0ushJ0</link>
      <description>In this live session, we&amp;#39;ll be talking about various patterns for Cloud Native applications with our friend Nish Anil. Many of these are patterns that you ca...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PDdHa0ushJ0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:08:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Details 9 Desktop Dev Options, from WPF to Blazor -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/03/25/desktop-options.aspx</link>
      <description>For .NET coders targeting Windows, the choices boil down to more traditional XAML-based solutions or newer options based on web tech.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel03/25/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/03/25/desktop-options.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:08:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Manager, Security Engineering (Infrastructure Security) - Remote OK | Marqeta</title>
      <link>https://www.marqeta.com/careers/2989969</link>
      <description>Be a part of the Modern Card Issuing revolution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.marqeta.com/careers/2989969</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:08:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News &amp;amp; Events - Release of draft Applied Cryptography knowledge area for public consultation</title>
      <link>https://www.cybok.org/news/release-of-draft-applied-cryptography-ka</link>
      <description>Cyber Security Body of Knowledge</description>
      <author> (CyBOK)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cybok.org/news/release-of-draft-applied-cryptography-ka</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:08:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Docker Desktop for Windows and WSL 2</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/installing-docker-desktop-for-windows/?hss_channel=tw-4083531</link>
      <description>In this post I show how to install Docker Desktop for Windows, including WSL 2, and explore the initial experience of running a container.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/installing-docker-desktop-for-windows/?hss_channel=tw-4083531</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:08:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>