<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>302: .NET MAUI Release Candidate Is Here!</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/302</link>
      <description>It is go time with the .NET MAUI RC!!</description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/302</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 09:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upload Files With Drag &amp;amp; Drop or Paste in Blazor - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/upload-files-drag-drop-paste-blazor/</link>
      <description>We can upload files to a Blazor Server application using Drag &amp;amp; Drop, as well as Copy/Paste functionality with the help of JSInterop.</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/upload-files-drag-drop-paste-blazor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 09:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hubert Horan - The Uber Bubble: Why Is a Company That Lost $20 Billion Claimed to Be Successful? - Brave New Europe</title>
      <link>https://braveneweurope.com/hubert-horan-the-uber-bubble-why-is-a-company-that-lost-20-billion-claimed-to-be-successful</link>
      <description>This is the first in a series of three articles from the end of 2019 that we have dug out of the archives in support of the Barcelona taxi drivers’ current conflict with Uber (see [...]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://braveneweurope.com/hubert-horan-the-uber-bubble-why-is-a-company-that-lost-20-billion-claimed-to-be-successful</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 09:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Electronics Cultural Issues Are Causing Disasters In Samsung Foundry, LSI, And Even DRAM Memory!</title>
      <link>https://semianalysis.substack.com/p/samsung-electronics-cultural-issues</link>
      <description>Samsung Electronics has a culture problem that has shaken it to its core. Samsung is slipping on all aspects of technology development including the one area they have historically crushed all competitors, DRAM.</description>
      <author> (Dylan Patel)</author>
      <guid>https://semianalysis.substack.com/p/samsung-electronics-cultural-issues</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 09:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Stallman - &amp;quot;The state of the Free Software movement&amp;quot; - April 13, 2022</title>
      <link>https://lunduke.substack.com/p/richard-stallman-the-state-of-the</link>
      <description>Free Software founder has choice words for Ubuntu, Apple. Announces a manual for GNU C.</description>
      <author> (Bryan Lunduke)</author>
      <guid>https://lunduke.substack.com/p/richard-stallman-the-state-of-the</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 09:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>flibit_unreal_unity.md</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/flibitijibibo/035087d8736441786b10e8c3879d50dd</link>
      <description>GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/flibitijibibo/035087d8736441786b10e8c3879d50dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 08:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A poem about Silicon Valley, assembled from Quora questions about Silicon Valley</title>
      <link>https://splinternews.com/a-poem-about-silicon-valley-assembled-from-quora-quest-1793856489</link>
      <description>Why do so many startups fail?Why are all the hosts on CouchSurfing male?Are we going to be tweeting for the rest of our lives?Why do Silicon Valley billionaires choose average-looking wives?</description>
      <author> (Jason O. Gilbert)</author>
      <guid>https://splinternews.com/a-poem-about-silicon-valley-assembled-from-quora-quest-1793856489</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Email Rule - Have a separate Inbox and an Inbox CC to reduce email stress. Guaranteed.</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/one-email-rule-have-a-separate-inbox-and-an-inbox-cc-to-reduce-email-stress-guaranteed</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve mentioned this tip before but once more for the folks in the back. This ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/one-email-rule-have-a-separate-inbox-and-an-inbox-cc-to-reduce-email-stress-guaranteed</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best engineering interview question I’ve ever gotten, Part 1
</title>
      <link>https://quuxplusone.github.io/blog/2022/01/06/memcached-interview/</link>
      <description>It’s been a while since I was on the receiving end of a software engineering
interview. But I still remember my favorite interview question. It was at MemSQL circa 2013.
(They haven’t even kept their name,
so I assume they’re not still relying on this specific interview question.
I don’t feel bad for revealing it. It’s a great story that I tell people a lot;
I’ve just never blogged it before.)

</description>
      <author> (Arthur O’Dwyer)</author>
      <guid>https://quuxplusone.github.io/blog/2022/01/06/memcached-interview/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange Egg Yolks: Why Are Some Egg Yolks So Orange?</title>
      <link>https://www.foodunfolded.com/article/why-are-some-egg-yolks-so-orange</link>
      <description>Does egg yolk colour matter? Why are yolks from hens in different countries different colours? Find out with FoodUnfolded.</description>
      <author> (March 23, 2020




By 
Annabel Slater
My Articles)</author>
      <guid>https://www.foodunfolded.com/article/why-are-some-egg-yolks-so-orange</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 01:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Does &amp;quot;Shitty Job&amp;quot; Mean in The Low-Skill, Low-Pay World?</title>
      <link>https://www.residentcontrarian.com/p/what-does-shitty-job-mean-in-the</link>
      <description>I once wrote an article about being poor, and I started it out with a story about a friend who had spent some time explaining to my wife (who, at the time, was struggling to maintain a household of four on entry-level retail money) how hard up for funds they were, and how stressful it was. The zinger of the story, such as it was, was that the woman and her husband were both doctors. They weren’t bad people, but they came from a context where things like “being broke” had entirely different meanings.</description>
      <author> (Resident Contrarian)</author>
      <guid>https://www.residentcontrarian.com/p/what-does-shitty-job-mean-in-the</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 01:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The games Nintendo didn&amp;#39;t want you to play: Tengen</title>
      <link>https://nicole.express/2022/the-center-point-can-not-hold.html</link>
      <description>Recently, I took a look at Nintendo’s MMC line of mappers, and some other boards. All boards for the NES’ western releases had to be manufactured by Nintendo...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicole.express/2022/the-center-point-can-not-hold.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 01:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Projects - Lessons Learned</title>
      <link>https://mco.dev/effective-projects-lessons-learned/</link>
      <description>I wrote this document for internal use at Google, but I believe it has broad applicability, not just in tech but in any field where people undertake team projects.</description>
      <author> (Marc Cohen)</author>
      <guid>https://mco.dev/effective-projects-lessons-learned/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THCon 2k22 CTF - &amp;quot;Local Card Maker&amp;quot; Writeup - Guy Lewin&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://lewin.co.il/thcon-2k22-ctf-local-card-maker-writeup/</link>
      <description>Writeup for the &amp;quot;Local Card Maker&amp;quot; challenge in THCon 2k22 CTF. Including SHA-1 exploitation and PHP LFI.</description>
      <author> (Author







Guy Lewin



View all posts)</author>
      <guid>https://lewin.co.il/thcon-2k22-ctf-local-card-maker-writeup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnings after 500 commits to my vimrc | I am Sang</title>
      <link>https://iamsang.com/en/2022/04/13/vimrc/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m a software engineer from South Korea and currently live in Berlin. I write articles and draw comics in Korean and English.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iamsang.com/en/2022/04/13/vimrc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hey... let&amp;#39;s use automapper to generate passwords. : programminghorror</title>
      <link>https://teddit.pussthecat.org/r/programminghorror/comments/u3h1dl/hey_lets_use_automapper_to_generate_passwords/</link>
      <description>FbCare and ElGr are the only specific references in the code snippet. FB could be many things, but it&amp;#39;s not immediately obvious, and ElGr is chopped to the point of being unrecognizable to anyone who isn&amp;#39;t familiar with the area of interest.</description>
      <author> (jiggajim)</author>
      <guid>https://teddit.pussthecat.org/r/programminghorror/comments/u3h1dl/hey_lets_use_automapper_to_generate_passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Experience with a Mac - Prashant Sengar</title>
      <link>https://prashants.in/blog/my-balanced-experience-mac-m1-chip-review/</link>
      <description>Reviews either state the Macbook to be the best product ever made, or the worst thing happened to mankind since Ancient Aliens.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://prashants.in/blog/my-balanced-experience-mac-m1-chip-review/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptographic Assumptions in Hidden-Order Groups</title>
      <link>https://alinush.github.io/2020/11/05/cryptographic-assumptions-in-hidden-order-groups.html</link>
      <description>In this post, we summarize some of the cryptographic hardness assumptions used in hidden-order groups.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alinush.github.io/2020/11/05/cryptographic-assumptions-in-hidden-order-groups.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tools that power Outlook for iOS</title>
      <link>https://myers.io/2022/04/16/the-tools-that-power-outlook/</link>
      <description>I’ve been responsible for the developer tooling for Outlook iOS for 6 years now. Back when I started, we had just a single Bash script that covered everything we though we needed at the time. Now, we have 30,000+ lines of Python code (including tests I have to admit) that depend directly on 50 Python packages. Most of these packages are ones you might expect such as requests, pylint, or black. However, 13 are our own and shared with others. Of those 13, 9 are open source and available for the general community. A further 3 out of the 50 packages we use are my own creation from outside work. While some are personal, and some were created at work, all the tools listed in this post were created by me.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://myers.io/2022/04/16/the-tools-that-power-outlook/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Robot Handing DNS Updates</title>
      <link>https://anchor.host/email-robot-handing-dns-updates/</link>
      <description>I know we&amp;#39;ve all been there. Staring at the endless stream of new emails wondering, &amp;quot;Can I automate this somehow?&amp;quot;. Trust me, I know. That answer is always</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anchor.host/email-robot-handing-dns-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An inherent source of correlation in the crypto market</title>
      <link>https://thomasvilhena.com/2022/04/an-inherent-source-of-correlation-in-crypto</link>
      <description>If you follow the crypto market, you may already be familiar with the strong direct correlation between cryptocurrencies prices, native or tokenized. When BTC goes down, pretty much everything goes down with it, and when BTC is up, everything is most likely to go up too. This correlation isn’t exclusive to BTC, impacts on the price of many other cryptocurrencies (such as ETH) also reverberate across a wide range of crypto assets, with different degrees of strength among them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thomasvilhena.com/2022/04/an-inherent-source-of-correlation-in-crypto</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinionated variable names &amp;#183; Caffeinspiration</title>
      <link>https://alexanderell.is/posts/opinionated-variable-names/</link>
      <description>I think a lot about the human part of code, especially the work our brains do when writing and reading it and interfacing with the computer. Rachelbythebay had a great take on a way to inject some brain-processing into a technical task - when you’re running a command to affect n servers, maybe it would be good to type that number in manually.</description>
      <author> (Alex Ellis)</author>
      <guid>https://alexanderell.is/posts/opinionated-variable-names/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Transaction Hash (Txhash) Details | Etherscan</title>
      <link>https://etherscan.io/tx/0xcd314668aaa9bbfebaf1a0bd2b6553d01dd58899c508d4729fa7311dc5d33ad7</link>
      <description>Ethereum (ETH) detailed transaction info for txhash 0xcd314668aaa9bbfebaf1a0bd2b6553d01dd58899c508d4729fa7311dc5d33ad7. The transaction status, block confirmation, gas fee, Ether (ETH), and token transfer are shown.</description>
      <author> (etherscan.io)</author>
      <guid>https://etherscan.io/tx/0xcd314668aaa9bbfebaf1a0bd2b6553d01dd58899c508d4729fa7311dc5d33ad7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 20:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staff archetypes</title>
      <link>https://staffeng.com/guides/staff-archetypes/</link>
      <description>Stories of folks reaching Staff Engineer roles.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://staffeng.com/guides/staff-archetypes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 20:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests: normalize all the things by NickCraver &amp;#183; Pull Request #2097 &amp;#183; StackExchange/StackExchange.Redis</title>
      <link>https://github.com/StackExchange/StackExchange.Redis/pull/2097</link>
      <description>In recent PRs, through no fault of their own, I can see a lot of inconsistency because they&amp;#39;re based on inconsistency in the existing test suite. This is one major overhaul to unify how things are ...</description>
      <author> (StackExchange)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/StackExchange/StackExchange.Redis/pull/2097</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 15:03:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Azure Load Testing</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/introducing-azure-load-testing/</link>
      <description>This post is about Azure Load Testing - Azure Load Testing is a fully managed Azure service that enables developers and testers to generate high-scale load with custom Apache JMeter scripts and gain actionable insights to catch and fix performance bottlenecks at scale. In this post I will explain how to get create an Azure Load Testing resource and execute it with Azure portal. Azure Load Testing helps us to execute Apache JMeter Tests - I already created one using Apache JMeter - You can checkout this blog post on how to create one.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/introducing-azure-load-testing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 13:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mjg59 | The Freedom Phone is not great at privacy</title>
      <link>https://mjg59.dreamwidth.org/59479.html</link>
      <description>The Freedom Phone advertises itself as a &amp;quot;Free speech and privacy first focused phone&amp;quot;. As documented on the features page, it runs ClearOS, an Android-based OS produced by Clear United (or maybe one of the bewildering array of associated companies, we&amp;#39;ll come back to that later). It&amp;#39;s advertised as including Signal, but what&amp;#39;s shipped is not the version available from the Signal website or any official app store - instead it&amp;#39;s this fork called &amp;quot;ClearSignal&amp;quot;.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mjg59.dreamwidth.org/59479.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 12:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>