<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor your GitHub Actions in Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://timheuer.com/blog/github-actions-extension-for-visual-studio/</link>
      <description>Want to manage your GitHub Actions in Visual Studio? Look no further and install this extension today!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://timheuer.com/blog/github-actions-extension-for-visual-studio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - phpgl/flappyphpant: A very simple Flappy Bird-like game written in PHP, built on PHP-GLFW and the VISU framework.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/phpgl/flappyphpant</link>
      <description>A very simple Flappy Bird-like game written in PHP, built on PHP-GLFW and the VISU framework. - GitHub - phpgl/flappyphpant: A very simple Flappy Bird-like game written in PHP, built on PHP-GLFW an...</description>
      <author> (phpgl)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/phpgl/flappyphpant</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 23:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom&amp;#39;s Updated Terms of Service Permit Training AI on User Content Without Opt-Out</title>
      <link>https://stackdiary.com/zoom-terms-now-allow-training-ai-on-user-content-with-no-opt-out/</link>
      <description>Zoom Video Communications, Inc. recently updated its Terms of Service to encompass what some critics are calling a significant invasion of user privacy.</description>
      <author> (Alex Ivanovs)</author>
      <guid>https://stackdiary.com/zoom-terms-now-allow-training-ai-on-user-content-with-no-opt-out/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 23:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Concretude of the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://notes.ghed.in/cloud-computing-water-consumption-90e7e46f5d54</link>
      <description>It’s ironic that the “cloud” of the tech titans behaves in the opposite way to that of nature: instead of bringing water, it consumes it.</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@ghedin)</author>
      <guid>https://notes.ghed.in/cloud-computing-water-consumption-90e7e46f5d54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layoffs and its impact</title>
      <link>https://aravind.dev/layoff/</link>
      <description>At a company I worked in, A senior leader used to start the town hall or quarterly business review meetings with, &amp;quot;Think, if this is your…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aravind.dev/layoff/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growth Experiment: How Much Traffic Unsplash Drives to Your Website - Fresh van Root</title>
      <link>https://freshvanroot.com/blog/how-much-traffic-unsplash-drives-website/</link>
      <description>Do 500K views and 10K downloads drive traffic to your website from your Unsplash profile? We ran an experiment and share the results.</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/rolfmi)</author>
      <guid>https://freshvanroot.com/blog/how-much-traffic-unsplash-drives-website/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bike: Row Types</title>
      <link>https://www.hogbaysoftware.com/posts/bike-row-types/</link>
      <description>Bike Outliner adds row types!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hogbaysoftware.com/posts/bike-row-types/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MassTransit Bus Stop - Request Response via Messaging (RPC)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=TWWVHWlBGIs</link>
      <description>Can I use messaging for request response (RPC)? Sure, why not! In this interactive episode, Chris and Dru talk about request response, and go through a coupl...</description>
      <author> (Chris Patterson
  
  
  
    Chris Patterson
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=TWWVHWlBGIs</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>06 We Speak: IBM MQ</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/fv-ag8h5lYA</link>
      <description>In this session, we continue with the &amp;quot;We Speak&amp;quot;, Mission Critical Series with an episode on how Azure Logic Apps can unlock scenarios where is required to i...</description>
      <author> (Andy Malone MVP
  
  
  
    Andy Malone MVP
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/fv-ag8h5lYA</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking is child&amp;#39;s play - SQL injection with Havij by 3 year old</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Fp47G4MQFvA</link>
      <description>Find me on Twitter @troyhuntYou know what really strikes me about a lot of the hacks we&amp;#39;ve seen lately? It just seems too easy. I mean we&amp;#39;re seeing a huge nu...</description>
      <author> (David Bombal
  
  
  
    David Bombal
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Fp47G4MQFvA</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disinterest.</title>
      <link>https://www.baldurbjarnason.com/2023/disinterest/</link>
      <description>One of the benefits of time is perspective. When you’re writing or coding, letting the work rest for a day or two usually lets you review it with a fresh perspective revealing its flaws as obvious.</description>
      <author> (Baldur Bjarnason)</author>
      <guid>https://www.baldurbjarnason.com/2023/disinterest/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humble Tech Book Bundle: Math for Programmers 2023 by Manning</title>
      <link>https://www.humblebundle.com/books/math-for-programmers-2023-manning-books</link>
      <description>Harness math, machine learning, and more to boost your coding skills with our latest bundle from Manning Publications. Pay what you want &amp;amp; support Trees, Water &amp;amp; People! </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.humblebundle.com/books/math-for-programmers-2023-manning-books</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tradeoffs in Testing</title>
      <link>https://dillonshook.com/tradeoffs-in-testing/</link>
      <description>I’m finally getting around to putting down in words the testing philosophy I’ve developed over the years. Some of it might rock the boat a bit, other parts may be obvious to some folks, but what I’d like you most to take away is a reflection on your own testing philosophy and the tradeoffs your making. There’s no free lunch.
Choosing how much time to invest in testing is all about balancing how confidently you can say your program is doing what you intend to and how fast you can modify or add to your program.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dillonshook.com/tradeoffs-in-testing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The universe is (probably) not a simulation</title>
      <link>https://blog.georgovassilis.com/2023/08/07/the-universe-is-probably-not-a-simulation/</link>
      <description>If this is a simulation, then the universe running it must be, too The simulation hypothesis [1] assumes that if it is possible to simulate a universe in some cosmological frame, it is probably hap…</description>
      <author> (George Georgovassilis)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.georgovassilis.com/2023/08/07/the-universe-is-probably-not-a-simulation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;Make something idiot-proof, the world will show you a better idiot&amp;quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.izoukhai.com/blog/make-something-idiot-proof-the-world-will-show-you-a-better-idiot</link>
      <description>Ever felt the frustration of crafting an &amp;#39;idiot-proof&amp;#39; masterpiece, only to watch the world conjure up a brand-new kind of &amp;#39;genius&amp;#39;?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.izoukhai.com/blog/make-something-idiot-proof-the-world-will-show-you-a-better-idiot</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Central Binomial Coefficient and Laplace&amp;#39;s Method</title>
      <link>https://cgad.ski/blog/the-central-binomial-coefficient-and-laplaces-method.html</link>
      <description>The central binomial coefficient is the sequence down the &amp;quot;center&amp;quot; of Pascal&amp;#39;s triangle, namely

These numbers show up, for example, in a random walk on the integers: if we start off at  and make  independent increments of  or , giving each choice even odds, then we will find ourselves back at the origin with probability

Some basic Markov process reasoning tells us that a random walk like this one can either be recurrent or dissipative: trajectories will either visit each position infinitely many times, or escape to infinity, spending only a finite number of steps at each position. Now, let  be our trajectory, and  be the number of times that . Since

the question of whether the random walk we have described is recurrent comes down to whether the central binomial coefficient grows quickly enough to make this series diverge. Does it? We can also consider the random walk on , moving at each step by an increment in the set , in which case the expected number of visits to the origin is

When are these processes recurrent? To answer either question, we need to figure out something about the asymptotic growth of central binomial coefficient.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cgad.ski/blog/the-central-binomial-coefficient-and-laplaces-method.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being a Disciplined Person In an Undisciplined World</title>
      <link>https://durmonski.com/self-improvement/disciplined-person/</link>
      <description>Can you become a disciplined person in the chaotic and undisciplined world we live in? Well, in this article we explore what are the options.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/durmonski/)</author>
      <guid>https://durmonski.com/self-improvement/disciplined-person/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing a recursive descent parser in Bash &amp;#183; m10k</title>
      <link>https://m10k.eu/2023/07/29/pkgex-parser.html</link>
      <description>Two years ago, I was tasked to write a program that generates RPM package
repositories from a large pool of packages. The pool is a set of directories that
contain all packages that were ever built for a given Miracle Linux release, and
the program would be used to pick specific packages from the pool and generate
repositories for yum and dnf. The existing program had hard-coded rules for
package selection that made it require frequent repairs, and it didn’t play nice
with modularity packages. Since the new solution should be an improvement over
the old one, I decided to separate the rules from the code, and for this I needed
a small domain-specific language. I had already written a lot of absurd things in
Bash at the time, so naturally I had to see if a parser could be another of those
things.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://m10k.eu/2023/07/29/pkgex-parser.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does a CTO know when they need a coach?</title>
      <link>https://blog.mocoso.co.uk/2023/06/26/how-does-a-cto-know-when-they-need-a-coach/</link>
      <description>Having a CTO coach can be really beneficial for you and your company.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.mocoso.co.uk/2023/06/26/how-does-a-cto-know-when-they-need-a-coach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My (Painful) Experience With Ubiquiti As A DevOps Engineer | tyzbit.blog</title>
      <link>https://tyzbit.blog/my-painful-experience-with-ubiquiti-as-a-devops-engineer</link>
      <description>My Experience With Ubiquiti As A DevOps Engineer</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tyzbit.blog/my-painful-experience-with-ubiquiti-as-a-devops-engineer</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on exit interviews</title>
      <link>https://rednafi.com/zephyr/notes_on_exit_interviews/</link>
      <description>If you’re a manager, then there’s no shortage of information for you on how to conduct exit interviews. But there aren’t many resources that focus on how to handle them from an employee’s perspective. I’ve been meaning to write a quick piece that isn’t biased by anyone else’s experience and is short enough so that I can quickly jog my memory in the future should the need arise. While I’ve participated in a few of them over the past five years, this text doesn’t attempt to combat the inexorable recency bias that may have seeped into the writing.</description>
      <author> (redowan delowar)</author>
      <guid>https://rednafi.com/zephyr/notes_on_exit_interviews/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing Randomness with LLDB</title>
      <link>https://bryce.co/lldb-remove-randomness/</link>
      <description>Use LLDB to bypass randomness without leaving your debugger.</description>
      <author> (Bryce Pauken)</author>
      <guid>https://bryce.co/lldb-remove-randomness/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Building web apps with Blazor and Spark.NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=x9gfr0A6jnQ</link>
      <description>Spark.NET is a web application framework that embraces ASP.NET and Entity Framework fundamentals while extending their capabilities and adding new ones, enab...</description>
      <author> (YouTube Movies &amp;amp; TV
  
  
  
    YouTube Movies &amp;amp; TV
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=x9gfr0A6jnQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sep 0.2.0 - Even Faster Parsing (~10 GB/s on Zen 3) and More</title>
      <link>https://nietras.com/2023/08/07/sep-0-2-0/</link>
      <description>Shortly after Introducing Sep - Possibly the World’s Fastest .NET CSV
Parser, Mark
Pflug author of
Sylvan.Data.Csv
adopted the PackUnsignedSaturate trick from Sep and added a Vector256/Avx2
path in version 1.3.2 for
impressive
improvements. This
meant Sylvan was suddenly slightly faster than Sep at the very low level parsing
of rows only. This I, of course, had to address and Sep
0.2.0 is the result. &amp;#128517;

</description>
      <author> (nietras)</author>
      <guid>https://nietras.com/2023/08/07/sep-0-2-0/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The time Michael Jordan helped a guy win $1 million</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/36146138/million-dollar-shot-michael-jordan-chicago-bulls-1993</link>
      <description>Thirty years ago, Don Calhoun got picked to try a three-quarter-court shot during a Bulls game. He made it, sending Michael Jordan and the Bulls into an all-out frenzy because he had won $1 million. Or so everybody thought.</description>
      <author> (Ryan Hockensmith)</author>
      <guid>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/36146138/million-dollar-shot-michael-jordan-chicago-bulls-1993</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring JavaScript and TypeScript Development in Visual Studio for ASP.NET Core Developers</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=1-U75WdCEbE</link>
      <description>Over the last 12 months, we made many improvements to the JavaScript and TypeScript developer experience in Visual Studio. We will discuss why and when you w...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=1-U75WdCEbE</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is GIT? #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Hp-_sxO3s6U</link>
      <description>What is GIT? #shortsSupport me on Patreon to access the source code:https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand.Net 7 SDK: https://dotnet.microsoft.com/en-us/downl...</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand
  
  
  
    Mohamad Lawand
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Hp-_sxO3s6U</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Using Zoom</title>
      <link>https://the.webm.ink/not-using-zoom</link>
      <description>Dear client,  Setting aside the earlier challenges of using Zoom under ChromeOS and Linux, I have mostly been declining invitations to Zo...</description>
      <author> (Webmink In Draft)</author>
      <guid>https://the.webm.ink/not-using-zoom</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car Bloat: “Huge Cars Are Terrible for Society”</title>
      <link>https://kottke.org/23/08/car-bloat-huge-cars-are-terrible-for-society</link>
      <description>

David Zipper, who researches and writes about mobility and transportation, recently did a big thread on Mastodon (and Bluesky) a</description>
      <author> (posted by Jason Kottke &amp;#160; Aug 07, 2023)</author>
      <guid>https://kottke.org/23/08/car-bloat-huge-cars-are-terrible-for-society</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZK - Leading Enterprise Java Web Framework</title>
      <link>https://www.zkoss.org/</link>
      <description>A highly productive open source Java framework for building amazing enterprise web and mobile applications.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.zkoss.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some tactics for writing in public</title>
      <link>https://jvns.ca/blog/2023/08/07/tactics-for-writing-in-public/</link>
      <description>Some tactics for writing in public</description>
      <author> (Julia Evans)</author>
      <guid>https://jvns.ca/blog/2023/08/07/tactics-for-writing-in-public/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>362: Developer Productivity - C# 12, Dev Tunnels, C# Dev Kit</title>
      <link>https://player.fireside.fm/v2/UDzB5o3V+hV9g_c5K/twitter</link>
      <description>Powerful podcast hosting and analytics. By podcasters, for podcasters.</description>
      <author> (Fireside Labs, LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://player.fireside.fm/v2/UDzB5o3V+hV9g_c5K/twitter</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>06 We Speak: IBM MQ</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=fv-ag8h5lYA</link>
      <description>In this session, we continue with the &amp;quot;We Speak&amp;quot;, Mission Critical Series with an episode on how Azure Logic Apps can unlock scenarios where is required to i...</description>
      <author> (Fox News
  
  
  
    Fox News
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=fv-ag8h5lYA</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Unity VS Code Tool Demise, Microsoft Previews One Powered by C# Dev Kit -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/08/07/vs-code-unity-tool.aspx</link>
      <description>Unity: &amp;#39;This plugin was a result of one of our hackweek experiments by a few of our former employees. Unfortunately, it&amp;#39;s never been fully functional and hasn&amp;#39;t received any updates for almost two years, bringing you an unstable coding experience.&amp;#39;</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel08/07/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/08/07/vs-code-unity-tool.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That wasn’t supposed to happen!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=bxyXT64MmFU</link>
      <description>Software developers often find themselves walking a tightrope between innovation and potential disaster. While we celebrate the brilliant achievements in sof...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=bxyXT64MmFU</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSA: Intel Graphics Drivers Now Collect Telemetry By Default</title>
      <link>https://www.techpowerup.com/312122/psa-intel-graphics-drivers-now-collect-telemetry-by-default</link>
      <description>The latest version of Intel Arc GPU Graphics Software introduced an interesting change that isn&amp;#39;t reflected in the Release Notes. The installer of the 101.4578 beta drivers add a &amp;quot;Compute Improvement Program&amp;quot; (CIP) component as part of the &amp;quot;typical&amp;quot; setup option that is enabled by default. Under the...</description>
      <author> (09:59
				by
				unclewebb)</author>
      <guid>https://www.techpowerup.com/312122/psa-intel-graphics-drivers-now-collect-telemetry-by-default</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 17:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>41 AK Expenses Tracker | Query User Transactions From Azure Cosmos DB &amp;amp; Azure Function</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=jX1d_8c5es4</link>
      <description>Join our Discord Serverhttps://discord.gg/GPrGJRuXJbJoin this channel to get access to perks:https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCRs-PO48PbbS0l7bBhbu5CA/joinSHO...</description>
      <author> (DevOps Directive
  
  
  
    DevOps Directive
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=jX1d_8c5es4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapter Design Pattern and C#: A Practical Approach</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Ny5xvQOUEW4</link>
      <description>In this video you will learn about the Adapter Design Pattern.00:00 Adapter Design Pattern Intent00:29 Adapter Design Pattern Motivation04:30 Adapter Design ...</description>
      <author> (Devs School
  
  
  
    Devs School
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Ny5xvQOUEW4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dependency Injection with Scrutor: Scanning and Registering</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2lGxhAUeT-E</link>
      <description>Hi there! Today we are going to see how we can scan our application for classes and register them in the DI container, alongside with their interfaces, using...</description>
      <author> (Spyros Katsios
  
  
  
    Spyros Katsios
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2lGxhAUeT-E</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core 8.0 Preview: All New AddBearerToken Extensions</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2023/08/aspnet-core-80-preview-all-new.html</link>
      <description>.NET, .NET Core, ASP.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2023/08/aspnet-core-80-preview-all-new.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualize Your Data with Charts in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=yMG8oPIuMig</link>
      <description>A big part of any mobile app is data, with Microcharts you can now visualize that data with amazing looking charts in your .NET MAUI app. Show data in a Data...</description>
      <author> (Coding Droplets
  
  
  
    Coding Droplets
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=yMG8oPIuMig</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Process for Submitting Pull Requests</title>
      <link>https://seankilleen.com/2023/08/my-process-for-submitting-pull-requests/</link>
      <description>I’ve been asked a lot of times about my process for submitting pull requests, so I figured I’d write it up!</description>
      <author> (Sean Killeen)</author>
      <guid>https://seankilleen.com/2023/08/my-process-for-submitting-pull-requests/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims of Room Temperature and Ambient Pressure Superconductor</title>
      <link>https://forums.spacebattles.com/threads/claims-of-room-temperature-and-ambient-pressure-superconductor.1106083/page-13</link>
      <description>Compilation of all Claims/Reports of Replication Efforts underway that I know of.
(By &amp;quot;Reliability of Claim&amp;quot;, I refer to the reliability regarding whether this individual/institution is actually attempting a replication of LK99 or not. It does not refer to the reliability or trustworthiness of...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://forums.spacebattles.com/threads/claims-of-room-temperature-and-ambient-pressure-superconductor.1106083/page-13</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struct memory layout optimizations, practical considerations</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/199841-A/struct-memory-layout-optimizations-practical-considerations?Key=a53d68c5-1801-429b-af30-3fd406eabc6e</link>
      <description>In my previous post I discussed how we could store the exact same information in several ways, leading to space savings of 66%! That leads to interesting que...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/199841-A/struct-memory-layout-optimizations-practical-considerations?Key=a53d68c5-1801-429b-af30-3fd406eabc6e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside STL: The map, set, multimap, and multiset - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230807-00/?p=108562</link>
      <description>A red-black tree.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230807-00/?p=108562</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing object between .NET host and WebView2 - G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/sharing-object-between-dotnet-host-and-webview2.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to share objects between .NET host and a WebView2 instance.</description>
      <author> (G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/sharing-object-between-dotnet-host-and-webview2.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Annotated Monthly | August 2023 | The JetBrains Blog</title>
      <link>https://jb.gg/4zkl2h</link>
      <description>.NET tutorials and tips</description>
      <author> (Rachel Appel)</author>
      <guid>https://jb.gg/4zkl2h</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use sessionStorage and localStorage in Blazor | BinaryIntellect Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://www.binaryintellect.net/articles/7d88d63b-768c-4e78-a934-cacac486b22a.aspx</link>
      <description>Traditionally developes used cookies to store small pieces of information on the client machine. Although you can use cookies in Blazor apps, there is a modern and more handy alternative -- sessionStorage and localStorage objects.</description>
      <author> (Bipin Joshi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.binaryintellect.net/articles/7d88d63b-768c-4e78-a934-cacac486b22a.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The High Performance Types You Ignored for Years in .NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=MGCNS6s6e5o</link>
      <description>Use code ARCH15 and get 15% off the brand new Solution Architecture course on Dometrain: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-solution-architectureBe...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=MGCNS6s6e5o</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Critical User Journeys in Azure </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/articles/critical-journeys-azure/</link>
      <description>Flowe explains how they combine metrics from many sources together in Azure to monitor Critical User Journeys and prevent downtime for a critical application.</description>
      <author> (Andrea Grillo
                
            
            
        Site Reliability EngineerFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/articles/critical-journeys-azure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Improve Performance With EF Compiled Query #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=tXthbeJZb4s</link>
      <description>&amp;#128640; Support me on Patreon to access the source code: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovicJoin my weekly .NET newsletter:https://www.milanjovanovic.techRead ...</description>
      <author> (TapRooT&amp;#174;
  
  
  
    TapRooT&amp;#174;
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=tXthbeJZb4s</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 12:03:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity Extension for Visual Studio Code: Preview Release </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/08/unity-vscode-preview/</link>
      <description>Microsoft released the initial preview of its Unity extension for Visual Studio Code. Extension builds upon the existing C# Dev Kit and C# extensions, providing developers with a toolkit for Unity development across Windows, macOS, and Linux. The integration aims to simplify the coding and debugging experience for Unity developers, regardless of the platform while using Visual Studio Code.</description>
      <author> (Almir Vuk)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/08/unity-vscode-preview/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - lucavallin/barco: Linux containers from scratch in C.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/lucavallin/barco</link>
      <description>Linux containers from scratch in C. Contribute to lucavallin/barco development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (lucavallin)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/lucavallin/barco</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have I Been Pwned: Terms of use</title>
      <link>https://haveibeenpwned.com/TermsOfUse</link>
      <description>Have I Been Pwned allows you to search across multiple data breaches to see if your email address or phone number has been compromised.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://haveibeenpwned.com/TermsOfUse</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>370: The Rise of LK-99</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/370</link>
      <description>It is time for some lightning topics! We have all sorts of good ones including the new and maybe real LK-99 superconductor, a chat about MacCatalyst, should you use 3rd party libraries? What is on Frank&amp;#39;s desk and when will this all end?</description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/370</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - chebykinn/sedmario: NES Super Mario Bros level 1 written in pure sed!</title>
      <link>https://github.com/chebykinn/sedmario</link>
      <description>NES Super Mario Bros level 1 written in pure sed! Contribute to chebykinn/sedmario development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (chebykinn)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/chebykinn/sedmario</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use a Microsoft Entra Verified&amp;#160;ID Employee credential to view paycheck data</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2023/08/07/use-a-microsoft-entra-verified-id-employee-credential-to-view-paycheck-data/</link>
      <description>This post shows how a Microsoft Entra Verified ID employee credential can be used to access user specific data. This demo shows possible paycheck data from Switzerland. A payment ID can be the prin…</description>
      <author> (damienbod)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2023/08/07/use-a-microsoft-entra-verified-id-employee-credential-to-view-paycheck-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of LK-99 | Merge Conflict ep. 370</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=djmzXd_GCaw</link>
      <description>It is time for some lightning topics! We have all sorts of good ones including the new and maybe real LK-99 superconductor, a chat about MacCatalyst, should ...</description>
      <author> (YouTube Movies &amp;amp; TV
  
  
  
    YouTube Movies &amp;amp; TV
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=djmzXd_GCaw</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techniques for Sorting a List in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-techniques-for-sorting-list/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will explore different techniques for sorting a List. We will examine List.Sort and the LINQ ordering extensions.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-techniques-for-sorting-list/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyed Services in the IServiceProvider in .NET 8 preview 7</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/40dab3bb-d17e-4357-b579-b1d95fb9bfda</link>
      <description>The .NET 8 preview 7 will bring another exciting feature some of you probably awaiting for a long time: Keyed services.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/40dab3bb-d17e-4357-b579-b1d95fb9bfda</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 06:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotW Any% 23:42 [WR]</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/PMestfpYPXA</link>
      <description>An incredibly unbalanced run. The plateau certainly isn&amp;#39;t awful, but compared to my best plateau time it loses 15-16 seconds. On the flip side I only lost 6 ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/PMestfpYPXA</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 05:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electron Band Structure In Germanium, My Ass</title>
      <link>https://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~kovar/hall.html</link>
      <description>Abstract: The exponential dependence of resistivity on temperature 
in germanium is found to be a great big lie.  My careful theoretical modeling and painstaking experimentation reveal 1) that my equipment 
is crap, as are all the available texts on the subject and 2) that this whole exercise was a complete waste of my 
time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~kovar/hall.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotW Any% 23:42 [WR]</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=PMestfpYPXA</link>
      <description>An incredibly unbalanced run. The plateau certainly isn&amp;#39;t awful, but compared to my best plateau time it loses 15-16 seconds. On the flip side I only lost 6 ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=PMestfpYPXA</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 03:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software in Audio and How to Lead</title>
      <link>https://www.codingblocks.net/podcast/software-in-audio-and-how-to-lead/</link>
      <description>Podcast: Play in new window | Download</description>
      <author> (About Allen Underwood)</author>
      <guid>https://www.codingblocks.net/podcast/software-in-audio-and-how-to-lead/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 01:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>