<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>goto in action - The exception from the rule</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/a1de0393-e0f9-491e-8c26-8ec34da60d16</link>
      <description>A lot of developers will say never use goto. This keyword is bad as it promotes spaghetti code. But as so often in live the exception confirms the rules. Let&amp;#39;s see where goto can increase the readability and maintainability.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/a1de0393-e0f9-491e-8c26-8ec34da60d16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 09:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Floppotron 3.0 - Computer Hardware Orchestra</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/kCCXRerqaJI</link>
      <description>The big upgrade of my PC hardware orchestra. 512 floppy disk drives, 16 hard disks and 4 scanners. What do you want to hear next? Write it in comments!Playin...</description>
      <author> (Sad Ken
  
  
  
    Sad Ken
  






    •
  
  
    
      19K views
    
      8 years ago)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/kCCXRerqaJI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#165 Mads Torgersen, ADHD | no dogma podcast</title>
      <link>https://nodogmapodcast.bryanhogan.net/165-mads-torgersen-adhd/</link>
      <description>Mads Torgersen and I chat about his recent diagnosis with Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) and how it has changed his life for the better.&amp;lt;iframe frameborder=&amp;quot;0&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;200px&amp;quot; scrolling=&amp;quot;no&amp;quot; seamless src=&amp;quot;https://player.simplecast.com/d0e8ba7f-1058-41fb-b062-d04d758c17a0?dark=false&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;100%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/iframe&amp;gt;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nodogmapodcast.bryanhogan.net/165-mads-torgersen-adhd/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 05:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benoit Essiambre</title>
      <link>https://benoitessiambre.com/macro.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://benoitessiambre.com/macro.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 04:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Line Through HTTPS</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2634/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2634/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 04:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Azure Container Apps with the Azure CLI and Compose Files</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/accelerating-azure-container-apps-with-the-azure-cli-and-compose/ba-p/3516636</link>
      <description>Azure Container Apps is a hosted service designed to make microservices and container-based solutions easy in a serverless model. My team (the Cloud Native Advocacy team) and I have been kicking the tires on this service since the preview was announced. &amp;#160; After working through some getting started e...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/188530)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/accelerating-azure-container-apps-with-the-azure-cli-and-compose/ba-p/3516636</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 02:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - sarsko/CreuSAT: CreuSAT - A formally verified SAT solver written in Rust and verified with Creusot.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sarsko/CreuSAT</link>
      <description>CreuSAT - A formally verified SAT solver written in Rust and verified with Creusot. - GitHub - sarsko/CreuSAT: CreuSAT - A formally verified SAT solver written in Rust and verified with Creusot.</description>
      <author> (sarsko)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sarsko/CreuSAT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 02:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citus 11 for Postgres goes fully open source, with query from any node</title>
      <link>https://www.citusdata.com/blog/2022/06/17/citus-11-goes-fully-open-source/</link>
      <description>Release blog post for Citus 11, which is now fully open source and includes the non-blocking shard rebalancer. Citus 11 also includes automatic schema and metadata syncing across nodes, enabling you to query from any node if your app needs that type of high query throughput.</description>
      <author> (Twitter icon    @marcoslot     GitHub icon    marcocitus)</author>
      <guid>https://www.citusdata.com/blog/2022/06/17/citus-11-goes-fully-open-source/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 01:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - DamianEdwards/AspNetCorePathAuthorization: A middleware to enable path-based authorization in an ASP.NET Core application.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/DamianEdwards/AspNetCorePathAuthorization</link>
      <description>A middleware to enable path-based authorization in an ASP.NET Core application. - GitHub - DamianEdwards/AspNetCorePathAuthorization: A middleware to enable path-based authorization in an ASP.NET C...</description>
      <author> (DamianEdwards)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/DamianEdwards/AspNetCorePathAuthorization</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Us For the First Ever SnarkyJS Week</title>
      <link>https://blog.o1labs.org/join-us-for-the-first-ever-snarkyjs-week-6c718ed2b090</link>
      <description>What is SnarkyJS?
A TypeScript framework for writing zero-knowledge apps (“zkApps”).</description>
      <author> (https://o1labs.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.o1labs.org/join-us-for-the-first-ever-snarkyjs-week-6c718ed2b090</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 23:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrix notes - anarcat</title>
      <link>https://anarc.at/blog/2022-06-17-matrix-notes/</link>
      <description>I have some concerns about Matrix (the protocol, not the movie that
came out recently, although I do have concerns about that as
well). I&amp;#39;ve been watching the project for a long time, and it seems
more a promising alternative to many protocols like IRC, XMPP, and
Signal.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anarc.at/blog/2022-06-17-matrix-notes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of QUBO formulations</title>
      <link>https://blog.xa0.de/post/List-of-QUBO-formulations/</link>
      <description>About the author:
                Daniel is co-founder and CTO at Aqarios GmbH. He holds a M.Sc.
                in Computer Science from LMU Munich, and has published papers
                in reinforcement learning. He writes about technical topics in
                quantum computing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.xa0.de/post/List-of-QUBO-formulations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Gould</title>
      <link>https://www.nathangould.com/posts/the-usage-based-data-stack-is-finally-here-and-pretty-cheap/</link>
      <description>Personal website and blog of Nathan Gould. Writing about technology, entrepreneurship, and whatever else seems interesting.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nathangould.com/posts/the-usage-based-data-stack-is-finally-here-and-pretty-cheap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hertzbleed Attack</title>
      <link>https://ellipticnews.wordpress.com/2022/06/14/hertzbleed-attack/</link>
      <description>I woke up to the news of a new form of timing-side-channel attack based on the dynamic frequency scaling of modern x86 processors. This is the Hertzbleed attack, which will be presented at the USEN…</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://ellipticnews.wordpress.com/2022/06/14/hertzbleed-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Tsai - Blog - Thoughts on SwiftUI After WWDC 2022</title>
      <link>https://mjtsai.com/blog/2022/06/17/thoughts-on-swiftui-after-wwdc-2022/</link>
      <description>Casey Liss:</description>
      <author> (Michael J. Tsai)</author>
      <guid>https://mjtsai.com/blog/2022/06/17/thoughts-on-swiftui-after-wwdc-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure as software</title>
      <link>https://www.justingarrison.com/blog/2022-06-01-infrastructure-as-software/</link>
      <description>What is beyond infrastructure as code?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.justingarrison.com/blog/2022-06-01-infrastructure-as-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship as a Risk Management Strategy</title>
      <link>https://dylancastillo.co/entrepreneurship-as-a-risk-management-strategy/</link>
      <description>Table of Contents


 * The Plan
 * What&amp;#39;s Next?


Entrepreneurship, contrary to popular belief, is a great risk management strategy. Thoughtful entrepreneurs take on similar risks as employees while getting a chance to win a much larger pot.

Also, it&amp;#39;s more fun!

If you&amp;#39;ve ever read a book about how to start</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dylancastillo.co/entrepreneurship-as-a-risk-management-strategy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>?? &amp;quot;&amp;quot; is a Code Smell / Jordan Eldredge</title>
      <link>https://jordaneldredge.com/blog/defaulting-to-empty-string-is-a-code-smell/</link>
      <description>Defaulting to empty string is a lie we tell our type checker.</description>
      <author> (Jordan Eldredge)</author>
      <guid>https://jordaneldredge.com/blog/defaulting-to-empty-string-is-a-code-smell/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix Stuck iCloud Syncing on macOS</title>
      <link>https://preslav.me/2022/06/16/howto-fix-stuck-icloud-syncing-macos/</link>
      <description>What to do when your Mac won&amp;#39;t sync important files to iCloud.</description>
      <author> (Preslav Rachev)</author>
      <guid>https://preslav.me/2022/06/16/howto-fix-stuck-icloud-syncing-macos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Knowledge Development Challenge For You</title>
      <link>https://scottscheper.com/letter/27/</link>
      <description>The Website of Scott P. Scheper of San Diego, California.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scottscheper.com/letter/27/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t catch errors without a reason</title>
      <link>https://robinwinslow.uk/dont-catch-errors</link>
      <description>Catching errors without thinking carefully about the user experience is an antipattern and a debugging nightmare.</description>
      <author> (https://twitter.com/nottrobin)</author>
      <guid>https://robinwinslow.uk/dont-catch-errors</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 300</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/sbhcGNMl8GA</link>
      <description>I’m in Melbourne; Upcoming NDC Event; Travel Updates; Podcast Recommendations; DivX SubTitles Data Breach; Sponsored by Kolidehttps://www.troyhunt.com/weekly...</description>
      <author> (Android Authority
  
  
  
    Android Authority
  




  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/sbhcGNMl8GA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The World&amp;#39;s Most Satisfying Checkbox | (Not Boring) Software</title>
      <link>https://www.andy.works/words/the-most-satisfying-checkbox</link>
      <description>The Art of Game Feel (a.k.a Juice) in Product Design</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.andy.works/words/the-most-satisfying-checkbox</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Live: Post-Build 2022 - Events</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learntv/learnlive-post-build-22/</link>
      <description>Every week starting May 31, 2022 through June 27, 2022 (5 episodes)</description>
      <author> (lbugnion)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learntv/learnlive-post-build-22/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCaml - Language extensions</title>
      <link>https://kcsrk.info/webman/manual/effects.html</link>
      <description>(Introduced in 5.0)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kcsrk.info/webman/manual/effects.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Live</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/shows/learn-live/</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s right there in the name: We present Microsoft Learn content Live. Every episode we&amp;#39;ll choose a Learn module and work through it. We&amp;#39;ll pull in guests to give you extra commentary from experts and sometimes even the engineers who built it. Join us and ask questions, live! Watch our latest series: Learn Live at Build 2022  Come together at Microsoft Build May 24-26 2022, to explore the latest innovations in code and application development—and to gain insights from peers and experts from around the world. We have 21 Learn Live sessions this year, including 3 in French, 2 in German, 2 in Spanish and 2 in Japanese! More information... Post Microsoft Build 2022  Join us for a medley of modules following Microsoft Build 2022. You will have a chance to learn LIVE, ask questions from our presenters and gain knowledge to help you complete Cloud Skills Challenges and certifications. More information... Azure Cosmos DB Certification Study Hall  Learn how to design, implement, and monitor cloud-native applications that store and manage data. Learn Live with our experts every Wednesday beginning January 12, 2022 and get certified with the Azure Cosmos DB Developer Specialty certification. More information... Use Bicep to deploy your Azure infrastructure as code  Learn how to deploy Azure resources by using Bicep. Bicep is a language and set of tools to help you to deploy your infrastructure as code. Bicep makes your deployments more consistent and repeatable. Learn Live with our experts every Tuesday beginning March 8, 2022. More information... Azure Hybrid Cloud Study Hall  Calling all IT Decision Makers and IT Implementers! Join us for the new Azure Hybrid study hall series. This fourteen-part weekly series will answer your questions live, walk through how to configure, deploy, manage your hybrid cloud resources using services and hybrid cloud technologies, and walk-through Microsoft Learn modules focused on Azure Arc and Azure Stack HCI. You will learn how you can manage your on-premises, edge and multicloud resources, and how you can deploy Azure services anywhere with Azure Arc and Azure Stack. The series will kick off on April 14th, 2022 and will have two new episodes every Thursday!. More information... Past series You can watch all our past content on demand! Aspectos b&amp;#225;sicos de Azure  Acomp&amp;#225;&amp;#241;anos semana a semana para repasar y aprender los Aspectos b&amp;#225;sicos de Azure. Cada semana desde el 14 de Marzo de 2022 hasta el 25 de Abril de 2022 (7 episodios) M&amp;#225;s informaci&amp;#243;n... Deploy your apps with Java on Azure using familiar tools and frameworks  Learn how you can build, migrate, and scale Java applications on Azure using the tools and frameworks that you know and love - from Spring, to Kubernetes, to Java EE. every Monday beginning March 21, 2022. More information... Start your Learning Journey into Azure AI with a Helping Hand - Powered by Women in AI  This series is designed to help you get started on a Microsoft Azure AI learning journey. Not matter your previous knowledge of AI, this actionable set of sessions will take you through what is available in Azure AI, Computer Vision and Conversational AI and give you space to ask a set of experts questions about each topic. We will only scratch the surface of what is available on Microsoft Learn and will encourage you to continue your learning between weekly sessions in the series. This series partners with the Microsoft Certified: Azure AI Fundamentals certification - if you follow this learning path you will be well on your way to taking this exam. Every week starting February 28, 2022 through March 14, 2022 (3 episodes) More information... Create microservices with .NET and ASP.NET  Create independently deployable, highly scalable, and resilient services using the free and open-source .NET platform. Learn Live with our experts every Tuesday beginning January 11, 2022 on how you can Create microservices with .NET and ASP.NET More information... Hybrid Infrastructure Study Hall  Calling all Windows Server administrators! Join us on Learn TV for this new Windows Server Hybrid study hall series. This seven-part weekly series will answer your questions live, walk through how to configure advanced Windows Server services using on-premises, hybrid, and cloud technologies, and walk through Microsoft Learn modules related to the new Windows Server Hybrid Administrator Associate certification. The series will kick off at Ignite on November 2nd and will have a new episode every Thursday (and a few Tuesdays) through December 16th. More information... Post Microsoft Ignite Module Medley  Continue your learning from Microsoft Ignite on Learn TV and join the Learn Live Module Medley series focused on six modules directly related to Ignite content. From learning how to plan and deploy Microsoft Teams to optimizing databases by using advanced modeling patterns for Azure Cosmos DB, Learn Live is the place to get your questions answered live and complete Leaning Modules together. Please note that the live show times listed are in Central European Time and not Pacific Time. More information... Modern web development with .NET 6  Starting Monday, November 15, 2021 (PST), join Scott Hanselman, Maira Wenzel, Jeff Fritz, Jon Galloway, James Montemagno, and Matt Soucoup live on Learn TV for a five-part series exploring modern web development with .NET 6. Each week, .NET experts will be walking through Learn modules and answering your questions live. From front-end development with Razor Pages and Blazor to backend development with APIs, Static Apps, and microservices, you&amp;#39;ll be guided by easy to digest conceptual content and hands-on exercises. More information... </description>
      <author> (markdefalco)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/shows/learn-live/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runs Testing Using C# Simulation -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/06/17/runs-testing.aspx</link>
      <description>Dr. James McCaffrey of Microsoft Research uses a full code program for a step-by-step explanation of this machine learning technique that indicates if patterns are random.
</description>
      <author> (By James McCaffrey06/17/2022)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2022/06/17/runs-testing.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 19:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ping/Pong Jasper Style</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2022/06/17/ping-pong-jasper-style/</link>
      <description>I’ve spit out quite a bit of blogging content the past several weeks on both Marten and Jasper: Marten just got better for CQRS&amp;#160;architectures&amp;#160;about some new functionality dreamed up by&amp;#160;Oskar …</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2022/06/17/ping-pong-jasper-style/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 19:01:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to simply workaround RAM-leaking libraries like Puppeteer. Universal way to fix RAM leaks once and forever</title>
      <link>https://devforth.io/blog/how-to-simply-workaround-ram-leaking-libraries-like-puppeteer-universal-way-to-fix-ram-leaks-once-and-forever/</link>
      <description>Learn how to workaround any kinds of leaks in 3rd-party libraries. Get ready-to-use leak-fixer code for NodeJS.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devforth.io/blog/how-to-simply-workaround-ram-leaking-libraries-like-puppeteer-universal-way-to-fix-ram-leaks-once-and-forever/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 19:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ante</title>
      <link>https://antelang.org/</link>
      <description>For exploring refinement types, lifetime inference, and algebraic effects</description>
      <author> (jfecher)</author>
      <guid>https://antelang.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 17:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platformer Toolkit by Game Maker&amp;#39;s Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://gmtk.itch.io/platformer-toolkit</link>
      <description>From Game Maker&amp;#39;s Toolkit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gmtk.itch.io/platformer-toolkit</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 17:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recut - Remove Silence From Your Videos Automatically</title>
      <link>https://getrecut.com/</link>
      <description>Because nobody&amp;#39;s got time for making hundreds of tedious cuts by hand.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://getrecut.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 15:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Build – Join us May 24-26 2022</title>
      <link>https://mybuild.microsoft.com/en-US/sessions/d2a86fe6-abb9-4939-a44d-ed660f9bb675</link>
      <description>Come together and discover the latest innovations in code and application development—and gain insights from peers and experts from around the world.</description>
      <author> (Microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://mybuild.microsoft.com/en-US/sessions/d2a86fe6-abb9-4939-a44d-ed660f9bb675</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 14:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>