<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>HTML/CSS: How to (Maybe) Prevent the Text of a Time Display from Jiggling Around, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://weblogs.asp.net/rweigelt/html-css-how-to-maybe-prevent-the-text-of-a-time-display-from-jiggling-around-part-2</link>
      <description>In my previous blog post, I described how to deal with text output of time codes (e.g., hours:minutes:seconds) in Windows Presentation Foundation (WPF) when using a font where not all digits take up&amp;amp;#160;&amp;amp;#8230;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://weblogs.asp.net/rweigelt/html-css-how-to-maybe-prevent-the-text-of-a-time-display-from-jiggling-around-part-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 06:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 7 - The StringSyntaxAttribute</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2022/12/net-7-stringsyntaxattribute.html</link>
      <description>With the release of .NET 7, a new attribute was introduced; the StringSyntaxAttribute .   What does the StringSyntaxAttribute do?   The Stri...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2022/12/net-7-stringsyntaxattribute.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 06:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add docker-compose project to run all apps by LuizFDS &amp;#183; Pull Request #41 &amp;#183; davidfowl/TodoApi</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidfowl/TodoApi/pull/41</link>
      <description>With docker-compose we now setup it as startup project and run it from Visual Studio. It will spin up both apps todoapi and todo-web-server plus jaeger and prometheus.</description>
      <author> (davidfowl)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/davidfowl/TodoApi/pull/41</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 05:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What was Microsoft&amp;#39;s first Integrated Development Environment (IDE)? #Shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=x4RjmDFBna4</link>
      <description>For #AskAnArchivist Day, we thought we&amp;#39;d ask our archivist Amy Stevenson about Microsoft&amp;#39;s first IDE.  Find all the docs on our latest IDEs right here: https...</description>
      <author> (Leila Gharani
  
  
  
    Leila Gharani
  




  Verified



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=x4RjmDFBna4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Thomas Achord</title>
      <link>https://alastairadversaria.com/2022/11/27/the-case-against-thomas-achord/</link>
      <description>Thomas Achord is the headmaster of a private classical Christian school, the co-author of the 2021 book Who is My Neighbor? An Anthology in Natural Relations, and is co-host of the Ars Politica pod…</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://alastairadversaria.com/2022/11/27/the-case-against-thomas-achord/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving wire:click not working - Jorge Colon Consulting</title>
      <link>https://jorgecolonconsulting.com/solving-wireclick-not-working/</link>
      <description>If wire:click not working there&amp;#39;s several steps you should take. We&amp;#39;re going to go through them and hopefully resolve your problem.</description>
      <author> (Jorge Colon)</author>
      <guid>https://jorgecolonconsulting.com/solving-wireclick-not-working/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving a Murder Mystery | Paul Osman</title>
      <link>https://paulosman.me/2022/11/29/solving-a-murder-mystery/</link>
      <description>A coworker asked me if I ever write about difficult bugs I’ve encountered. I hadn’t thought about doing that before, but I like the idea. The conversation made me think about a bug I ran into at Honeycomb that I want to document before I forget the details. Solving this one was a team effort, requiring different insights from different people. It was also the kind of bug I could only imagine solving with good observability and teamwork.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://paulosman.me/2022/11/29/solving-a-murder-mystery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is External Validation And When It Becomes Unhealthy</title>
      <link>https://durmonski.com/psychology/external-validation/</link>
      <description>Learn more about external validation. Why we crave it. Why it can be a good. And how to heal from constantly needing external validation.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/durmonski/)</author>
      <guid>https://durmonski.com/psychology/external-validation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic DAOs</title>
      <link>https://lorenzopieri.com/robotic_daos/</link>
      <description>Picture this future scenario. It’s a busy Monday morning, the streets are buzzing and the robo-taxi you called has barely found some space for a temporary stop. Wow it’s real: no driver, as your friend Mark told you. You jump in the back seat and shout your destination out loud. The taxi speeds up slowly and you are on your way. Just 15 minutes later you hop off, you check your phone: payment confirmed, all good. Then a message from Mark: “Ride complete, thanks for choosing us! :) See you soon buddy!”. Mark does not actually own the robo-taxi, but he receives a small payment for each ride. You don’t remember exactly, but Mark said something about making a loan to the robo-taxi owning itself. And what was the other bit…? Oh yea, just by loaning a percentage of the full taxi cost he gets a say into where the taxi should roam and even a 10% discount on a ride! Now you are too busy, but you promise yourself to look more into this. As a user yourself, investing in robo-taxis sounds like a no-brainer.  Your future-self just interacted with a Robotic DAO. In this article I want to cover 3 simple points: Introduce the novel concept of Robotic DAOs, why they are interesting and what is missing to actually see one live.  What is a Robotic DAO?  A robotic DAO is a Decentralised Autonomous Organisation which funds, oversees and profits from a fleet of revenue generating autonomous assets. The assets are physical entities, often robots, which after an initial loan become economically self-sufficient and can repay the initial loan plus distributing extra profits to the original funders. Operational autonomy is not a strict requirement, but autonomous assets need less resources to operate and have a more predictable behaviour, which in turn make them more attractive as an investment.  Let’s keep it concrete and examine an hypothetical scenario with robo-taxis, from original funding to daily operations. A DAO is established and a target asset class is decided: robo-taxis. The economic behaviour of the taxi is set in advance: location of the fleet, pricing, hours of operations, interests on loan repayment and so on. Crowdsourced decision making is hard, but robo-taxis behaviour is simple enough that consensus is achieved quickly: the first fleet will be deployed in San Francisco, charging the average market rate and operating 20hrs with a night maintenance session. The DAO strikes a deal with a robo-taxi manufacturer for 1000 taxis, with a heavy discount due to the large order. Similar deals are secured with a company orchestrating and servicing the taxis, a software firm that will manage the booking systems, insurance companies and law firms. All agreements are provisional to a successful fundraiser. The opportune licences and authorizations are agreed with the city council.  It’s time to fundraise and the news is all around the web. A community owned fleet of taxis is going to be deployed and contributions of any size are accepted, simply owning a share of a robo-taxi is enough to obtain some perks.  Few months pass by,  the fundraiser is oversubscribed, and a year later the first taxi is operational. Each taxi operates as an autonomous entity, a SubDAO, collecting revenues from rides and buying services to maintain itself. Sophisticated SubDAOs will be created with a budget for marketing and premium navigation software, but the first SubDAOs are very simple: wait around the busiest city streets to find customers and use the default manufacturer navigation. The ride experience is indistinguishable for any other private robo-taxi service, but the profit from the rides is distributed back to the original funders through the DAO. Actually a small percentage is accumulated in the asset treasury wallet, to shield the asset from unexpected charges and eventually upgrade it for increased profitability.  Robotic DAO Perks and Specs  Some thoughts about what makes Robotic DAOs interesting.  Robotics DAOs reward communities twice: they provide financial returns to the funders, but more importantly offer a useful service to the overall society. The service is created bottom-up and is tailored to the needs of the majority.  Robotics DAOs redistribute the benefits of automation to the society at large, as opposed to few large companies: the robots are self-owning entities economically programmed with the ethics established by the DAO voters. DAOs profits can be reinvested into the most profitable and effective robots, in a self-fulfilling loop.  Thanks to crowdfunding, DAOs can leverage economies of scale which others cannot and take bold risks which individual companies would struggle to justify. Some DAOs will fail, leaving the investors with nothing. But the failure will not been due to fraud or corruption; society at large has tested an autonomous entity on the free market and it did not work. A new learning about what will work next.  Robotic DAOs have a powerful built-in incentive mechanism to use the service and marketing given by the community, which will give a competitive edge versus any privately owned automation company. There is a very direct sense of ownership in buying a fraction of a robo-taxi and seeing a small microtransaction hit your wallet when a friend of yours rides it.  Robotic DAO assets need to be as simple as possible so that their behaviour is predictable and easy to automate. At the same time good robotic DAO assets are relatively expensive, to justify the DAO overhead. Candidates are robo-taxis, public transports, vending machines and automated shops, mobile robots and robot manipulators, humanoid-robots, smart grids and real-estate.  Finally, Robotic DAOs will de facto become a financial asset class on its own. Contrary to other financial instruments, this would be a solid class backed by physical entities, with direct and measurable benefits for the overall society. Any successful Robotic DAOs would contribute to increasing the global productivity thanks to automation, but without increasing inequality and in fact raising the living standard of anybody benefiting from the robot services.  How to De-Risk a Robotic DAO and What’s Missing  Robotics DAOs need to mitigate 5 main risk areas: Market, Operations, Product, Tech, and Legal.  Market: This is the easiest one, make sure to provide services that are in demand. To be on the safe side, target an existing market such as urban car rides.  Operations: Robotic DAO have decentralised decision making and as such are inherently less agile and efficient than private companies owning fleets of robots. The advantage coming from the community involvement will eventually fade if the unit economics are not competitive. As such, Robotic DAOs need to target highly automated and predictable assets which require little decision making. Dealing with daily operations such as complaints and user feedback should be highly automated too.  Product: Choose an asset which will provide solid recurring revenue overtime and with long obsolescence time, both in terms of functionalities and appeal. Easier said than done, since most robotics assets are still iterating in search of the best designs.  Regarding market, operations and products, vending machines appear to be an established and battle-tested asset that satisfy the above criterias.  Tech: Keep the overhead from decentralised decision making at minimum. Current DAOs are still iterating on fair voting mechanisms, architecture best practices and scalability.  Legal: Tricky. The purest form of Robotic DAO would be self-owning SubDAO assets being allowed to enter into legal agreements, with the DAO participants able to loan to SubDAO or sell the loans rights to other participants. Having SubDAO behaviour formalised in code makes the assets attractive, since they are independent from any third party, similarly to the status of Bitcoin in the cryptocurrency space. An easier formulation would be to have the DAO own the assets instead, but this could in principle trigger liabilities to the DAO contributors in case of assets bankruptcy. In any case, the whole area around DAOs owning assets and entering into legal contracts is still uncharted.  Looking Forward  Robotics DAOs offer an alternative to privately or government owned automation at scale, but to be feasible and competitive they will require advancements in asset autonomy and DAOs scalability. In the near term, hybrid structures with LLCs behind DAOs and SubDAOs and/or partially centralised decision making offer an intriguing route to experiment with Robotics DAOs.  Many of the concepts introduced are early and still hard to articulate, I hope it made some sense to you! Would you participate in a Robotic DAO? Would you build one? Let me know in the comments or reach out privately!</description>
      <author> (Lorenzo Pieri)</author>
      <guid>https://lorenzopieri.com/robotic_daos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Agile a welfare program for developers?</title>
      <link>https://tomaskohl.com/code/2022/agile-is-a-welfare-program-for-developers/</link>
      <description>How do you make developers comfortable? You could implement Scrum. Just don&amp;#39;t expect to get anything done anytime soon.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tomaskohl.com/code/2022/agile-is-a-welfare-program-for-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual Recursion in Language</title>
      <link>http://raganwald.com/2022/11/03/mutual-recursion.html</link>
      <description>This is not a programming post.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://raganwald.com/2022/11/03/mutual-recursion.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ripoff or bargain?</title>
      <link>https://www.darrennix.com/blog/ripoff-or-bargain/</link>
      <description>Imagine a horrible world where the only internet connection (laptop or phone) is from the inflight wifi beaming down from Southwest flights criss-crossing overhead – basically dialup. &amp;#160;Then one day Google Fiber announces that 2Gbps fiber is coming to your neighborhood. &amp;#160;

What’s the most you would be willing to pay</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.darrennix.com/blog/ripoff-or-bargain/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company, team, self.</title>
      <link>https://lethain.com/company-team-self/</link>
      <description>Back when I was managing at Uber, I latched onto a thinking tool that I drilled into the teams I worked with: reach the right outcomes by prioritizing the company first, your team second, and yourself third. This company/team/self framework proved itself a helpful decision-making tool, and almost always led to the “correct” outcome. It also helped me articulate why I disagreed with some of my peers’ decisions, which violated this hierarchy by placing individual or team preferences over the company’s priorities.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lethain.com/company-team-self/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory Safe Languages in Android 13</title>
      <link>https://security.googleblog.com/2022/12/memory-safe-languages-in-android-13.html</link>
      <description>Posted by Jeffrey Vander Stoep    For more than a decade, memory safety vulnerabilities have consistently represented more than 65% of vulne...</description>
      <author> (Posted by Jeffrey Vander Stoep)</author>
      <guid>https://security.googleblog.com/2022/12/memory-safe-languages-in-android-13.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ArgumentException and ArgumentOutOfRangeException helpers in .NET 8</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/f4bc6fcc-5691-4f72-b9bb-75aeeb59230a</link>
      <description>Do you remember how .NET 6 introduced the ArgumentNullException.ThrowIfNull guard? And afterward, with .NET 7 we&amp;#39;ve got this excellent bit: ArgumentException.ThrowIfNullOrEmpty? Guess what, there might come some new handy additions for the upcoming .NET 8 iteration.
So let&amp;#39;s see what are those new changes and how they make the code simpler.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/f4bc6fcc-5691-4f72-b9bb-75aeeb59230a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 23:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much does Rust&amp;#39;s bounds checking actually cost?</title>
      <link>https://blog.readyset.io/bounds-checks/</link>
      <description>Rust prevents out-of-bounds memory accesses and buffer overruns via runtime bounds checks - what’s the cost of those bounds checks for a real-world, production application?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.readyset.io/bounds-checks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 22:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2022</title>
      <link>https://adventofcode.com/2022</link>
      <description>Our sponsors help make Advent of Code possible:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://adventofcode.com/2022</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 22:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET MAUI Community Toolkit Monthly Standup, December 2022</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=tqQhW104UKI</link>
      <description>Join us for our monthly team standup as we discuss the current happenings in the .NET MAUI Community Toolkit! https://github.com/CommunityToolkit/Maui</description>
      <author> (YouTube Movies
  
  
  
    YouTube Movies
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=tqQhW104UKI</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 21:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 448 - Azure and OSS</title>
      <link>https://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-448-Azure-and-OSS</link>
      <description>The Azure Podcast</description>
      <author> (Evan Basalik)</author>
      <guid>https://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-448-Azure-and-OSS</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 21:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Steve Smith: Domain-Driven Design and Architecture - Episode 209</title>
      <link>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/steve-smith-domain-driven-design-and-architecture</link>
      <description>Steve works with companies that want to avoid the trap of technical debt by helping their teams deliver quality software quickly. Steve and his team at NimblePros have been described by clients as a “force multiplier,” amplifying the value of existing development teams. Steve’s client list includes Microsoft, Quicken Loans, Celina Insurance, and many other satisfied customers. And he also offers career coaching to developers through Dev better.com. &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [3:20] What is onion architecture? [4:07] Steve discusses Domain-Driven design. [5:15] Domain-Driven Design is all about how to take big complicated problems in software, and break them up into smaller pieces that we as developers can isolate, think about, design, test, and then construct together in a modular fashion with other pieces. [6:00] The key concepts of Domain-Driven Design. [9:13] How and why DDD came about. [12:28] Why Steve thinks about it in terms of having a bounded context per application that you deploy. [16:33] Historical records of things should always be duplicate data. There should be a snapshot of the data at that time. [17:06] Where should people begin if/when they are new to the book? [17:54] What exactly is clean architecture? [23:01] Steven talks about having one infrastructure project where there are all these dependencies versus multiple. [24:09] Steve names the three main projects. [30:49] Very mature and high-stakes professions have chosen to put constraints on themselves, and with positive effect. How can we take this into architecture and design? &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:  — New video podcast!   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!  programming@palermo.net     &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/steve-smith-domain-driven-design-and-architecture</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 21:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Xamarin apps to .NET MAUI | .NET Conf 2022</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_XT7m5oIKCs</link>
      <description>This session will walk you through the changes you need to make to your libraries and UI when upgrading your Xamarin apps to .NET Multi-platform App UI. We&amp;#39;l...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_XT7m5oIKCs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 19:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s new in the .NET MAUI Community Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/whats-new-in-the-dotnet-maui-community-toolkit/</link>
      <description>Check out what&amp;#39;s new in the latest .NET MAUI Community Toolkit releases.</description>
      <author> (Kym Phillpotts)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/whats-new-in-the-dotnet-maui-community-toolkit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 19:03:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pratyush Mishra</title>
      <link>https://pratyushmishra.com/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pratyushmishra.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 19:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing WITHOUT Mocks or Interfaces!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2oRofOH2NT4</link>
      <description>A common approach people take with testing is mocking. Specifically defining interfaces for dependencies which are then typically mocked so you can test in i...</description>
      <author> (CodeOpinion
  
  
  
    CodeOpinion
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2oRofOH2NT4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 17:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a new JavaScript linting experience in Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/building-a-new-javascript-linting-experience-in-visual-studio/</link>
      <description>Available today in the 17.4 public release, Visual Studio has revamped its ESLint support! The new linting experience includes:&amp;#160; Linting support – for not only JavaScript and TypeScript files, but also for JSX/TSX, Vue and HTML files.&amp;#160; Quick actions and fixes,</description>
      <author> (Maria Solano)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/building-a-new-javascript-linting-experience-in-visual-studio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 17:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not even trying to cross an airtight hatchway: Calling a function in your own process by synthesizing a function pointer</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20221201-46/?p=107528</link>
      <description>You can already attack yourself in far more interesting ways.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20221201-46/?p=107528</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 16:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using .NET’s NativeAOT to fix the biggest serverless issue</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=3QJDJl-zDFM</link>
      <description>Get $50 free AWS Credit by adding &amp;quot;AWS CREDIT #NICK&amp;quot; in the &amp;quot;Tell us about your project&amp;quot; area: https://bit.ly/nickawsGet the source code: https://github.com/...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  




  Verified



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=3QJDJl-zDFM</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 15:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice of Recent Security Incident - The LastPass Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.lastpass.com/2022/11/notice-of-recent-security-incident/</link>
      <description>We are working diligently to understand the scope of the incident and identify what specific information has been accessed.</description>
      <author> (Karim Toubba)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.lastpass.com/2022/11/notice-of-recent-security-incident/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 14:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emacs 29 is nigh! What can we expect?</title>
      <link>https://blog.phundrak.com/emacs-29-what-can-we-expect/</link>
      <description>It was announced a couple of hours ago, Emacs 29’s branch is now cut from the master branch!</description>
      <author> (Lucien Cartier-Tilet)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.phundrak.com/emacs-29-what-can-we-expect/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 14:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Producer-Consumer Applications With .NET Channels Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/dotnet-producer-consumer-channels/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to look at creating producer/consumer applications in .NET by using bounded and unbounded Channels.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/dotnet-producer-consumer-channels/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 11:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>