<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring your apps with Sentry in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://askxammy.com/monitoring-your-apps-with-sentry-in-net-maui/</link>
      <description>Launching our apps is just the first step; maintaining user satisfaction is the ongoing challenge. After releasing our apps in the store, our primary goal is ensuring this satisfaction by delivering a seamless and relevant experience. Yet, we often lack insights into issues some users may encounter. This underscores the necessity for tools that serve as our eyes, tracking pivotal user interactions and events. Why is monitoring vital? It helps in timely identification and even prediction of potential glitches, enabling us to address them before users report. While various tools offer these capabilities, this article will delve into Sentry, a renowned remote crash reporting tool, discussing its features and step-by-step implementation
The explanation will be divided into the following points:
&amp;#128313; What exactly Sentry is?
&amp;#128313; Getting started with Sentry implementation
&amp;#128313; Initiating the App Monitoring
&amp;#128313; Getting Familiar with the Sentry Dashboard

Let &amp;#39;s start!
What exactly Sentry is?
It&amp;#39;s an open-source tool designed to track errors within your applications. Sentry monitors any issues arising in your app, offering detailed insights that help prioritize, identify, and reproduce each problem, ensuring a swift and effective resolution. With this tool you can take action on broken lines of code, crashes, and failed API calls.
Getting started with Sentry implementation
To apply Sentry monitoring to your applications, you must do the following steps:
Step 1⃣: Create your Sentry account
Go to the Sentry site and click on the Get Started button, located at the top right of the page.





You can choose how to register:

Directly with Sentry: You&amp;#39;ll find a form asking for basic personal information to complete your registration. (✍️ I will use this option for this article.)







Via third-party accounts: At the bottom of the form you also have the option to register using your Google, Github, or Azure Devops accounts.

Step 2⃣: Setting up Sentry
After your account is created, a screen will pop up offering you the choice to install Sentry or set up your team. For now, we&amp;#39;ll concentrate on installing Sentry, please press its Start button.





Choosing the Platform to Monitor
In the next step, you must choose the platform you want to monitor. Sentry provides support for a wide variety, categorized by their main functionalities, such as Desktop, Web, Mobile, among others. The detailed list can be seen in the attached animation. To reach this article, you will navigate to the Mobile tab and select .NET Multiplatform App UI (MAUI).








Once you have selected the platform you are going to work with, click the Configure SDK button located at the lower right corner of the page.
Configuring your MAUI SDK
Sentry details every necessary step for its integration into your application: from the necessary Nuget package to initialization and implementation. It even offers a sample application. This information is essential for your setup, so make sure to keep it handy; you will need it in the next steps.








⚠ Save the DSN endpoint that this step shows you; you&amp;#39;ll need it for the Visual Studio implementation.
Step 3⃣: Implementing Sentry in our MAUI App
Open your MAUI project in Visual Studio. For this demonstration, I created one named SentrySample.
&amp;#128295; Initial setup
➖ From the NuGet Package, add the Sentry.Maui package to your project.





➖ Go to your MauiProgram.cs file
In the CreateMauiApp method, find the .UseMauiApp&amp;lt;App&amp;gt;() line. Right below it, add UserSentry(). This function has various useful overloads to explore. However, in this article, we will focus on the one that uses a DSN as a parameter.
What is the DSN?
The DSN (Data Source Name) in Sentry acts as a distinctive identifier for the data source of a specific project. It facilitates the direct linking of events from your application to the corresponding Sentry project. This address instructs Sentry on how to organize and store incoming data. Essentially, it guarantees that error and performance metrics from your application are correctly channeled to the right project within your Sentry account.
Let’s implement it in code
Do you remember the endpoint DSN saved in the previous step? Add it in this method.

Initiating the App Monitoring
With your initial configuration in place, you&amp;#39;re all set to begin monitoring the various events and scenarios in your app.
Where should you start with your monitoring? Here&amp;#39;s my recommendation:
&amp;#128313; Begin with a pre-established document outlining the specific events or scenarios you want to track.
&amp;#128313; Assign unique identifiers for each scenario within this document. It&amp;#39;s essential to use clear and intuitive naming so it&amp;#39;s easily understandable to anyone reviewing it. For instance, if you aim to track when a user logs in via Facebook, a potential identifier might be facebook_login, accompanied by pertinent data like the user&amp;#39;s name and email.
Exploring App Monitoring &amp;#160;available methods
Now that our monitoring scenarios are set up, let&amp;#39;s dive into the various methods provided by the SentrySdk. In this guide, I&amp;#39;ll introduce you to some of the main Sentry methods:
➖ CaptureMessage
While Sentry SDKs don&amp;#39;t auto-capture messages, this method enables manual submission of textual information to Sentry, enhancing monitoring precision.
It receives the following parameters:
&amp;#128313; Message: Is the message to send. - Receives a string as a value - [Mandatory]
&amp;#128313; SentryLevel: Allows you to define the level of severity or importance of the event that is sent to Sentry. It’s important to specify the appropriate level, as it allows us to ensure that messages are prioritized and categorized correctly within the Sentry system. &amp;#160;[Optional]
It’s an Enum that contains the following values:
▪ Debug: Offers insights for debugging purposes, detailing the inner workings or state of the system.
▪ Info: Provides general informational messages that signify normal, non-error events.
▪ Warning: Flags potential problems or unusual occurrences that don&amp;#39;t currently impact functionality but may do so in the future.
▪ Error: Highlights a significant issue, which though not fatal, may impede functionality.
▪ Fatal: Indicates a critical error that might cause the system to terminate.
How can we implement this in code?

➖ CaptureException
Enables you to capture exceptions that arise within your app.
&amp;#128313; Exception: Capturers a exception. - [Mandatory]
&amp;#128313; Configure scope: &amp;#160;It allows you to define a specific context for exceptions that you forward to Sentry. In your report, you can include details such as the severity of the error and assign specific tags, among others. I will provide an example that showcases some essential configurations, and we invite you to further explore its capabilities.

➖ CaptureEvent
Allows you to capture the monitoring of an event. This method accepts data of the SentryEvent type. You can include various essential details for your monitoring, such as the error level, a message, and more. I encourage you to delve deeper into its features.
How can we implement it in code?

We have explored some of the main methods. I invite you to continue delving deeper into others.
⚠ Some of these methods necessitate capturing detailed user information, like their email or name. In such cases, it&amp;#39;s crucial to inform the user about the collection of their data.









Getting Familiar with the Sentry Dashboard
At last, you&amp;#39;ll discover where to view all the data you’ve been monitoring! Let&amp;#39;s start with a straightforward example: capturing a message that we&amp;#39;ll then observe on the Sentry Dashboard.
Creating the example
I&amp;#39;ll demonstrate using the default .NET MAUI application as an example. Head to MainPage.xaml.cs—I&amp;#39;ll be working with the built-in counter code. Further, we&amp;#39;ll incorporate Sentry&amp;#39;s CaptureMessage function, as outlined below:

To get information for Sentry, it’s important that you run the application and click the counter button.

Entering to the dashboard
In your Sentry Dashboard, navigate to Issues. A list of your monitoring records will promptly display. While other examples might appear in this segment, let&amp;#39;s concentrate on the entry we generated earlier—highlighted with pink lines—that reads, You clicked the counter button 1 time.&amp;#160;









Click on the highlighted item. On this page, you can view the record&amp;#39;s comprehensive details, including the name of the originating application, the .NET version in use at the time of the record&amp;#39;s creation, the operating system version, and of course, the message you sent, among others information. There is a wealth of crucial information here that warrants your attention and that will allow you to make decisions in your app. Scroll through to take it all in!
Here&amp;#39;s a glimpse of what it looks like:








&amp;#160;

&amp;#128640; Voil&amp;#224;! You&amp;#39;re now all set to monitor your .NET MAUI applications with Sentry. Keep building awesome apps and enjoy the peace of mind Sentry provides!&amp;#160; &amp;#128214;&amp;#128588;
Spanish post:

https://es.askxammy.com/monitoreando-tus-aplicaciones-con-sentry-en-net-maui

References:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9-50zH8fqYA

Thanks for reading my article! &amp;#128154;&amp;#128149;</description>
      <author> (About Leomaris Reyes)</author>
      <guid>https://askxammy.com/monitoring-your-apps-with-sentry-in-net-maui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 13:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers Should Deploy Their Own Code</title>
      <link>https://matt-rickard.com/developers-should-deploy-their-own-code</link>
      <description>This is the platonic ideal. We&amp;#39;re not there yet, but the all signs point to this rather than specialization.

Applications and their infrastructure (functions, queues, permissions, runtime) have always been closely intertwined. Fewer handoffs mean quicker deployments and less context loss.

So – Why can&amp;#39;t developers deploy their own code (yet)?

 1. Provisioned infrastructure economy1

Competing product teams must be allocated resources at companies with provisioned infrastructure. Finance depar</description>
      <author> (Matt Rickard)</author>
      <guid>https://matt-rickard.com/developers-should-deploy-their-own-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 13:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Register Users with Firebase Auth in .NET #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=tUEJ1SOBa3g</link>
      <description>&amp;#128204; Check out my Pragmatic Clean Architecture course: https://bit.ly/3Zn41BK&amp;#128640; Support me on Patreon to access the source code: https://www.patreon.com/milanj...</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=tUEJ1SOBa3g</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>zksecurity &amp;#183; Luma</title>
      <link>https://lu.ma/zksecurity</link>
      <description>View and subscribe to events from zksecurity on Luma. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lu.ma/zksecurity</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreWCF 1.4.0 Released: RabbitMQ and Apache Kafka Support Added </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/09/corewcf-140-released/</link>
      <description>This month, there have been several significant releases in the CoreWCF ecosystem. Version 1.4.0 was rolled out, featuring new transport options such as RabbitMQ (AMQP) and Apache Kafka. While these additions were well-received, it&amp;#39;s worth noting that the transports MSMQ and NetNamedPipe remain in the preview stage, indicating ongoing development efforts.</description>
      <author> (Almir Vuk)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2023/09/corewcf-140-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 09:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CQRS Validation with MediatR Pipeline and FluentValidation</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/cqrs-validation-with-mediatr-pipeline-and-fluentvalidation</link>
      <description>Validation is an essential cross-cutting concern that you need to solve in your application. You want to ensure the request is valid before you consider processing it.
Another important question you need to answer is how you approach different types of validation. For example, I consider input and business validation differently, and each deserves a specific solution.
I want to show you an elegant solution for validation using MediatR and FluentValidation.
If you aren&amp;#39;t using CQRS with MediatR, don&amp;#39;t worry. Everything I explain about validation can easily be adapted to other paradigms.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/cqrs-validation-with-mediatr-pipeline-and-fluentvalidation</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 01:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 367</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=UlElqHD15mY</link>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ll make this one up as we go &amp;#128522;</description>
      <author> (Northwest Health Services
  
  
  
    Northwest Health Services
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=UlElqHD15mY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 00:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio &amp;#39;Tea &amp;amp; Technology&amp;#39; Video Miniseries Starts Next Week -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/09/29/visual-studio-miniseries.aspx</link>
      <description>The goal of the miniseries is to provide an insider&amp;#39;s snapshot look at some of the people who contribute to shaping the Visual Studio IDE every day.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel09/29/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/09/29/visual-studio-miniseries.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 00:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealFill: Reference-Driven Generation for Authentic Image Completion</title>
      <link>https://realfill.github.io/</link>
      <description>RealFill: Reference-Driven Generation for Authentic Image Completion</description>
      <author> (1Google Research, 2Cornell University)</author>
      <guid>https://realfill.github.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 00:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controls for WinUI and the Uno Platform - Nick&amp;#39;s .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/winui-and-uno-controls/</link>
      <description>I was discussing the features of the Uno Platform today and realised that we sometimes gloss over all the features. In this post we’re going to do a walk through of some of the different controls, styles and themes available to Windows (WinUI/Windows App SDK) and Uno Platform developers. Gallery One of the best ways ... Read more</description>
      <author> (Nick)</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/winui-and-uno-controls/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Include interactive Clojure/script code snippets in a web page with SCI &amp;amp; friends</title>
      <link>https://blog.jakubholy.net/2023/interactive-code-snippets-fulcro/</link>
      <description>I have long dreamt about having interactive code snippets of Fulcro in my teaching materials. Showing people code they could modify and see it render right next to it. Fulcro is a ClojureScript library, but it uses some heavy macros - and those typically require JVM Clojure. Well, not anymore. I was able to rewrite them into Borkdude’s Small Clojure Interpreter (SCI) dialect of Clojure. I.e. I can ask SCI to evaluate a piece of code with these macros, which SCI will macro-expand into more cljs, and execute. With SCI, my Fulcro sci.configs, CodeMirror, and Nextjournal’s clojure-mode, I can have a beautiful in-page editor with code evaluation. And I will show you how to do the same, for your blog.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jakubholy.net/2023/interactive-code-snippets-fulcro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Impressions with the Raspberry Pi 5</title>
      <link>https://blog.alexellis.io/first-impressions-with-the-raspberry-pi-5/</link>
      <description>For someone who runs the Raspberry Pi as a server, build agent and for Kubernetes, how does the new version  stack up? And should you upgrade?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.alexellis.io/first-impressions-with-the-raspberry-pi-5/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can&amp;#39;t Control Your Data in the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://karl-voit.at/cloud/</link>
      <description>There is this well cited argument that cloud companies like Google, Apple, Amazon, Facebook, and you-name-it are able to protect your personal data much better than you are able to. They have military grade security restrictions, better backup methods, and are able to do this much cheaper.</description>
      <author> (Karl Voit)</author>
      <guid>https://karl-voit.at/cloud/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts Live 2023 - My Recap</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/experts-live-2023-my-recap-4ack</link>
      <description>I’m excited to share with you my experience at Experts Live Europe 2023, a premier conference for IT...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/experts-live-2023-my-recap-4ack</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Death of the Author • Matt Neary</title>
      <link>http://blog.mattneary.com/the-death-of-the-author</link>
      <description>As everybody knows, Nietzsche announced long ago that “God is dead.” Or more accurately, he wrote the parable of the madman, who was the first to realize that God was dead. As Nietzsche’s madman tried to spread his message, he was thrown out of... | Matt Neary | Svbtle</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://blog.mattneary.com/the-death-of-the-author</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Database Transactions</title>
      <link>https://dineshgowda.com/posts/demystifying-database-transcations/</link>
      <description>The most compelling feature of relational database systems is ACID(Atomicity Consistency Isolation Durability). Isolation is achieved using transactions. Isolation is needed to avoid race conditions when concurrent actors act upon the same row.
SQL standard defines isolation with different levels. Every isolation level offers certain guarantees and possible anomalies that can occur.</description>
      <author> (dinesh gowda)</author>
      <guid>https://dineshgowda.com/posts/demystifying-database-transcations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the Birthday Paradox Teaches Us About Protecting Patron Privacy</title>
      <link>https://chimpy.me/blog/posts/what-the-birthday-paradox-teaches-us-about-protecting-patron-privacy/</link>
      <description>Background</description>
      <author> (Ray Voelker)</author>
      <guid>https://chimpy.me/blog/posts/what-the-birthday-paradox-teaches-us-about-protecting-patron-privacy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>is: an inspector for your environment</title>
      <link>https://www.olafalders.com/2023/09/28/is-an-inspector-for-your-environment/</link>
      <description>Can we make working at the command line a little less cumbersome?</description>
      <author> (oalders)</author>
      <guid>https://www.olafalders.com/2023/09/28/is-an-inspector-for-your-environment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand How It Works</title>
      <link>https://martinrue.com/understand-how-it-works/</link>
      <description>One of the best pieces of advice I ever got was from my grandfather. He would often share some lesson he’d learnt that he thought was useful to me.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martinrue.com/understand-how-it-works/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>https://sjer.red/blog/writing/</link>
      <description>If you can&amp;#39;t write then you can&amp;#39;t think.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sjer.red/blog/writing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factorial Numbers</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2835/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2835/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO recommends dropping component of many flu vaccines</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2023/09/29/who-recommends-dropping-component-of-many-flu-vaccines/</link>
      <description>The WHO has recommended dropping a component of many flu vaccines because the viruses it protects against appear to have been driven into extinction in the Covid pandemic.</description>
      <author> (Helen Branswell)</author>
      <guid>https://www.statnews.com/2023/09/29/who-recommends-dropping-component-of-many-flu-vaccines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 21:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET | Using MongoDb in under 20 minutes.</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=w6htel3T6KY</link>
      <description>Feel free to support me on Patreon:- https://www.patreon.com/OleinicVasiliiDetailed design newsletter:- https://voleinic.substack.comIn this video we will co...</description>
      <author> (Website Learners
  
  
  
    Website Learners
  




  Verified



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=w6htel3T6KY</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 21:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solution: Full Stack Development Challenge in C#</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XuugKbEiFDg</link>
      <description>On Tuesday, I issued a challenge to build an API, a desktop UI, and a web UI for an employee directory using C#. Hopefully, by this time you have been able t...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XuugKbEiFDg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 21:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draggable objects</title>
      <link>https://www.redblobgames.com/making-of/draggable/</link>
      <description>Many of my interactive pages have a draggable object. I want the reader to move the object around, and I want the diagram to respond in some way. Here I’ll document the code I use to make this work with both mouse and touch input, using browser features that are widely supported since 2020. Here’s a common case I want to support:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.redblobgames.com/making-of/draggable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 20:03:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy washing: Google claims to support privacy while lobbying against it | Proton</title>
      <link>https://proton.me/blog/google-lobbying</link>
      <description>Just as Big Oil has used greenwashing to block environmental protections, Big Tech uses privacy washing to stand in the way of privacy.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://proton.me/blog/google-lobbying</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 19:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirbstr (@kirbstr@techhub.social)</title>
      <link>https://techhub.social/@kirbstr/111148950526108155</link>
      <description>Attached: 3 images

Went to FB to share the eff opt-out link on my biz page (the one referenced in @pluralistic@mamot.fr latest thread) and now I have restrictions?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://techhub.social/@kirbstr/111148950526108155</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 19:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>09-  We Speak: IBM 3270</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=KMXw-Cqey2I%3Fsi%3DWRomZ9joJXy9P_JH</link>
      <description>In this session, we continue with the &amp;quot;We Speak&amp;quot;, Mission Critical Series with an episode on how Azure Logic Apps can unlock scenarios where is required to i...</description>
      <author> (John Savill&amp;#39;s Technical Training
  
  
  
    John Savill&amp;#39;s Technical Training
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=KMXw-Cqey2I%3Fsi%3DWRomZ9joJXy9P_JH</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EP 28: Response Compression in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/net-newsletter-by-waseem/ep-28-response-compression-in-asp-net-core-55e595b38859</link>
      <description>In today’s newsletter we are going to discuss:</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@mwaseemzakir)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/net-newsletter-by-waseem/ep-28-response-compression-in-asp-net-core-55e595b38859</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Template meta-programming: Avoiding saying a type before it is complete - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230929-00/?p=108839</link>
      <description>Deferring use until after the class is defined.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230929-00/?p=108839</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>