<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Motivation in Software Engineering - Dev Leader Weekly 98</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/06/14/uncovering-motivation-in-software-engineering-dev-leader-weekly-98</link>
      <description>Welcome to another issue of Dev Leader Weekly! In this issue, I discuss how to breakdown what keeps you engaged as a software engineer.
</description>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2025/06/14/uncovering-motivation-in-software-engineering-dev-leader-weekly-98</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dnsimg - storing images in txt records</title>
      <link>https://asherfalcon.com/blog/posts/2</link>
      <description>I was intrigued by the idea of storing images in DNS records, and I wanted to test out how effectively images could be stored in DNS records. I've always been interested in TXT records because they seem to be a useful way of storing arbitrary data, and in this blog post I'll discuss how I went from an idea to developing the project into almost a protocol sort of method for storing an image on a domain name.</description>
      <guid>https://asherfalcon.com/blog/posts/2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HR is not your friend</title>
      <link>https://www.miserablyemployed.com/blogs/rants/hr-is-not-your-friend</link>
      <description>This is a public service announcement from your friends at Miserably Employed.  Early in most people’s careers, you’re first exposed to Human Resources when you’re hired. They interview you, onboard you, and get things rolling. You think they are nice, but the truth is that they are paid to pretend to be nice. HR acts </description>
      <guid>https://www.miserablyemployed.com/blogs/rants/hr-is-not-your-friend</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing FIX Data With ClickHouse | BenjaminWootton.com</title>
      <link>https://benjaminwootton.com/insights/analysing-fix-data-with-clickhouse/</link>
      <description>Using ClickHouse String and Array Processing functions to analyse FIX Protocol data.</description>
      <guid>https://benjaminwootton.com/insights/analysing-fix-data-with-clickhouse/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Model Write the Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.dbreunig.com/2025/06/10/let-the-model-write-the-prompt.html</link>
      <description>Notes from a talk I delivered at the 2025 Data + AI Summit, detailing the problem with prompts in your code and how DSPy can make everything better.</description>
      <guid>https://www.dbreunig.com/2025/06/10/let-the-model-write-the-prompt.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing for Longevity</title>
      <link>https://ente.io/blog/longevity/</link>
      <description>How a company like Ente optimizes for longevity</description>
      <guid>https://ente.io/blog/longevity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsing, Not Guessing | Francis Sunday</title>
      <link>https://codehakase.com/shorts/parsing-not-guessing/</link>
      <description>Using ASTs over regex to build a predictable, lightweight, theme-aware Markdown renderer in Go.</description>
      <guid>https://codehakase.com/shorts/parsing-not-guessing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I fight bots in my free time</title>
      <link>https://xeiaso.net/talks/2025/bsdcan-anubis/</link>
      <description>I made Anubis, a lightweight, open-source Web Application Firewall designed to block automated bot attacks without frustrating real users. Anubis uses techniques like TLS fingerprinting and JavaScript proof of work to keep your site safe while staying flexible, fast, and easy to deploy.
</description>
      <guid>https://xeiaso.net/talks/2025/bsdcan-anubis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding .md URLs for Raw Markdown Content in Next.js</title>
      <link>https://www.bengubler.com/posts/2025-06-14-raw-markdown-urls-nextjs</link>
      <description>How to add .md URLs to your Next.js blog to serve raw markdown content, inspired by Vercel's docs.</description>
      <author> (Ben Gubler)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bengubler.com/posts/2025-06-14-raw-markdown-urls-nextjs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things that influence my mental state -Louis-André Labadie</title>
      <link>https://louis-andre.net/journal/what-influences-my-mental-state</link>
      <description>I've been thinking lately about what actually keeps me balanced, as opposed to activities that I think should. I don't want to fall into prescriptive thinking about wellness - meditation is good, exercise is good, social connection is good - without paying attention to what specifically works for a given temperament.</description>
      <guid>https://louis-andre.net/journal/what-influences-my-mental-state</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Live In a Golden Age of Interoperability</title>
      <link>https://borretti.me/article/we-live-in-a-golden-age-of-interoperability</link>
      <description>On the growth of open standards.</description>
      <guid>https://borretti.me/article/we-live-in-a-golden-age-of-interoperability</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your idea probably sucks</title>
      <link>https://kyrylo.org/software/2025/06/15/your-idea-probably-sucks.html</link>
      <description>If you think you have a brilliant idea, I have bad news: your idea probably sucks.</description>
      <guid>https://kyrylo.org/software/2025/06/15/your-idea-probably-sucks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 23:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven replies to the viral Apple reasoning paper – and why they fall short</title>
      <link>https://garymarcus.substack.com/p/seven-replies-to-the-viral-apple</link>
      <description>Also: another paper that seals the deal</description>
      <guid>https://garymarcus.substack.com/p/seven-replies-to-the-viral-apple</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On technique: what is it and how do you get it? - Robert Howard - Brisbane Woodworker - Classes in Woodworking and Woodcarving</title>
      <link>https://roberthoward.com.au/on-technique-what-is-it-and-how-do-you-get-it/</link>
      <description>I have spent a good part of the past five years* teaching woodwork. As most teachers probably find, I have learnt as much as my students have. In fact, I am moved to say that if you seriously wish to learn, for example, how to cut a better dovetail, the most efficient way to improve yourself is to attempt to teach someone else how to do it. The great thing about teaching is that you are quickly forced to confront a lot of things that you otherwise might easily ignore, avoid or simply be unaware of.</description>
      <guid>https://roberthoward.com.au/on-technique-what-is-it-and-how-do-you-get-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG Anti-Patterns with Skylar Payne - Jason Liu</title>
      <link>https://jxnl.co/writing/2025/06/11/rag-anti-patterns-with-skylar-payne/</link>
      <description>AI Consulting, RAG, and other personal notes.</description>
      <guid>https://jxnl.co/writing/2025/06/11/rag-anti-patterns-with-skylar-payne/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs Your Agile Process Sucks</title>
      <link>https://www.miserablyemployed.com/blogs/rants/7-signs-your-agile-process-sucks</link>
      <description>Congratulations. You’ve adopted Agile. You have daily standups. You’ve plastered Jira with enough tickets to wallpaper your overpriced open office. You’re doing the thing. But here’s the truth: you’re not Agile. You’re not even mildly flexible. You’re just tired—trapped in a Kafkaesque backlog spiral while pretending t</description>
      <guid>https://www.miserablyemployed.com/blogs/rants/7-signs-your-agile-process-sucks</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A2A Is For UI</title>
      <link>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2025/06/14/a2a</link>
      <description>Sat June 14, 2025</description>
      <guid>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2025/06/14/a2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gap Through Which We Praise the Machine</title>
      <link>https://ferd.ca/the-gap-through-which-we-praise-the-machine.html</link>
      <description>My current theory of agentic programming: people are amazing at adapting the tools they're given and totally underestimate the extent to which they do it, and the amount of skill we build doing that is an incidental consequence of how badly the tools are designed.</description>
      <guid>https://ferd.ca/the-gap-through-which-we-praise-the-machine.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust and Procedural Fetishism</title>
      <link>https://ben-mini.com/2025/trust-and-procedural-fetishism</link>
      <description>I recently finished reading Abundance by Ezra Klein and Derek Thompson. The book explains the various missteps taken by the U.S. government that led us to where we are today: a bureaucratic sludge of policies and regulations that’s caused ambitious projects to go over budget (e.g., Healthcare.gov) or remain unfinished (e.g., California High-Speed Rail). Klein and Thompson propose a renaissance of our public institutions- an invigorated era where government “gets out of the way” of itself and executes on projects only it can do.</description>
      <author> (Ben Wallace)</author>
      <guid>https://ben-mini.com/2025/trust-and-procedural-fetishism</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs, Vibe-Coding, and Where I Draw the Line - ordep.dev</title>
      <link>https://ordep.dev/posts/llms</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://ordep.dev/posts/llms</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Analyzed 16,384 Bundle Combinations (And You Should Too) | blog | puruvj.dev</title>
      <link>https://www.puruvj.dev/blog/neodrag-16k-bundle-combos</link>
      <description>How building a modular drag-and-drop library led me to analyze every possible plugin combination and achieve radical bundle size transparency for developers.</description>
      <guid>https://www.puruvj.dev/blog/neodrag-16k-bundle-combos</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One more reason to choose Postgres over MySQL</title>
      <link>https://tanin.nanakorn.com/one-more-reason-to-use-postgres-vs-mysql/</link>
      <description>Almost always, I'd choose Postgres over any database for a new project because it's flexible and support multi-variances of scenarios that may require different performance characteristics.

However, I don't generally feel strongly about MySQL vs. Postgres. Either seems fine.... until I've learned MySQL doesn't support Transactional DDL. Transactional DDL means</description>
      <guid>https://tanin.nanakorn.com/one-more-reason-to-use-postgres-vs-mysql/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Deploy Schema Changes to a Million Databases</title>
      <link>https://turso.tech/blog/how-to-deploy-schema-changes-to-a-million-databases</link>
      <description>Your SaaS application just hit a major milestone. 100,000 active users, each with their own isolated database. You're celebrating until you realise you need to deploy a schema change. What used to be a simple ALTER TABLE now means coordinating migrations across 100,000 separate databases. And if you're building the next big thing, that number could be heading toward millions.</description>
      <guid>https://turso.tech/blog/how-to-deploy-schema-changes-to-a-million-databases</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fujifilm X half: Is it the perfect family camera ?</title>
      <link>https://arslan.io/2025/06/14/fujifilm-x-half-is-it-the-perfect-family-camera/</link>
      <description>When Fujifilm announced the Fujifilm X half, the internet was literally divided into two halves. Some people were disappointed that it offered limited features for its high price, while others were delighted and found it intriguing. In fact, some even predicted that the X half would sell out quickly. 

As</description>
      <guid>https://arslan.io/2025/06/14/fujifilm-x-half-is-it-the-perfect-family-camera/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>