<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Cloud Advocate (Available Globally) in London, London, United Kingdom | Engineering at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/785636/Senior-Cloud-Advocate-Available-Globally</link>
      <description>Apply for Senior Cloud Advocate (Available Globally) job with Microsoft in London, London, United Kingdom. Engineering at Microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/785636/Senior-Cloud-Advocate-Available-Globally</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 09:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Human Genome Is Full of Viruses</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/medical-myths-and-models/the-human-genome-is-full-of-viruses-c18ba52ac195</link>
      <description>Your body requires viruses, but viruses don’t always require a body</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@bencallif)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/medical-myths-and-models/the-human-genome-is-full-of-viruses-c18ba52ac195</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 08:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Story of the PS2’s Backwards Compatibility From the Engineer Who Built It</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@freelansations/the-story-of-the-ps2s-backwards-compatibility-from-the-engineer-who-built-it-ec39cf5a0353</link>
      <description>As the PS2 turns 20 in Japan, a look back on its PS1 backwards compatibility from the eyes of the former Sony engineer responsible for it.</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@freelansations)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@freelansations/the-story-of-the-ps2s-backwards-compatibility-from-the-engineer-who-built-it-ec39cf5a0353</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 05:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northern Italy quarantines 16 million people</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-middle-east-51787238</link>
      <description>Milan and Venice are among the cities in the lock-down zone as Italy tries to contain the coronavirus.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/bbcnews)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-middle-east-51787238</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 05:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We have to talk about this Python, Gunicorn, Gevent thing</title>
      <link>https://rachelbythebay.com/w/2020/03/07/costly/</link>
      <description>Even if you're in a terrible situation, you should probably try to learn 
from it.  You never know if your purpose in life is to actually serve as 
a warning to others as that "Demotivational" poster puts it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rachelbythebay.com/w/2020/03/07/costly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primes Demo - Making an 8 Bit pipelined CPU</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YxScH_ZQAZA</link>
      <description>I've hit a big milestone in my CPU Build, the core of the processor is complete. There will be a few refinements as I convert more of it over to PCB's but the underlying functionality of the processor is done. 

As a demonstration and test I've implemented the "Sieve of Eratosthenes" it's an efficient prime number finding algorithm. I have two modifications from the simple form of the algorithm, even numbers are skipped entirely and the Sieve is segmented into blocks of 256 values. This prevents large delays between the early smaller primes as it fills in a larger table. 

Read more about the Sieve here: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sieve_of_Eratosthenes
Or Eratosthenes himself here: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eratosthenes

The "instructions per cycle" I give in the video is approximate, I'll build some hardware for measuring it more precisely in the future but it's inline with expectations. There is a larger table of processors for comparison here: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Instructions_per_second

That bit where I say "the last few evenings" may have been a gross understatement.</description>
      <author> (James Sharman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YxScH_ZQAZA</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 02:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders, Biden Can Expect Near-Equal Gain From Warren’s Exit</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2020/03/05/sanders-biden-can-expect-near-equal-gain-from-warrens-exit/</link>
      <description>Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) is reportedly set to drop out of the Democratic race for president, and her exit, on the heels of a poor showing in Super Tuesday contests, is expected to give an almost equal boost to Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) and former Vice President Joe Biden, according to recent Morning Consult polling tracking the race.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/MissouriEli)</author>
      <guid>https://morningconsult.com/2020/03/05/sanders-biden-can-expect-near-equal-gain-from-warrens-exit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 02:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wang Xiuying · The Word from Wuhan · LRB 22 February 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.lrb.co.uk/the-paper/v42/n05/wang-xiuying/the-word-from-wuhan</link>
      <description>People on the left call for a united front against the virus. Liberals are determined to hold the government to account...</description>
      <author> (Wang Xiuying)</author>
      <guid>https://www.lrb.co.uk/the-paper/v42/n05/wang-xiuying/the-word-from-wuhan</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 01:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>draft-ietf-mls-protocol-09</title>
      <link>https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/draft-ietf-mls-protocol-09</link>
      <description>The Messaging Layer Security (MLS) Protocol (Internet-Draft, 2020)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/draft-ietf-mls-protocol-09</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 01:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://wwwext.amgen.com/community-guidelines/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wwwext.amgen.com/community-guidelines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not a 'math person'? You may be better at learning to code than you think</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2020-03-math-person-code.html</link>
      <description>Want to learn to code? Put down the math book. Practice those communication skills instead.</description>
      <author> (by                                         University of Washington)</author>
      <guid>https://phys.org/news/2020-03-math-person-code.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 21:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firecracker</title>
      <link>https://firecracker-microvm.github.io/</link>
      <description>Until now, you needed to choose between containers with fast startup times and high density, or VMs with strong hardware-virtualization-based security and workload isolation. With Firecracker, you no longer have to choose. Firecracker enables you to deploy workloads in lightweight virtual machines, called microVMs, which provide enhanced security and workload isolation over traditional VMs, while enabling the speed and resource efficiency of containers. Firecracker was developed at Amazon Web Services to improve the customer experience of services like AWS Lambda and AWS Fargate.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://firecracker-microvm.github.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 20:32:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsafe.As Method (System.Runtime.CompilerServices)</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/api/system.runtime.compilerservices.unsafe.as?view=netcore-3.1</link>
      <description>&lt;p sourcefile="api/System.Runtime.CompilerServices.Unsafe.As.yml" sourcestartlinenumber="1" jsonPath="/members/0/summary"&gt;Casts the given object to the specified type.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <author> (dotnet-bot)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/api/system.runtime.compilerservices.unsafe.as?view=netcore-3.1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 20:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering digital transformation with .NET, ML and Azure</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SriyUJEpMAU</link>
      <description>Data entry automation is a huge space and has tremendous impact to many countries around the world. Raul Roa is a software engineer in the Dominican Republic who is using .NET Core and Azure to help drive the digital transformation for his country and many others around the world.

In this episode, we chat with Raul at the Caribbean Developers Conference to learn how he’s using technology to improve the lives of the people in this country 


[01:07] - What tools are being used?
[03:34] - How did they move from mono to .NET Core?
[05:30] - What impact has their work had?
[10:51] - Benefits of the cloud for the Caribbean

TagShelf
https://tagshelf.com/

Get started with .NET
https://dotnet.microsoft.com/learn?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli

ML .NET
https://dotnet.microsoft.com/apps/machinelearning-ai/ml-dotnet?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli

Machine Learning in Azure
https://docs.microsoft.com/azure/machine-learning/overview-what-is-azure-ml?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli

#azure #dotnet #machinelearning #CaribbeanDevelopers</description>
      <author> (dotNET)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SriyUJEpMAU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 19:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power up your browser with History Search</title>
      <link>https://historysearch.com/</link>
      <description>Quickly find any webpage youʼve been before using keywords</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://historysearch.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 18:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I have seen things</title>
      <link>https://muratbuffalo.blogspot.com/2020/03/i-have-seen-things.html</link>
      <description>   I still don't have any idea what Instagram or Facebook stories is. Tried Googling and still don't have a good idea about it.  — Murat Dem...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://muratbuffalo.blogspot.com/2020/03/i-have-seen-things.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 15:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What a Googol-to-One Gear Ratio Looks Like</title>
      <link>https://www.kottke.org/20/03/heres-what-a-googol-to-one-gear-ratio-looks-like</link>
      <description>To celebrate being alive for a billion seconds, Daniel Bruin built a machine with 100 gears with a 10-to-1 gear ratio...meaning th</description>
      <author> (posted by Jason Kottke   Mar 05, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://www.kottke.org/20/03/heres-what-a-googol-to-one-gear-ratio-looks-like</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 15:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft's Miguel de Icaza Ponders New Use for WebAssembly -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/03/06/de-icaza-webassembly.aspx</link>
      <description>Miguel de Icaza doesn't post to his personal blog often, but when he does, developers listen. </description>
      <author> (By David Ramel03/06/2020)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/03/06/de-icaza-webassembly.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 15:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Clearance Jobs - ClearanceJobs</title>
      <link>https://www.clearancejobs.com/</link>
      <description>Find defense and intelligence jobs requiring federal government security clearance and connect with recruiters on the largest security-cleared career network.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.clearancejobs.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dev Your Life</title>
      <link>https://devyourlife.com/</link>
      <description>Visit the post for more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devyourlife.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live Share Spaces - Visual Studio Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=vsls-contrib.spaces</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=vsls-contrib.spaces</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in PowerShell 7 – Check it out!</title>
      <link>https://www.thomasmaurer.ch/2020/03/whats-new-in-powershell-7-check-it-out/</link>
      <description>As you know, the PowerShell team just released the new PowerShell version called PowerShell 7. PowerShell 7 will brings a couple of new features and enhancements not only for users who used PowerShell Core 6 but also for people who are currently using Windows PowerShell 5.0. I want to quickly give you an overview of</description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://www.thomasmaurer.ch/2020/03/whats-new-in-powershell-7-check-it-out/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll Two Ways on Windows: Installing &amp; building Jekyll / GitHub Pages blogs with Ruby on Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://seankilleen.com/2020/03/installing-building-jekyll-github-pages-blogs-with-ruby-on-windows/</link>
      <description>I wanted to write up these steps as I took the time to get my blog up and running on my new laptop, in case it helps someone else get started.  Today, we’ll explore two ways of doing this – the Windows way for those of you who like working via Windows, and the WSL way. I like having both set up so that I can use whatever suits me.  The Windows Way  Before we Begin: Pitfalls we’ll be avoiding          FYI: Normally, I’d run choco install ruby -y, which would install ruby v2.7.0.1 at the time of this writing. However, that led to a pitfall later in the process where I’d see that nokogiri is not currently supported on Ruby 2.7, so I need to pin the 2.6.x package, which we’ll do during this tutorial for this reason.           Ruby DevKit used to be a thing for windows. Now ridk uses msys2, so we’ll be installing that during this step as well.      Step 1: Install the Packages          Open PowerShell as an admin (this is important for chocolately packages)      We’ll need msys, so I run choco install msys2 -y   I need to find the 2.6.x version of ruby that will work, so I go to the Chocolatey page for the Ruby package   I expand the “Version History” section and see the current 2.6 version is 2.6.5.1   So, I run choco install ruby --version=2.6.5.1 -y   I then pin the package so it won’t accidentally be upgraded later. To do this, I run choco pin add -n=ruby.   Step 2: Getting the Ruby DevKit installed     I close and re-open PowerShell as a non-admin (to let the paths update, and maybe because I’m just a little superstitious at this point).   I run ridk version to make sure that the prompt shows up and the version numbers look correct   I run ridk install. At the prompt, I hit enter to let it do its thing.   It installs. At the end, I see the phrase there is nothing to do so I hit enter at the prompt and allow it to exit.   I run ridk enable to enable it.   Step 3: Getting the Bundler Installer Configured     I re-open the PowerShell window (superstition, remember?)   I run bundler --version and see that it’s 1.17.x out of the box.   I run gem install bundler to upgrade it to version 2.x   Step 4: Installing the packages     I go to the source directory that has my Gemfile.   I delete the gemfile.lock file, as I’d like to ensure the packages are being recreated as bundler sees fit.   I run bundle install   I wait. For a while. Because I have native dependencies in some of these gems, some code literally needs to get compiled while I wait. I sip some coffee.   Step 5: Running the site     I run bundle exec jekyll serve to compile and serve the site   The WSL (Windows Subsystem for Linux) Way  These steps assume I’ll still be committing &amp; pushing code via my Windows install, so they leave out setting up git on Ubuntu. (Happy to discuss how to do that in the comments; just ping me if you get stuck.)     Enable WSL. If you haven’t already open PowerShell as an admin an run Enable-WindowsOptionalFeature -Online -FeatureName Microsoft-Windows-Subsystem-Linux. You’ll need to restart after.   Go to the windows store and install a Linux distro of choice. I chose Ubuntu 18.04 LTS.   Open your WSL instance once it’s installed and set a password when you’re prompted to do so. (Pssst – do you have the new Windows Terminal? You can open a prompt right from that. It’s nifty.)   Run sudo apt-get update to update your packages   Run sudo apt-get install ruby-full build-essential to install Ruby   Run sudo gem install bundler to install bundler   Head to your current source code’s directory (mine is in C:\SeanK\Repositories\seankilleen.github.io, so I used cd /mnt/c/Users/SeanK/Repositories/seankilleen.github.io   You’ll have to install some other dependencies (at least on Ubuntu) – sudo apt-get install --reinstall zlibc zlib1g zlib1g-dev   Run bundle install. You’ll be prompted for your password during. Allow it time to finish.   Run bundle exec jekyll serve.   And there you have it! Jekyll two ways on Windows. :)  Happy publishing! </description>
      <author> (Sean Killeen)</author>
      <guid>https://seankilleen.com/2020/03/installing-building-jekyll-github-pages-blogs-with-ruby-on-windows/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just a Dash</title>
      <link>https://symonefowler.com/</link>
      <description>I know it’s been a while, but kids! I didn’t think a Facebook post was appropriate for this as I really wanted to keep this around as a reminder for anyone who reads it and for myself. I’m not looking for a discussion on what you think is right or wrong, that’s for you to keep on your internet space.</description>
      <author> (by SymoneF)</author>
      <guid>https://symonefowler.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keybase</title>
      <link>https://keybase.io/</link>
      <description>Keybase is for keeping everyone's chats and files safe, from families to communities to companies. MacOS, Windows, Linux, iPhone, and Android.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://keybase.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thought Download</title>
      <link>https://devyourlife.com/thought-download</link>
      <description>Of course we know our own thoughts and opinions, right? You’d be surprised how much energy we spend on unintentional thoughts. There’s a simple solution: do a thought download. Thought loops happen when we fixate on some part of a thought. We end up with the illusion that we’re thinking about it and therefore maybe […]</description>
      <author> (By Layla Sells)</author>
      <guid>https://devyourlife.com/thought-download</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Gratitudes</title>
      <link>https://devyourlife.com/public-gratitudes</link>
      <description>Close to a decade ago I decided to take on the 30 days of Gratitude challenge. I wanted a place to track my 3 daily gratitudes (yes, I made up the pluralization) that back in 2012 would be easy to get to. At the time I didn’t use Facebook and decided that would be a […]</description>
      <author> (By Layla Sells)</author>
      <guid>https://devyourlife.com/public-gratitudes</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeanKilleen.com</title>
      <link>https://seankilleen.com/</link>
      <description>Ramblings on bytes and life from a digital thirty-something. </description>
      <author> (Sean Killeen)</author>
      <guid>https://seankilleen.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abhishek Gupta – Medium</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@abhishek1987</link>
      <description>Read writing from Abhishek Gupta on Medium. Cloud Advocate at Microsoft working on Open source, Kubernetes, Azure. Mostly using Go and Java. Every day, Abhishek Gupta and thousands of other voices read, write, and share important stories on Medium.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@abhishek1987</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miguel de Icaza</title>
      <link>https://tirania.org/blog/</link>
      <description>Miguel de Icaza's Blog</description>
      <author> (@COPYRIGHT@)</author>
      <guid>https://tirania.org/blog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Different Disciplines in Your Career with Stephen Toub</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Careers-Behind-the-Code/Careers-Behind-the-Code-With-Stephen-Toub</link>
      <description>This month's episode features Stephen Toub, a Partner Architect on the .NET team focused on performance and building great libraries.   The libraries that Stephen stewards are at the base of your .NET</description>
      <author> (by Steve Carroll (msft))</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Careers-Behind-the-Code/Careers-Behind-the-Code-With-Stephen-Toub</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Maurer MVP</title>
      <link>https://www.thomasmaurer.ch/</link>
      <description>Blog of Thomas Maurer - Microsoft MVP - Focusing on Cloud Computing and Datacenter, especially Microsoft Azure, Windows Server, Container, Windows10, PowerShell and more.</description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://www.thomasmaurer.ch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>