<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Why is Windows using only even-numbered processors? - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230620-00/?p=108358</link>
      <description>Spreading out the load over cores.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230620-00/?p=108358</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure App Configuration and .NET API: a smart and secure way to manage configurations</title>
      <link>https://www.code4it.dev/blog/azure-app-configuration-dotnet-api/</link>
      <description>Centralizing configurations can be useful for several reasons: security, consistency, deployability. In this article, we’re gonna use Azure App Configuration to centralize the configurations used in a .NET API application.</description>
      <author> (Davide Bellone)</author>
      <guid>https://www.code4it.dev/blog/azure-app-configuration-dotnet-api/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsing websites in C# with Html Agility Pack or AngleSharp</title>
      <link>https://blog.elmah.io/parsing-websites-in-c-with-html-agility-pack-or-anglesharp/</link>
      <description>Learn how to parse a website from .NET/C# using the two most popular NuGet packages for the job: Html Agility Pack and AngleSharp.</description>
      <author> (Written by Thomas Ardal, June 20, 2023)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.elmah.io/parsing-websites-in-c-with-html-agility-pack-or-anglesharp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring .NET streaming API scenarios</title>
      <link>https://davidpine.net/blog/dotnet-async-enumerable</link>
      <description>Use the IAsyncEnumerable&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; interface to stream data from a server to a client.</description>
      <author> (David Pine)</author>
      <guid>https://davidpine.net/blog/dotnet-async-enumerable</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Assistant Yellow</title>
      <link>https://www.home-assistant.io/yellow/</link>
      <description>The easiest way to run Home Assistant. Now available for pre-order.</description>
      <author> (Home Assistant)</author>
      <guid>https://www.home-assistant.io/yellow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Bulk Updates in Entity Framework Core - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/efcore-bulk-updates/</link>
      <description>Discover how to perform bulk updates in Entity Framework Core. Explore the new ExecuteUpdate and ExecuteDelete methods.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/efcore-bulk-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A History of JavaScript Modules and Bundling, For the Post-ES6 Developer | 8th Light</title>
      <link>https://8thlight.com/insights/a-history-of-javascript-modules-and-bundling-for-the-post-es6-developer</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Devlin Glasman)</author>
      <guid>https://8thlight.com/insights/a-history-of-javascript-modules-and-bundling-for-the-post-es6-developer</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 06:06:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# Source Code Generators - Bruno Sonnino</title>
      <link>https://blog.revolution.com.br/2023/06/11/c-source-code-generators/</link>
      <description>C# 9 introduced a new feature that allows you to inspect user code as it is being compiled and generate new C# source files that are added to the compilation. This enables you to write code that runs during compilation and produces additional source code based on the analysis of your program. In this blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.revolution.com.br/2023/06/11/c-source-code-generators/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 06:06:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL Code Generator–Avoid generating types that are not needed</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/06/graphql-code-generatoravoid-generating.html</link>
      <description>If you are using GraphQL in your frontend(or even backend) applications I hope you are not creating all the types yourself. Thanks to the bu...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/06/graphql-code-generatoravoid-generating.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 06:06:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When is an implementation detail an implementation detail?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2023/06/19/when-is-an-implementation-detail-an-implementation-detail/</link>
      <description>On the tension between encapsulation and testability.</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2023/06/19/when-is-an-implementation-detail-an-implementation-detail/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 06:06:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Create a Microsoft Power App for your ASP.NET Core Web API</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/saVqRI7QjoY</link>
      <description>Learn how to quickly build a front-end for your .net web APIs (using Power Platform) with Julia Kasper and Marcel Ferreira.Featuring: Julia Kasper, Marcel Fe...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/saVqRI7QjoY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 02:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving Files with .NET MAUI Community Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://askxammy.com/saving-files-with-net-maui-community-toolkit/</link>
      <description>Knowing how to save files in our applications is very important, however, the perception has been that implementation can be tedious. Thanks to the .NET MAUI Community Toolkit using FileSaver, you can now save files much faster. In this article I will show you all the necessary elements to achieve it.

&amp;#128295;&amp;#160;First of all... What do I need to know?
What is .NET MAUI Community Toolkit??

It’s a collection of reusable elements such as animations, behaviors &amp;#160;converters, among others, for developing applications for iOS, Android, macOS and WinUI using MAUI.

✍️ Important!&amp;#160;Adding this configuration to your project just once is enough to fully benefit from the Community Toolkit. If you&amp;#39;ve already implemented it using another NuGet feature, feel free to skip this step.

&amp;#160;

[expand title=&amp;#128295; Still haven&amp;#39;t implemented it? Check it here!
]

Add from NuGet Package: Community.Toolkit.Maui



Now let’s initialize:&amp;#160;Go to your MauiProgram.cs file

In the CreateMauiApp method, place in the .UseMauiApp&amp;lt;App&amp;gt;()&amp;#160;line and just below it add the following line of code:

⚠ Don’t forget to add the using CommunityToolkit.Maui;at the top of the class.
[/expand]

Platform Settings
Once you have the MAUI Community Toolkit installation ready. Let’s continue by adding some platform settings. To implement them, follow the instructions added below:

On Android: Go to &amp;#160;Platform ➖ Android&amp;#160;➖&amp;#160;AndroidManifes.cs and add the following code:



&amp;#160; &amp;#160; &amp;#160; On Tizen: Go to &amp;#160;Platform ➖ Tizen ➖ tizen-manifest.xml and add the following code:


 &amp;#160;For iOS/MacCatalyst&amp;#160;and&amp;#160;Windows&amp;#160;you don’t need an additional configuration.

Let’s start!&amp;#160;
What is a FileSaver?
This is an API that is part of the MAUI Community Toolkit, which allows you to select a file and save it to a destination folder on your device&amp;#39;s file system
How to implement it?&amp;#160;

Step 1⃣&amp;#160;: Let&amp;#39;s use Dependency Injection
For this example, we will use Dependency Injection. If you want to know more about this topic you can enter to the article .NET Dependency Injection.
➖ Registering the FileSaver: For the first step, we need to use the FileSaver, which is responsible for saving the desired file on the system. Since we&amp;#39;ll be using Dependency Injection, we need to register it.
To do this, go to MauiProgram.cs, navigate to the CreateMauiApp method, and add the following code after the builder.

➖Injecting the service: Now go to your MainPage.xaml.cs, and let&amp;#39;s inject the File Saver as I show you below:

Step 2⃣: Saving the file
We will use the SaveAsync() method, which displays a dialog on the screen to allow us to select a file and save it to a destination folder on the file system. This method contains the following set of properties:
➖ Initial path: This is the initial path (suggested) that appears by default in the dialog box when the user goes to save their file. - It’s of string type.
➖ File name: Upon saving a file, the user is presented with a suggested name, which can be edited or kept as is. It is essential to include the file extension in the suggested name. - It’s of string type. – [Mandatory]&amp;#160;
➖ Stream: This is an abstraction of a stream of bytes. Here, you will manage all the contents of the file that you want to save. - It’s of Stream type. – [Mandatory]&amp;#160;
➖ CancellationToken: Allows you to send a cancellation for the operation you are doing. - It’s of CancellationToken type. – [Mandatory]&amp;#160;
Now let&amp;#39;s se how to do it in code
Add the cancellationToken: To do so, locate the comment in step 1 that says Add the CancellationToken here and add the following line of code:

⚠ If you want to cancel it, you just have to do the following:

To prepare the content of the file that we are going to save, we must first create a new method, in this example we will call it SaveFile. Inside, you will see two lines of code which I explain below:
&amp;#128313; We create a stream that we will later pass as a parameter to the SaveAsync method. For this example, we will use text, but you can replace it with other type of content you wish to save.
&amp;#128313; We call &amp;#160;the SaveAsync method, we use SampleFile.txt as the suggested file name.

Finally, let&amp;#39;s see the result!




Additional Topics
FileSaverResult
The FileSaverResult covers the result returned by the SaveAsync method. It contains a set of properties and methods that can help determine if the operation was successful or if there was an exception, among other informations as shown below:
&amp;#128313; File Path: Is a property that refers to the location on disk where the file was saved. - It’s of string type.
&amp;#128313; Exception: Returns the Exception in case the save operation failed.
&amp;#128313; IsSuccessful: Indicates the success of the operation by returning a boolean value.
&amp;#128313; EnsureSuccess: Is a method that checks if the operation was successfull.
To access these methods and properties, just save the result of SaveAsync using await and don&amp;#39;t forget to make the method async.


And done! &amp;#128526; From now on, you know how to save files in your .NET MAUI applications! &amp;#128154;&amp;#128149;
&amp;lt;Label Text=”Thanks for reading!&amp;#160;&amp;#128075; ” /&amp;gt;
Spanish post:

https://es.askxammy.com/guardando-archivos-con-net-maui-community-toolkit/

References:

Gerald Versluis&amp;#39;s Video
https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/communitytoolkit/maui/essentials/file-saver?tabs=tizen?WT.mc_id=DT-MVP-50033
</description>
      <author> (About Leomaris Reyes)</author>
      <guid>https://askxammy.com/saving-files-with-net-maui-community-toolkit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Improving Productivity &amp;amp; Reducing Support Time with Tag Helpers</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=kbbaiUIjBEg</link>
      <description>Tag Helpers are one of the most useful features to save time in ASP.NET Core. In this week&amp;#39;s episode, community MVP Mitchel Sellers shows us his open-source ...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=kbbaiUIjBEg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use RuntimeHelpers.IsReferenceOrContainsReferences to micro-optimize collections - G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/how-to-use-runtimehelpers-isreferenceorcontainsreferences-to-micro-optimize-coll.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to use RuntimeHelpers.IsReferenceOrContainsReferences to micro-optimize collections in .NET.</description>
      <author> (G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/how-to-use-runtimehelpers-isreferenceorcontainsreferences-to-micro-optimize-coll.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bookshelf Sorting</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2791/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2791/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 22:06:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Performance Issues: How Project Loom Eliminates Asynchrony</title>
      <link>https://backendhance.com/en/blog/2023/project-loom/</link>
      <description>Anyone who develops a backend application with more than a handful of users knows that most performance problems are related to I/O. In modern web applications, these are typically network calls. Whether it’s REST requests to another service, queries to an external database, or communication with middleware. We handle all these cases - consciously or unconsciously - in asynchronous threads. This way, we no longer block the main thread. Doing this correctly is not trivial.</description>
      <author> (Marcus Held)</author>
      <guid>https://backendhance.com/en/blog/2023/project-loom/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can ChatGPT Help My Non-Coder Partner Build Software?</title>
      <link>https://blog.picheta.me/can-chatgpt-help-my-non-coder-partner-build-software</link>
      <description>An AI Experiment: Challenging a Non-Coder to Use ChatGPT for File Comparison - Here&amp;#39;s What Happened.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.picheta.me/can-chatgpt-help-my-non-coder-partner-build-software</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The gotchas of CSS Nesting | Kilian Valkhof</title>
      <link>https://kilianvalkhof.com/2023/css-html/the-gotchas-of-css-nesting/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve written before about the problems you can run into with CSS nesting (keep in mind that article uses an older syntax but the point still stands) and the question that @ChallengeCSS tweeted out today made me realize there&amp;#39;s actually a few more gotcha&amp;#39;s. Here&amp;#39;s what they tweeted: Everyone is exited about CSS Nesting but […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kilianvalkhof.com/2023/css-html/the-gotchas-of-css-nesting/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data dump diversion</title>
      <link>https://jlericson.com/2023/06/19/data_dump.html</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been writing non-stop about the Stack Overflow
strike and there&amp;#39;s a little
side-story that might slip by if you aren&amp;#39;t paying attention. I&amp;#39;m
talking about the decision to not upload the Stack Exchange Data
Dump to the Internet
Archive. If you aren&amp;#39;t deep in the weeds
of Stack Exchange, it&amp;#39;s easy to miss this esoteric topic that looks
inconsequential from the outside, but might sit at the core of the
conflict.
</description>
      <author> (Jon Ericson)</author>
      <guid>https://jlericson.com/2023/06/19/data_dump.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My macOS Accessibility Setup - Ravi Atluri</title>
      <link>https://raviatluri.in/articles/my-mac-accessibility-setup</link>
      <description>Accessibility setup and tools for everyday use on macOS/OSX</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://raviatluri.in/articles/my-mac-accessibility-setup</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reddit is dangerous. The admins are out of control. Humanity needs a viable alternative.</title>
      <link>https://maximiliankohler.blogspot.com/2023/06/reddit-is-dangerous-humanity-needs-an-alternative.html</link>
      <description>Generally, I identify problems and their causes, and propose solutions. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://maximiliankohler.blogspot.com/2023/06/reddit-is-dangerous-humanity-needs-an-alternative.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Hire Clojure Developers</title>
      <link>https://blog.janetacarr.com/how-to-hire-clojure-developers/</link>
      <description>This odd thing keeps happening to me where companies reach out to ask if I know of any Clojure developers they can hire instead of just hiring me. I understand why they do this. I am not interested in full-time position, after all. I think most people would bitterly look</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.janetacarr.com/how-to-hire-clojure-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside of the WASP&amp;#39;s nest: deep dive into PyPI-hosted malware</title>
      <link>https://blog.virustotal.com/2023/06/inside-of-wasps-nest-deep-dive-into.html</link>
      <description>          Photo by Matheus Queiroz  on Unsplash    In late 2022 we decided to start monitoring PyPI , arguably the most important Python rep...</description>
      <author> (Alexey Firsh)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.virustotal.com/2023/06/inside-of-wasps-nest-deep-dive-into.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacobson&amp;#39;s Rank | denvaar&amp;#39;s Site</title>
      <link>https://denvaar.github.io/posts/jacobsons_rank.html</link>
      <description>Rank is a fundamental operation for Succinct Data Structures. It counts the number of set bits up to a given index in a bit array. How can this be done in constant time and sub-linear space?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://denvaar.github.io/posts/jacobsons_rank.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How building a new project saved my main business</title>
      <link>https://kiza.dev/notes/side-project-saved-main-business</link>
      <description>How refocusing on customer needs, targeting potential clients, and enhancing core value brought renewed success. A seemingly distracting project became a catalyst for growth.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kiza.dev/notes/side-project-saved-main-business</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How technology has changed the world since I was young</title>
      <link>https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/how-technology-has-changed-the-world</link>
      <description>A bit of future shock.</description>
      <author> (Noah Smith)</author>
      <guid>https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/how-technology-has-changed-the-world</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just use QWERTY!</title>
      <link>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2023/06/just-use-qwerty/</link>
      <description>The QWERTY layout is, I grant you, an illogical mess. I&amp;#39;m happy to hear your arguments that Dvorak is the one true way. Or that Colemak is several percent faster. But QWERTY is a standard now. Everyone uses it on their laptops and phones. It is used everywhere. Except, it turns out, streaming services. They [...]</description>
      <author> (https://shkspr.mobi/blog/author/admin/)</author>
      <guid>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2023/06/just-use-qwerty/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Biases Ranked by Popularity</title>
      <link>https://osolmaz.github.io/blog/cognitive-biases-ranked-by-popularity</link>
      <description>If you have spent some time on rationalist forums, you might have come across images that try to visualize cognitive biases that humans are prone to:</description>
      <author> (Onur Solmaz)</author>
      <guid>https://osolmaz.github.io/blog/cognitive-biases-ranked-by-popularity</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why LLM-assisted table transformation is a big deal</title>
      <link>https://blog.jonudell.net/2023/06/18/why-llm-assisted-table-transformation-is-a-big-deal/</link>
      <description>Last week I had to convert a table in a Google Doc to a JSON structure that will render as an HTML page. This is the sort of mundane task that burns staggering amounts of information workers’…</description>
      <author> (Published by Jon Udell			
		

		
						
				View all posts by Jon Udell)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jonudell.net/2023/06/18/why-llm-assisted-table-transformation-is-a-big-deal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Debt is Tech Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.madsbuch.com/tech-debt-tax/</link>
      <description>There is this saying about tech debt: When you move fast in a software team,
you build up debt that you must pay off later. The engineering team uses this
to get a break and align the current understanding of the product with the code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.madsbuch.com/tech-debt-tax/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ease of picking up web development is greatly exaggerated</title>
      <link>https://cushychicken.github.io/webapp-dev-is-hard/</link>
      <description>I quit my job in July 2021, and started writing a webapp for something to do. (Are you an FPGA engineer, and looking for a new job? Check us out at www.FPGAjobs.com.) I had assumed, as a credentialed engineer and longtime HN lurker, that picking up web development was going to be pretty easy. I was absolutely wrong. Here’s why.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cushychicken.github.io/webapp-dev-is-hard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-assumptions ZFS, part 1 | nikvdp</title>
      <link>https://nikvdp.com/post/zfs-part1/</link>
      <description>This is the first in a series of articles about ZFS, and is part of what I hope
becomes an ongoing series here: the zero-assumptions write up. This article
will be written assuming you know nothing about ZFS.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nikvdp.com/post/zfs-part1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plain Text Journaling</title>
      <link>https://peppe.rs/posts/plain_text_journaling/</link>
      <description>a static site {for, by, about} me </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://peppe.rs/posts/plain_text_journaling/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Five-Year Rule of Software Transitions</title>
      <link>https://blog.robenkleene.com/2023/06/19/software-transitions-the-five-year-rule/</link>
      <description>Roben Kleene’s blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.robenkleene.com/2023/06/19/software-transitions-the-five-year-rule/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My generic Open Source Project FAQ</title>
      <link>https://carlschwan.eu/2023/06/19/my-generic-open-source-project-faq/</link>
      <description>People are often asking the same questions again and again about some of my projects, so it might be a good opportunity to write a small FAQ.
If you get redirected here, don’t take it personally; I am getting asked these questions very often, and I feel people often misunderstand how open-source projects work.
Why does X not have feature Y? The most likely reason is that it still needs to be implemented.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://carlschwan.eu/2023/06/19/my-generic-open-source-project-faq/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I started (and stopped) making games</title>
      <link>https://austinhenley.com/blog/makinggames.html</link>
      <description>During college I paid my bills by making games. This is the story of how I got started and why I stopped.</description>
      <author> (Austin Z. Henley)</author>
      <guid>https://austinhenley.com/blog/makinggames.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ferricy: Building a custom 34-key split keyboard</title>
      <link>https://www.snprajwal.com/blog/ferricy-custom-split-keyboard/</link>
      <description>Ergonomics, productivity, and style - all at once ;)</description>
      <author> (Prajwal S N)</author>
      <guid>https://www.snprajwal.com/blog/ferricy-custom-split-keyboard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Narrow Waists Can Be Interior or Exterior: PyObject vs. Unix Files</title>
      <link>https://www.oilshell.org/blog/2023/06/narrow-waist.html</link>
      <description>|
blog | oilshell.org</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.oilshell.org/blog/2023/06/narrow-waist.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an IBM 3270 terminal controller</title>
      <link>https://ajk.me/building-an-ibm-3270-terminal-controller</link>
      <description>I wanted to connect an IBM 3270 mainframe terminal to the Hercules emulator but couldn&amp;#39;t find a working controller. So I decided to build my own.</description>
      <author> (Andrew Kay)</author>
      <guid>https://ajk.me/building-an-ibm-3270-terminal-controller</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 21:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Maps to Your Cross-Platform .NET Apps</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/easily-add-maps-to-your-cross-platform-net-apps-mapsui-adds-support-for-uno-platform/</link>
      <description>Discover how MAPSUI seamlessly integrates with Uno Platform, enhancing cross-platform .NET applications with powerful mapping capabilities.</description>
      <author> (Uno Platform Team)</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/easily-add-maps-to-your-cross-platform-net-apps-mapsui-adds-support-for-uno-platform/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 19:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Functions Community Standup | Microsoft Build updates!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=0xnv8lQDKNM</link>
      <description>Join us for the June 2023 edition of the Azure Functions community live stream! Get an overview of the new Azure Functions announcements from the Microsoft B...</description>
      <author> (Santrel Media
  
  
  
    Santrel Media
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=0xnv8lQDKNM</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 19:06:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Implement a Soft Delete Strategy with Entity Framework Core | The .NET Tools Blog</title>
      <link>https://jb.gg/ma9wtf</link>
      <description>Learn to use a Soft Delete strategy using Entity Framework Core and the latest versions of .NET.</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://jb.gg/ma9wtf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolverine’s Middleware Strategy is a Different Animal</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/06/19/wolverines-middleware-strategy-is-a-different-animal/</link>
      <description>I saw someone on Twitter today asking to hear how Wolverine differs from MediatR. First off, Wolverine is a much bigger, more ambitious tool than MediatR is trying to be and covers far more use cas…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/06/19/wolverines-middleware-strategy-is-a-different-animal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 17:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Create a Pull Request in Visual Studio - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/create-a-pull-request-in-visual-studio/</link>
      <description>Create a Pull Request in Visual Studio with the newest preview.</description>
      <author> (Jessie Houghton)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/create-a-pull-request-in-visual-studio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 17:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spargine Dev Tool: Never Lose Source Code Ever Again!</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/06/19/spargine-dev-tool-never-lose-source-code-ever-again/</link>
      <description>Exciting news for developers! Introducing the Spargine Dev Tool: Never Lose Source Code Ever Again! Check out this article to learn more about its powerful ‘backup’ command and how it c…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave
		

		
			I live in San Diego, Ca USA			
				View all posts by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/06/19/spargine-dev-tool-never-lose-source-code-ever-again/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 24MB to 14MB in 6 Seconds: The Visual Studio Extension You NEED for Image Optimization!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=i-afbz0o5f0</link>
      <description>In this video, I&amp;#39;m excited to share with you a super handy extension in Visual Studio that&amp;#39;s going to make your web projects lighter and faster. As developer...</description>
      <author> (Devs School
  
  
  
    Devs School
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=i-afbz0o5f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Auth Setting That Everyone MUST Change in .NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=meBxWjA_2YY</link>
      <description>Check out my new course From Zero to Hero: Logging in .NET and use code LOG20 at checkout for 20% off: https://bit.ly/loggingdotnet valid for the first 400 p...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=meBxWjA_2YY</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:05:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integer compression: Implementing FastPFor encoding in C#</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/199586-A/integer-compression-implementing-fastpfor-encoding-in-c?Key=c3c2eaf7-e1e8-4a29-ad15-84a365447967</link>
      <description>In the previous post I outlined the requirements we have for FastPFor in RavenDB. Now I want to dig into the actual implementation. Here is the shape of the ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/199586-A/integer-compression-implementing-fastpfor-encoding-in-c?Key=c3c2eaf7-e1e8-4a29-ad15-84a365447967</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:05:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>