<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>ABP Modules</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=jXroxIBPlWI</link>
      <description>🚀Get a quick overview of how modular development works with ABP.IO!</description>
      <author> (Volosoft)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=jXroxIBPlWI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source devs say AI crawlers dominate traffic, forcing blocks on entire countries</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/ai/2025/03/devs-say-ai-crawlers-dominate-traffic-forcing-blocks-on-entire-countries/</link>
      <description>AI bots hungry for data are taking down FOSS sites by accident, but humans are fighting back.</description>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/ai/2025/03/devs-say-ai-crawlers-dominate-traffic-forcing-blocks-on-entire-countries/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HN Popularity Contest</title>
      <link>https://refactoringenglish.com/tools/hn-popularity/</link>
      <description>The highest-ranking personal blogs of Hacker News</description>
      <guid>https://refactoringenglish.com/tools/hn-popularity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is Grounded and Needs to Learn How to Soar</title>
      <link>https://tomcritchlow.com/2025/03/21/better-ai-mode/</link>
      <description>A short proposal for the future of search</description>
      <guid>https://tomcritchlow.com/2025/03/21/better-ai-mode/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snakes in a Pane: Building Snake Entirely Within a tmux Config File</title>
      <link>https://willhbr.net/2025/03/20/snakes-in-a-pane/</link>
      <description>Honestly I’d stop if I could, but I just get carried away. After making a compiler for tmux, then solving sudoku, then playing video I wasn’t planning on making a game. These things just happen to you. Well maybe not to you, but they happen to me. Unlike the video player, this isn’t just rendering Snake inside tmux. The entire game—input, game logic, and rendering—is done using tmux config files. You just load tmux with this config, and you’ll have...</description>
      <guid>https://willhbr.net/2025/03/20/snakes-in-a-pane/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure as Markdown?</title>
      <link>https://danshiebler.com/2025-03-25-infrastructure-as-markdown/</link>
      <description>Ever had a complex Python function you wanted to quickly host as an API? Managing dependencies like databases, secret keys, or heavy utilities like audio processing libraries can be quite cumbersome. Typically, I handle this with a pattern involving: Docker: to manage and install dependencies AWS Parameter Store: to securely...</description>
      <guid>https://danshiebler.com/2025-03-25-infrastructure-as-markdown/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You should know this before choosing Next.js</title>
      <link>https://eduardoboucas.com/posts/2025-03-25-you-should-know-this-before-choosing-nextjs/</link>
      <description>Picking the technology stack for a project is an important and consequential decision. In the enterprise space in particular, it often involves a multi-year commitment with long-lasting implications on the roadmap of the project, the pace of its development, the quality of the deliverables, and even the ability to assemble and maintain a happy team.The open-source software model is a fundamental answer to this. By using software that is developed in the open, anyone is free to extend it or modify it in whatever way fits their use case. More crucially, the portability of open-source software gives developers and organisations the freedom to move their infrastructure between different providers without fear of getting locked in to a specific vendor.This is the expectation with Next.js, an open-source web development framework created and [governed by Vercel](https://nextjs.org/governance), a cloud provider that offers managed hosting of Next.js as a service.</description>
      <guid>https://eduardoboucas.com/posts/2025-03-25-you-should-know-this-before-choosing-nextjs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who moved my (virtual) cheese?</title>
      <link>https://obra.studio/blog/2025/03/24/who-moved-my-cheese/</link>
      <description>Musings on redesigning software, user's mental models and guidelines on what to do when redesigning.</description>
      <guid>https://obra.studio/blog/2025/03/24/who-moved-my-cheese/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shape of Code » Half-life of Microsoft products is 7 years</title>
      <link>https://shape-of-code.com/2025/03/23/half-life-of-microsoft-products-is-7-years/</link>
      <description>I get a lot of pushback from developers/managers when I tell them that the average application has a relatively short lifetime, i.e., half-life of 4-8 years.  The pushback kicks in when I start citing data, up until then my listeners appear surprised/skeptical.  The fact that source code has a brief and lonely existence is accepted, but telling them about the (one study) evidence that a coding mistake is more likely to disappear because of an unrelated coding change than as a result of fixing a fault report appears to make them feel uncomfortable.</description>
      <guid>https://shape-of-code.com/2025/03/23/half-life-of-microsoft-products-is-7-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I recommend against Brave</title>
      <link>https://thelibre.news/no-really-dont-use-brave/</link>
      <description>If you are keen on personal privacy, you might have come across Brave Browser. Brave is a Chromium-based browser that promises to deliver privacy with built-in ad-blocking and content-blocking protection. It also offers several quality-of-life features and services, like a VPN and Tor access. I mean, it's even listed on</description>
      <guid>https://thelibre.news/no-really-dont-use-brave/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nostalgia — bayindirh</title>
      <link>https://blog.bayindirh.io/blog/nostalgia/</link>
      <description>The people I'm following on the internet put me inside a small but vibrant retrocomputing bubble. When this is combined with the synthwave composers I tend to listen lately, I'm being transported to my earlier years on this planet, repeatedly. The fact that I have grown with a Commodore 64, 486 systems, boomboxes and big Hi-Fi racks makes this a rather harsh, but enjoyable ride every time.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.bayindirh.io/blog/nostalgia/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hartwork Blog · How much security is in long-term support?</title>
      <link>https://blog.hartwork.org/posts/how-much-security-is-in-long-term-support/</link>
      <description>Everyone loves the idea of long-term support
— LTS for short —
where a vendor promises you to provide security updates for a few years:
little friction and strong security.
Does long-term support live up to that dream?
It does not.
What makes me say that?</description>
      <guid>https://blog.hartwork.org/posts/how-much-security-is-in-long-term-support/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lost Art of Commit Messages</title>
      <link>https://www.seyhan.me/blog/post/lost-art-of-commit-messages</link>
      <description>Personal blog of Seyhan Dzhamur</description>
      <guid>https://www.seyhan.me/blog/post/lost-art-of-commit-messages</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCPs Part 2: Building an App Opener MCP Server for macOS</title>
      <link>https://blog.fka.dev/blog/2025-03-23-building-app-opener-mcp-server-for-macos/</link>
      <description>Learn how to build a custom MCP server that allows Claude Desktop to open applications on your macOS system. This step-by-step guide shows you how to create a tool that brings AI assistance to your daily workflow.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.fka.dev/blog/2025-03-23-building-app-opener-mcp-server-for-macos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating MacPaint's Source Code | ℤ→ℤ</title>
      <link>https://ztoz.blog/posts/macpaint-source-code/</link>
      <description>2025-03-25</description>
      <guid>https://ztoz.blog/posts/macpaint-source-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When's the best time to surge when cycling up a hill?</title>
      <link>https://leblancfg.com/surge-cycling-up-a-hill.html</link>
      <description>A simple cycling simulator that calculates the time it takes to cycle up a hill with a surge of power.</description>
      <author> (https://leblancfg.com/author/francois-leblanc.html)</author>
      <guid>https://leblancfg.com/surge-cycling-up-a-hill.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Apocalyptic Computing</title>
      <link>https://thomashunter.name/posts/2025-03-23-post-apocalyptic-computing</link>
      <description>12 min read    Mar 23, 2025</description>
      <guid>https://thomashunter.name/posts/2025-03-23-post-apocalyptic-computing</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ski itinerary optimization</title>
      <link>https://www.alexandercogneau.com/posts/ski-path-optimization/</link>
      <description>Every year, my wife and I go skiing in the French Alps.
This time, we set our sights on something ambitious: skiing 100 kilometers in a single day. On a typical day, with breaks and a leisurely pace, we cover 40 to 50 kilometers.
So 100 felt like a stretch, but not impossible. The lifts run from roughly 9-17, giving us only eight hours. To make it work, we needed to properly plan for it.</description>
      <guid>https://www.alexandercogneau.com/posts/ski-path-optimization/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducible Software Releases – Simon Josefsson's blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.josefsson.org/2025/03/24/reproducible-software-releases/</link>
      <description>Around a year ago I discussed two concerns with software release archives (tarball artifacts) that could be improved to increase confidence in the supply-chain security of software releases.  Repeating the goals for simplicity:</description>
      <guid>https://blog.josefsson.org/2025/03/24/reproducible-software-releases/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Choose What to Work On - Tynan.com</title>
      <link>https://tynan.com/workonwhat/</link>
      <description>A reader, “Moo”, asked me to write about my process for entrepreneurship and how I choose what to write on. Despite being a lifelong entrepreneur and being relatively successful at it, I don’t write a lot about it because I routinely make decisions that trade money for other things (freedom, autonomy, quality of life, stubborn […]</description>
      <guid>https://tynan.com/workonwhat/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's build a VORON 0</title>
      <link>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2025/03/25/lets_build_a_voron_0/</link>
      <description>About 1.5 years ago I ventured into 3D printing by building a VORON Trident.
It was a very fun project and I’ve even used the printer quite a bit.</description>
      <guid>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2025/03/25/lets_build_a_voron_0/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the relationship between sigmoid, softmax and tanh</title>
      <link>https://blog.itdxer.com/2025/03/20/on-relation-between-sigmoid-softmax-and-tanh.html</link>
      <description>20 Mar 2025</description>
      <guid>https://blog.itdxer.com/2025/03/20/on-relation-between-sigmoid-softmax-and-tanh.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing NPM Packages Very Quickly</title>
      <link>https://healeycodes.com/installing-npm-packages-very-quickly</link>
      <description>Building a package manager with a fast install step.</description>
      <guid>https://healeycodes.com/installing-npm-packages-very-quickly</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Server Sent Event protocol with Spring Webflux</title>
      <link>https://blog.ght1pc9kc.fr/en/2025/the-server-sent-event-protocol-with-spring-webflux/</link>
      <description>WebSockets are often mentioned for server events, but they are not the only option. Spring Boot WebFlux can send Server Sent Events out of the box. To change from the usual chat application examples, here’s how to implement server notifications in Java with Spring Webflux.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.ght1pc9kc.fr/en/2025/the-server-sent-event-protocol-with-spring-webflux/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REST in Peace? Django's Framework Problem</title>
      <link>https://danlamanna.com/posts/rest-in-peace-djangos-framework-problem/</link>
      <description>The Django REST Framework maintainer has removed access to thousands of community discussions, leaving even other maintainers pleading for read-only access. What does this mean for Django’s ecosystem sustainability?</description>
      <guid>https://danlamanna.com/posts/rest-in-peace-djangos-framework-problem/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 Weeks of “One Solution Every Week” — Vishnu's Pages</title>
      <link>https://iamvishnu.com/posts/12-weeks-of-coding</link>
      <description>I have been solving problems and writing code for over a decade. In recent years, I’ve been spending more time on the management side of things, which doesn’...</description>
      <guid>https://iamvishnu.com/posts/12-weeks-of-coding</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking and Fixing Content-Defined Chunking</title>
      <link>https://blog.ktruong.dev/breaking-cdc/</link>
      <description>A collection of my (future) writings about cryptography, music and other random stuff.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.ktruong.dev/breaking-cdc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When You're On Vacation, Be On Vacation - Don't Break Prod</title>
      <link>https://dontbreakprod.com/posts/when-youre-on-vacation-be-on-vacation</link>
      <description>Don't Break Prod provides bite-sized pieces of career advice for software engineers.</description>
      <guid>https://dontbreakprod.com/posts/when-youre-on-vacation-be-on-vacation</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stoop Coffee: How a Simple Idea Transformed My Neighborhood</title>
      <link>https://supernuclear.substack.com/p/stoop-coffee-how-a-simple-idea-transformed</link>
      <description>Editor’s note: This is a guest post from Patty Smith.</description>
      <guid>https://supernuclear.substack.com/p/stoop-coffee-how-a-simple-idea-transformed</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 2.5: Our most intelligent AI model</title>
      <link>https://blog.google/technology/google-deepmind/gemini-model-thinking-updates-march-2025/</link>
      <description>Gemini 2.5 is our most intelligent AI model, now with thinking.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.google/technology/google-deepmind/gemini-model-thinking-updates-march-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring new .NET releases with Dev Containers - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-in-dev-container/</link>
      <description>Learn how to set up and use dev containers for experimenting with new .NET releases.</description>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-in-dev-container/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TypeScript Migrates to Go: What's Really Behind That 10x Performance Claim?</title>
      <link>https://www.architecture-weekly.com/p/typescript-migrates-to-go-whats-really</link>
      <description>JavaScript is slow!!! You could get that from the announcement with a 10x performance increase after migrating the TypeScript compiler to Go. The real story? Node.js works well at I/O but struggles with CPU-intensive tasks like compilation. Read more to learn in detail why and what you can learn from it for your systems design!</description>
      <guid>https://www.architecture-weekly.com/p/typescript-migrates-to-go-whats-really</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🆘Bill Cole 🇺🇦 (@grumpybozo@toad.social)</title>
      <link>https://toad.social/@grumpybozo/114213600922816869</link>
      <description>@jwz@mastodon.social The stats we collect for the #SpamAssassin project (mass-scan results from participating sites) have long shown that spammers are more consistent at making SPF, DKIM, and DMARC correct than are legitimate senders. DMARC in particular has no discernible benefit for most senders, so it is a useless signal. 

Rejecting mail based solely on authentication failures of those deeply flawed authentication methods does more harm than good.</description>
      <guid>https://toad.social/@grumpybozo/114213600922816869</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 15:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Started with AI in Your Business?</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=x1sTesyQmOw</link>
      <description>Thinking about using AI in your business? In this shorts we discuss how it really works!

Here is the full video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CXpWjxCIY_E&amp;list=PLsNclT2aHJcOsPustEkzG6DywiO8eh0lB 

#aiforbusiness  #entrepreneurship  #businessgrowth  #techtips</description>
      <author> (Volosoft)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=x1sTesyQmOw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the CurrentUser in ABP? | ABP.IO</title>
      <link>https://abp.io/community/articles/how-to-change-the-currentuser-in-abp-i3uu1m7g</link>
      <description>ABP Framework provides a powerful service for accessing information about the currently authenticated user in your application. Understanding how to u...</description>
      <guid>https://abp.io/community/articles/how-to-change-the-currentuser-in-abp-i3uu1m7g</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check this before choosing a Key-Value Store</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_z_TkSFXNts</link>
      <description>💌 Free Developer Insights: https://guiferreira.me/newsletter

#softwaredevelopment #softwareengineering</description>
      <author> (Gui Ferreira)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_z_TkSFXNts</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Tried Out This MassTransit Error Handling Solution - My thoughts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=N4lQnT9k66Q</link>
      <description>Giveaway: https://gleam.io/QY45F/milan-jovanovic
Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Get the source code here: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic



Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=N4lQnT9k66Q</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extract HTML to a Razor component in Visual Studio with 1 Click</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=g0h3gj5XDgk</link>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself adding too much code to a .razor file and wanted an easy way to move it to its own reusable component? When working with HTML in a Razor file, you can now use CTRL+. or right-click and select Quick Actions and Refactorings to automatically extract your selected HTML markup to a new Razor component in Visual Studio.


✅ Download Visual Studio Toady: https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2022-v17-13-is-now-available/

Connect with .NET: 
Blog:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/blog
Twitter: https://aka.ms/dotnet/twitter
TikTok:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/tiktok
Mastodon:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/mastodon
LinkedIn:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/linkedin
Facebook:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/facebook
Docs: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet
Forums: https://aka.ms/dotnet/forums
🙋‍♀️Q&amp;A: https://aka.ms/dotnet-qa
👨‍🎓Microsoft Learn: https://aka.ms/learndotnet

#dotnet</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=g0h3gj5XDgk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level Up Your Razor Pages: Meet htmx, Your New Best Friend - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/level-up-your-razor-pages-meet-htmx-your-new-best-friend/</link>
      <description>Hey there, fellow ASP.NET developer! If you’re tired of wrestling with JavaScript frameworks or want to simplify your life, you’re in for a treat. Today, we’re diving into the wonderful world of HTMX and why it might just be the missing piece to make your ASP.NET Razor Pages even more awesome.</description>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/level-up-your-razor-pages-meet-htmx-your-new-best-friend/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Claude with External Tools: MCPs in Action</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/extend-claude-model-context-protocol/</link>
      <description>Learn how Model Context Protocol (MCP) breaks through Claude's knowledge limitations by enabling real-time web search and external tool integration through the desktop application.</description>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/extend-claude-model-context-protocol/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>