<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine production, April 2021 - Global Commission for Post-Pandemic Policy</title>
      <link>https://globalcommissionforpostpandemicpolicy.org/vaccine-production-april-2021/</link>
      <description>This is the first of what we plan as monthly updates on the world’s progress in producing vaccines to protect against COVID-19 and of manufacturers’ latest targets for total output by the end of this year.</description>
      <author> (/by GCPPP Staff)</author>
      <guid>https://globalcommissionforpostpandemicpolicy.org/vaccine-production-april-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 17:07:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Story of One Whale Who Tried to Bridge the Linguistic Divide Between Animals and Humans</title>
      <link>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/story-one-whale-who-tried-bridge-linguistic-divide-between-animals-humans-180951437/</link>
      <description>While captive in a Navy program, a beluga whale named Noc began to mimic human speech. What was behind his attempt to talk to us?</description>
      <author> (Charles Siebert)</author>
      <guid>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/story-one-whale-who-tried-bridge-linguistic-divide-between-animals-humans-180951437/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 15:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Linux Phones stay around this time?</title>
      <link>https://linmob.net/will-linux-phones-stay-around-this-time/</link>
      <description>While working through the old posts in order to adjust the front matter (and sometimes more), I thought: Will this last? Or will this go south soon, like it did around with previous projects again? A recent reddit post reinforced this line of thought, so I decided to write down my thoughts on the issue.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://linmob.net/will-linux-phones-stay-around-this-time/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 14:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dekuNukem/bob_cassette_rewinder</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dekuNukem/bob_cassette_rewinder</link>
      <description>Renew and Refill Bob Cassette for a fraction of the cost! - dekuNukem/bob_cassette_rewinder</description>
      <author> (dekuNukem)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dekuNukem/bob_cassette_rewinder</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 13:06:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing GNU Emacs to Native Code</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2004.02504</link>
      <description>Emacs Lisp (Elisp) is the Lisp dialect used by the Emacs text editor family.
GNU Emacs can currently execute Elisp code either interpreted or
byte-interpreted after it has been compiled to byte-code. In this work we
discuss the implementation of an optimizing compiler approach for Elisp
targeting native code. The native compiler employs the byte-compiler&amp;#39;s internal
representation as input and exploits libgccjit to achieve code generation using
the GNU Compiler Collection (GCC) infrastructure. Generated executables are
stored as binary files and can be loaded and unloaded dynamically. Most of the
functionality of the compiler is written in Elisp itself, including several
optimization passes, paired with a C back-end to interface with the GNU Emacs
core and libgccjit. Though still a work in progress, our implementation is able
to bootstrap a functional Emacs and compile all lexically scoped Elisp files,
including the whole GNU Emacs Lisp Package Archive (ELPA). Native-compiled
Elisp shows an increase of performance ranging from 2.3x up to 42x with respect
to the equivalent byte-code, measured over a set of small benchmarks.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 6 Apr 2020])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2004.02504</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 11:07:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the ProblemDetails Class in ASP.NET Core Web API</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/using-the-problemdetails-class-in-asp-net-core-web-api/</link>
      <description>ProblemDetails class in ASP.NET Core Web APIs helps us to standardize our error handling and have better communication with API clients.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/using-the-problemdetails-class-in-asp-net-core-web-api/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 07:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CommandDotNet</title>
      <link>https://commanddotnet.bilal-fazlani.com/</link>
      <description>A modern framework for building modern CLI apps</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://commanddotnet.bilal-fazlani.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 06:32:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>readme.so - Easiest Way to Create A README</title>
      <link>https://readme.so/</link>
      <description>Use readme.so&amp;#39;s markdown editor and ready made templates to easily create a simple README for your repositories</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://readme.so/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 04:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Microsoft Engineer Explains How to Fix Your Computer Problem</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8_9EBvrdVKs</link>
      <description>Retired Microsoft operating system developer Davepl explains how to fix most common computer problems.  Applicable to both Mac and Windows, this time-honored...</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage
  
  
    

    
      
    Dave&amp;#39;s Garage
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8_9EBvrdVKs</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 03:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Performance for Developers on a Deadline</title>
      <link>https://joshghent.com/webperf-on-deadline/</link>
      <description>Web performance is a vital part of your business to ensure customers keep returning. But, it can be difficult to get the time for it. Here&amp;#39;s a guide on how to improve your website&amp;#39;s performance on a deadline</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joshghent.com/webperf-on-deadline/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:06:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing for Buying:
How to Break Through the Ceiling in Product-Led Growth</title>
      <link>https://sarahguo.com/blog/designing-for-buying</link>
      <description>Product-oriented teams are triumphantly declaring, “Sales and marketing had their time. The future is product-led growth.” In other words: if you build it, users will come. We at Greylock are longtime investors in product-led growth (PLG) companies such as Clockwise, Clubhouse, Coda, Demisto, Dropbox, Figma, Quip and Sqreen. I’ve recently invested in this trend of end-users becoming increasingly networked into communities, and therefore increasingly powerful. We understand the power of bottoms-up distribution. But we also continually see great product founders get caught flat-footed, underachieving against their growth goals when they rely solely on organic end-user adoption as their go-to-market (GTM) strategy, rather than as part of a whole-company system. Let’s look at the limits of PLG, a playbook for incorporating it into a more complete GTM strategy, and some of the unique challenges of getting this right.</description>
      <author> (Sarah Guo27 Apr, 2021 &amp;#183; 26 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://sarahguo.com/blog/designing-for-buying</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:06:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why textareas can&amp;#39;t grow?</title>
      <link>https://ruky.me/2021/05/01/why-textareas-cant-grow/</link>
      <description>Textareas are a basic and and an important element in any website UI. You might need textareas for a comment section, chat box, etc.



However, textareas have one small problem that you can&amp;#39;t seem to find an answer, that is textareas won&amp;#39;t automatically grow in height, as you would need them to be</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ruky.me/2021/05/01/why-textareas-cant-grow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Didn’t Buy Safemoon And You Can’t Either</title>
      <link>https://colmcqux.wordpress.com/2021/04/30/i-didnt-buy-safemoon-and-you-cant-either/</link>
      <description>I was reading the Sun newspaper the other day and there was some article yapping on about Safemoon – a new pyramid scheme a new cryptocoin thingy that has increased in value by infinity since…</description>
      <author> (myfoodeeblog)</author>
      <guid>https://colmcqux.wordpress.com/2021/04/30/i-didnt-buy-safemoon-and-you-cant-either/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:06:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Controller</title>
      <link>https://store.nintendo.com/pro-controller.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://store.nintendo.com/pro-controller.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:06:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re: Very slow clang kernel config ..</title>
      <link>https://lore.kernel.org/lkml/CAHk-=whs8QZf3YnifdLv57+FhBi5_WeNTG1B-suOES=RcUSmQg@mail.gmail.com/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lore.kernel.org/lkml/CAHk-=whs8QZf3YnifdLv57+FhBi5_WeNTG1B-suOES=RcUSmQg@mail.gmail.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:06:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream desktop – Sam Squire&amp;#39;s personal blog</title>
      <link>https://elaeis.cloud-angle.com/?p=165</link>
      <description>My computer should try benefit my life as much as possible. Modern desktops don’t even try. They don’t learn about me or give me advice. I want to give my demographics to my computer, my location, my salary and have the computer calculate things about me. We have all this untapped computer resource but most people only idle their computers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://elaeis.cloud-angle.com/?p=165</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:06:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let Your Employees Ask Questions</title>
      <link>https://obviousstartupadvice.com/2021/04/06/let-your-employees-ask-questions/</link>
      <description>For your first ten employees as a founder, you not only have to be very clear on the why and the what, but you have to be comfortable occasionally venturing into the how too. You have the context o…</description>
      <author> (Eric Marcoullier and Megan Hanson)</author>
      <guid>https://obviousstartupadvice.com/2021/04/06/let-your-employees-ask-questions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Made an Album Without Knowing Anything About Music</title>
      <link>https://www.mountainpass.tv/howimadeanalbumwithoutknowinganythingaboutmusic</link>
      <description>Could a software engineer with a background in artificial intelligence and no theoretical or practical knowledge about music make an album?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.mountainpass.tv/howimadeanalbumwithoutknowinganythingaboutmusic</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:06:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For whom the bell tolls</title>
      <link>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/for-whom-the-bell-tolls</link>
      <description>I am seeing more CEOs vocalizing publicly the decision that their company and ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/for-whom-the-bell-tolls</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 23:06:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling monorepo maintenance - The GitHub Blog</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/2021-04-29-scaling-monorepo-maintenance/</link>
      <description>Today, GitHub can repack even the largest repositories we host in a fraction of the time it used to take. Here&amp;#39;s how we did it, and why.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/2021-04-29-scaling-monorepo-maintenance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 23:06:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing How Updates Work with Docker Desktop 3.3 - Docker Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.docker.com/blog/changing-how-updates-work-with-docker-desktop-3-3/</link>
      <description>Learn from Docker experts to simplify and advance your app development and management with Docker. Stay up to date on Docker events and new version announcements!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.docker.com/blog/changing-how-updates-work-with-docker-desktop-3-3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 22:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edward Snowden at Private Investment Club Zoom Meeting - April 24th 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hv3UC4lz3oQ</link>
      <description>Intervention of Edward Snowden at Private Investment Club Zoom Meeting on April 24th 2021.After talking for just a few minutes, Edward Snowden exposes his ho...</description>
      <author> (thevintagerose)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hv3UC4lz3oQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 21:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O11 Dynamic MINI - Highly Modular water-cooll friendly small PC chassis</title>
      <link>https://lian-li.com/product/o11-dynamic-mini/</link>
      <description>O11D MINI adding to the O11 Dynamic series, the classic and mordern looking. A case that would accommodate the maximum number of water-cooling configurations without being oversized. With a modular back panel design, the user has the option to choose from 3 slots/ 5 slots/ 7 slots I/O shield to optimize the case to the configuration of user&amp;#39;s choice. Supports mini-ITX, micro-ATX, ATX, and E-ATX motherboard sizes. and up to 9 fans to cool the chassis.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lian-li.com/product/o11-dynamic-mini/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 21:05:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifier</title>
      <link>https://simplifier.neocities.org/index.html</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://simplifier.neocities.org/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 21:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard interface software</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/dL0GO9SeBh0</link>
      <description>Support these videos on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/beneater or https://eater.net/support for other ways to support.------------------Social media:Websi...</description>
      <author> (Ben Eater
  
  
    

    
      
    Ben Eater
  
    



  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/dL0GO9SeBh0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>System Builder</title>
      <link>https://pcpartpicker.com/list/vBhBRT</link>
      <description>Note: Wattages are estimates only. Actual power draw may differ from listed values.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pcpartpicker.com/list/vBhBRT</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 20:09:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ideas Filter</title>
      <link>http://ideasfilter.com/</link>
      <description>This is showing apps/plugins/extensions from various marketplaces with the option to filter for ideas for which many people pay but arent too happy with the current solution (low rating).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://ideasfilter.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 20:09:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code livestreams</title>
      <link>https://code.visualstudio.com/livestream?WT.mc_id=devcloud-18509-cxa</link>
      <description>Join the Visual Studio Code team and our community in our livestream series! Every month, we host a release party to highlight what&amp;#39;s new in the latest version of VS Code. We also host other live events highlighting our community members and cool projects they&amp;#39;ve made.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code.visualstudio.com/livestream?WT.mc_id=devcloud-18509-cxa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 19:05:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The MVP reconnect daily</title>
      <link>https://paper.li/buddingeek/1492363674?pub_id=36b191b0-8f5d-4cb6-b679-5ae6e8f072f0</link>
      <description>A selection of articles, blog posts, videos and photos recommended by Vijay</description>
      <author> (Vijay)</author>
      <guid>https://paper.li/buddingeek/1492363674?pub_id=36b191b0-8f5d-4cb6-b679-5ae6e8f072f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 18:07:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenBSD 6.9</title>
      <link>https://www.openbsd.org/69.html</link>
      <description>OpenBSD 6.9</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.openbsd.org/69.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 18:07:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>