<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>S1ngularity/nx attackers strike again</title>
      <link>https://www.aikido.dev/blog/s1ngularity-nx-attackers-strike-again</link>
      <description>The attackers behind the nx attack have struck again, targeting a large amount of packages, with a first-of-its-kind worm payload.</description>
      <category>nodejs</category>
      <category>angular</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>sql</category>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <guid>https://www.aikido.dev/blog/s1ngularity-nx-attackers-strike-again</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 18:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godot 4.5, making dreams accessible – Godot Engine</title>
      <link>https://godotengine.org/releases/4.5/</link>
      <description>From mind-blowing effects now made possible by the stencil buffer to accessible descriptions of your GUI elements that opens up the possibility for people with disabilities to play your game — we are proud to present to you Godot 4.5.</description>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>webasm</category>
      <category>nodejs</category>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <category>audio</category>
      <guid>https://godotengine.org/releases/4.5/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphin Progress Report: Release 2509</title>
      <link>https://dolphin-emu.org/blog/2025/09/16/dolphin-progress-report-release-2509/</link>
      <description>The Dolphin Blog is full of stories surrounding games, their development, and the challenges they present to emulate them. And in these stories, we sometimes have some recurring characters that we gain a better understanding of over time. Factor 5 and their Star Wars: Rogue Squadron games continue to amaze us time and time again as we find different ways that they push the hardware to its limits. The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker uses many graphical tricks to create a timeless style, that surprise again in again with just how much care was put into every detail. And, of course the Metroid Prime series shows up often given its sensitivity to even subtle changes to emulation.
However, as with every story, there have to be villains as well. One such villain is the The Disney Trio of Destruction™. For years, users have awaited the final showdown with these games. And guess what? They're finally playable right now. But are these games truly villains? Or were they just misunderstood? In this report, we dive into The Disney Trio of Destruction™ once and for all to determine their true nature.
Not every returning character is a game. Sometimes we also have to deal with our own issues, such as Dual Core mode. It is constantly breaking games, disabled in many popular games by default, and the source of most crashes in Dolphin. But is Dual Core really a hack? Or is Dolphin simply doing something wrong. In this report, we'll dive into the history of Dual Core and make a change that was long overdue.
On top of all of this, several longstanding features in Dolphin also saw some major upgrades, and we'll also get to those throughout the Dolphin Progress Report. With that, let us begin.</description>
      <category>hardware</category>
      <category>audio</category>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <category>conference</category>
      <guid>https://dolphin-emu.org/blog/2025/09/16/dolphin-progress-report-release-2509/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Your” vs “My” in user interfaces</title>
      <link>https://adamsilver.io/blog/your-vs-my-in-user-interfaces/</link>
      <description>Adam Silver – interaction designer - London, UK</description>
      <category>amazon</category>
      <guid>https://adamsilver.io/blog/your-vs-my-in-user-interfaces/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FBI couldn't get my husband to decrypt his Tor nodes, so they told a judge he used his GRAPHICS DRIVER to access the "dark web" and jailed him PRE TRIAL for 3 years.</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/TOR/comments/1ni5drm/the_fbi_couldnt_get_my_husband_to_decrypt_his_tor/</link>
      <description>(Eastern District of Michigan - Detroit) My husband, Conrad Rockenhaus, is wrongly incarcerated in a county jail. I’m posting this here because...</description>
      <category>health</category>
      <category>linux</category>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/TOR/comments/1ni5drm/the_fbi_couldnt_get_my_husband_to_decrypt_his_tor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ctrl/tinycolor and 40+ NPM Packages Compromised - StepSecurity</title>
      <link>https://www.stepsecurity.io/blog/ctrl-tinycolor-and-40-npm-packages-compromised</link>
      <description>The popular @ctrl/tinycolor package with over 2 million weekly downloads has been compromised alongside 40+ other NPM packages in a sophisticated supply chain attack. The malware self-propagates across maintainer packages, harvests AWS/GCP/Azure credentials using TruffleHog, and establishes persistence through GitHub Actions backdoors - representing a major escalation in NPM ecosystem threats.</description>
      <category>nodejs</category>
      <category>cloud</category>
      <category>regex</category>
      <category>conference</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <guid>https://www.stepsecurity.io/blog/ctrl-tinycolor-and-40-npm-packages-compromised</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>William Gibson Reads Neuromancer</title>
      <link>http://bearcave.com/bookrev/neuromancer/neuromancer_audio.html</link>
      <description>The author Ray Bradbury is
one of the early science fiction authors that moved science fiction
into a literary form.  As a writer Bradbury constructs beautifully
written stories and novels.  Bradbury's writing is in stark contrast
to Bradbury as a speaker.  The first time I heard Ray Bradbury speak
was at the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) yearly conference
in Los Angeles in the 1980s.  Hearing Bradbury speak is an almost
painful experience.  The pictures that Bradbury can paint with the
written word seem to be entirely missing when Bradbury speaks.  He is
halting, awkward and does not seem to know where he wants to go
in his talk.</description>
      <category>audio</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <guid>http://bearcave.com/bookrev/neuromancer/neuromancer_audio.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Attack Turns Concert Into Facial Recognition Surveillance Experiment</title>
      <link>https://www.gadgetreview.com/massive-attack-turns-concert-into-facial-recognition-surveillance-experiment</link>
      <description>Massive Attack used live facial recognition technology on concertgoers, turning surveillance into provocative art that sparked debate about privacy.</description>
      <guid>https://www.gadgetreview.com/massive-attack-turns-concert-into-facial-recognition-surveillance-experiment</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 09:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The awe keeps dropping</title>
      <link>https://morrick.me/archives/10137</link>
      <description>A reaction and assorted observations about Apple's September 9 Awe-Dropping event.</description>
      <category>hardware</category>
      <category>marketing</category>
      <category>apple</category>
      <guid>https://morrick.me/archives/10137</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 08:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux phones are more important now than ever. - feddit.org</title>
      <link>https://feddit.org/post/18353777</link>
      <description>## E: apparently it needs to be said that I am not suggesting you switch to
Linux on your phone today; just that development needs to accelerate. Please
don’t be one of the 34 people that replied to tell me Linux is not ready.
Android has always been a fairly open platform, especially if you were
deliberate about getting it that way, but we’ve seen in recent months an
extremely rapid devolution of the Android ecosystem: 1. The closing of
development of an increasing number of components in AOSP.
[https://9to5google.com/2025/03/26/google-android-aosp-developement-private/] 2.
Samsung [https://trendslife.in/samsung-one-ui-removed-bootloader-unlock/],
Xiaomi
[https://droidwin.com/xiaomi-might-no-longer-allow-bootloader-unlocking-on-miui/]
and OnePlus [https://droidwin.com/now-oneplus-restricts-bootloader-unlocking/]
have removed the option of bootloader unlocking on all of their devices. I
suspect Google is not far behind. 3. Google implementing Play Integrity API and
encouraging developers to implement it. Notably the EU’s own identity
verification wallet requires this, in stark contrast to their own laws and
policies, despite the protest of hundreds on Github. 4. And finally, the
mandatory implementation of developer verification across Android systems. Yes,
if you’re running a 3rd-party OS like GOS you won’t be directly affected by
this, but it will impact 99.9% of devices, and I foresee many open source
developers just opting out of developing apps for Android entirely as a result.
We’ve already seen SyncThing simply discontinue development
[https://forum.syncthing.net/t/discontinuing-syncthing-android/23002] for this
reason, citing issues with Google Play Store. They’ve also repeatedly denied
updates for NextCloud with no explanation, only restoring it after mass outcry.
And we’ve already seen Google targeting any software intended to circumvent ads,
labeling them in the system as “dangerous” and “untrusted”. This will most
certainly carry into their new “verification” system. Google once competed with
Apple for customers. But in a world where Google walks away from the biggest
antitrust trial since 1998 with yet another slap on the wrist, competition is
dead, and Google is taking notes from Apple about what they can legally get away
with. Android as we know it is dead. And/or will be dead very soon. We need an
open replacement.</description>
      <category>linux</category>
      <guid>https://feddit.org/post/18353777</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 05:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React Won by Default – And It's Killing Frontend Innovation | Loren Stewart</title>
      <link>https://www.lorenstew.art/blog/react-won-by-default/</link>
      <description>Exploring how React's dominance by default stifles frontend innovation, and why deliberate framework choices lead to better tools for performance, developer experience, and ecosystem diversity.</description>
      <category>svelte</category>
      <category>health</category>
      <category>compilers</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://www.lorenstew.art/blog/react-won-by-default/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 02:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's New in C# 14: Null-Conditional Assignments</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivankahl.com/csharp-14-null-conditional-assignments/</link>
      <description>C# 14, coming with .NET 10, introduces null-conditional assignment, a feature that lets you safely assign values to properties or indexers without endless if statements. Learn more about this new feature in this article.</description>
      <category>compilers</category>
      <guid>https://blog.ivankahl.com/csharp-14-null-conditional-assignments/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unit Test Isolation using MVCC</title>
      <link>https://blog.alexsanjoseph.com/posts/20250913-improving-pytest-with-mvcc/</link>
      <description>Pasting random things together</description>
      <category>sql</category>
      <category>git</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://blog.alexsanjoseph.com/posts/20250913-improving-pytest-with-mvcc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fetch streams are great, but not for measuring upload/downloading progress</title>
      <link>https://jakearchibald.com/2025/fetch-streams-not-for-progress/</link>
      <description>They're inaccurate, and there are better ways.</description>
      <guid>https://jakearchibald.com/2025/fetch-streams-not-for-progress/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trying to play "Guess Who" with an LLM</title>
      <link>https://www.zansara.dev/posts/2025-09-15-playing-guess-who-with-an-llm/</link>
      <description>I expected a different kind of fun.</description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <category>amazon</category>
      <guid>https://www.zansara.dev/posts/2025-09-15-playing-guess-who-with-an-llm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why RJs Are Dying: An Analysis of AI Job Displacement in Media</title>
      <link>https://www.unvritt.com/story/why-radio-jockeys-are-dying-djkax/view</link>
      <description>A forensic-grade analysis of how AI voice technology, venture capital, and economic pressures are systematically displacing radio jockeys and other voice professionals. Understand the displacement curve and its implications for the future of creative work.</description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://www.unvritt.com/story/why-radio-jockeys-are-dying-djkax/view</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray Tracing in JAX - Kaylee George</title>
      <link>https://kayleegeorge.github.io/blog/jax-ray-tracer/</link>
      <description>personal website</description>
      <category>rust</category>
      <category>compilers</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>git</category>
      <category>math</category>
      <guid>https://kayleegeorge.github.io/blog/jax-ray-tracer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making family IT support effortless (and free)</title>
      <link>https://garrit.xyz/posts/2025-09-15-making-family-it-support-effortless-and-free</link>
      <description>Generalist software developer writing about scalable infrastructure, fullstack development and DevOps practices.</description>
      <category>rust</category>
      <guid>https://garrit.xyz/posts/2025-09-15-making-family-it-support-effortless-and-free</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Monitors in X11 and i3</title>
      <link>https://mil.ad/blog/2025/virtual-monitor-x11.html</link>
      <description>I finally made the switch from X11/i3 to Wayland/Sway, and things are, for the most part, better on Wayland. I’ve managed to replicate almost everything from my setup, albeit with different tools, but there are exceptions and I thought I’d write about one that I have not managed to replicate on Sway.</description>
      <category>html</category>
      <guid>https://mil.ad/blog/2025/virtual-monitor-x11.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revocation ain't no thang.</title>
      <link>https://dadrian.io/blog/posts/revocation-aint-no-thang</link>
      <description>Adam Langley wrote about how revocation in the Web PKI doesn’t work over 10 years ago. Since then, the Web PKI has drastically changed for the better, despite not appearing to “solve” revocation. Unfortunately, many people interpret Adam’s post to mean “we must build a better revocation system for the Web PKI, today”. In reality, revocation does not make sense to solve anymore, and people should stop trying to solve it directly, because the actual solution to revocation in the public Web PKI is short-lived certificates.</description>
      <guid>https://dadrian.io/blog/posts/revocation-aint-no-thang</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In response to a developer asking about systems</title>
      <link>https://notes.eatonphil.com/2025-09-15-what-is-systems-and-how-do-i-learn.html</link>
      <description>In response to a developer asking about systems</description>
      <category>sql</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <guid>https://notes.eatonphil.com/2025-09-15-what-is-systems-and-how-do-i-learn.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning up my $HOME with XDG Base Directory Specification</title>
      <link>https://evgeniipendragon.com/posts/cleaning-up-my-home-with-xdg-base-directory-specification/</link>
      <description>In my career I worked with plenty of different software that require the presence of certain environment variables for them to function properly. From time to time I would notice that the program either offers it as an option or requires you to have XDG_... type variable be set in your environment. I never looked too deeply into it, however I understood that it provided base paths for the locations of configuration and application files. I simply never tried to understand what those variables are and why they begin with XDG. Recently, I have stumbed upon several software configurations where I have encountered XDG variables again. So, I decided to look it up and find out what all of that was about.</description>
      <category>linux</category>
      <guid>https://evgeniipendragon.com/posts/cleaning-up-my-home-with-xdg-base-directory-specification/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Only Way to Build Trust Is to Give Trust</title>
      <link>https://www.davidpoll.com/2025/09/the-only-way-to-build-trust-is-to-give-trust/</link>
      <description>A former report reached out recently. It was one of those unexpected messages that stops you mid-scroll, the kind that makes you put your phone down and actually think.They wanted me to know I’d be...</description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>apple</category>
      <category>math</category>
      <guid>https://www.davidpoll.com/2025/09/the-only-way-to-build-trust-is-to-give-trust/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Opus and o3 saved me from permanent blindness</title>
      <link>https://mmaaz.ca/writings/blindness.html</link>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I suddenly started going blind in my left eye. Yes, really. If I closed my right eye, about 80% of my vision was dark grey or black. I couldn't see my own hand in front of my face! Thankfully, Opus and o3 (I'll just refer to them as AI; all queries were sent to one or both, and distinguishing between them is not important to the story) massively helped me, and, I believe, essentially saved me from it becoming a permanent issue. Eventually, I was diagnosed with a rare autoimmune disease called MOG-associated disease (MOGAD). I'm not sure what this looks like going forward. But, here, I'd like to tell my story. This is part medical case study, part personal story, and part AI capabilities demonstration.</description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://mmaaz.ca/writings/blindness.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coders End, From Typers To Thinkers | etsd.tech</title>
      <link>https://etsd.tech/posts/coders-end/</link>
      <description>Typing the code was never the point. Thinking the code is. An exciting future for anyone who understands where their real value lies.</description>
      <category>math</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://etsd.tech/posts/coders-end/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backgrounds Are Important</title>
      <link>https://leejo.github.io/2025/09/15/backgrounds/</link>
      <description>Backgrounds Are Important</description>
      <category>audio</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>youtube</category>
      <guid>https://leejo.github.io/2025/09/15/backgrounds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Slotted Hash Cons for Alpha Invariance</title>
      <link>https://www.philipzucker.com/slotted_hash_cons/</link>
      <description>Slotted e-graphs https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3729326 are a data structure that compactly stores many equivalent terms in an alpha invariant aware way. I’ve been very excited by them but also very confused by them.</description>
      <category>wiki</category>
      <category>nodejs</category>
      <guid>https://www.philipzucker.com/slotted_hash_cons/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inline Notes</title>
      <link>https://keystonebit.com/posts/inline-notes</link>
      <description>Inline notes are an alternative to footnotes. When you click on a highlighted phrase, you get the inline note added to the paragraph right after the phrase.</description>
      <category>css</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <guid>https://keystonebit.com/posts/inline-notes</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring What Matters</title>
      <link>https://www.alnewkirk.com/measuring-what-matters/</link>
      <description>Most people-performance metrics are noise. Lines of code, story points, "impact" — all distort reality. The fairer measure is simple: clear commitments made and fulfilled. Stop tracking proxies and start measuring what actually matters.</description>
      <guid>https://www.alnewkirk.com/measuring-what-matters/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Am Trapped In Insta-Purgatory With No Recourse</title>
      <link>http://blog.mjb.me.uk/2025/09/i-am-trapped-in-insta-purgatory-with-no.html</link>
      <description>How Insta Has Persisted  Of all the social media platforms that came during my youth, Instagram has been the most persistent. It has managed...</description>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>http://blog.mjb.me.uk/2025/09/i-am-trapped-in-insta-purgatory-with-no.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argumentum ad colossum</title>
      <link>https://chrisdone.com/posts/argumentum-ad-colossum/</link>
      <description>I’m coining a new phrase to use for discussion purposes:
argumentum ad colossum.</description>
      <category>containers</category>
      <category>amazon</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <guid>https://chrisdone.com/posts/argumentum-ad-colossum/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adios Chicos, 25 Years of KDE – Jonathan Riddell's Diary</title>
      <link>https://jriddell.org/2025/09/14/adios-chicos-25-years-of-kde/</link>
      <description>It was the turn of the millenium when I got my first computer fresh at university.  Windows seemed uninteresting, it was impossible to work out how it worked or write programs for it.  SuSE Linux 6.2 was much more interesting to try and opened a world of understanding how computers worked and wanting to code on them.  These were the days of the .com boom and I went to big expos in London where they showered you with freebies and IBM competed with SuSE and Red Hat for the biggest stall.  IBM said that Linux had made it on the server and now was going to take over the desktop so I realised that working with KDE would be a good idea.  And as a novice coder it was very perfect for learning Qt and how open development worked and I loved the free software ideals.  Going to the pre-Akademy conference (it was called Kastle then) in Nove Hrady was a great intro to the community in person and in some ways I learnt more about software development in a week there then my years at uni.</description>
      <category>linux</category>
      <guid>https://jriddell.org/2025/09/14/adios-chicos-25-years-of-kde/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OS - macOS Tahoe</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/os/macos/</link>
      <description>macOS Tahoe with a new design, more ways to work seamlessly across devices, and new features to turbocharge productivity every day.</description>
      <category>audio</category>
      <category>apple</category>
      <category>gaming</category>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/os/macos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So You Want to Host Your Own LLM? Don’t.</title>
      <link>https://mahdiyusuf.com/so-you-want-to-host-your-own-llm-dont/</link>
      <description>Self-hosting LLMs is the new crypto mining—costly, wasteful, and outdated fast. Use a MacBook or APIs until home-scale AI truly arrives.</description>
      <category>hardware</category>
      <category>ai</category>
      <category>apple</category>
      <category>linux</category>
      <guid>https://mahdiyusuf.com/so-you-want-to-host-your-own-llm-dont/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cables Stuck Too Deep</title>
      <link>https://gardnermcintyre.com/cables</link>
      <description>I miss the days when I wondered what people did with their time.</description>
      <category>math</category>
      <guid>https://gardnermcintyre.com/cables</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 01:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wanted to spy on my dog, ended up spying on TP-Link</title>
      <link>https://kennedn.com/blog/posts/tapo/</link>
      <description></description>
      <category>audio</category>
      <category>amazon</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <guid>https://kennedn.com/blog/posts/tapo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 23:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.0 · asciinema blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.asciinema.org/post/three-point-o/</link>
      <description>News about asciinema development and new releases</description>
      <category>rust</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>linux</category>
      <guid>https://blog.asciinema.org/post/three-point-o/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal Ushers in a New Era of Peer-to-Peer Payments, Reimagining How Money Moves to Anyone, Anywhere - Sep 15, 2025</title>
      <link>https://newsroom.paypal-corp.com/2025-09-15-PayPal-Ushers-in-a-New-Era-of-Peer-to-Peer-Payments,-Reimagining-How-Money-Moves-to-Anyone,-Anywhere</link>
      <description>Send and receive money as easily as sending a text, across apps, borders, and currencies.</description>
      <category>cryptography</category>
      <guid>https://newsroom.paypal-corp.com/2025-09-15-PayPal-Ushers-in-a-New-Era-of-Peer-to-Peer-Payments,-Reimagining-How-Money-Moves-to-Anyone,-Anywhere</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&lt;City&gt;-Style Pizza</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3142/</link>
      <description></description>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3142/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>