<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Container &amp;amp; Data Lifetime with .NET Aspire</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ilYm4-QcbsA</link>
      <description>.NET Aspire 9 adds new control over the lifetime of containers on your local developer environment. Let&amp;#39;s look at how to manage them with the new APIs!

What&amp;#39;s new in .NET Aspire 9: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet/aspire/whats-new/dotnet-aspire-9 
Container Resource Lifetimes: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet/aspire/fundamentals/app-host-overview?tabs=docker#container-resource-lifecycle 
Persisting Data with Volumes: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet/aspire/fundamentals/persist-data-volumes 
New Dashboard Features: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet/aspire/fundamentals/dashboard/explore#resource-actions 
.NET Aspire Docs: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet/aspire 
.NET Aspire Learning Path: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/paths/dotnet-aspire/ 

Chapters:
00:00 - Introduction &amp;amp; project walkthrough
01:20 - New .NET Aspire dashboard features
02:00 - Persisting containers lifetime
03:40 - Working with volumes in .NET Aspire
05:40 - Working with data bind mounts
07:00 - Wrap-up


Connect with .NET: 
Blog:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/blog
Twitter: https://aka.ms/dotnet/twitter
TikTok:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/tiktok
Mastodon:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/mastodon
LinkedIn:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/linkedin
Facebook:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/facebook
Docs: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet
Forums: https://aka.ms/dotnet/forums
&amp;#128587;‍♀️Q&amp;amp;A: https://aka.ms/dotnet-qa
&amp;#128104;‍&amp;#127891;Microsoft Learn: https://aka.ms/learndotnet

#dotnet #dotnetaspire #containers</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ilYm4-QcbsA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI generated code accelerates technical debt</title>
      <link>https://leaddev.com/software-quality/how-ai-generated-code-accelerates-technical-debt</link>
      <description>GitClear’s latest report exposes rising code duplication and declining quality as AI coding tools gain in popularity.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://leaddev.com/software-quality/how-ai-generated-code-accelerates-technical-debt</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI App Builders - Take 2 - Lovable - Nick&amp;#39;s .NET Travels</title>
      <link>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/ai-app-builders-take-2-lovable/</link>
      <description>Following from my previous attempt at building a simple app to retrieve the ABN for a business, I figured I’d give lovable.dev a go. This will be a quick post to cover some of the likes/dislikes from this process. Firstly I have to hand it to Lovable, they’ve done a great job with the user ... Read more</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nicksnettravels.builttoroam.com/ai-app-builders-take-2-lovable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform Workflow: Plan It, Build It, Rule the Cloud - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/terraform-workflow-plan-it-build-it-rule-the-cloud/</link>
      <description>If you’ve ever tried assembling IKEA furniture without looking at the instructions (we’ve all been there), you know how chaotic it can get. Terraform is no different—if you don’t follow the right workflow, you’ll end up with a cloud mess instead of a well-structured infrastructure. Thankfully, Terraform has a straightforward workflow that helps you move from defining your infrastructure to deploying it seamlessly. In this post, we’ll break down the key steps of the Terraform workflow and how to use them like a pro!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/terraform-workflow-plan-it-build-it-rule-the-cloud/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 13:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consuming private Swift Packages in GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://blog.ostebaronen.dk/2025/02/consuming-private-swift-packages-in-gh-actions.html</link>
      <description>I had a case for a native App we are working on where we already have some Swift Packages in Azure DevOps Repos, which we would like to consume in a project that lives in GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ostebaronen.dk/2025/02/consuming-private-swift-packages-in-gh-actions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear fusion: WEST beats the world record for plasma duration!</title>
      <link>https://www.cea.fr/english/Pages/News/nuclear-fusion-west-beats-the-world-record-for-plasma-duration.aspx</link>
      <description>​On 12 February, the CEA’s WEST machine was able to maintain a plasma for more than 22 minutes. In doing so, it smashed the previous record for plasma duration achieved with a tokamak. This leap forward demonstrates how our knowledge of plasmas and technological control of them over longer periods is becoming more mature, and offers hope that fusion plasmas can be stabilised for greater amounts of time in machines such as ITER.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cea.fr/english/Pages/News/nuclear-fusion-west-beats-the-world-record-for-plasma-duration.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 05:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XOR</title>
      <link>https://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/quasiblog/xor/</link>
      <description>[Simon Tatham, 2025-02-14]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/quasiblog/xor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 02:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I&amp;#39;m Writing a Scheme Implementation in 2025 (The Answer is Async Rust)</title>
      <link>https://maplant.com/2025-02-17-Why-I'm-Writing-a-Scheme-Implementation-in-2025-(The-Answer-is-Async-Rust).html</link>
      <description>This blog post is an introduction to scheme-rs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://maplant.com/2025-02-17-Why-I'm-Writing-a-Scheme-Implementation-in-2025-(The-Answer-is-Async-Rust).html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 01:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why prehistory is fascinating me so much</title>
      <link>https://michelenasti.com/2024/prehistory/</link>
      <description>There is something that I am very curious about, let&amp;#39;s say I am a nerd about: prehistory.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://michelenasti.com/2024/prehistory/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming principles as memes - Code with Jason</title>
      <link>https://www.codewithjason.com/programming-principles-as-memes/</link>
      <description>In 1976 in The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins explained that the unit of selection for evolution is not the group or species or individual but the gene. Genes that are best at causing themselves to get replicated are the ones that do get replicated, and so those genes then become predominant. An organism’s body is […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.codewithjason.com/programming-principles-as-memes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLite is learnable</title>
      <link>https://hiandrewquinn.github.io/til-site/posts/the-learnability-of-sqlite/</link>
      <description>This is a response to pid1.call’s “Siren Call of SQlite on the Server”, which itself is a response to articles like Wesley Aptekar-Cassels’s “Consider SQLite” espousing SQLite as a server-side technology. Cards on the table, I both love SQLite and think pid1 has the more correct take here.
When I decided on a dime after college to move countries and be with my wife, part of the package deal was that I had to throw away my dreams of easing into the software industry by resting on the laurels of my strong, but not MIT-level-known-worldwide-strong, alma mater (sorry Wildcats).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hiandrewquinn.github.io/til-site/posts/the-learnability-of-sqlite/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To attach headers to Cloudflare Pages responses</title>
      <link>https://chrisding.xyz/posts/to-attach-headers-to-cloudflare-pages-responses</link>
      <description>Adding header to Cloudflare Pages: enabling CORS, disabling search engine indexing for pages.dev, and applying security configurations.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chrisding.xyz/posts/to-attach-headers-to-cloudflare-pages-responses</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can I ethically use LLMs?</title>
      <link>https://ntietz.com/blog/can-i-ethically-use-llms/</link>
      <description>The title is not a rhetorical question, and I&amp;#39;m not going to bury an answer.
I don&amp;#39;t have an answer.
This post is my exploration of the question, and why I think it is a question1.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ntietz.com/blog/can-i-ethically-use-llms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaDA: LLMs That Don&amp;#39;t Gaslight You</title>
      <link>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2025/02/17/diffusion</link>
      <description>A new language model uses diffusion instead of next-token prediction. That means the text it can back out of a hallucination before it commits. This is a big win for areas like law &amp;amp; contracts, where global consistency is valued</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://timkellogg.me/blog/2025/02/17/diffusion</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My LLM codegen workflow atm</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2025/02/16/my-llm-codegen-workflow-atm/</link>
      <description>A detailed walkthrough of my current workflow for using LLms to build software, from brainstorming through planning and execution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2025/02/16/my-llm-codegen-workflow-atm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A year of uv: pros, cons, and should you migrate</title>
      <link>https://www.bitecode.dev/p/a-year-of-uv-pros-cons-and-should</link>
      <description>Yes, probably.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.bitecode.dev/p/a-year-of-uv-pros-cons-and-should</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Append-only programming</title>
      <link>https://iafisher.com/blog/2024/08/append-only-programming</link>
      <description>A tongue-in-cheek way to write software.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iafisher.com/blog/2024/08/append-only-programming</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoHo IPv6 in 2025 ... still dicey</title>
      <link>https://herczegzsolt.hu/posts/soho-ipv6-in-2025-still-dicey/</link>
      <description>My home internet provider offers native IPv6 connectivity by default, which I’ve been using for many years. It was never a perfect experience, but as more software adopts IPv6, the more issues I started having. I’ve developed habits like repeatedly refreshing websites, toggling the WiFi on’n’off or aborting SSH just to retry with the -4 flag. Less patient users already disabled IPv6 on their devices. It’s been time to stabilize my IPv6 setup or disable it completely.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://herczegzsolt.hu/posts/soho-ipv6-in-2025-still-dicey/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Just a Tool” and Other Stories — Natalia Ilyin</title>
      <link>http://www.nataliailyin.net/blog/2025/2/6/ai-is-just-a-tool-and-other-stories</link>
      <description>Ever one to hope for the best, last semester I suggested that students use ChatGPT as a “research partner” in the big bibliographic project they do in the Fall term of  Parallel Narratives , their Junior-level history-and-criticism class. In a 27-person class, only one student took me up on the idea</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.nataliailyin.net/blog/2025/2/6/ai-is-just-a-tool-and-other-stories</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kafka at the low end: how bad can it get?</title>
      <link>https://broot.ca/kafka-at-the-low-end.html</link>
      <description>There is oft-quoted advice that Kafka does poorly as a job queue. I’ve experienced
this myself, and I wanted to formalize it a bit.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://broot.ca/kafka-at-the-low-end.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything I&amp;#39;ve Learned from Figgie</title>
      <link>https://dj.theory-a.com/writing/figgie-lesson</link>
      <description>Figgie is a free Jane Street developed game that aims to teach intuition about trading. Although I don&amp;#39;t consider myself a trader I&amp;#39;ve always been curious and wanted to develop an intuition around it.  Here are a few takeaways that I&amp;#39;ve viscerally felt from playing the game for a few hours:1/ The difficulty in drawing out the marginal seller informs the rarity. If you have to increasing up your bid without and takers it means that everyone is hoarding. Your edge needs to be larger than the premium necessary to pry it from the crowd.2/ Likewise, when you have to constantly drop your bid to draw out the marginal buyer it means the suit is discounted. The buyer is usually gambling or hedging. There isn&amp;#39;t much information in these trades.3/ Alpha exists in having a earlier and clearer idea of reality than everyone else. It exhibits itself in being able to buy at cheap prices when the trading revolves around hedging. 4/ Alpha evaporates as you use it and coalesces into a clearer market picture. As the trading starts to revolve around the goal card instead of hedging, you have less and less alpha because the prices now reflect the reality you had early-access to.5/ Alpha efficiency is the ratio of value gained vs information leaked in the trade. The most efficient trades work with noisy crowd movements vs standing out from the crowd.6/ Price appreciation due to markets approaching truth is not reversible because truth is not reversible. 7/ Pure signal does not exist, every signal is probabilistic.8/ Humans need to work with the models because a lot of the game is modeling humans and how humans model humans and models.9/ You can&amp;#39;t really calculate EV fast enough to act on market offers and bids. Often you have an intuition around buy/sell have to use the last executed price as an anchor for fair value.10/ Uncertainty creates value around things that are not valuable. As clarity increases, the value of non-winners quickly drop to zero.11/ Market makers can be a win-win source of edge because they can actually price what hoarders value at infinity.12/ The best deals are from people who started off lucky because they have negative information about the real world. For example, they might think something is very common when it is rare and so sell it cheaply. (This is how many locals make money off of American tourists who are abundant with dollars)13/ Market close creates fire sale opportunities.14/ Creating false markets is very expensive and is similar to a 51% attack on market truth seeking.15/ Where you start informs your strategy. Sometimes you have alpha sometimes you do not. Sometimes all you can do is minimize losses and wait for the next round.16/ The two main situations seem to be either inventory averse or inventory tolerant. The only time you actually like inventory is when you have enough edge to act as an Oracle.18/ Even when you think you have alpha, you have to size appropriately due to tail risks.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dj.theory-a.com/writing/figgie-lesson</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ideal Candidate Will Be Punched In the Stomach</title>
      <link>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/ideal-candidate/</link>
      <description>The description suggests that this is some kind of extended metaphor about work. It appears to be written in that _Choose Your Own Adventure_ style second-person voice, yet there are no choices to be found within. Against your better judgment, you follow the link.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/ideal-candidate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direnv - and reinventing the wheel with envloader</title>
      <link>https://willwa.de/2025/02/18/direnv-and-reinventing-the-wheel.html</link>
      <description>I hate having to do this. But I have.
I’ve made ANOTHER tool to load up your env vars in a terminal. Why? Because I had a mare getting direnv to work on my specific Windows machine. It was really due to the way our office locked down the way a users $PROFILE works - that is it puts everything on OneDrive and there was a ton of admin issues getting it all working correctly.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://willwa.de/2025/02/18/direnv-and-reinventing-the-wheel.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Care About Cost as Software Engineer?</title>
      <link>https://obrepalski.com/posts/why-care-about-cost/</link>
      <description>Cost optimisation has been one of my main focus areas for the past two years, and I’ve heard the same question come up multiple times: “Why should software engineers care about this?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://obrepalski.com/posts/why-care-about-cost/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This menu needs to die</title>
      <link>https://birchtree.me/blog/this-menu-needs-to-die/</link>
      <description>M.G. Siegler: The Great AI UI Unification

And depending on which model you choose to use, you get other options from there, as various buttons will be enabled in the message box for &amp;#39;Web Search&amp;#39; and now &amp;#39;Deep Research&amp;#39;. Oh and I forgot the &amp;#39;+&amp;#39; button, which has</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://birchtree.me/blog/this-menu-needs-to-die/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Toddler Mindset: Decision-Making Without Constraints | Writing by Vinay Gaba</title>
      <link>https://www.vinaygaba.me/writing/the-toddler-mindset/</link>
      <description>Most decisions at work and in life are made under a temporary set of constraints. We accept the world as it is, optimizing within limits that may not even be real. What if we approached decisions like a toddler—ignoring the rules, focusing on what’s possible, and bending reality to fit our goals?</description>
      <author> (Vinay Gaba)</author>
      <guid>https://www.vinaygaba.me/writing/the-toddler-mindset/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Digital Profiles and Avatars</title>
      <link>https://blog.anirudha.dev/decentralised-profile-standard</link>
      <description>Introducing ERC-7866: A Decentralised Profile Standard.</description>
      <author> (https://hashnode.com/@anirudha)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.anirudha.dev/decentralised-profile-standard</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Processing Lines of Output in a Loop with Your Shell Can Be Slow — Nick Janetakis</title>
      <link>https://nickjanetakis.com/blog/processing-lines-of-output-in-a-loop-with-your-shell-can-be-slow</link>
      <description>I ended up rewriting a tool from Bash to Python and one reason for that was processing lines of output in a loop was slow.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nickjanetakis.com/blog/processing-lines-of-output-in-a-loop-with-your-shell-can-be-slow</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Deep Research problem — Benedict Evans</title>
      <link>https://www.ben-evans.com/benedictevans/2025/2/17/the-deep-research-problem</link>
      <description>OpenAI’s Deep Research is built for me, and I can’t use it. It’s another amazing demo, until it breaks. But it breaks in really interesting ways.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ben-evans.com/benedictevans/2025/2/17/the-deep-research-problem</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating compound words for artificial languages</title>
      <link>https://joshuatanner.dev/blog/posts/blog-vocabulary-optimization/</link>
      <description>One of the things that struck me about learning Japanese is that once you know a decent number of kanji, there are a lot of words you can read and understand without ever having seen before. This is because kanji often convey specific meanings: the word for building (建物) is build+thing, confidence (自信) is self+believe, etc. In some cases you can even guess the kanji of a word you hear for the first time, and get to its meaning that way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joshuatanner.dev/blog/posts/blog-vocabulary-optimization/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect is the friend of&amp;#160;never – Jakub Stasiak&amp;#39;s Website</title>
      <link>https://stasiak.at/20250210-perfect-is-the-friend-of-never.html</link>
      <description>I read this article recently: “VSCode’s SSH Agent Is Bananas” by Thomas Ptacek.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stasiak.at/20250210-perfect-is-the-friend-of-never.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How xAI made the world largest GPU cluster operational in 122 days — Kasper Junge</title>
      <link>http://blog.kasperjunge.com/posts/2025/how-xai-made-the-world-largest-gpu-cluster-operational-in-122-days/</link>
      <description>In the Grok 3 launch video at 1:00:05, Elon Musk explains how xAI was able to make the world’s largest GPU cluster operational in 122 days.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://blog.kasperjunge.com/posts/2025/how-xai-made-the-world-largest-gpu-cluster-operational-in-122-days/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing type inference for high quality type errors</title>
      <link>https://blog.polybdenum.com/2025/02/14/designing-type-inference-for-high-quality-type-errors.html</link>
      <description>Type inference has a reputation for causing unhelpful error messages from the compiler when there is a type error. For example, here’s a typical comment:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.polybdenum.com/2025/02/14/designing-type-inference-for-high-quality-type-errors.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Engineer&amp;#39;s Proclivity for Perfection</title>
      <link>https://patrickprunty.com/blog/the-engineers-proclivity-for-perfection</link>
      <description>Or why it&amp;#39;ll never be perfect—let alone &amp;quot;done&amp;quot;.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://patrickprunty.com/blog/the-engineers-proclivity-for-perfection</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;ll give up Neovim when you pry it from my cold, dead hands</title>
      <link>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2025/02/18/ill_give_up_neovim_when_you_pry_it_from_my_cold_dead_hands/</link>
      <description>I recently came upon a horror story where a developer was forced to switch editor from Neovim to Cursor
and I felt I had to write a little to cleanse myself of the disgust I felt.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jonashietala.se/blog/2025/02/18/ill_give_up_neovim_when_you_pry_it_from_my_cold_dead_hands/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t call yourself a senior until you&amp;#39;ve worked on a legacy project</title>
      <link>https://www.infobip.com/developers/blog/seniors-working-on-a-legacy-project</link>
      <description>Everybody hates working on legacy projects, me as well. Working on one, however, helped me get a deeper understanding of the dev process.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.infobip.com/developers/blog/seniors-working-on-a-legacy-project</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 23:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Pi-hole v6 – Pi-hole</title>
      <link>https://pi-hole.net/blog/2025/02/18/introducing-pi-hole-v6/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pi-hole.net/blog/2025/02/18/introducing-pi-hole-v6/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 23:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving on from 18F. —&amp;#160;ethanmarcotte.com</title>
      <link>https://ethanmarcotte.com/wrote/leaving-18f/</link>
      <description>I had a wonderful job, until I didn’t. This is about what happened—and what is happening.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ethanmarcotte.com/wrote/leaving-18f/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 22:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Team Fortress 2 SDK &amp;#183; ValveSoftware/source-sdk-2013@0759e2e</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ValveSoftware/source-sdk-2013/commit/0759e2e8e179d5352d81d0d4aaded72c1704b7a9</link>
      <description>The 2013 edition of the Source SDK. Contribute to ValveSoftware/source-sdk-2013 development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ValveSoftware/source-sdk-2013/commit/0759e2e8e179d5352d81d0d4aaded72c1704b7a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 21:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scripton Python IDE</title>
      <link>https://scripton.dev/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scripton.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 20:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Blog</title>
      <link>https://nestenius.se/hardware/test-blog/</link>
      <description>Proxies are vital for load balancing and security, but they obscure the actual client IP, scheme, and domain, causing broken links, inaccurate logging, and other headaches. In this post, we’ll look at how ASP.NET Core’s Forwarded Headers Middleware restores these details so your services behave as though they’re directly on the public internet. What is […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nestenius.se/hardware/test-blog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 18:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Generative AI Con</title>
      <link>https://www.wheresyoured.at/longcon/</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s been just over two years and two months since ChatGPT launched, and in that time we&amp;#39;ve seen Large Language Models (LLMs) blossom from a novel concept into one of the most craven cons of the 21st century — a cynical bubble inflated by OpenAI CEO Sam Altman built to sell</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.wheresyoured.at/longcon/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 17:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;m glad AI didn&amp;#39;t exist when I learned to code</title>
      <link>https://blog.shivs.me/im-glad-ai-didnt-exist-when-i-learned-to-code</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m glad AI didn&amp;#39;t exist when I learned to code</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.shivs.me/im-glad-ai-didnt-exist-when-i-learned-to-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 17:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C#, Tests, Playwright, and CHAOS!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=WFQSdP0osNw</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Let&amp;#39;s work on SharpSite, an open source CMS that you can contribute to and learn from.  https://sharpsite.org</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=WFQSdP0osNw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 16:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>