<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Code It Any Way You Want: Constant vs Read-Only Property</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/03/29/code-it-any-way-you-want-constant-vs-read-only-property/</link>
      <description>This article demonstrates the performance of using a public constant versus a read-only property.</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/03/29/code-it-any-way-you-want-constant-vs-read-only-property/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 09:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Software Architecture for .NET 8 and C# 12 - Coding Sonata</title>
      <link>https://codingsonata.com/book-review-software-architecture-for-dotnet-8/</link>
      <description>This is an in-depth review on book: Software Architecture for .NET 8 and C# 12, Co-authored by Gabriel Baptista and Francesco Abbruzzese.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/aram1987)</author>
      <guid>https://codingsonata.com/book-review-software-architecture-for-dotnet-8/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 08:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The race to replace Redis</title>
      <link>https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/966631/6bf2063136effa1e/</link>
      <description>On March 21, Redis Ltd. announced that the Redis &amp;quot;in-memory data store&amp;quot; project would now be
released under non-free, source-available licenses, starting with Redis 7.4. The
news is unwelcome, but not entirely unexpected. What is unusual with this situation is
the number of Redis alternatives to choose from; there are at least
four options to choose as a replacement for those who wish to stay
with free software, including a pre-existing fork called KeyDB and the Linux Foundation&amp;#39;s newly-announced Valkey project. The question now is which one(s)
Linux distributions, users, and providers will choose to take its place.</description>
      <author> (By Joe BrockmeierMarch 28, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://lwn.net/SubscriberLink/966631/6bf2063136effa1e/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 06:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matter and Privacy</title>
      <link>https://seancoates.com/blogs/matter-and-privacy</link>
      <description>When I was still working at Faculty, we took on a new client that was not yet named Matter. We eventually transitioned from an agency-client relationship to a startup relationship, where I became the </description>
      <author> (Sean Coates)</author>
      <guid>https://seancoates.com/blogs/matter-and-privacy</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 02:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI21 Labs Unveils Jamba: The First Production-Grade Mamba-Based AI Model</title>
      <link>https://www.maginative.com/article/ai21-labs-unveils-jamba-the-first-production-grade-mamba-based-ai-model/</link>
      <description>Jamba is a groundbreaking SSM-Transformer model that offers the best of both worlds, addressing the drawbacks of traditional Transformer architectures while maintaining their powerful capabilities.</description>
      <author> (Richard Banfield)</author>
      <guid>https://www.maginative.com/article/ai21-labs-unveils-jamba-the-first-production-grade-mamba-based-ai-model/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 01:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keynes was wrong because he failed to consider class conflict – William Mitchell – Modern Monetary Theory</title>
      <link>https://billmitchell.org/blog/?p=61635</link>
      <description>I was asked during an interview the other day from Paris whether I was a Post Keynesian. I replied not at all and explained that I have never felt that my ideas fit into that category although in a facile sense we are all post keynesian in a temporal sense. Most progressive economists would answer yes if confronted with that question, even most of the economists involved in advancing Modern Monetary Theory (MMT). My point of departure is that while there was a lot of important analytical material in Keynes’ writing that is worth preserving and integrating into, say, MMT, where Keynes went astray was his antipathy to the insights provided by Karl Marx. In particular, I consider that Keynes seriously misunderstood what the dynamics of the class conflict were within a capitalist mode of production. Keynes made major errors in his predictions that one can directly attribute to this blinkered approach to capitalism. I was reminded of this when I read an Op Ed in the Japan Times this week (March 10, 2024) – The economic future of our overworked grandchildren. This blinkered approach, which has fed into the modern Post Keynesian literature – which examines capitalism as if it is an ahistorical, neutral system of production and distribution – is a major reason that I do not associate my work with that school of thought.</description>
      <author> (bill)</author>
      <guid>https://billmitchell.org/blog/?p=61635</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elevating Bacalhau with NATS.io: Simplifying Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://blog.bacalhau.org/p/elevating-bacalhau-with-natsio-simplifying</link>
      <description>5 Days of Bacalhau</description>
      <author> (Walid Baruni)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.bacalhau.org/p/elevating-bacalhau-with-natsio-simplifying</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>beautiful do-nothing scripts</title>
      <link>https://www.chrisyxlee.com/blog/beautiful-do-nothing-scripts/</link>
      <description>I want to show off demo screenshots and code snippets from a do-nothing script I wrote last year. &amp;#129402;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.chrisyxlee.com/blog/beautiful-do-nothing-scripts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A designer’s guide to loving the terminal — Alex Chan</title>
      <link>https://www.alexchantastic.com/designers-guide-to-the-terminal</link>
      <description>An introduction to the wonders of using the terminal as a designer.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.alexchantastic.com/designers-guide-to-the-terminal</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockchip NPU update 2: MobileNetV1 is done</title>
      <link>https://blog.tomeuvizoso.net/2024/03/rockchip-npu-update-2-mobilenetv1-is.html</link>
      <description>Progress For&amp;#160; the last couple of weeks I have kept chipping at a new userspace driver for the NPU in the Rockchip RK3588 SoC. I am very happ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.tomeuvizoso.net/2024/03/rockchip-npu-update-2-mobilenetv1-is.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom useFetch wrapper for Nuxt</title>
      <link>https://barish.me/blog/nuxt-usefetch/</link>
      <description>useFetch in Nuxt can be hard to customize since wrapping it manually loses type completion. Here&amp;#39;s how to do it correctly.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://barish.me/blog/nuxt-usefetch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8529 people have contributed to scikit-learn</title>
      <link>https://breadchris.com/blog/8529-people-have-contributed-to-scikit-learn/</link>
      <description>The code that scikit-learn comprises has been committed to by 8529+ people.
python/cpython - 2640
numpy/numpy - 1581
scipy/scipy - 1447
joblib/threadpoolctl - 10
scikit-learn/scikit-learn - 2837
It is possible that some of these people introduced typo changes, or the code they contributed has been rewritten by someone else. But the repo was affected by them, no less. Their accounts were authenticated to contribute to the history of a notable library in the ML training community.</description>
      <author> (breadchris)</author>
      <guid>https://breadchris.com/blog/8529-people-have-contributed-to-scikit-learn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turbo Native iOS and Android apps in 15 minutes | Masilotti.com</title>
      <link>https://masilotti.com/turbo-native-apps-in-15-minutes/</link>
      <description>A quick-start guide to building Turbo Native apps for Ruby on Rails developers, no Swift or Kotlin experience necessary.</description>
      <author> (Joe Masilotti)</author>
      <guid>https://masilotti.com/turbo-native-apps-in-15-minutes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Problem With Goals</title>
      <link>https://www.chiefrabbit.com/p/the-problem-with-goals</link>
      <description>Goals are good for setting a direction, for giving you something to achieve. But systems are how you make progress. Goals are for the future. Systems give you something actionable and satisfying to do in the present.</description>
      <author> (Derek Pharr)</author>
      <guid>https://www.chiefrabbit.com/p/the-problem-with-goals</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Ruby on Rails OOM Mystery: The Case of the Hungry Hippo | Prefab</title>
      <link>https://prefab.cloud/blog/rails-oom-killed/</link>
      <description>Explore the interaction of rails, puma, workers and kubernetes as we track down some 137 oomkilled kubernetes errors</description>
      <author> (Jeff DwyerPrefab Founder &amp;amp; Engineer)</author>
      <guid>https://prefab.cloud/blog/rails-oom-killed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers: Stop Donating Your Work to Cloud Service Providers! | TDengine</title>
      <link>https://tdengine.com/developers-stop-donating-your-work/</link>
      <description>In the war for software freedom, the greatest enemy is no longer proprietary software but cloud service providers.</description>
      <author> (Jeff)</author>
      <guid>https://tdengine.com/developers-stop-donating-your-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operating an Entire Company on a Minimal Two-Core PostgreSQL Instance: Index Tuning, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://robertrode.com/2024/03/28/operating-an-entire-company-on-a-minimal-two-core-postgresql-instance-index-tuning-part-2.html</link>
      <description>Optimizing PostgreSQL is a relevant and controversial topic (&amp;quot;How much resources should I invest in optimization vs. hardware?&amp;quot;): The first part of the series, &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://robertrode.com/2023/11/15/operating-an-entire-company-on-a-minimal-two-core-postgresql-instance-query-optimization-insights-part-1.html&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;Query Optimization Insights&amp;quot;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, made it to the top 4 posts on &amp;lt;a ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robertrode.com/2024/03/28/operating-an-entire-company-on-a-minimal-two-core-postgresql-instance-index-tuning-part-2.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a competitor analysis tool using ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://brianchristner.io/how-to-build-a-competitor-analysis-tool-using-chatgpt/</link>
      <description>Discover how to effortlessly track competitors with a no-code tool combining Gmail, Google Sheets, ChatGPT, and Zapier. Learn to automate competitor analysis for insights and strategic advantage, without needing coding skills.</description>
      <author> (Brian Christner)</author>
      <guid>https://brianchristner.io/how-to-build-a-competitor-analysis-tool-using-chatgpt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a SOTA Adversarial Attack on LLMs 38x Faster</title>
      <link>https://blog.haizelabs.com/posts/acg/</link>
      <description>Last summer, a group of CMU researchers developed one of the first automated red-teaming methods for LLMs [1]. Their approach, the Greedy Coordinate Gradient (GCG) algorithm, was able to jailbreak white-box models like Vicuna convincingly and models like Llama 2 to a partial degree. Interestingly, the attacks generated by GCG also transferred to black-box models, implying the existence of a shared, underlying set of common vulnerabilities across models.
GCG is a perfectly good initial attack algorithm, but one common complaint is its lack of efficiency.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.haizelabs.com/posts/acg/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A gentle introduction to ESR&amp;#39;s `reposurgeon`</title>
      <link>https://andrew-quinn.me/reposurgeon/</link>
      <description>Greetings, fellow traveller. By this point in your journey you may have ran across the enigmatic Eric S. Raymond a couple of times; I assume you have hit upon this page because of a legendary and exact blade he has forged called reposurgeon. However, you, like me, are young, and are not yet wise enough in the ways of SVN to even make a toy conversion to Git – fear not. I will give you just enough to get started.</description>
      <author> (Convert SVN authors to Git authors)</author>
      <guid>https://andrew-quinn.me/reposurgeon/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Does It Mean to “Own Your Content”?</title>
      <link>https://anderegg.ca/2024/03/28/what-does-it-mean-to-own-your-content</link>
      <description>Late last year I was starting to hype myself up to write more. One thing I got hung up on was, “how do I post from my phone”? Honestly, I’m still slightly hung up on this. But thinking it through: I really don’t post enough that it can’t wait until I’m in front of a computer.</description>
      <author> (Gavin Anderegg)</author>
      <guid>https://anderegg.ca/2024/03/28/what-does-it-mean-to-own-your-content</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Men Who Sold The Moon</title>
      <link>https://www.notthesky.com/posts/essays/the-men-who-sold-the-moon/</link>
      <description>Eden Kupermintz&amp;#39;s personal blog containing poetry, short stories, and more!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.notthesky.com/posts/essays/the-men-who-sold-the-moon/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First time right, with software development</title>
      <link>https://davidvlijmincx.com/posts/first-time-right-software/</link>
      <description>Applying first time right during the software development life circle.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidvlijmincx.com/posts/first-time-right-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving the “Are You a Millionaire?” Problem with ZK certificates</title>
      <link>https://neimanslab.org/2024-03-28/zk_certificates.html</link>
      <description>Are you a millionaire? Would you like to show off your millionaire status without exposing your level of wealth? Let’s see how to solve the “are you a millionaire?” problem with elegant cryptography.</description>
      <author> (Neiman)</author>
      <guid>https://neimanslab.org/2024-03-28/zk_certificates.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should you do anything about a productive but overleveled employee?</title>
      <link>https://www.sherifnada.com/overleveled-employees</link>
      <description>At some point in your managerial life, you may find yourself in a situation where someone on your team is over-leveled i.e: their compensation or title is meaningfully higher than what their impact merits. Maybe you overestimated their seniority when hiring them. Maybe you inherited a team where a previous manager gave them a promotion or a raise they weren’t ready for. Or maybe your company rewrote your career ladder and it turned out that some people’s salaries or titles were previously inflated. Point is: someone’s title or compensation is seriously higher than what their impact justifies. What do you do?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.sherifnada.com/overleveled-employees</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 23:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large language models use a surprisingly simple mechanism to retrieve some stored knowledge</title>
      <link>https://news.mit.edu/2024/large-language-models-use-surprisingly-simple-mechanism-retrieve-stored-knowledge-0325</link>
      <description>Researchers find large language models use a simple mechanism to retrieve stored knowledge when they respond to a user prompt. These mechanisms can be leveraged to see what the model knows about different subjects and possibly to correct false information it has stored.</description>
      <author> (Adam Zewe
  |
  MIT News)</author>
      <guid>https://news.mit.edu/2024/large-language-models-use-surprisingly-simple-mechanism-retrieve-stored-knowledge-0325</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 22:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting the Method Name from a Task in C# | no dogma blog</title>
      <link>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2024/03/getting-the-method-name-from-a-task-in-c/</link>
      <description>Getting the name of a method from a task is not trivial, but this post will show you how to do it and includes an extension method for you to use.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nodogmablog.bryanhogan.net/2024/03/getting-the-method-name-from-a-task-in-c/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 20:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Media] Lars Bergstrom (Google Director of Engineering): &amp;quot;Rust teams are twice as productive as teams using C++.&amp;quot;</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/rust/comments/1bpwmud/media_lars_bergstrom_google_director_of/</link>
      <description>Posted in r/rust by u/TotempaaltJ • 488 points and 80 comments</description>
      <author> (TotempaaltJ)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/rust/comments/1bpwmud/media_lars_bergstrom_google_director_of/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 19:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I called Create&amp;#173;Environment&amp;#173;Block with a process&amp;#39;s token, but I didn&amp;#39;t get that process&amp;#39;s environment - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240328-00/?p=109590</link>
      <description>That&amp;#39;s not what the Create&amp;#173;Environment&amp;#173;Block function does.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240328-00/?p=109590</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 17:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“CVE-2024-21388”- Microsoft Edge’s Marketing API Exploited for Covert Extension Installation</title>
      <link>https://labs.guard.io/cve-2024-21388-microsoft-edges-marketing-api-exploited-for-covert-extension-installation-879fe5ad35ca</link>
      <description>By Oleg Zaytsev (Guardio Labs)</description>
      <author> (https://labs.guard.io)</author>
      <guid>https://labs.guard.io/cve-2024-21388-microsoft-edges-marketing-api-exploited-for-covert-extension-installation-879fe5ad35ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 16:01:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# MongoDB Insert Benchmarks – What You Need To Know</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/28/c-mongodb-insert-benchmarks-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <description>Curious about C# MongoDB insert benchmarks? In this article, I show you BenchmarkDotNet code and the results for several variations of inserting data!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/28/c-mongodb-insert-benchmarks-what-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 14:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital wallets and the “only Apple Pay does this” mythology</title>
      <link>https://birchtree.me/blog/digital-wallets-and-the-only-apple-pay-does-this-mythology/</link>
      <description>Apple Pay is great, but I think there is some misunderstanding out there about the details of how it works.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://birchtree.me/blog/digital-wallets-and-the-only-apple-pay-does-this-mythology/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 13:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>