<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>This Pattern Helps You Get Rid of Exceptions</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5MxJK1r8S_I</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović
  
  
  
    Milan Jovanović
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5MxJK1r8S_I</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incident report for January 10, 2024 &amp;#183; Resend</title>
      <link>https://resend.com/blog/incident-report-for-january-10-2024</link>
      <description>Detailed summary of what went wrong and how the incident was resolved.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://resend.com/blog/incident-report-for-january-10-2024</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 10:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A decade long Steam issue, is everyone just too fast for Valve?</title>
      <link>https://blog.freudenjmp.com/posts/no-user-logon/</link>
      <description>Valve has shown to occasionally not act on community feedback and bug reports. A story about a decade old bug.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.freudenjmp.com/posts/no-user-logon/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 10:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piped</title>
      <link>https://piped.kavin.rocks/@tccoder3547?si=yp6uWFOVsv3edFTJ</link>
      <description>An alternative privacy-friendly YouTube frontend which is efficient by design.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://piped.kavin.rocks/@tccoder3547?si=yp6uWFOVsv3edFTJ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 10:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Initialization With Collection Expressions in .NET</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-simple-initialization-with-collection-expressions-in-net-8/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will explore a new C# 12 feature called Collection Expressions, along with some code samples.</description>
      <author> (Muhammad Afzal Qureshi)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-simple-initialization-with-collection-expressions-in-net-8/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Kafka Component by g7ed6e &amp;#183; Pull Request #951 &amp;#183; dotnet/aspire</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/951</link>
      <description>Relates to #884</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspire/pull/951</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 05:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollama</title>
      <link>https://ollama.ai/</link>
      <description>Get up and running with large language models, locally.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ollama.ai/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 05:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fancy New Toy! – Behind The Screen – 2024 January, Week 2</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/01/12/fancy-new-toy-behind-the-screen-2024-january-week-2/</link>
      <description>Welcome to another Behind The Screen vlog. I picked up a fancy new toy that I&amp;#39;ll be using to incorporate into my videos for designing systems!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/01/12/fancy-new-toy-behind-the-screen-2024-january-week-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 03:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - marimo-team/marimo: A reactive notebook for Python — run reproducible experiments, execute as a script, deploy as an app, and version with git.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/marimo-team/marimo</link>
      <description>A reactive notebook for Python — run reproducible experiments, execute as a script, deploy as an app, and version with git. - GitHub - marimo-team/marimo: A reactive notebook for Python — run repro...</description>
      <author> (marimo-team)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/marimo-team/marimo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevDocs</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.io/</link>
      <description>Fast, offline, and free documentation browser for developers. Search 100+ docs in one web app including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Ruby, Python, Go, C, C++, and many more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devdocs.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attending NeurIPS 2023</title>
      <link>https://awaisrauf.github.io/deepCuriosity/Attending-NeurIPS2023</link>
      <description>NeurIPS is the top conference for artificial intelligence (AI) research [2]. It offers an excellent opportunity to present your work to fellow researchers, gain a sense of the latest developments in AI, and connect with the people driving the field. Despite having my paper accepted, I couldn’t attend the last two sessions due to COVID and visa issues. However, I managed to participate in this year’s conference in New Orleans, United States. It was an incredible week filled with all things AI. In the following, I will document the talks I attended, the papers I liked, the people I met, and the things I learned.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://awaisrauf.github.io/deepCuriosity/Attending-NeurIPS2023</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming in just ONE language should be lauded. – Cliffski&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.positech.co.uk/cliffsblog/2023/11/02/programming-in-just-one-language-should-be-lauded/</link>
      <description>I recently read about the news that garbage collection support, which was added to C++, is now actually being removed from it. Apparently most people didn’t use it, or even knew it was officially added, so it is no great loss. It always shocks me to read articles about C++ with a version number, because as far as I am concerned, C++ has no version number and never will, in the same way that a language such as English has no ‘version number’. I’m 54 and its pretty rare that I add a new word to my English vocabulary, and its even rarer for me to learn something new about C++ that I start to use in my code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.positech.co.uk/cliffsblog/2023/11/02/programming-in-just-one-language-should-be-lauded/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My CSS resets</title>
      <link>https://keithjgrant.com/posts/2024/01/my-css-resets/</link>
      <description>Every now and then, I see someone post their latest and greatest set of CSS resets.
Here’s mine.
</description>
      <author> (Keith J. Grant)</author>
      <guid>https://keithjgrant.com/posts/2024/01/my-css-resets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of APIs As Enivisioned By Industry Leaders</title>
      <link>https://matthewreinbold.github.io/APIFutures/</link>
      <description>Do you see a future that isn&amp;#39;t listed here? Feel compelled to expand or comment on something seen here? Join us in shaping the future of APIs!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matthewreinbold.github.io/APIFutures/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons I learned in the last 10 years</title>
      <link>https://mihamedven.com/blog/lessons-i-learned-in-the-last-10-years/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been a software developer for nearly 10 years. These are some of the lessons I have learned along the way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mihamedven.com/blog/lessons-i-learned-in-the-last-10-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In praise of WordPress</title>
      <link>https://birtles.blog/2023/11/28/in-praise-of-wordpress/</link>
      <description>After over a year of fighting with Eleventy and then Astro to set up a this blog just right I find myself needing to set up yet another blog, this time for work. I could just build on what I’ve got with Astro but I can’t help but wonder if I would have been better off sticking with WordPress after all.</description>
      <author> (Brian Birtles)</author>
      <guid>https://birtles.blog/2023/11/28/in-praise-of-wordpress/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playing with Fire – How We Executed a Critical Supply Chain Attack on PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://johnstawinski.com/2024/01/11/playing-with-fire-how-we-executed-a-critical-supply-chain-attack-on-pytorch/</link>
      <description>Security tends to lag behind adoption, and AI/ML is no exception.&amp;#160; Four months ago, Adnan Khan and I exploited a critical CI/CD vulnerability in PyTorch, one of the world’s leading ML platform…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://johnstawinski.com/2024/01/11/playing-with-fire-how-we-executed-a-critical-supply-chain-attack-on-pytorch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shipping a Project in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://irazayats.com/24-hours/</link>
      <description>Three days before the New Year&amp;#39;s, I had an idea to build a simple printable calendar app.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://irazayats.com/24-hours/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why autonomous trucking is harder than autonomous rideshare</title>
      <link>https://kevinchen.co/blog/autonomous-trucking-harder-than-rideshare/</link>
      <description>Freeways were supposed to be easy. What happened?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kevinchen.co/blog/autonomous-trucking-harder-than-rideshare/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why it&amp;#39;s almost always a good thing when staff quit - Dan Norris</title>
      <link>https://dannorris.me/why-its-almost-always-a-good-thing-when-staff-quit/</link>
      <description>June 2001 In my final year of University, after months of applying for jobs, I was close to giving up hope. It was 2001 when one man finally gave me a chance, and made me realise I might be able to make something of myself. The man was Mark Smith. He was the boss of […]</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/dannorrisprofile)</author>
      <guid>https://dannorris.me/why-its-almost-always-a-good-thing-when-staff-quit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#RAG #RetrieverOptimization #HybridSearch #AI #ML6</title>
      <link>https://www.ml6.eu/blogpost/elevating-your-retrieval-game-insights-from-real-world-deployments</link>
      <description>Discover the key elements in optimizing Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) with smart chunking, embedding models, and hybrid search strategies. Evaluate with metrics like Hit Rate, MRR, MAP, and NDCG. Enhance user experience by enabling follow-up questions. Unleash the full potential of RAG by improving and understanding your retriever.</description>
      <author> (Sebastian WehkampMachine Learning Engineer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.ml6.eu/blogpost/elevating-your-retrieval-game-insights-from-real-world-deployments</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running Wikepedia offline</title>
      <link>https://blog.georgovassilis.com/2024/01/12/running-wikepedia-offline/</link>
      <description>This post explains how to run Wikipedia offline on Linux inside a Docker container. Prerequisites (not explained here): a web browser to access the offline copy a Linux server connected to your net…</description>
      <author> (George Georgovassilis)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.georgovassilis.com/2024/01/12/running-wikepedia-offline/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending HttpClient With Delegating Handlers in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/extending-httpclient-with-delegating-handlers-in-aspnetcore</link>
      <description>Delegating handlers are like ASP.NET Core middleware. Except they work with the HttpClient. I&amp;#39;ll show you how to work with delegating handlers</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/extending-httpclient-with-delegating-handlers-in-aspnetcore</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing HTML in HTML</title>
      <link>https://ankarstrom.se/~john/articles/html/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve just finished the final rewrite of my website. I&amp;#39;m
              not lying: this is the last time I&amp;#39;m ever going to do it.
              This website has gone through countless rewrites – from
              WordPress to Jekyll to multiple static site
              generators of my own – but this is the final one. I know
              so, because I&amp;#39;ve found the ultimate method for writing
              webpages: pure HTML.</description>
      <author> (John Ankarstr&amp;#246;m)</author>
      <guid>https://ankarstrom.se/~john/articles/html/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Moderation APIs are Really, Really Bad</title>
      <link>https://blog.haizelabs.com/posts/content-moderation-apis-are-bad/</link>
      <description>With an ever-growing collection of text content on the web, and ever-growing LLM-powered systems that automatically interact with such data, scalable content moderation emerges as a significant challenge.
One seemingly reasonable solution is from OpenAI. Since a tenet of their mission is to ensure AI benefits all of humanity, careful development and deployment of their models is top of mind.
As part of this effort, OpenAI offers the free Moderation API.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.haizelabs.com/posts/content-moderation-apis-are-bad/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best way to get NVM working in CI/CD systems</title>
      <link>https://gagor.pl/2023/04/the-best-way-to-get-nvm-working-in-ci/cd-systems/</link>
      <description>TL;DR While reasoning is important, readers may not be interested in all the frustrations I experienced while figuring out how to get things done. If you’re looking for a quick solution, skip to the “What eventually worked?” section. However, if you’re interested in the thought process behind the solution, keep reading.
NVM is nice and simple, how hard it might be to get it working with CI/CD? Over the past few days, I’ve been working on providing nvm for both my company’s Docker base images and for CI/CD.</description>
      <author> (timor)</author>
      <guid>https://gagor.pl/2023/04/the-best-way-to-get-nvm-working-in-ci/cd-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Library is a Superpower</title>
      <link>https://anderegg.ca/2024/01/12/the-library-is-a-superpower</link>
      <description>I volunteer with a great local program. Through it, I help connect newcomers to the local tech scene. One of the standard pieces of advice I give is: get a library card.</description>
      <author> (Gavin Anderegg)</author>
      <guid>https://anderegg.ca/2024/01/12/the-library-is-a-superpower</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Changes in GPT-4, Uncovered</title>
      <link>https://dmicz.github.io/machine-learning/openai-changes/</link>
      <description>The tool instructions in this article are not up to date as of 1/11/2024, see this post to learn more about the new tool OpenAI added to block conversations about U.S. elections using function calls.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dmicz.github.io/machine-learning/openai-changes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source Controlled Linux ~ colinramsay.co.uk</title>
      <link>https://colinramsay.co.uk/2024/01/03/source-controlled-linux.html</link>
      <description>The personal website of Colin Ramsay, a software developer from Cornwall who is the Technical Director with Go Tripod</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://colinramsay.co.uk/2024/01/03/source-controlled-linux.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIY Terraform Cloud, Part 1 - The Game Plan</title>
      <link>https://blog.digger.dev/diy-terraform-cloud-part-1-the-game-plan/</link>
      <description>What would it take to migrate away from Terraform Cloud? After Hashicorp moved to resource-based pricing and BSL license last year, this question is on the roadmaps of many infrastructure teams. This article outlines the scope of such a migration.

In this article I will describe the main aspects of</description>
      <author> (Igor Zalutski)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.digger.dev/diy-terraform-cloud-part-1-the-game-plan/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My theory for the dropping global TFR - LED Lighting     | Mark Essien</title>
      <link>https://markessien.com/posts/light-theory-for-tfr/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://markessien.com/posts/light-theory-for-tfr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I learned selling my company</title>
      <link>https://www.harryglaser.com/what-i-learned-selling-my-company/</link>
      <description>At my first company, I internalized the standard advice to never think about M&amp;amp;A. The consensus was, and is, to just keep growing the business and good things will come. I did that, and I was lucky that good things did come in the form of a $130M acquisition</description>
      <author> (Harry Glaser)</author>
      <guid>https://www.harryglaser.com/what-i-learned-selling-my-company/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are you producing?</title>
      <link>https://destructive-thoughts.com/2024/01/12/what-are-you-producing.html</link>
      <description>People are obsessed with productivity. There are apps that claim to
boost your productivity, courses, blog posts, entire books. A question
that is rarely asked is: what are you producing? Are you creating
worthless proofs of concept for a startup that siphons off money from
rich people or the state? Don’t worry about productivity, you’re doing
just fine. Do you help pushing out tank-like vehicles that pollute the
environment and turn our cities into dystopian hellscapes? By all means,
consider being less productive. Are you developing surveillance tools
for a corporation that thrives on ad money? I implore you, be as
unproductive as you can.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://destructive-thoughts.com/2024/01/12/what-are-you-producing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com : X-ACTO Desk Knife Holder, 5.5 x 6.5 Inches, Silver and Black (X2013) : Xacto Knife Holder : Office Products</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/X-ACTO-Holder-Inches-Silver-X2013/dp/B0073CBHE6?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202401</link>
      <description>Amazon.com : X-ACTO Desk Knife Holder, 5.5 x 6.5 Inches, Silver and Black (X2013) : Xacto Knife Holder : Office Products</description>
      <author> (Visit the X-Acto Store)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/X-ACTO-Holder-Inches-Silver-X2013/dp/B0073CBHE6?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202401</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 22:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding a drone using .NET &amp;amp; ChatGPT AI and flying it in mixed reality | .NET Conf 2023 Student Zone</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5ChGYf10z1M</link>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ll use Unity 3D, .NET, and focus on UDP Client-Server networking for drone communication. ChatGPT AI assists programmers, offering insights to boost decis...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5ChGYf10z1M</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheet Bend</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2880/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2880/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text and Strings Part 1 - C# in the Cards Episode 4</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YFxEmB7vt-8</link>
      <description>In this lesson, we will introduce strings and text operations in the C# language.  Text and notebooks that accompany this lesson can be found at https://www....</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter
  
  
  
    Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YFxEmB7vt-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US regulator considers stripping inspection authority from Boeing employees</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/1588974e-db75-4a02-9aff-deb0b75ed379?shareType=nongift</link>
      <description>Mid-air blowout of 737 Max 9 prompts review of system where company staff certify aircraft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ft.com/content/1588974e-db75-4a02-9aff-deb0b75ed379?shareType=nongift</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sortable Lists for Blazor using a SortableJS Component - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-blazor-sortable/</link>
      <description>Blazor Sortable is a new a open source community Blazor component for creating sortable lists of items using SortableJS.</description>
      <author> (Burke Holland)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-blazor-sortable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com: I&amp;#39;m sorry but I cannot fulfill this request it goes against OpenAI use policy. My purpose is to provide helpful and respectful information to users-Brown : Office Products</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/fulfill-request-respectful-information-users-Brown/dp/B0CM82FJL2?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202401</link>
      <description>Amazon.com: I&amp;#39;m sorry but I cannot fulfill this request it goes against OpenAI use policy. My purpose is to provide helpful and respectful information to users-Brown : Office Products</description>
      <author> (Brand: FOPEAS)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/fulfill-request-respectful-information-users-Brown/dp/B0CM82FJL2?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202401</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 19:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In C++/WinRT, how can I await multiple coroutines and capture the results?, part 3 - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240112-59/?p=109267</link>
      <description>Dealing with awaitables that return void, and questioning our life choices.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240112-59/?p=109267</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASIEST Way To Approach Data Processing in C# - Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Z4qUWxTH0Mw</link>
      <description>Are you wondering how to process data effectively in C#? There&amp;#39;s a simple design pattern that paves the foundation for doing this!The pipeline design pattern...</description>
      <author> (Learning Journal
  
  
  
    Learning Journal
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Z4qUWxTH0Mw</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cloudflare Was Able to Support 55 Million Requests per Second With Only 15 Postgres Clusters</title>
      <link>https://newsletter.systemdesign.one/p/postgresql-scalability</link>
      <description>#32: Learn More - Awesome PostgreSQL Scalability (5 minutes)</description>
      <author> (NK)</author>
      <guid>https://newsletter.systemdesign.one/p/postgresql-scalability</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bound for greater Bindings</title>
      <link>https://www.gonemobile.io/89</link>
      <description>Bindings are often used to integrate native libraries into .NET MAUI apps.  We talk about the challenges of creating bindings for Android and iOS platforms and some alternative techniques such as Slim bindings and Platform Channels for accessiong Swift/ObjC and Java/Kotlin code or libraries in your .NET MAUI apps.</description>
      <author> (Jonathan Dick, Allan Ritchie)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gonemobile.io/89</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 8 &amp;#128293;&amp;#128640; : Guide to Secure User Authentication - Exploring Identity new Features</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ORzt0lks2H4</link>
      <description>In this video we will discussed the new features with Identity in .NET 8Support me on Patreon to access the source code:https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawand...</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand
  
  
  
    Mohamad Lawand
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ORzt0lks2H4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 16:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Machine Learning in C#. Classification using ML.NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=R3kRf7hNVMg</link>
      <description>Dive into the world of Machine Learning with C#! &amp;#129302;✨ In this video, I guide you through building a powerful email subject classifier using ML.NET. Learn step...</description>
      <author> (Nick Proud
  
  
  
    Nick Proud
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=R3kRf7hNVMg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 16:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core News - 01/12/2024</title>
      <link>https://us7.campaign-archive.com/?u=66fdd2122e968863d381a26e1&amp;id=16db19f43a</link>
      <description>Would you like to advertise with us? Visit the Media Kit for details on how to sponsor this newsletter with thousands of readers every week.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://us7.campaign-archive.com/?u=66fdd2122e968863d381a26e1&amp;id=16db19f43a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M365 Admin App: A Customer .NET MAUI Migration Story</title>
      <link>https://player.fireside.fm/v2/ce4Mj65y+wASZflD3/twitter</link>
      <description>Powerful podcast hosting and analytics. By podcasters, for podcasters.</description>
      <author> (Fireside Labs, LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://player.fireside.fm/v2/ce4Mj65y+wASZflD3/twitter</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop using Code Coverage as a Quality metric</title>
      <link>https://neatstack.substack.com/p/stop-using-code-coverage-as-a-quality?r=8rnby&amp;amp;showWelcome=true</link>
      <description>“When a measure becomes a target, it ceases to be a good measure” - Goodhart&amp;#39;s Law Code coverage serves as a valuable metric for gauging the extent of code covered by test cases. However, using it as the metric to determine code quality is misplaced.</description>
      <author> (Ritesh Mehrotra)</author>
      <guid>https://neatstack.substack.com/p/stop-using-code-coverage-as-a-quality?r=8rnby&amp;amp;showWelcome=true</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waiting for Postgres 17: Incremental base backups</title>
      <link>https://pganalyze.com/blog/5mins-postgres-17-incremental-backups</link>
      <description>We walk through the incremental backup feature committed to the Postgres 17 development branch by Robert Haas. We show an example on our local machine.</description>
      <author> (By Lukas FittlDecember 21, 2023)</author>
      <guid>https://pganalyze.com/blog/5mins-postgres-17-incremental-backups</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Implement The Pipeline Design Pattern in C#</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/01/12/how-to-implement-the-pipeline-design-pattern-in-c/</link>
      <description>Learn about the pipeline design pattern in C#. Discover how to create and chain pipeline stages. Get code examples, tips, and use cases for this design pattern.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/01/12/how-to-implement-the-pipeline-design-pattern-in-c/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statement regarding the ongoing SourceHut outage</title>
      <link>https://outage.sr.ht/</link>
      <description>sourcehut is a network of useful open source tools for software project maintainers and collaborators, including git repos, bug tracking, continuous integration, and mailing lists.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://outage.sr.ht/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>