<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Community Toolkit Extravaganza!</title>
      <link>https://www.xamarinpodcast.com/87</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s the Xamarin Community Toolkit extravaganza!

The toolkit it out! It&amp;#39;s glorious! You should use it today because it&amp;#39;ll solve all of your Xamarin app development needs!

.... or it&amp;#39;ll at least make your life a bit easier ...</description>
      <author> (Xamarin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.xamarinpodcast.com/87</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 09:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-02-12</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/02/app-developer-links-2021-02-12/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/02/app-developer-links-2021-02-12/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 09:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cofoundry CMS - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/162/cofoundry-cms</link>
      <description>Cofoundry is an open source .NET Core CMS designed to work unobtrusively with your application.

It&amp;#39;s simple to install and our code-first approach to content and feature definition means we can optimize both the developer and content editor experience without having to compromise on either.

F…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/162/cofoundry-cms</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 08:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks! vNext</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/?show=1726</link>
      <description>.NET Rocks! is a weekly talk show for anyone interested in programming on the Microsoft .NET platform. The shows range from introductory information to hardcore geekiness.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/?show=1726</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 07:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building A Custom Event Hubs Event Processor with .NET | Azure SDK Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/custom-event-processor/?WT.mc_id=DOP-MVP-4025064</link>
      <description>Azure Event Hubs is a highly scalable publish-subscribe service that can ingest millions of events per second and stream them to multiple consumers. This lets you process and analyze the massive amounts of data produced by your connected devices and applications.</description>
      <author> (Matt Ellis Principal Software Engineer, Azure SDK Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/custom-event-processor/?WT.mc_id=DOP-MVP-4025064</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 06:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IronPython: First steps - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/dotnet/net-development/ironpython-first-steps/</link>
      <description>Python is one of the most popular languages. Julio Sampaio explains how IronPython allows you to integrate Python with .NET.</description>
      <author> (Julio Sampaio)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/dotnet/net-development/ironpython-first-steps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 06:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Unit Test Existing C# Apps? Easy—With a Mocking Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-to-unit-test-existing-csharp-app-easy-with-mocking-tool</link>
      <description>Using a mocking tool to write the unit tests required for your existing C# app is an easy task with JustMock.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-to-unit-test-existing-csharp-app-easy-with-mocking-tool</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 06:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Abbot, a powerful ChatOps tool for collaborative work</title>
      <link>https://haacked.com/archive/2021/02/11/introducing-abbot/</link>
      <description>Introducing Abbot, your friendly neighborhood chat bot. It’s the best way to automate tasks from chat to work together with others.</description>
      <author> (Phil Haack)</author>
      <guid>https://haacked.com/archive/2021/02/11/introducing-abbot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 06:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure App Service, Health checks and zero downtime deployments</title>
      <link>https://blog.johnnyreilly.com/2021/02/azure-app-service-health-checks-and-zero-downtime-deployments.html</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been working recently on zero downtime deployments using Azure App Service. They&amp;#39;re facilitated by a combination of Health checks  and ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.johnnyreilly.com/2021/02/azure-app-service-health-checks-and-zero-downtime-deployments.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 06:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clippings.io for Kindle - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/63/clippings.io.-kindle-highlights-and-notes-organiser</link>
      <description>Whether you are a student, author, academic or casual reader clippings.io provides all of the functionality you&amp;#39;ll need to manage the clippings you make on your Kindle.

The app allows you to not only organize but also export your clippings to Evernote, Word or PDF.

Using the Chrome extension …</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/63/clippings.io.-kindle-highlights-and-notes-organiser</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 05:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Infrastructure Engineer Job in Albury Area</title>
      <link>https://www.seek.com.au/job/51513295</link>
      <description>Seeking a Senior Infrastructure Engineer to come and work in a team that loves technology, and how it can help create successful learners.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.seek.com.au/job/51513295</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 04:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn’s Alternate Universe</title>
      <link>https://every.to/divinations/linkedins-alternate-universe-21780381</link>
      <description>How the professional platform makes networking weird</description>
      <author> (by Nathan Baschez)</author>
      <guid>https://every.to/divinations/linkedins-alternate-universe-21780381</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 04:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARL CHARLES MCBRIDE</title>
      <link>https://unicourt.com/case/pc-bk5-darl-charles-mcbride-1290201</link>
      <description>On 12/15/2020 DARL CHARLES MCBRIDE filed a Bankruptcy - Chapter 13 court case in U.S. Bankruptcy Courts. Court records for this case are available from Nevada Bankruptcy.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://unicourt.com/case/pc-bk5-darl-charles-mcbride-1290201</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 04:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Profiling - In Production</title>
      <link>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/performance-profiling-in-production</link>
      <description>In part 3 on performance profiling,&amp;#160; Esteban Herrera shows us how to profile ...</description>
      <author> (Mark Downie)</author>
      <guid>https://www.poppastring.com/blog/performance-profiling-in-production</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 03:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustum planes from the projection matrix</title>
      <link>https://fgiesen.wordpress.com/2012/08/31/frustum-planes-from-the-projection-matrix/</link>
      <description>Another quick one. Now this is another old trick, but it’s easy to derive and still not as well-known as it deserves to be, so here goes. All modern graphics APIs ultimately expect vertex coo…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fgiesen.wordpress.com/2012/08/31/frustum-planes-from-the-projection-matrix/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 03:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Developer Salaries: Looking Back 20 Years</title>
      <link>https://codesubmit.io/blog/the-evolution-of-developer-salaries/#tracing-developer-salaries-in-america-from-2001-to-2019</link>
      <description>Much has been covered about developer salaries based on coding language, location, job title, and so on. But little has been done to chart the rise and fall of developer salaries over the years - until now.</description>
      <author> (Tracy Phillips)</author>
      <guid>https://codesubmit.io/blog/the-evolution-of-developer-salaries/#tracing-developer-salaries-in-america-from-2001-to-2019</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 02:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The .NET Docs Show - A beginner&amp;#39;s introduction to APIs in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ekezoV4DcNA</link>
      <description>Community member and API wizard Sophie Obomighie joins the panel to share her API magic with muggles all over the world.Featuring: Sophie Obomighie (@Obomigh...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ekezoV4DcNA</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 01:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code C++ Tool Customizes IntelliSense for Target Platforms -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/11/vscode-cpp-update.aspx</link>
      <description>Visual Studio Code developers using Microsoft&amp;#39;s C/C++ extension have gained the ability to customize the way IntelliSense works when coding for different platforms.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel02/11/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/11/vscode-cpp-update.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 01:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do You Actually Agree To When You Accept All Cookies</title>
      <link>http://www.conradakunga.com/blog/what-do-you-actually-agree-to-when-you-accept-all-cookies/</link>
      <description>I have been writing software for exactly twenty years now. In the course of this I have learnt very many things, which I hope to journal over time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.conradakunga.com/blog/what-do-you-actually-agree-to-when-you-accept-all-cookies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art of Sustaining at Things – Unstructed.tech</title>
      <link>https://unstructed.tech/2021/02/11/art-of-sustaining-at-things/</link>
      <description>We tend to believe that relying on motivation is a good way to keep doing things. This is utterly wrong. Motivation is a spark, not a fuel.</description>
      <author> (By Mihailo Joksimovic)</author>
      <guid>https://unstructed.tech/2021/02/11/art-of-sustaining-at-things/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:07:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#1 Riding with Peloton - Back of the Napkin VC</title>
      <link>https://www.thenapkinvc.com/speakeasy/riding-with-peloton</link>
      <description>Back of the Napkin VC is a refreshingly simple framework for evaluating startups, business and technology. We rely on a few simple models - Business Equations, Unit Economics, and Flywheels - to evaluate high-level levers, identify critical metrics, estimate growth trajectories, and more.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.thenapkinvc.com/speakeasy/riding-with-peloton</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:07:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podman</title>
      <link>https://podman.io/</link>
      <description>08 Feb 2021 &amp;#187;
      Easy Development Dependency Management With Podman and Tent</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://podman.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:07:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scientific Method Has a Big Problem</title>
      <link>https://koratkar.com/2021/02/11/dead-science</link>
      <description>I don’t think the scientific method works.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://koratkar.com/2021/02/11/dead-science</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:07:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typing, RSI, and what I do differently</title>
      <link>https://senryu.pub/afternoonrobot/articles/typing-rsi-and-what-i-do-differently</link>
      <description>Or, &amp;quot;Any excuse to talk about folk music&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://senryu.pub/afternoonrobot/articles/typing-rsi-and-what-i-do-differently</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:07:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ramanujan Machine Redux | Persiflage</title>
      <link>https://www.galoisrepresentations.com/2021/02/11/ramanujan-machine-redux/</link>
      <description>I had no intention to discuss the Ramanujan Machine again, but over the past few days there has been a flurry of (attempted) trollish comments on that post, so after taking a brief look at the latest version, I thought I would offer you my updates. (I promise for the last time.)</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://www.galoisrepresentations.com/2021/02/11/ramanujan-machine-redux/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:07:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a fun technique with iframes on the web – ciphrd</title>
      <link>https://ciphrd.com/2021/02/10/iframe-feedback-a-fun-technique-with-iframes-on-the-web/</link>
      <description>What would happen if a &amp;lt;iframe&amp;gt; tag on a page pointed to the same page ? In HTML, iframes are elements designed to display documents under an URL, as if we would load it as we normally do in our browsers. See it as a small window within a web document which can display another web document. For instance, what you see here is an &amp;lt;iframe&amp;gt; pointing to the homepage of this website, https://ciphrd.com:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ciphrd.com/2021/02/10/iframe-feedback-a-fun-technique-with-iframes-on-the-web/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:07:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Environment Aware Sessions in SSH – Steven Wade</title>
      <link>https://stevenwadejr.com/2021/02/11/environment-aware-sessions-in-ssh/</link>
      <description>In my first week on the job as a software developer, I deleted an entire table’s worth of data from a client’s database. Luckily, we had a backup from the night before and that table was low traffic. What happened was that I thought I was on the staging server and I was doing some testing and needed to clear out the existing data. I was not on staging. I was on production. I learned a valuable lesson and I was determined never to make the same mistake again.



Enter, color coded SSH sessions:







I developed color schemes for different environments that would easily stand out and alert me of where I was.



For my local environment, I use a black background with green text. This is part Matrix and part me not having a computer growing up in the 90s and missing out on the nostalgia of pre-GUI terminals. On staging, I use a blue/violet mix that isn’t jarring to the eye or mind but still catches my attention and makes me aware of the environment. Lastly, for production-based servers I use a red background which definitely stands for “ALERT, whatever you do will have consequences!”



To color code the environments I use separate profiles within iTerm. Once I customized the profiles to my liking, I needed a way to easily and dynamically switch between them. I did some googling and came across a bash function on StackOverflow called it2prof. Essentially this function is a shortcut to an iTerm command to switch profiles but the function is a lot cleaner to use: it2prof staging. That command will then switch the current iTerm window’s profile to the profile and color scheme of my “staging” profile.



To connect to an environment, I use shortcuts and aliases to run my commands at once, for instance: ssh staging aliases to it2prof staging &amp;amp;&amp;amp; ssh steven@stage01 which will change the terminal profile and then ssh into my staging server.



This level of safe guarding will likely do for most people, however, I am paranoid and now I have multiple production environments to deal with. For instance, at work, we use a control box to do our releases, but we also have individual production servers that you can log into. So I wanted an extra notification of where I was to pop up.















Text to ASCII! I wanted a proper warning message to pop up and be as in my face as possible to let me know which boxes I was on. I used this tool to convert my text to ASCII art which I then saved to text files either on my local machine or the remote server.



If you have your own user on a server you could do like what I did on the staging environment and update the .bashrc file to output the contents of a file when your Bash profile is loaded (upon log in). To do this, update your .bashrc file with a line like cat env_msg.txt where “env_msg.txt” is the text file containing your ASCII art.



My production servers use different user permissions so instead, I stored those warning files locally and just updated my aliases. For work, I created a fub (short for Follow Up Boss) function that helps me do various things, one of them being ssh-ing into a server. I simply updated each SSH command with a call to cat my text file like so: it2prof control &amp;amp;&amp;amp; cat /Users/steven/production-warning.txt &amp;amp;&amp;amp; ssh production01. Now all I have to type into my terminal is fub ssh prod01 and my terminal profile turns red, I get the boldface production warning, and I’m ssh’d into the proper machine.



Now, I’m always aware of what machine I’m working on and I haven’t made the same mistake again as I did all those years ago.



Do what you need to to guard/help yourself. Remember, stay safe out there.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stevenwadejr.com/2021/02/11/environment-aware-sessions-in-ssh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:06:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nouriel Roubini: ‘Tether is a criminal enterprise,’ SEC should probe Elon Musk’s bitcoin tweets</title>
      <link>https://amycastor.com/2021/02/11/nouriel-roubini-tether-is-a-criminal-enterprise-sec-should-probe-elon-musks-bitcoin-tweets/</link>
      <description>Roubini: “Tether is a criminal enterprise, and a bunch of whales and insiders are manipulating the price of bitcoins and other shitcoins day in and day out.”</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://amycastor.com/2021/02/11/nouriel-roubini-tether-is-a-criminal-enterprise-sec-should-probe-elon-musks-bitcoin-tweets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Remote Friendly Won’t Do</title>
      <link>https://www.shinkim.io/posts/why-remote-friendly-wont-do</link>
      <description>Remote friendly is a term that has abruptly outlived its usefulness. In today&amp;#39;s world where 70% of companies hiring on Hacker News are open to permanent remote positions as of January 2021, one could argue that most of the tech in</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.shinkim.io/posts/why-remote-friendly-wont-do</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:06:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feeds Considered Harmful</title>
      <link>https://suketk.com/feeds-considered-harmful</link>
      <description>Technology is merely a tool. It can work for us or against us. If we use it with agency, we can leverage the world’s information to better our lives. If we use it indiscriminately, we find ourselves at the mercy of the Algorithm, passively consuming content. Our generation is at an inflection point - either we use technology intentionally or it uses us.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://suketk.com/feeds-considered-harmful</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Failure Stories</title>
      <link>https://k8s.af/</link>
      <description>A compiled list of links to public failure stories related to Kubernetes.
Most recent publications on top.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://k8s.af/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:05:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principal Program Manager in Redmond, Washington, United States | Engineering at Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/985603</link>
      <description>Apply for Principal Program Manager job with Microsoft in Redmond, Washington, United States. Engineering at Microsoft</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/us/en/job/985603</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:05:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering a 24-year-old bug in the Linux Kernel</title>
      <link>https://engineering.skroutz.gr/blog/uncovering-a-24-year-old-bug-in-the-linux-kernel/</link>
      <description>How a failing rsync run led to the discovery of a long-standing bug in the Linux TCP implementation.</description>
      <author> (By Apollon Oikonomopoulos)</author>
      <guid>https://engineering.skroutz.gr/blog/uncovering-a-24-year-old-bug-in-the-linux-kernel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Built Litestream</title>
      <link>https://litestream.io/blog/why-i-built-litestream/</link>
      <description>Despite an exponential increase in computing power, our applications require more machines than ever because of architectural decisions made 25 years ago. You can eliminate much of your complexity and cost by using SQLite &amp;amp; Litestream for your production applications.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/)</author>
      <guid>https://litestream.io/blog/why-i-built-litestream/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 23:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Management Made Easy with Johanna Rothmann | Hanselminutes with Scott Hanselman</title>
      <link>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/johanna-rothmann-on-modern-management-made-easy-M672GPjX</link>
      <description>Johanna Rothman has been in software and management for many years and she&amp;#39;s taken what she knows about managing teams and put it into a great three-volume set &amp;quot;Modern Management Made Easy.&amp;quot; She covers not just managing organizations, managing teams, but also managing yourself. Scott talks to Johanna about the trials and tribulations of management and how Johanna&amp;#39;s insights can help.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/johanna-rothmann-on-modern-management-made-easy-M672GPjX</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 23:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public-Key Cryptography Standard (PKCS) #11 v 3.0 has been released: What is it, and what does it mean for RHEL?</title>
      <link>https://www.redhat.com/en/blog/public-key-cryptography-standard-pkcs-11-v-30-has-been-released-what-it-and-what-does-it-mean-rhel</link>
      <description>OASIS has announced that its members have approved Version 3.0 of the Public-Key Cryptography Standard (PKCS) #11. In this post we&amp;#39;ll look at what&amp;#39;s new in Version 3.0 and what you can expect to see in Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL).</description>
      <author> (Robert Relyea)</author>
      <guid>https://www.redhat.com/en/blog/public-key-cryptography-standard-pkcs-11-v-30-has-been-released-what-it-and-what-does-it-mean-rhel</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 23:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America&amp;#39;s 1% Has Taken $50 Trillion From the Bottom 90% | Time</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5888024/50-trillion-income-inequality-america/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://time.com/5888024/50-trillion-income-inequality-america/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 22:07:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source HTTP API packages and tools | ASP.NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/open-source-http-api-packages-and-tools/</link>
      <description>Brady Gaster continues his series on building HTTP APIs in .NET with a deep dive on some of the top open source packages and tools.</description>
      <author> (Brady Gaster)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspnet/open-source-http-api-packages-and-tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 22:07:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On .NET Live - Generating docs for ASP.NET Core Web APIs with Swashbuckle</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SCR1IdW0PCk</link>
      <description>In this live session, we&amp;#39;ll be joined by Richard Morris. He&amp;#39;ll be talking to us about his open source project, Swashbuckle!Featuring:  Richard Morris (@domai...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SCR1IdW0PCk</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 22:07:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 364 - Virtual Networking with Functions</title>
      <link>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-364-Virtual-Networking-with-Functions</link>
      <description>Russell, Sujit, and Cynthia chats with Michael Collier about different considerations regarding Azure Functions ranging from virtual networking, hosting, common use cases and some of the existing limitations to be aware of.</description>
      <author> (Sujit D&amp;#39;Mello)</author>
      <guid>http://azpodcast.azurewebsites.net/post/Episode-364-Virtual-Networking-with-Functions</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 21:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Regression Using PyTorch: Defining a Network -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/11/pytorch-define.aspx</link>
      <description>Dr. James McCaffrey of Microsoft Research presents the second of four machine learning articles that detail a complete end-to-end production-quality example of neural regression using PyTorch.</description>
      <author> (By James McCaffrey02/11/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/11/pytorch-define.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 21:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Code with Infer#</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Analyzing-Code-with-Infer</link>
      <description>Want to detect reliability and security bugs before they ship? Matthew Jin and Xiaoyu Liu show Infer#, a static analysis tool you can use to validate the correctness of source code without needing to </description>
      <author> (by Robert Green, Leslie Richardson [MSFT])</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Visual-Studio-Toolbox/Analyzing-Code-with-Infer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 21:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C#/WinRT Authoring Preview Unveiled -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/11/csharp-winrt.aspx</link>
      <description> Microsoft unveiled a preview of authoring support in an update to the C#/WinRT tool used to help C# developers more easily work with interfaces to the Windows Runtime, the underlying infrastructure used by Windows to expose its APIs.  </description>
      <author> (By David Ramel02/11/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/11/csharp-winrt.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 21:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staying safe with .NET containers | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/staying-safe-with-dotnet-containers/</link>
      <description>An update on using .NET and containers together, learn how to tackle staying safe and keeping your container images up-to-date.</description>
      <author> (Richard Lander Program Manager, .NET Team Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/staying-safe-with-dotnet-containers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 20:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release v5.0.211103 &amp;#183; dotnet/format</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/format/releases/tag/v5.0.211103</link>
      <description>View Complete Diff of Changes
New Features

Can now apply codestyle codefixes automatically with dotnet format --fix-codestyle
Can now apply analyzer codefixes automatically with dotnet format --fi...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/format/releases/tag/v5.0.211103</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 20:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Rust 1.50.0 | Rust Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2021/02/11/Rust-1.50.0.html</link>
      <description>Empowering everyone to build reliable and efficient software.</description>
      <author> (Feb. 11, 2021 &amp;#183; The Rust Release Team)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2021/02/11/Rust-1.50.0.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 20:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Product Manager - Data &amp;amp; Security Products</title>
      <link>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/2453306</link>
      <description>Remote - US / Canada</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://boards.greenhouse.io/github/jobs/2453306</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 19:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Code Analyzer for .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.timheuer.com/blog/building-a-code-analyzer-for-net/</link>
      <description>Learn with me as I build my first C# Code Analyzer and Code Fix using Visual Studio and the Roslyn SDK!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.timheuer.com/blog/building-a-code-analyzer-for-net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 19:05:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build native and hybrid mobile apps with Mobile Blazor Bindings</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qTPHAlHom20</link>
      <description>Extend your Blazor skills from the web to mobile apps with Mobile Blazor Bindings. This experimental project enables using Blazor to build native and hybrid ...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
    

    
      
    dotNET
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qTPHAlHom20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 17:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GooglePlacesApi - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/82/googleplacesapi</link>
      <description>The Google Places API can be used to find locations and their details like geolocation, address and other data. It returns a predicted list of locations based on the input string. In this post I will show some details about the plugin I created. This nuget package makes it even easier to use the AP…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/82/googleplacesapi</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum cryptography network spans 4600 km in China – Physics World</title>
      <link>https://physicsworld.com/a/quantum-cryptography-network-spans-4600-km-in-china/</link>
      <description>Fibre and satellite links connect four major cities</description>
      <author> (Hamish Johnston
							is an online editor of Physics World)</author>
      <guid>https://physicsworld.com/a/quantum-cryptography-network-spans-4600-km-in-china/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 16:06:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The COM static store, part 4: Aggregating into a single object | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210211-00/?p=104845</link>
      <description>So far, we’ve been looking at how you can use the COM static store to hold a singleton which will be run down when COM uninitializes. But what if you have a lot of things you want to save? I mean,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210211-00/?p=104845</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 16:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I don&amp;#39;t use the &amp;quot;else&amp;quot; keyword in my code anymore</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_ougvb8mT7k</link>
      <description>Subscribe: http://bit.ly/ChapsasSubBecome a Patreon and get source code access: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsasHello everybody I&amp;#39;m Nick and in this video...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
    

    
      
    Nick Chapsas
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_ougvb8mT7k</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 15:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is now telling users that its iOS apps are out of date (despite no updates being available) – product considerations</title>
      <link>https://spencerdailey.com/2021/02/10/google-itself-is-now-telling-users-their-apps-are-out-of-date-despite-no-updates-being-available/</link>
      <description>[Update: Users can’t reproduce this any longer, as they have pushed a server-side fix for this issue. It still counts as an embarrassing failure by Google. If you would like to see what the bug looked like, there’s a video at the bottom of the article.]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://spencerdailey.com/2021/02/10/google-itself-is-now-telling-users-their-apps-are-out-of-date-despite-no-updates-being-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 14:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beej&amp;#39;s Guide to Network Programming</title>
      <link>https://beej.us/guide/bgnet/html/</link>
      <description>Hey! Socket programming got you down? Is this stuff just a little too difficult to figure out from the man pages? You want to do cool Internet programming, but you don’t have time to wade through a gob of structs trying to figure out if you have to call bind() before you connect(), etc., etc.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://beej.us/guide/bgnet/html/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 14:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>satwikkansal/wtfpython</title>
      <link>https://github.com/satwikkansal/wtfpython</link>
      <description>What the f*ck Python? Contribute to satwikkansal/wtfpython development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (satwikkansal)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/satwikkansal/wtfpython</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 13:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to remote desktop fullscreen RDP with just SOME of your multiple monitors</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/how-to-remote-desktop-fullscreen-rdp-with-just-some-of-your-multiple-monitors</link>
      <description>I saw this over on the Microsoft Remote Desktop Uservoice Allow ability to ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/how-to-remote-desktop-fullscreen-rdp-with-just-some-of-your-multiple-monitors</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 13:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exporting Open Telemetry Data to Jaeger</title>
      <link>https://rehansaeed.com/exporting-open-telemetry-data-to-jaeger/</link>
      <description>How to optimally export Open Telemetry metrics, logs, and traces for .NET to Jaeger.</description>
      <author> (Muhammad Rehan Saeed)</author>
      <guid>https://rehansaeed.com/exporting-open-telemetry-data-to-jaeger/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 13:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tusdotnet - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/83/tusdotnet</link>
      <description>tusdotnet is a .NET server implementation of the tus protocol for resumable file uploads over http(s). It supports all major extensions of tus and runs on both .NET 4.x and .NET Core and on both OWIN and ASP.NET Core.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/83/tusdotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 12:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>system76/launch</title>
      <link>https://github.com/system76/launch</link>
      <description>System76 Launch Configurable Keyboard. Contribute to system76/launch development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (system76)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/system76/launch</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 10:06:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do You Write Code With Your Mouse?</title>
      <link>https://themouseless.dev/</link>
      <description>Build Your Mouseless Development Environment</description>
      <author> (About The Author)</author>
      <guid>https://themouseless.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 10:06:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>spec: add generic programming using type parameters &amp;#183; Issue #43651 &amp;#183; golang/go</title>
      <link>https://github.com/golang/go/issues/43651#issuecomment-776944155</link>
      <description>We propose adding support for type parameters to Go. This will change the Go language to support a form of generic programming. A detailed design draft has already been published, with input from m...</description>
      <author> (golang)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/golang/go/issues/43651#issuecomment-776944155</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 10:06:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>