<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Chemical Formulas</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3040/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3040/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 03:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trouble with Bryan Johnson</title>
      <link>https://blog.jakobschwichtenberg.com/p/the-trouble-with-bryan-johnson</link>
      <description>Right now Longevity influencer Bryan Johnson is speedrunning through that famous Eric Hoffer quote:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jakobschwichtenberg.com/p/the-trouble-with-bryan-johnson</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sewell&amp;#39;s Pump | The Eli Whitney Museum and Workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.eliwhitney.org/gilbert/sewells-pump</link>
      <description>by William W. L. Glenn, M.D.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.eliwhitney.org/gilbert/sewells-pump</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&amp;#39;re Not the CEO of the Product: Rants of a PM</title>
      <link>https://scifilogan.bearblog.dev/youre-not-the-ceo-of-the-product-rants-of-a-pm/</link>
      <description>The most common thing I hear about the Product Manager job is that you are in effect a CEO of the product. My hottest take is this is about the furthest you ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scifilogan.bearblog.dev/youre-not-the-ceo-of-the-product-rants-of-a-pm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern iOS Theming with UITraitCollection</title>
      <link>https://dlo.me/archives/2025/01/20/theming-ios-apps-uitraitcollection/</link>
      <description>Learn how to implement dynamic theming in your iOS app using `UITraitAppearance` introduced in iOS 17. This comprehensive guide covers everything from setting up a simple light and dark theme to applying trait overrides for seamless switching. Download the sample code from GitHub to get started and enhance your app&amp;#39;s UI today.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dlo.me/archives/2025/01/20/theming-ios-apps-uitraitcollection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I got a heat pump, and my energy bill went up!</title>
      <link>https://www.heatpumped.org/p/i-got-a-heat-pump-and-my-energy-bill-went-up</link>
      <description>Heat pumps save energy, but does that mean that they save money? It’s important to understand the differences in cost between electricity and gas.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.heatpumped.org/p/i-got-a-heat-pump-and-my-energy-bill-went-up</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking Beyond HackerNews</title>
      <link>https://aien.me/looking-beyond-hackernews/</link>
      <description>A curated list of alternative tech communities and news sources for expanding your digital horizons and diversifying your daily tech reading.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aien.me/looking-beyond-hackernews/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debugging An Undebuggable App</title>
      <link>https://bryce.co/undebuggable/</link>
      <description>This app has a surprising number of anti-debugging protections. Let&amp;#39;s figure out how to bypass them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bryce.co/undebuggable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing a DSL for Terminal Interaction</title>
      <link>https://noelwelsh.com/posts/codata-interpreter-terminal/</link>
      <description>In this post we&amp;#39;ll build a DSL for terminal interaction. The terminal is familiar to most programmers, and terminal applications are common for developer focused tools. Most terminal features are controlled by writing specially formatted text. However, applications benefit from higher-level abstractions, motivating libraries that present a more ergonomic interface1. Our implementation will showcase codata interpreters, monads, and the central role of designing for composition and reasoning.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://noelwelsh.com/posts/codata-interpreter-terminal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering Call Of Duty Anti-Cheat</title>
      <link>https://ssno.cc/posts/reversing-tac-1-4-2025/</link>
      <description>I’ve been reversing Black Ops Cold War for a while now, and I’ve finally decided to share my research regarding the user-mode anti-cheat inside the game. It’s not my intention to shame or promote cheating/bypassing of the anti-cheat, so I’ve redacted a few things.
To clear up any confusion, Black Ops Cold War does not have the kernel-mode component of Ricochet that Modern Warfare (2019) and later titles have. I’ll be referring to the anti-cheat as TAC (Treyarch Anti-Cheat) as the game I reversed is a Treyarch game. Also, whenever I provide function pseudocode, it will be the best I can do since the actual decompilation is super cluttered with a lot of junk/resolving code. The biggest difference between the newer games is the kernel-mode driver, while the majority of anti-cheat code is user-mode and very similar to TAC.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ssno.cc/posts/reversing-tac-1-4-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling strangers uncle and auntie</title>
      <link>https://solmaz.io/calling-strangers-uncle-and-auntie</link>
      <description>Cultures can be categorized across many axes, and one of them is whether you can call an older male stranger uncle or female stranger auntie. For example, calling a shopkeeper uncle might be sympathetic in Singapore, whereas doing the same in Germany (Onkel) might get a negative reaction: “I’m not your uncle”.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://solmaz.io/calling-strangers-uncle-and-auntie</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing a handful of sensors for your next DIY project</title>
      <link>https://olegtarasov.me/environmental-sensors/</link>
      <description>I test the performance of different environmental sensors for a room thermostat DIY project</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://olegtarasov.me/environmental-sensors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plank Reloaded: Still Stupidly Simple</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.greyh.at/posts/plank-reloaded/</link>
      <description>When Plank first emerged, it promised to be the simplest dock on the planet. Today, Plank Reloaded carries that torch forward, bringing modern updates and solid Cinnamon desktop support while maintaining that same commitment to simplicity.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thoughts.greyh.at/posts/plank-reloaded/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programing Pipelines Using Dependent Types</title>
      <link>https://andrevidela.com/blog/2025/program-pipelines.idr/</link>
      <description>Sometimes, writing a large program is conceptually as simple as translating from a big unstructured input into a more and more structured output. In this post, we present a data structure to talk about such programs and demonstrate its use and flexbility using a single-pass compiler as case-study.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrevidela.com/blog/2025/program-pipelines.idr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ribbon mic – kHz</title>
      <link>https://khz.ac/sound/ribbon-mic/</link>
      <description>i would have used 2.5 μm 1000-grade aluminum foil, but the only quantities
easily available on the internet are small, expensive, 6-by-12 cm rectangles
sold specifically for reribboning microphones. since i had an interest in
keeping this microphone cheap and repeatable, i wanted something a little more
reliable as a source. so, naturally, i turned to alibaba. after speaking to
around eight suppliers, i found that either:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://khz.ac/sound/ribbon-mic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How breaking invisible family pacts forge unstoppable founders.</title>
      <link>https://josef.cn/blog/invisible-pact</link>
      <description>Why founders who defy family expectations become the most relentless ones</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://josef.cn/blog/invisible-pact</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices are Dead. Long Live Best Practices.</title>
      <link>https://jonpauluritis.com/articles/best-practices-are-dead-long-live-best-practices/</link>
      <description>Went down a rabbithole on the old web and I learned that &amp;#39;Bloodletting&amp;#39; was a common medical procedure for the better part of 3000 years. I&amp;#39;m kind of spellbound by the duration- it was one hell of a lindy effect. Our first evidence of its use appeared in Egypt...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jonpauluritis.com/articles/best-practices-are-dead-long-live-best-practices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The algorithm isn&amp;#39;t always to blame</title>
      <link>https://mijndertstuij.nl/posts/the-algorithm-not-always-to-blame/</link>
      <description>We can&amp;#39;t blame the algorithm for the state of the internet, not for all of it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mijndertstuij.nl/posts/the-algorithm-not-always-to-blame/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sizing up MI300A’s GPU</title>
      <link>https://chipsandcheese.com/p/sizing-up-mi300as-gpu</link>
      <description>AMD’s Instinct MI300A is a giant APU, created by swapping out two GPU chiplets (XCDs) for three CPU chiplets (CCDs).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chipsandcheese.com/p/sizing-up-mi300as-gpu</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyeing with woad – Salt extraction method</title>
      <link>https://marinaskua.com/blogs/marinaskua/dyeing-with-woad-salt-extraction-method</link>
      <description>This year I&amp;#39;ve got into gardening in a big way, partially inspired by my wish to grow my own dye plants. I have an abundance of calendula and coreopsis, which will yield golden-yellow, green and maybe orange. I have a couple of madder plants that I&amp;#39;ll eventually harvest for their roots, giving a lovely red. And back in spring, I sowed some woad seeds in the hope of growing my own blue dye. I opted for woad rather than the more potent indigo partially out of a bit of nostalgia&amp;#160;for our British textiles history, and partially knowing that the plants do well in our climate.
Germination wasn&amp;#39;t great, but the ones that did sprout, I planted out in the garden. The plants have been growing over the summer, only slightly held back by the slugs and caterpillars that are currently running rampant.

I&amp;#39;ve never dyed with woad or indigo before –&amp;#160;both can be processed to produce&amp;#160;indigotin, the valuable blue pigment that&amp;#39;s so strongly associated with these plants. While I&amp;#39;d love to brew up a proper vat to extract those rich, deep blues, I definitely don&amp;#39;t have enough plants growing for a big enough harvest to make it worthwhile. Preparing a vat takes multiple steps, chemicals that I don&amp;#39;t have to hand, and a fair amount of time. But, inspired by Rebecca Desnos, I decided to try a less common method of extracting the pigment, using salt.&amp;#160;

I picked about half the leaves from each plant, resulting in 50 grams of fresh leaves. That&amp;#39;s convenient because my wool yarn is&amp;#160;in 50 gram skeins, and I use 1:1 as a ratio of dyestuff to fibre when trying out new dye material. It&amp;#39;s usually a good starting point, and I use the results to inform the quantities I use for future batches.&amp;#160;
I washed the leaves and, in a stainless steel bowl (which is non-reactive so won&amp;#39;t affect the dye colour), tore them into small pieces. In the meantime I put a couple of skeins in an alum and cream of tartar mordant bath to simmer while I prepared the woad.&amp;#160;

I sprinkled&amp;#160;some salt over the torn leaves – I wish I could tell you how much salt, but I eyeballed it. I&amp;#39;m terrible like that. Maybe you can see from the photo roughly the amount I used.

Next is the fun bit. The salt draws moisture out of the leaves – much like preparing vegetables like aubergine and courgette to avoid sogginess when&amp;#160;cooking. In order to extract as much water – and colour – out of the leaves, you need to squish them up.&amp;#160;

On first contact with the salt a small amount of green liquid started seeping out of the leaves, and squishing with my hands drew out loads of deep green juice. There&amp;#39;s something immensely satisfying about the process of squeezing and crushing the leaves, foamy green dye oozing out between your fingers, leaving little clumps of wilted leaves.&amp;#160;
Once I was satisfied that not much more pigment was coming out of the leaves, it was times to add the damp, mordanted yarn. I used my Mendip 4-Ply in Sheep (Sunny).

I put the yarn in the bowl, trying to maximise contact between the dye liquid and the wool. Breaking up the clumps of leaves and pressing them into the yarn, kneading the pigment into the skein while taking care to avoid tangles, was good fun.

At this stage things are all still decidedly green in colour, bright and fresh. I was looking out for a colour change, ultimately expecting a colour in the turquoise–teal range. I wasn&amp;#39;t expecting a very strong colour, as the&amp;#160;amounts of dye in woad are a lot less concentrated than in indigo.

As I kept squeezing and turning the yarn to try and get even coverage,&amp;#160;it did seem that the colour was shifting very slightly. The leaves dried up after a while, so I removed the yarn and added a little more salt in the hope of extracting a little more colour.&amp;#160;

After some more kneading of the leaf scraps, it seemed to work! I was able to get a bit more moisture out, which helped even out and strengthen the colour on the yarn.&amp;#160;

As the colour was exposed to oxygen it definitely started turning a bit more teal.&amp;#160;Once I got about as much coverage as I thought I was going to get, I decided to fix the colour with some heat. This may not be necessary, but I tend to be a bit belt-and-braces about these things. I wrapped up the skein&amp;#160;loosely in a compostable carrier&amp;#160;bag and put it in the microwave for a minute.&amp;#160;

On unwrapping the skein, the colour change was immediately noticeable, as was a strong smell. Woad is a brassica, much like cabbage, broccoli and kale. You can probably imagine it! Now that the dyeing process was finished, I hung the yarn up to dry. Usually I&amp;#39;d let the yarn sit in the dye bath until the water is completely cold, but as there wasn&amp;#39;t a typical dye bath here, I decided to let the skein dry completely, and rinse it a couple of days later.&amp;#160;
I had heard that woad, prepared using a standard method for natural dyes, can yield pinky-apricot colours. Not entirely optimistically, I boiled up some water to pour over the seemingly spent woad leaves, thinking I didn&amp;#39;t have much to lose if nothing happened.&amp;#160;

An eerie blue tinge was evident, looking like copper sulphate, which was encouraging that there was at least still a little pigment left in the leaves. I added this to a pan with warm water and a fresh mordanted skein of the same wool yarn. Leaving the pan on low heat, I really didn&amp;#39;t expect much – maybe there was a slight yellowy tinge appearing. Then returning a while later I was amazed to find the peachy tones I had read about!&amp;#160;

I left the yarn to cool overnight before rinsing both skeins. Both colours became a little paler, which I&amp;#160;expected, but there was very little colour run-off into the water and the resulting shades are quite lovely.&amp;#160;

&amp;#160;As a not-at-all-experienced dye plant grower, I can definitely say that woad has earned its place in my garden. The blue tones are rare and invaluable – and to be able to use the spent leaves for a completely different colour is a massive bonus! I&amp;#39;ll be sowing a lot more seeds next year and have an area dedicated to woad, and hopefully then I&amp;#39;ll have enough to harvest for a real vat to aim for those deep blues!&amp;#160;
&amp;#160;For more yarn and craft related projects, consider subscribing on Patreon where I post a making video every month. If you enjoyed this post, you can buy me a coffee on Ko-fi&amp;#160;as a thank-you.&amp;#160;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marinaskua.com/blogs/marinaskua/dyeing-with-woad-salt-extraction-method</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-01-20 office of secure transportation</title>
      <link>https://computer.rip/2025-01-20-office-of-secure-transportation.html</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve seen them at least twice on /r/whatisthisthing, a good couple dozen times
on the road, and these days, even in press photos: GMC trucks with custom
square boxes on the back, painted dark blue, with US Government &amp;quot;E&amp;quot; plates.
These courier escorts, &amp;quot;unmarked&amp;quot; but about as subtle as a Crown Vic with a
bull bar, are perhaps the most conspicuous part of an obscure office of a
secretive agency. One that seems chronically underfunded but carries out a
remarkable task: shipping nuclear weapons.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://computer.rip/2025-01-20-office-of-secure-transportation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we&amp;#160;made Blurhash 128x faster — Uploadcare Blog</title>
      <link>https://uploadcare.com/blog/faster-blurhash/</link>
      <description>Blurhash creates compact blurred image previews as ASCII strings. Alex Karpinsky of Uploadcare made it 128x faster.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://uploadcare.com/blog/faster-blurhash/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Write. | rugu</title>
      <link>https://www.rugu.dev/en/blog/write/</link>
      <description>Written at 2025-01-20</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.rugu.dev/en/blog/write/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to solve computational science problems with AI: Physics-Informed Neural Networks (PINNs)</title>
      <link>https://mertkavi.com/how-to-solve-computational-science-problems-with-ai-physics-informed-neural-networks-pinns/</link>
      <description>Disclaimer: Any opinions expressed are solely my own.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mertkavi.com/how-to-solve-computational-science-problems-with-ai-physics-informed-neural-networks-pinns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am (not) a Failure: Lessons Learned From Six (and a half) Failed Startup Attempts</title>
      <link>http://blog.rongarret.info/2025/01/i-am-not-failure-lessons-learned-from.html</link>
      <description>A while back I wrote : I&amp;#39;ve had many, many failures in my life.&amp;#160; (Hm, maybe I should write a blog post about that.) This is that post.&amp;#160; I&amp;#39;m ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://blog.rongarret.info/2025/01/i-am-not-failure-lessons-learned-from.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI quietly funded independent math benchmark before setting record with o3</title>
      <link>https://the-decoder.com/openai-quietly-funded-independent-math-benchmark-before-setting-record-with-o3/</link>
      <description>OpenAI&amp;#39;s involvement in funding FrontierMath, a leading AI math benchmark, only came to light when the company announced its record-breaking performance on the test. Now, the benchmark&amp;#39;s developer Epoch AI acknowledges they should have been more transparent about the relationship.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://the-decoder.com/openai-quietly-funded-independent-math-benchmark-before-setting-record-with-o3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 23:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EF Core 9.0: Reading EntityConfigurations from Classes with Non-Public Constructors</title>
      <link>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2025/01/ef-core-90-reading-entityconfigurations.html</link>
      <description>.NET, ASP.NET Core, Visual Studio, Azure, Jaliya Udagedara</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaliyaudagedara.blogspot.com/2025/01/ef-core-90-reading-entityconfigurations.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 23:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixxx - Free DJ Mixing Software App</title>
      <link>https://mixxx.org/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mixxx.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 20:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coworking, recording, and periodic chat</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FHNXbLPgBqQ</link>
      <description>&amp;#128172; JOIN US ON DISCORD 
Join the Build With Me Discord: https://bbb.dev/discord

&amp;#129489;‍&amp;#128187; LET&amp;#39;S CONNECT ON SOCIAL
Twitch: https://twitch.com/baldbeardedbuilder
BlueSky: https://bsky.app/profile/baldbeardedbuilder.com
TikTok: https://tiktok.com/@baldbeardedbuilder
Twitter: https://twitter.com/michaeljolley
Instagram: https://instagram.com/baldbeardedbuilder
Blog: https://baldbeardedbuilder.com

&amp;#128187; WHAT DO I USE?
All the gear/software I use is listed at https://bbb.dev/uses</description>
      <author> (Bald. Bearded. Builder.)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=FHNXbLPgBqQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 19:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Met Paul Graham Once</title>
      <link>http://okayfail.com/2025/i-met-pg-once.html</link>
      <description>Are tech industry leaders going to discriminate against me?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://okayfail.com/2025/i-met-pg-once.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 18:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a web app with C#</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=GLZKccCl_Vc</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Let&amp;#39;s work on SharpSite, an open source CMS that you can contribute to and learn from.  https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/SharpSite</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=GLZKccCl_Vc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 18:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block AI scrapers with Anubis</title>
      <link>https://xeiaso.net/blog/2025/anubis/</link>
      <description>I got tired with all the AI scrapers that were bullying my git server, so I made a tool to stop them for good.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xeiaso.net/blog/2025/anubis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s talk about FluentAssertions and OSS &amp;#128308; LIVE</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2iOuj3Ra8iU</link>
      <description>Check out my courses: https://dometrain.com
Support the stream: https://streamlabs.com/nick_chapsas

Become a Patreon and get source code access: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsas

Don&amp;#39;t forget to comment, like and subscribe :)

Social Media:
Follow me on GitHub: http://bit.ly/ChapsasGitHub
Follow me on Twitter: http://bit.ly/ChapsasTwitter
Connect on LinkedIn: http://bit.ly/ChapsasLinkedIn

Keep coding merch: https://keepcoding.shop

#csharp #dotnet</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2iOuj3Ra8iU</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbage Collection in C# vs. Ownership in Rust – Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/memory-wars-garbage-collection-in-c-vs-ownership-in-rust/</link>
      <description>Regarding memory management, programming languages take different approaches to ensure your applications don’t crash and burn. Think of it as cleaning up after a party: C# hires a janitor (garbage collector) to tidy up for you while Rust hands you a checklist and says, “You’ve got this.” Both methods work, but they have their quirks. Let’s dive into how memory is handled in these two languages and what makes each approach unique.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/memory-wars-garbage-collection-in-c-vs-ownership-in-rust/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-R1</title>
      <link>https://github.com/deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-R1</link>
      <description>Contribute to deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-R1 development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-R1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion Cache in C# - Removal, Expiration, and FailSafe Cache Operations</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wmvEFWSE49g</link>
      <description>Fusion Cache is an awesome third-party package that we can use in DotNet for both in-memory and distributed caches.

Let&amp;#39;s dive into how the removal and expiration of cache entries work alongside the fail-safe mechanism!

----
&amp;#128273; Membership &amp;amp; Subscriptions:
- &amp;#128232; Weekly Newsletter: https://weekly.devleader.ca
- &amp;#127960;️ Private Discord Community: https://sidestack.io/devleader

&amp;#129504; Courses:
- All Courses: https://www.devleader.ca/courses
- Get Promoted As A Software Engineer: https://dometrain.com/course/career-getting-promoted-as-a-software-engineer/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Nailing The Behavioral Interview: https://dometrain.com/course/career-nailing-the-behavioral-interview/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Getting Started with C#: https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- Deep dive C#: https://dometrain.com/course/deep-dive-csharp?ref=nick-cosentino
- C# Zero to Hero BUNDLE: https://dometrain.com/bundle/from-zero-to-hero-csharp/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Reflection in .NET: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-reflection-in-dotnet/?ref=nick-cosentino
- Refactoring For C# Devs: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-refactoring-for-csharp-developers?ref=nick-cosentino
- [FREE] Intro to Software Development: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLzATctVhnsggb3lj53T8fJSK6LJQFUyKS

&amp;#128483;️ Social Media &amp;amp; Links:
- All My Links: https://linktr.ee/devleader
- Vlogs:  @DevLeaderBTS @CodeCommute 
- Blog: https://www.devleader.ca/
- TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@devleader
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickcosentino
- Threads: https://threads.net/@dev.leader
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevLeaderCa
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/DevLeaderCa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/dev.leader
- GitHub: https://github.com/ncosentino/
- Twitch: https://twitch.tv/devleaderca
- YouTube: https://youtube.com/@DevLeader?sub_confirmation=1

❤️ Affiliations &amp;amp; Products/Services That I Love:
- @BrandGhostAI for all of my content creation: https://brandghost.ai
- AI shorts helper Opus Clip: https://opus.pro/?via=2f9e97
- VPS hosting from RackNerd: https://my.racknerd.com/aff.php?aff=9013
- VPS hosting from Contabo: https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-101028632-12454592
- Newsletter platform ConvertKit: https://convertkit.com/?lmref=c5X7KQ
- Newsletter referral system SparkLoop: https://dash.sparkloop.app/signup?aff=9fe76c8b
----

#softwareengineering #softwaredeveloper #softwareengineer</description>
      <author> (Dev Leader)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wmvEFWSE49g</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please Don&amp;#39;t Force Dark Mode — Vishnu&amp;#39;s Pages</title>
      <link>https://iamvishnu.com/posts/please-dont-force-dark-mode</link>
      <description>Dear website designers,  Please don’t force dark mode on your users. If dark mode is a characteristic of your brand, please ensure you choose a comfortable...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iamvishnu.com/posts/please-dont-force-dark-mode</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 12:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK&amp;#39;s elite hardware talent is being wasted.</title>
      <link>https://josef.cn/blog/uk-talent</link>
      <description>Imperial, Oxford, and Cambridge produce world-class engineers. Yet post-graduation, their trajectory is an economic tragedy - and a hidden arbitrage opportunity.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://josef.cn/blog/uk-talent</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 10:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering Bambu Connect - Consumer Action Taskforce</title>
      <link>https://wiki.rossmanngroup.com/wiki/Reverse_Engineering_Bambu_Connect</link>
      <description>Please note that all submissions to the site are subject to the wiki&amp;#39;s licence, CC 4.0 BY-SA, as found here</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wiki.rossmanngroup.com/wiki/Reverse_Engineering_Bambu_Connect</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 09:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape the walled garden and algorithm black boxes with RSS feeds</title>
      <link>https://www.johnwalker.nl/posts/escape-the-walled-garden-with-rss</link>
      <description>Take control of your content consumption with RSS and Atom feeds. Escape algorithmic black boxes, gain more control over what and how you consume in order to be more intentional with your media consumption.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.johnwalker.nl/posts/escape-the-walled-garden-with-rss</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 06:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cache CORS Preflight Requests</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/5fc7cb62-d5ad-4f07-831c-d6c1c6974641</link>
      <description>Almost all applications are using CORS (Cross-Origin Resource Sharing) to allow the client to access the resources from the server. When the client sends a request to the server, the server will respond with the Access-Control-Allow-Origin header to allow the client to access the resources.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/5fc7cb62-d5ad-4f07-831c-d6c1c6974641</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 05:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>