<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How I got Claude to write code I could actually ship</title>
      <link>https://graphite.dev/blog/how-i-got-claude-to-write-better-code</link>
      <description>Teach AI agents to break down monolithic, AI-generated diffs into clear, focused, reviewable pull requests using Graphite’s gt mcp.</description>
      <guid>https://graphite.dev/blog/how-i-got-claude-to-write-better-code</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jola.dev - When Software Engineers Think They Need More Focus Time</title>
      <link>https://jola.dev/posts/enough-focus-time</link>
      <description>Johanna Larsson is a software engineer, manager, writer, speaker. With over 14 years of experience in software development and management, she has worked with clients from various industries, including finance, healthcare, and education. She is passionate about creating innovative solutions that solve real-world problems. She is also an advocate for diversity and inclusion in the tech industry. She believes that technology can be a force for good and strives to make a positive impact in the world. She is committed to using her skills and expertise to create a better future for all.</description>
      <guid>https://jola.dev/posts/enough-focus-time</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Wasting Time | Stephan Joppich</title>
      <link>https://stephanjoppich.com/wasting-time/</link>
      <description>When I was a teenager, I spent my entire free time playing video games. Mostly League of Legends but also Call of Duty, Age of Empires, or Minecraft. This wasn’t a casual hobby. It was an obsession. I would come home from school, toss my backpack into the corner, boot up my computer, and play — often late into the night. School […]</description>
      <guid>https://stephanjoppich.com/wasting-time/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Deep Noodle Blog | The Realities of Semantic Search</title>
      <link>https://deepnoodle.ai/blog/the-realities-of-semantic-search</link>
      <description>Why semantic search isn't a silver bullet, and practical tips for building search interfaces.</description>
      <guid>https://deepnoodle.ai/blog/the-realities-of-semantic-search</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replacing cron jobs with a centralized task scheduler</title>
      <link>https://mayhul.com/posts/scheduled-tasks/</link>
      <description>A brief description of our task scheduling system</description>
      <author> (Mayhul Arora)</author>
      <guid>https://mayhul.com/posts/scheduled-tasks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Their ID</title>
      <link>https://use-their-id.com/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://use-their-id.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I’m Giving Up My Design Title—And What That Says About The Future of Design — Suff Syed</title>
      <link>https://www.suffsyed.com/futurememo/why-im-leaving-design</link>
      <description>Suff Syed, former Head of Product Design, announces his shift to a technical role, arguing that design has been commoditized in the AI era while technical depth is now where innovation happens. He argues design has become baseline, while innovation now lies in systems, agents, and orchestration. The</description>
      <guid>https://www.suffsyed.com/futurememo/why-im-leaving-design</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Useless useCallback</title>
      <link>https://tkdodo.eu/blog/the-useless-use-callback</link>
      <description>Why most memoization is downright useless...</description>
      <guid>https://tkdodo.eu/blog/the-useless-use-callback</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do support that doesn’t scale</title>
      <link>https://www.stedi.com/blog/do-support-that-doesnt-scale</link>
      <description>Many companies hurt their support by scaling too soon with tools meant for volume, not quality. This piece explores a different approach – one focused on speed, empathy, and fixing root causes.</description>
      <guid>https://www.stedi.com/blog/do-support-that-doesnt-scale</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model2Vec as a fasttext alternative - Minish Blog &amp; Documentation</title>
      <link>https://minish.ai/blog/2025-07-28-fasttext</link>
      <description>Model2Vec is typically viewed as a fast alternative to a sentence transformer. There’s a good reason for that, because:</description>
      <guid>https://minish.ai/blog/2025-07-28-fasttext</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Robot Vacuums</title>
      <link>https://rishikeshs.com/robot-vacuums/</link>
      <description>Notes I collected while shopping for a robot vacuum - all the confusing features and tech I had to figure out.</description>
      <guid>https://rishikeshs.com/robot-vacuums/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obsidian Tricks: Entity Notes</title>
      <link>https://adventures.michaelfbryan.com/posts/obsidian-tricks/entity-notes/</link>
      <description>An entity is a person, place, or organization that you want to track in your Second Brain. By creating separate notes in your Obsidian vault for each entity and using the power of backlinks, you can create a rich, interconnected knowledge base.</description>
      <guid>https://adventures.michaelfbryan.com/posts/obsidian-tricks/entity-notes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Blueprint For A Modern Day LLM</title>
      <link>https://nofone.io/llm-blueprint</link>
      <description>Modern day LLMs stack started from a Transformer architecture, most refined &amp; revolutionized by the attention mechanism as provided in 'Attention is All You Need'. The basic idea is that you can avoid using compute heavy models like RNNs by creating Query, Key, Value matrices that represent different relationships between tokens (i.e., 'words') Since then, there has been a ton of advancement and research into how to develop capabilities like chat-like responses, reasoning, long-context, etc.</description>
      <guid>https://nofone.io/llm-blueprint</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Real Ask</title>
      <link>https://frederickvanbrabant.com/blog/2025-07-22-the-real-ask/</link>
      <description>When someone comes to you with a question to do something, instead of blindly doing the ask, take a step back and try to understand what they actually want to achieve. Often this task might actually not be the best way to achieve the goal they are set out to do.</description>
      <guid>https://frederickvanbrabant.com/blog/2025-07-22-the-real-ask/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>thoughts on “do 100 thing” - Tasshin</title>
      <link>https://tasshin.com/blog/thoughts-on-do-100-thing/</link>
      <description>here’s a bunch of running thoughts on the "do 100 thing" challenge idea, on what I’ve learned so far, what works for me &amp; might for U as well!!!</description>
      <guid>https://tasshin.com/blog/thoughts-on-do-100-thing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs can now identify public figures in images</title>
      <link>https://minimaxir.com/2025/07/llms-identify-people/</link>
      <description>ChatGPT and Claude won’t, but Gemini will.</description>
      <guid>https://minimaxir.com/2025/07/llms-identify-people/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You are what you measure (even in open source) | DUNK</title>
      <link>https://nikodunk.com/2025-06-10-you-are-what-you-measure</link>
      <description>Transparency in open-source software A lot of effort is wasted in volunteering. Especially when people are giving away their time for free, I think we need to be just as careful as what we point their time at as if they were charging for their time. For solo projects, there’s...</description>
      <guid>https://nikodunk.com/2025-06-10-you-are-what-you-measure</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Rewriting Training Data Improved Kimi 2’s Performance</title>
      <link>https://www.dbreunig.com/2025/07/27/kimi-applies-rephrasing-to-pre-training-data.html</link>
      <description>Two weeks ago, Beijing-based Moonshot AI launched Kimi K2, an open source model that rivaled the coding capabilities of larger, closed models. It’s a really impressive model (though it’s coding capabilities have since been overshadowed by Qwen 3 Coder), especially since it’s cheaper to run than Claude 3.5 Haiku.</description>
      <guid>https://www.dbreunig.com/2025/07/27/kimi-applies-rephrasing-to-pre-training-data.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unconventional Computing Systems: Macro Computing - Technologist &amp; Entrepreneur</title>
      <link>https://igorkomolov.com/projects/unconventional-computing-systems-macro-computing/</link>
      <description>Exploring computing systems built using unconventional, large-scale materials and methods.</description>
      <guid>https://igorkomolov.com/projects/unconventional-computing-systems-macro-computing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural-Demographic Theory</title>
      <link>https://peterturchin.com/structural-demographic-theory/</link>
      <description>The causes of revolutions and major rebellions are in many ways similar to processes that cause earthquakes (Goldstone 1991: 35). In both revolutions and earthquakes it is useful to distinguish the…</description>
      <guid>https://peterturchin.com/structural-demographic-theory/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't use external CSS: (Maurycy's blog)</title>
      <link>https://maurycyz.com/misc/inline_css/</link>
      <description>No adblocker detected. Consider using an extention like uBlock Origin to save time and bandwidth. Click here to close.</description>
      <guid>https://maurycyz.com/misc/inline_css/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kite Incident</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3121/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3121/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terence Tao (@tao@mathstodon.xyz)</title>
      <link>https://mathstodon.xyz/@tao/114915604830689046</link>
      <description>In the field of cybersecurity, a distinction is made between the "blue team" task of building a secure system, and the "red team" task of locating vulnerabilities in such systems.  The blue team is more obviously necessary to create the desired product; but the red team is just as essential, given the damage that can result from deploying insecure systems.

The nature of these teams mirror each other; mathematicians would call them "dual".  The output of a blue team is only as strong as its weakest link: a security system that consists of a strong component and a weak component (e.g., a house with a securely locked door, but an open window) will be insecure (and in fact worse, because the strong component may convey a false sense of security).  Dually, the contributions to a red team can often be additive: a red team report that contains both a serious vulnerability and a more trivial one is more useful than a report that only contains the serious issue, as it is valuable to have the blue team address both vulnerabilities. (But excessive low-quality reports can dilute attention from critical issues.) 

Because of this, unreliable contributors may be more useful in the "red team" side of a project than the "blue team" side, though the blue team can still accommodate such contributors provided that the red team is competent enough to catch almost all of the errors that the contributor to the blue team might make.  Also, unreliable red team contributions only add value if they _augment_ the output of more reliable members of that team, rather than _replace_ that output, and if their output can be effectively filtered or triaged by more experienced red team members. (1/3)</description>
      <guid>https://mathstodon.xyz/@tao/114915604830689046</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 19:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - 9001/copyparty: Portable file server with accelerated resumable uploads, dedup, WebDAV, FTP, TFTP, zeroconf, media indexer, thumbnails++ all in one file, no deps</title>
      <link>https://github.com/9001/copyparty</link>
      <description>Portable file server with accelerated resumable uploads, dedup, WebDAV, FTP, TFTP, zeroconf, media indexer, thumbnails++ all in one file, no deps - 9001/copyparty</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/9001/copyparty</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 19:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Embeddings Explained: A Visual and Intuitive Guide - a Hugging Face Space by hesamation</title>
      <link>https://huggingface.co/spaces/hesamation/primer-llm-embedding</link>
      <description>This app explains how language models transform text into meaningful representations through embeddings. It provides a visual guide to help you understand traditional and modern language model tech...</description>
      <guid>https://huggingface.co/spaces/hesamation/primer-llm-embedding</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPN use surges in UK as new online safety rules kick in</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/356674b0-9f1d-4f95-b1d5-f27570379a9b</link>
      <description>Jump in apps disguising internet users’ location threatens to undermine government efforts to protect children</description>
      <guid>https://www.ft.com/content/356674b0-9f1d-4f95-b1d5-f27570379a9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allianz Life says 'majority' of customers' personal data stolen in cyberattack | TechCrunch</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/07/26/allianz-life-says-majority-of-customers-personal-data-stolen-in-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Exclusive: Allianz Life said the "majority" of its customers and employees had data stolen in the July cyberattack. The company said it has notified the FBI.</description>
      <guid>https://techcrunch.com/2025/07/26/allianz-life-says-majority-of-customers-personal-data-stolen-in-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I hacked my washing machine - Nex's Blog</title>
      <link>https://nexy.blog/2025/07/27/how-i-hacked-my-washing-machine/</link>
      <description>I ran out of characters for microblogging so this is where the big words go</description>
      <guid>https://nexy.blog/2025/07/27/how-i-hacked-my-washing-machine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Architecture Tests for CancellationTokens and sealed classes</title>
      <link>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/feac44f3-2c6e-4994-80c3-e2a17efbb8f3</link>
      <description>Architectural Unit tests are nice to constraint your system (like which parts of your application can access other parts of your application). This blog post is not about that - that is covered a lot in the internet. No, I want to show what I did in a recent project: Checking if all controllers do use CancellationToken and some other entities are sealed.
</description>
      <guid>https://steven-giesel.com/blogPost/feac44f3-2c6e-4994-80c3-e2a17efbb8f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 06:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enough AI copilots! We need AI HUDs</title>
      <link>https://www.geoffreylitt.com/2025/07/27/enough-ai-copilots-we-need-ai-huds</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://www.geoffreylitt.com/2025/07/27/enough-ai-copilots-we-need-ai-huds</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 06:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>