<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>John Conway 1/6 [The Free Will Lectures] - Free Will and Determinism [2009]</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tmx2tpcdKZY</link>
      <description>Lecture 1 | Free Will Lecture Series | Meet John Conway; hear about Simon Kochen and how the theorem came about. Thoughts on senility. Free will and determinism in science and philosophy over the last two millennia; the implications of Newtonian and quantum mechanics. What Conway and Kochen mean by “free will.” What the theorem does, and doesn’t, imply about behavior. A brief introduction to the three underlying principles of the theorem: SPIN, FIN, and TWIN. The idea of talking to particles, and how it’s like playing 20 questions with your sisters.

The Free Will lectures
2009, Princeton University.

https://paw.princeton.edu/article/conway-lectures</description>
      <author> (Graduate Mathematics)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tmx2tpcdKZY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 08:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things That Turbo Pascal is Smaller Than</title>
      <link>https://prog21.dadgum.com/116.html</link>
      <description>Turbo Pascal 3 for MS-DOS was released in September 1986. Being version 3, there were lesser releases prior to it and flashier ones after, but 3 was a solid representation of the Turbo Pascal experience: a full Pascal compiler, including extensions that it made it practical for commercial use, tightly integrated with an editor. And the whole thing was lightning fast, orders of magnitude faster at building projects than Microsoft's compilers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://prog21.dadgum.com/116.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 08:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving away from GMail</title>
      <link>https://rolisz.ro/2020/04/11/moving-away-from-gmail/</link>
      <description>tl;dr: I like PurelyMail and I will slowly switch all my online accounts to use it. I've been using it for almost three months and I didn't have any issues (except with some Hotmail/Outlook addresses).  I have a GMail account since 2006 (that's the date of the first</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/rolisz)</author>
      <guid>https://rolisz.ro/2020/04/11/moving-away-from-gmail/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 07:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email provider got hacked, data of 600,000 users now sold on the dark web | ZDNet</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/email-provider-got-hacked-data-of-600000-users-now-sold-on-the-dark-web/</link>
      <description>Italian email provider Email.it confirms security breach.</description>
      <author> (https://twitter.com/campuscodi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.zdnet.com/article/email-provider-got-hacked-data-of-600000-users-now-sold-on-the-dark-web/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 05:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Memories" - 256 byte MSDOS intro</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Imquk_3oFf4</link>
      <description>the tiny megademo! 8 FX + MIDI soundscapes
download &amp; comment : https://www.pouet.net/prod.php?which=85227
shown April 2020 @ Revision Demoparty</description>
      <author> (Héll Mood)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Imquk_3oFf4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 05:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Death of Hype: What's Next for Scala</title>
      <link>http://www.lihaoyi.com/post/TheDeathofHypeWhatsNextforScala.html</link>
      <description>A recent tweet by a friend of mine noted how the public interest in the Scala programming language seems to have plateaued or waned, which matches my feeling of the latest trends and zeitgeist. This blog post will go into why I think that has happened, where Scala stands now, and what the future holds for the Scala community.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.lihaoyi.com/post/TheDeathofHypeWhatsNextforScala.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 03:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The limitations of Android N Encryption</title>
      <link>https://blog.cryptographyengineering.com/2016/11/24/android-n-encryption/</link>
      <description>Over the past few years we’ve heard more about smartphone encryption than, quite frankly, most of us expected to hear in a lifetime. We learned that proper encryption can slow down even sophi…</description>
      <author> (Matthew Green)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cryptographyengineering.com/2016/11/24/android-n-encryption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 01:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE EVIL OF 5G TECHNOLOGY - David Icke | London Real</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Nr-CFJJYB0</link>
      <description>BUSINESS ACCELERATOR - Open Now: https://londonreal.tv/biz/
2020 SUMMIT TICKETS: https://londonreal.tv/summit/


NEW MASTERCLASS EACH WEEK: http://londonreal.tv/masterclass-yt
David Icke is an English writer and public speaker, known since the 1990s as a professional conspiracy theorist calling himself a "full time investigator into WHO and WHAT is really controlling the world." 

As a former footballer, BBC sports television presenter, and spokesman for the Green Party, his interview on Terry Wogan’s show in 1991 turned him from a respected household name into a laughingstock across the country.

Now, he is the author of over 20 books and over 10 DVDs, and have lectured in over 25 countries, speaking live for up to 10 HOURS to huge audiences, filling stadiums like Wembley Arena.

His new movie Renegade, is the first ever feature film about his life and work.

Watch the FULL EPISODE here: https://londonreal.tv/e/david-icke-2/

DAVID ICKE

Website: https://www.davidicke.com/

Twitter: https://twitter.com/davidicke

Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/davidickeofficial/

About London Real: 
Founded by Brian Rose in 2011. London Real is the curator of people worth watching. Our mission is to promote personal transformation through inspiration, self-discovery and empowerment. 
We feature interesting guests with fascinating stories and unique perspectives on life. We aim to take viewers on a journey through the lives of others and ultimately inspire them to embark on one of their own.

Don't miss our weekly episodes, hit subscribe: http://bit.ly/SubscribeToLondonReal

Website: http://www.londonreal.tv

Facebook:https://www.facebook.com/LondonReal/

Instagram:https://www.instagram.com/therealbrianrose

London Real Academy: 
BUSINESS ACCELERATOR: https://londonreal.tv/biz
LIFE ACCELERATOR: https://londonreal.tv/life
BROADCAST YOURSELF: https://londonreal.tv/by
SPEAK TO INSPIRE: https://londonreal.tv/inspire 

TRIBE: Join a community of high-achievers on a mission to transform themselves and the world! https://londonreal.tv/tribe

#LondonReal #Motivation</description>
      <author> (London Real)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Nr-CFJJYB0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 01:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#badBIOS features explained</title>
      <link>https://blog.erratasec.com/2013/10/badbios-features-explained.html</link>
      <description>  Dan Goodin at Ars Technica has reported on Dragos Ruiu's " badBIOS " analysis. I thought I'd explain how some of this stuff works.      Fi...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.erratasec.com/2013/10/badbios-features-explained.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Voices Project</title>
      <link>https://voicesriseup.org/</link>
      <description>The Voices Project is a grassroots recovery advocacy organization that is changing the way America thinks about recovery, one voice at a time. End the silence, end addiction. Learn more and get involved.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://voicesriseup.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Accidentally Permanently Terminated My Account</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@alexhowlett/youtube-accidentally-permanently-terminated-my-account-4b5852c80679</link>
      <description>For the past two years, the Boston Basic Income YouTube channel has been live streaming our weekly discussion group as we explore…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@alexhowlett)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@alexhowlett/youtube-accidentally-permanently-terminated-my-account-4b5852c80679</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 23:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Borders to stay closed, travellers urged to 'see Australia first' once curbs ease</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/politics/federal/borders-to-stay-closed-travellers-urged-to-see-australia-first-once-curbs-ease-20200410-p54iw4.html</link>
      <description>Australians will have to wait until the end of this year or beyond to restart overseas travel amid estimates the coronavirus crisis has wiped out tourism worth $9 billion a month.</description>
      <author> (David Crowe)</author>
      <guid>https://www.smh.com.au/politics/federal/borders-to-stay-closed-travellers-urged-to-see-australia-first-once-curbs-ease-20200410-p54iw4.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 22:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Conway on Numberphile</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLt5AfwLFPxWIL8XA1npoNAHseS-j1y-7V</link>
      <description>The legendary John Conway</description>
      <author> (Numberphile
      
      

    
      Numberphile
    

    
    
    
  
        •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLt5AfwLFPxWIL8XA1npoNAHseS-j1y-7V</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 21:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life, Death and the Monster (John Conway) - Numberphile</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xOCe5HUObD4</link>
      <description>Acclaimed mathematician John H. Conway speaks about the mystery he'd most like to solve. Conway playlist: http://bit.ly/ConwayNumberphile
More links &amp; stuff in full description below ↓↓↓

Monster Group video: http://youtu.be/jsSeoGpiWsw
More John Conway videos, including Game of Life stuff: http://bit.ly/JohnConway

Support us on Patreon: http://www.patreon.com/numberphile

NUMBERPHILE
Website: http://www.numberphile.com/
Numberphile on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/numberphile
Numberphile tweets: https://twitter.com/numberphile
Subscribe: http://bit.ly/Numberphile_Sub

Numberphile is supported by the Mathematical Sciences Research Institute (MSRI): http://bit.ly/MSRINumberphile

Videos by Brady Haran

Brady's videos subreddit: http://www.reddit.com/r/BradyHaran/

Brady's latest videos across all channels: http://www.bradyharanblog.com/

Sign up for (occasional) emails: http://eepurl.com/YdjL9

Numberphile T-Shirts: https://teespring.com/stores/numberphile
Other merchandise: https://store.dftba.com/collections/numberphile</description>
      <author> (Numberphile)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xOCe5HUObD4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 21:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking my Sixth Form College network in 1991</title>
      <link>https://blog.oneunicorn.com/2020/04/10/nimbus/</link>
      <description>Hacking my school network in 1991</description>
      <author> (ajcvickers)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.oneunicorn.com/2020/04/10/nimbus/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 20:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artist Relief Submission Manager</title>
      <link>https://artistrelief.submittable.com/submit</link>
      <description>IMPORTANT: Due to a very high volume of submissions, the application may come down temporarily. We HIGHLY recommend that you draft your responses in a separate word processing program and paste it into the application to have a saved copy of your answers in the event that you need to reapply.

Before applying, we highly recommend reviewing our FAQ for questions related to eligibility, application, selection process, and disbursement.
To be eligible, you must be able to answer ”Yes“ to the prompts listed below. 

  I am a practicing artist able to demonstrate a sustained commitment to my work, career, and a public audience;
  I am experiencing dire financial need due to the COVID-19 pandemic
  I am 21 years of age or older
  I am legally able to receive taxable income in the U.S. (e.g. citizen, green card holder, and/or permanent resident who can provide a W9 and SSN or ITIN)
  I have been living and working in the U.S. for the last two years
  I am not a full-time employee, board member, director, officer, or immediate family member of any of the coalition partners
  I have not previously been awarded a relief grant from this fund

If eligible, you can apply below. If you’ve used Submittable before and have an existing account, you will need to enter your login credentials. If it’s your first time using Submittable, you will need to create a new account. This is a quick and simple process. If you have any technical issues on Submittable, please contact support@submittable.com. 
For all questions related to eligibility, application, selection process, and disbursement, please review our FAQ. For all other inquiries, email info@artistrelief.org but kindly expect a delay in response due to volume and capacity.</description>
      <author> (Submittable)</author>
      <guid>https://artistrelief.submittable.com/submit</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 19:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 50 Years of Effort, Researchers Made Silicon Emit Light</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/after-50-years-of-effort-researchers-made-silicon-emit-light/</link>
      <description>We’re approaching the speed limit for electronic computer chips. If we want to go faster, we’ll need data-carrying photons—and some tiny lasers.</description>
      <author> (Daniel Oberhaus)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wired.com/story/after-50-years-of-effort-researchers-made-silicon-emit-light/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 18:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Morning Breakfast Cereal - Anger</title>
      <link>https://www.smbc-comics.com/comic/anger</link>
      <description>Saturday Morning Breakfast Cereal - </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.smbc-comics.com/comic/anger</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 16:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Billion Views — Brady Haran</title>
      <link>https://www.bradyharanblog.com/blog/a-billion-views</link>
      <description>A nerdy, numbery milestone.  Our small  family of channels  has passed a billion views on YouTube.</description>
      <author> (by Brady Haran)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bradyharanblog.com/blog/a-billion-views</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 16:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIX: Making Computers Easier To Use -- AT&amp;T Archives film from 1982, Bell Laboratories</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XvDZLjaCJuw</link>
      <description>For more from the AT&amp;T Archives, visit http://techchannel.att.com/archives

The Unix System: Making Computers Easier to Use - 1982

This 23-minute film about UNIX was designed for students with an interest in engineering, math, computer science or other sciences. The film was made available to the public in December 1982. It covers different ways that UNIX could be employed practically in a computing environment. Another film about UNIX released at the same time, "The UNIX System: Making Computers More Productive," was aimed at computer science majors and corporate trainees, and presented a more detailed discussion of the UNIX system and its various applications.

Hosted by Victor Vyssotsky in a Carl-Sagan-esque turtleneck sweater, this film includes Dennis Ritchie, one of UNIX's inventors, along with Bell Labs staffers and programmers Brian Kernighan, Catherine Ann Brooks, Lorinda Cherry, Alfred Aho, Nina Macdonald, and John Mashey.

Dennis Ritchie and Ken Thompson started work on what would become UNIX originally in 1969. They developed it to run on a DEC PDP-7 to begin with; it would eventually be ported to other computers. By 1976, UNIX was used in more than 30 Bell Labs groups, and there were UNIX installations at over 80 universities.

Footage Courtesy of AT&amp;T Archives and History Center, Warren, NJ</description>
      <author> (AT&amp;T Tech Channel)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XvDZLjaCJuw</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 15:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeRDP</title>
      <link>https://www.freerdp.com/</link>
      <description>FreeRDP is a free remote desktop protocol client.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.freerdp.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 09:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>