<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>GCC version 14 coming soon – and will drop Itanium support</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2024/04/12/gcc_14_sinks_itanic/</link>
      <description>Linux kernel cut it loose, now leading FOSS compiler lands depth-charge on Itanic</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2024/04/12/gcc_14_sinks_itanic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 03:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Recovery Kit Version Two</title>
      <link>https://www.doscher.com/recovery-kit-version-2/</link>
      <description>If you&amp;#39;re not familiar with the Recovery Kit, it&amp;#39;s something I made back in 2019 and posted to my original back7.co blog. I created it before I knew what a &amp;quot;cyberdeck&amp;quot; was beyond a simple part of William Gibson&amp;#39;s Neuromancer. I wanted a rugged computer enclosure for my Raspberry</description>
      <author> (Jay Doscher)</author>
      <guid>https://www.doscher.com/recovery-kit-version-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 02:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Clever Way To Implement Pessimistic Locking in EF Core</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/a-clever-way-to-implement-pessimistic-locking-in-ef-core</link>
      <description>Sometimes, especially in high-traffic scenarios, you absolutely need to ensure that only one process can modify a piece of data at a time. Entity Framework Core is a fantastic tool, but it doesn&amp;#39;t have a direct mechanism for pessimistic locking. In this article, I&amp;#39;ll show you how we can solve that problem with raw SQL queries.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/a-clever-way-to-implement-pessimistic-locking-in-ef-core</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 01:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons after a half-billion GPT tokens - Ken Kantzer&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://kenkantzer.com/lessons-after-a-half-billion-gpt-tokens/</link>
      <description>My startup (gettruss.io) released a few LLM-heavy features in the last six months, and the narrative around LLMs that I read on Hacker News is now starting to diverge from my reality, so I thought I’d share some of the more “surprising” lessons after churning through just north of 500 million tokens, by my estimate. […]</description>
      <author> (Ken)</author>
      <guid>https://kenkantzer.com/lessons-after-a-half-billion-gpt-tokens/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B2B Marketing Automation: Platforms, Tools, Examples, Cases</title>
      <link>https://khomichenko.com/b2b-marketing-automation/</link>
      <description>B2B marketing automation: explore top platforms, tools, real-world examples, compelling case studies and elevate your marketing strategy</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://khomichenko.com/b2b-marketing-automation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULIDs and Primary Keys</title>
      <link>https://blog.daveallie.com/ulid-primary-keys</link>
      <description>Not all non-sequential primary keys are created equal, the ULID format is a fantastic substitute for the typical UUIDv4 choice.</description>
      <author> (Dave Allie)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.daveallie.com/ulid-primary-keys</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Learning Japanese</title>
      <link>https://alexanderweichart.de/2_Areas/Japanese/Notes-on-Learning-Japanese</link>
      <description>12.04.2024 A random stream of consciousness on learning Japanese. it is a great joy to learn such a logical and beautiful language with very few exceptions or rules you have to learn by heart it feels like playing Lego for example: 食べる(“taberu”) (to eat) replace ending “ru” with “tai”: 食べたい (“tabetai”) (want to eat) replace “i” with “kunai”: 食べたくない(“tabetakunai”) (do not want to eat) replace “i” with “katta”: 食べたかった (“tabetakunakutta”) (did not want to eat) words are ‘conjugated’ by attaching helper words in a sense, it’s similar to functional programming however, every now and then learning Japanese feels impossible like a mountain that’s too high to climb spending the few hours I have left each day after work and chores in an artificial Japanese environment consisting of recursively reviewing Anki flashcards writing out Kanji and watching Japanese videos just to progress forward a bit and not forget what I’ve learned so far knowing full well it’s no natural way to acquire the language but having no other choice since I’m stuck on the other side of the world limited by time and not at the point yet where I can fully “immerse” myself yet I sometimes wish I could just go Japan not just for a two week vacation but for a few years not just as a foreign tourist but as a someone who ‘lives there’ but I’m also fully aware of my inability to speak the language fluently find a job there or live a ‘normal’ live in Japan so I stop thinking about it and enter my artificial environment again since it’s the best tool I have right now to make this wish a reality .</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://alexanderweichart.de/2_Areas/Japanese/Notes-on-Learning-Japanese</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Way to Get Things Done</title>
      <link>https://ofdollarsanddata.com/the-best-way-to-get-things-done/</link>
      <description>How to get through your to-do list efficiently and whether maximizing productivity is worth it.</description>
      <author> (Posted March 19, 2024 by Nick Maggiulli)</author>
      <guid>https://ofdollarsanddata.com/the-best-way-to-get-things-done/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The getting-punched-in-the-face theory of efficient markets</title>
      <link>https://reprog.wordpress.com/2024/04/11/the-getting-punched-in-the-face-theory-of-efficient-markets/</link>
      <description>Suppose every day I punched you in the head for fun. Then you offered to pay me to not punch you in the head.</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://reprog.wordpress.com/2024/04/11/the-getting-punched-in-the-face-theory-of-efficient-markets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ten Years and Counting: My Affair with Microservices</title>
      <link>https://blog.allegro.tech/2024/04/ten-years-microservices.html</link>
      <description>In early 2024, I hit ten years at Allegro, which also happens to be how long I’ve been working with microservices.
This timespan also roughly corresponds to how long the company as a whole has been using them, so I think it’s a good time to outline the story of project
Rubicon: a very ambitious gamble which completely changed how we work and what our software is like. The idea probably seemed rather extreme at the time, yet I
am certain that without this change, Allegro would not be where it is today, or perhaps would not be there at all.

</description>
      <author> (michal.kosmulski)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.allegro.tech/2024/04/ten-years-microservices.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube’s Screen Stealer</title>
      <link>https://joe-steel.com/2024-04-12-YouTubes-Screen-Stealer.html</link>
      <description>Something&amp;#39;s distinctly different about this &amp;quot;aerial&amp;quot; still frame.

Yesterday, I had the YouTube app open on my Apple TV in my office. I went to do something else, and when I looked back it wasn’t the Apple TV aerial screensaver, but a YouTube app “screen saver” with a slideshow of heavily compressed still images.
The Apple TV in my living room had an older version of the YouTube app (presumably from April 2nd if the dates in the version names are to be believed.) That version didn’t try to override my screensaver like the one in my office.
It seems the YouTube app, if the app is open, will start a screensaver slideshow of generic still images taken from videos if there isn’t a video that I’ve paused.
Look at the compression shred this still.

If there is a paused video it will be a slideshow of the YouTube thumbnail art endlessly zooming in, fading to black, and starting over.
Some of the worst sins of mankind exist in YouTube thumbnails, and they’re not designed to be screensavers.
You know what is designed to be a screensaver? The Apple TV’s aerial screensaver. Far and away the most lauded feature of the Apple TV platform. Beloved by all (except people that get creeped out by jellyfish) and yet replaced by either chunky-compressed stills from drone footage, or looping thumbnails.
To top it all off, it has static, white text (famously the best to use for screensavers) for video details, static YouTube logo, and a graphic for the directional pad, indicating that pressing the top will start playing the video being used in the screensaver. If you have an older Apple TV in your house (my office Apple TV is the 4th gen one) with the awful touchpad you can even trigger it when you try and pick up the remote from the furniture.
YouTube’s not the first company to “innovate” in the screensaver space, and it’s not exclusive to the Apple TV. A few years ago my boyfriend had a set-top box that would initial start a slideshow of ugly nature photos, and then after a while they started dropping in ads into the slideshow.
I fully expect YouTube’s aim here is to capitalize on all this “free” real estate and start sliding in ads, promoting specific videos from partners, or showcasing movies available to rent or buy. I know that’s cynical, but so is YouTube as a business.
Setting that aside, I pay for YouTube Premium because the ads are so awful I can’t stand them, but because there’s some pretense of this being a screensaver I still get these slideshows that are the future home of ads for other people.
On April 4th, Janko Roettgers published a piece about a recent Roku patent filing about injecting ads over the source input feed when the source input feed is paused. The patent also says the display device will discern content and context to place a relevant ad over the paused video stream.
As Janko points out, Roku already monetizes screensavers on its platform. Feel free to peruse Roku’s site where they brag about chunks of the screen they’re willing to sell.
I don’t think advertising, in the abstract, is evil. I do, however, think it’s insidious to inject advertising into every pore —especially when those pores don’t belong to you, like when you’re the YouTube app, not even a platform.
Screen Saved
If you want to bypass the YouTube app change, I heard from Rob Bhalla on Mastodon that if you change the screensaver to start at 2 minutes, instead of the Apple TV’s default 5 minutes, then the Apple TV’s screensaver kicks in before the YouTube one and you never see theirs. Thanks to  YouTube not having any screensaver controls, and no idea what your actual screensaver settings on the Apple TV are, they hard coded in a start time just prior to the default 5 minutes.
That’s how you know it’s really there to help improve user experience, and not just a craven money grab by absolute hacks.
Sure, they might change this to start even earlier. In which case, we’re at the mercy of Apple to protect customer experience. I wouldn’t hold my breath on that one. App Store rejections are for indie devs, and people trying to skirt giving Apple money, not YouTube overriding the screensaver.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://joe-steel.com/2024-04-12-YouTubes-Screen-Stealer.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I accidentally built a meme search engine</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2024/04/12/i-accidentally-built-a-meme-search-engine/</link>
      <description>I built a magical meme search engine using siglip/CLIP and vector encoding images. It was a fun way to learn about this powerful technology. I&amp;#39;m sharing the code so you can build your own and discover forgotten gems in your photo library. Let&amp;#39;s unleash the power of AI on our images!</description>
      <author> (Harper Reed &amp;lt;harper@modest.com&amp;gt;)</author>
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2024/04/12/i-accidentally-built-a-meme-search-engine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The One Billion Row Challenge in CUDA: from 17 minutes to 17 seconds</title>
      <link>https://tspeterkim.github.io/posts/cuda-1brc</link>
      <description>On my journey to learn CUDA, I decided to tackle the One Billion Row Challenge with it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tspeterkim.github.io/posts/cuda-1brc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M&amp;amp;Ms: A Cautionary Tale</title>
      <link>https://newsletter.memesmotivations.com/p/m-and-ms-a-cautionary-tale</link>
      <description>A story about why it&amp;#39;s now or never for a lot of ideas.</description>
      <author> (Louie Bacaj)</author>
      <guid>https://newsletter.memesmotivations.com/p/m-and-ms-a-cautionary-tale</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I improved my crypto trading bot’s exit strategy - cryptomaton</title>
      <link>https://www.cryptomaton.org/2024/04/11/how-i-improved-my-crypto-trading-bots-exit-strategy/</link>
      <description>Exit strategies like Stale Asset Selloff and Stop Loss Decay can really make a difference for your crypto trading bot.</description>
      <author> (Andrei)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cryptomaton.org/2024/04/11/how-i-improved-my-crypto-trading-bots-exit-strategy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Multiple Large Language Models in one Pass &amp;#183; Analyst 18</title>
      <link>https://dezoito.github.io/2024/03/28/comparing-from-multiple-LLMs.html</link>
      <description>28 Mar 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dezoito.github.io/2024/03/28/comparing-from-multiple-LLMs.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-as-a-Product and Data-Contract: An evolutionary approach to data maturity</title>
      <link>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2024/04/09/data-as-a-product-and-data-contract-an-evolutionary-approach-to-data-maturity.html</link>
      <description>Using Simon Wardley’s evolution model, I propose a framework for visualizing the maturity of data within a business context, emphasizing the importance of treating data as a product and implementing data contracts to facilitate integration and ensure trust. Ultimately, I suggest that starting with a focus on data-as-a-product is crucial for organizations embarking on their data mesh journey, paving the way for a comprehensive and agile transformation.</description>
      <author> (Olivier Wulveryck)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.owulveryck.info/2024/04/09/data-as-a-product-and-data-contract-an-evolutionary-approach-to-data-maturity.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common pitfalls of digital health startups &amp;amp;amp; advice on how to avoid them</title>
      <link>https://bettychang.xyz/advice-for-digital-health-founders/</link>
      <description>Sharing hard-won advice for founders of early-stage digital health startups on how to survive and succeed in a bearish market.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bettychang.xyz/advice-for-digital-health-founders/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>asymmetric routing around the firewall</title>
      <link>https://devnonsense.com/posts/asymmetric-routing-around-the-firewall/</link>
      <description>This is a follow-up to my previous post about some mysterious TCP connection timeouts in the UC Berkeley wired network.
I received many thoughtful emails in response to that post, and there was an excellent discussion on Hacker News. I’m very grateful to everyone who spent time helping with my ridiculous home networking issues.
Since then, I’ve learned some new information that (mostly) solves the mystery. In this post, I’ll first summarize the main theories people suggested, then tell the story of how a Bunny CDN engineer came to the rescue, and finally describe the root cause.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devnonsense.com/posts/asymmetric-routing-around-the-firewall/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstract methods and NotImplementedError in Ruby</title>
      <link>https://nithinbekal.com/posts/abstract-methods-notimplementederror-ruby/</link>
      <description>Nithin Bekal&amp;#39;s blog about programming - Ruby, Rails, Vim, Elixir.</description>
      <author> (Nithin Bekal)</author>
      <guid>https://nithinbekal.com/posts/abstract-methods-notimplementederror-ruby/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fhur</title>
      <link>https://fhur.me/posts/2024/the-internet-has-changed</link>
      <description>fhur&amp;#39;s blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fhur.me/posts/2024/the-internet-has-changed</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey Management</title>
      <link>https://mihirchronicles.com/monkey-management/</link>
      <description>Harvard Business Review in 1974 published “Who&amp;#39;s Got the Monkey” authored by William Oncken Jr and Donald L. Wass. The article described unsolved problems of…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mihirchronicles.com/monkey-management/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes from YC W21 to W24, with Love</title>
      <link>https://notes.kevinslin.com/pages/advice-ycw21-to-ycw24-rfw4yxpkj5qpxajzz7xfou5</link>
      <description>&amp;gt; This post was inspired by a recent conversation with a YC grad about post-batch life and lessons learned.

### On Startup Advice

I will start by saying you should take all advice with a grain of sa</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://notes.kevinslin.com/pages/advice-ycw21-to-ycw24-rfw4yxpkj5qpxajzz7xfou5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding and Fixing Standard Misconceptions About Program Behavior</title>
      <link>https://blog.brownplt.org/2024/04/12/behavior-misconceptions.html</link>
      <description>Posted on 12 April 2024.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.brownplt.org/2024/04/12/behavior-misconceptions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating OpenAI&amp;#39;s ChatGPT into cross-platform .NET applications</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/blog/integrating-chatgpt-into-your-net-applications/</link>
      <description>Learn how to integrate OpenAI&amp;#39;s ChatGPT into cross-platform .NET applications using Uno Platform. This guide covers the use of C# markup, integration through NuGet packages, configuration management with Uno Extensions and MVUX for state management.</description>
      <author> (Uno Platform Team)</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/blog/integrating-chatgpt-into-your-net-applications/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 19:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The guide to Git I never had.</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@jake.page91/the-guide-to-git-i-never-had-a89048d4703a</link>
      <description>&amp;#129658; Doctors have stethoscopes.</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@jake.page91)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@jake.page91/the-guide-to-git-i-never-had-a89048d4703a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 18:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - tinygrad/open-gpu-kernel-modules: NVIDIA Linux open GPU with P2P support</title>
      <link>https://github.com/tinygrad/open-gpu-kernel-modules</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Linux open GPU with P2P support. Contribute to tinygrad/open-gpu-kernel-modules development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (tinygrad)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/tinygrad/open-gpu-kernel-modules</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 16:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Lost Faith in Kagi</title>
      <link>https://d-shoot.net/kagi.html</link>
      <description>Issues with Kagi&amp;#39;s AI focus, finances and leadership</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://d-shoot.net/kagi.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The case of the string being copied from a mysterious pointer to invalid memory - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240412-00/?p=109636</link>
      <description>Using AppVerifier to deduce the heap allocation history.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240412-00/?p=109636</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HeatpumpMonitor.org</title>
      <link>https://heatpumpmonitor.org/</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://heatpumpmonitor.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Performance Tip: Cloning Various Types</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/04/12/general-performance-tip-cloning-various-types/</link>
      <description>The post discusses the process of cloning different types of objects, with Microsoft recommending the use of JSON serialization for this purpose. The author explores the performance differences in …</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/04/12/general-performance-tip-cloning-various-types/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 10:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Response to Hashicorp&amp;#39;s Cease and Desist Letter | OpenTofu</title>
      <link>https://opentofu.org/blog/our-response-to-hashicorps-cease-and-desist/</link>
      <description>On April 3rd, we received a Cease and Desist letter from HashiCorp regarding our implementation of the &amp;quot;removed&amp;quot; block in OpenTofu, claiming copyright infringement on the part of one of our core developers. We were also made aware of an article posted that same day with the same accusations. We have investigated these claims and are publishing the C&amp;amp;D letter, our response and the source code origin document resulting from our investigation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://opentofu.org/blog/our-response-to-hashicorps-cease-and-desist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:00:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Basics: Exploring Android Manifest in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/beyond-basics-exploring-android-manifest-net-maui</link>
      <description>See what’s stored in the Android Manifest file so you can set platform-specific configurations in your .NEW MAUI app.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/beyond-basics-exploring-android-manifest-net-maui</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 simple design tips to improve your Web UI</title>
      <link>https://jonhilton.net/design-tips/</link>
      <description>Spruce up your features</description>
      <author> (Jon Hilton)</author>
      <guid>https://jonhilton.net/design-tips/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing MSTest SDK - Improved Configuration &amp;amp; Flexibility - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-mstest-sdk/</link>
      <description>The new MSTest SDK is here and provides an easier way to configure your MSTest projects. Learn all about this release, how to get started, and its great improvements when using MSTest.</description>
      <author> (Marco Rossignoli)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-mstest-sdk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Referencing external Docker containers in .NET Aspire using the new custom resources API</title>
      <link>https://anthonysimmon.com/referencing-external-docker-containers-dotnet-aspire-custom-resources/</link>
      <description>.NET Aspire reaches a new level of extensibility with preview 5, which allows for the creation of custom resources controlled by your code.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://anthonysimmon.com/referencing-external-docker-containers-dotnet-aspire-custom-resources/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>