<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>A WPF Statusbar Control</title>
      <link>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2023/Aug/08/A-WPF-Statusbar-Control</link>
      <description>Statusbar controls are boring, but because of the way that they are used there are a number of caveats like ensuring the UI updates even in linear code, allowing for timeouts of status messages and resetting to default, and to provide some visual clues to draw attention to the status messages displayed. In this post I talk about a custom status bar control and helper that make it super easy to use a new status bar control or attach additional functionality to an existing status bar.</description>
      <author> (https://facebook.com/rickstrahl)</author>
      <guid>https://weblog.west-wind.com/posts/2023/Aug/08/A-WPF-Statusbar-Control</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 01:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why do we need containers? #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Lf6BxOuQIBk</link>
      <description>Why do we need containers and what are their use cases? #shortsSupport me on Patreon to access the source code:https://www.patreon.com/mohamadlawandLet us co...</description>
      <author> (YouTube Movies &amp;amp; TV
  
  
  
    YouTube Movies &amp;amp; TV
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Lf6BxOuQIBk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stream</title>
      <link>https://iframe.cloudflarestream.com/225ac190a2b3a7185016bd6d6e76c978</link>
      <description>Stream</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iframe.cloudflarestream.com/225ac190a2b3a7185016bd6d6e76c978</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Speaker Series: Fireside chat with Troy Hunt and Alex Krivit  - Cloudflare TV</title>
      <link>https://cloudflare.tv/shows/developer-speaker-series/developer-speaker-series-fireside-chat-with-troy-hunt-and-alex-krivit/ja4z36gn</link>
      <description>Join Alex Krivit, Product Manager at Cloudflare, as he sits down for a Fireside Chat with Troy Hunt, the founder of Have I Been PWned. Hear how Cache Reserve is helping Troy serve over 99% of requests from cache.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cloudflare.tv/shows/developer-speaker-series/developer-speaker-series-fireside-chat-with-troy-hunt-and-alex-krivit/ja4z36gn</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCD, Please by dukope</title>
      <link>https://dukope.itch.io/lcd-please</link>
      <description>Passport Control in Your Pocket</description>
      <author> (Casey Labrack)</author>
      <guid>https://dukope.itch.io/lcd-please</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragging Docks and Tugging Toolbars on Wayland</title>
      <link>https://blog.david-redondo.de/kde/wayland/qt/2023/08/08/xdg-toplevel-drag.html</link>
      <description>Most of our desktop applications have a toolbar, sometimes theyeven have multiple toolbars next to or stacked on top of each other.More complex desktop appli...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.david-redondo.de/kde/wayland/qt/2023/08/08/xdg-toplevel-drag.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STD009: The Standard 3.0</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XRjQezUMQjY</link>
      <description>In this session, Paul and I are joined to discuss several topics mainly around:- Cul-De-Sac Patterns - New Approach- Rethinking systems design- The Standard ...</description>
      <author> (Hassan Habib
  
  
  
    Hassan Habib
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=XRjQezUMQjY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zen and the Art of Logging</title>
      <link>https://www.lelanthran.com/chap10/content.html</link>
      <description>The more you know, the more you realize you know nothing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lelanthran.com/chap10/content.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Legacy of Bram Moolenaar - Jan van den Berg</title>
      <link>https://j11g.com/2023/08/07/the-legacy-of-bram-moolenaar/</link>
      <description>This weekend we learned that Bram Moolenaar had passed away at the age of 62. And this news affected me more than I expected. Like so many: I did not know Bram personally. But I’ve been using a tool made by Bram for more than half my life — at least weekly, sometimes daily. That…&amp;#160;Read More &amp;#187;The Legacy of Bram Moolenaar</description>
      <author> (Jan van den Berg)</author>
      <guid>https://j11g.com/2023/08/07/the-legacy-of-bram-moolenaar/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On sound programming: Playing a single note with SDL2</title>
      <link>https://blog.fredrb.com/2023/08/08/audio-programming-note-sdl/</link>
      <description>Playing a single note with SDL2 I have successfully avoided sound programming for all my programming life. Even when I tried making games, sound was always an afterthought. However, recently I got a new pair of headphones, and wondered: “what makes sound good?”, or “how much of the quality can be improved by hardware?”, and even “what is the structure of a sound file?”. If you’re looking for answers to all these questions — sorry, you are in the wrong place.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.fredrb.com/2023/08/08/audio-programming-note-sdl/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://chat.openai.com/share/f5341665-7f08-4fca-9639-04201363506e</link>
      <description>How about everything you said to save the pan you&amp;#39;ve got, you&amp;#39;ll get it. Hour by Hour. Hour by Hour. Hour by Hour.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chat.openai.com/share/f5341665-7f08-4fca-9639-04201363506e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogged Answers: My Experience Modernizing Packages to ESM</title>
      <link>https://blog.isquaredsoftware.com/2023/08/esm-modernization-lessons/</link>
      <description>Details on the painful experiences and hard-earned lessons I&amp;#39;ve learned migrating the Redux packages to ESM</description>
      <author> (Mark Erikson)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.isquaredsoftware.com/2023/08/esm-modernization-lessons/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In good hands</title>
      <link>https://stephanango.com/in-good-hands</link>
      <description>There is a feeling I search for: being in good hands. It is the feeling I look to give and the feeling I look to receive.</description>
      <author> (Stephan Ango)</author>
      <guid>https://stephanango.com/in-good-hands</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Ramsey - sink or swim</title>
      <link>https://jaredramsey.com/blog/20230807.html</link>
      <description>Looking back at my own career, as well as noticing patterns in employees I&amp;#39;ve mentored over the years,
      I&amp;#39;ve noticed a common scenario play out during the &amp;quot;awkward teenage years&amp;quot; of most, if not all, software engineers&amp;#39; careers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaredramsey.com/blog/20230807.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Electric Grid: History and Overview</title>
      <link>https://blog.chaselambda.com/2023/03/25/us-electric-grid-history-and-overview.html</link>
      <description>Disclosure: I had help writing parts of this article with ChatGPT. I think it’s nontheless an interesting and quick read.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.chaselambda.com/2023/03/25/us-electric-grid-history-and-overview.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subscriber Only: A Technical Post Mortem</title>
      <link>https://0x1.pt/2023/08/08/subscriber-only-a-technical-post-mortem/</link>
      <description>I closed down Subscriber Only, here&amp;#39;s a couple of interesting things I did and learned while working on it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://0x1.pt/2023/08/08/subscriber-only-a-technical-post-mortem/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grading for proud</title>
      <link>https://blog.jgrizou.com/grading-for-proud/</link>
      <description>I hate grading. Not the hard part of giving constructive feedback, but the easy part of assigning a number to a human being.
First, grades measure position, ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jgrizou.com/grading-for-proud/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIY Tailscale Funnel | Gabriel&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabrielsimmer.com/posts/diy-tailscale-funnel/</link>
      <description>I really do love Tailscale, if it wasn&amp;#39;t obvious by my previous infrastructure update post. When they announced their Funnel feature, I jumped on it as an opportunity to try an alternative to Cloudflare Tunnels. And while it worked pretty well, I was mildly disappointed by some missing features. Key among them being the ability to setup custom DNS entries to point to services. So not only was the URL really long, I also didn&amp;#39;t fully have control over it and I also had to do path routing to various services, which can be finicky at the best of times.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.gabrielsimmer.com/posts/diy-tailscale-funnel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s missing from values in data tables</title>
      <link>https://jrhawley.ca/2023/07/28/data-table-values</link>
      <description>Storing data in tables is such an integral part of data collection, curation, processing, analysis, and archiving. And for each of the these different purposes, there are different opinions and...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jrhawley.ca/2023/07/28/data-table-values</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My final take on Gradle (vs. Maven)</title>
      <link>https://blog.frankel.ch/final-take-gradle/</link>
      <description>I tweet technical content that I consider interesting, but the funny tweets are the ones that get the most engagement. I attended the JavaLand conference in March, stumbled upon the Gradle booth, and found this gem: Things have changed a lot &amp;#128514;&amp;#128514;&amp;#128514;“When you can’t beat them, join them” pic.twitter.com/SnX3KN57o8— Nicolas Frankel &amp;#127482;&amp;#127462; (@nicolas_frankel) March 22, 2023 Of course, at some point, a fanboy hijacked the thread and claimed the so-called superiority of Gradle. In this post, I’</description>
      <author> (Nicolas Fr&amp;#228;nkel)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.frankel.ch/final-take-gradle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Elliptic Curve Arithmetic in OpenSSL — Store Halfword Byte-Reverse Indexed</title>
      <link>https://sthbrx.github.io/blog/2023/08/07/going-out-on-a-limb-efficient-elliptic-curve-arithmetic-in-openssl/</link>
      <description>So I&amp;#39;ve just managed to upstream some changes to OpenSSL for a new strategy I&amp;#39;ve developed for efficient arithmetic used in secp384r1, a curve prescribed by NIST for digital signatures and key exchange. In spite of its prevalence, its implementation in OpenSSL has remained somewhat unoptimised, even as less frequently used curves (P224, P256, P521) each have their own optimisations.</description>
      <author> (OzLabs)</author>
      <guid>https://sthbrx.github.io/blog/2023/08/07/going-out-on-a-limb-efficient-elliptic-curve-arithmetic-in-openssl/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Lifetime Reading Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.honest-broker.com/p/my-lifetime-reading-plan</link>
      <description>I share some private details of how I educated myself through books</description>
      <author> (Ted Gioia)</author>
      <guid>https://www.honest-broker.com/p/my-lifetime-reading-plan</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Make A Change, But Not Sure What To Do Next?</title>
      <link>https://jasonfeifer.beehiiv.com/p/limit-options</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s time to start narrowing your options.</description>
      <author> (Jason Feifer)</author>
      <guid>https://jasonfeifer.beehiiv.com/p/limit-options</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winning Connect4</title>
      <link>https://www.steveindusteves.com/p/connect4-mcts</link>
      <description>With Monte-Carlo Tree Search</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.steveindusteves.com/p/connect4-mcts</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Integrated Vector Database Can Boost Your LLM Apps?</title>
      <link>https://blog.myscale.com/2023/06/06/why-integrated-database-solution-can-boost-your-llm-apps/</link>
      <description>The large language model has brought so many amazing ideas into reality, like bots on anything, knowledge experts, research assistant and many others. Most of those great apps combine LLM with a sp...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.myscale.com/2023/06/06/why-integrated-database-solution-can-boost-your-llm-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn-On Found</title>
      <link>https://cabel.com/2023/08/06/turn-on-found/</link>
      <description>I’ve waited a long time for this. In 1969, producers George Schlatter and Ed Friendly wanted to create another monster comedy hit like they had with Rowan &amp;amp; Martin’s Laugh-In, a cha…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cabel.com/2023/08/06/turn-on-found/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections one year into a PhD program</title>
      <link>https://lambdaland.org/posts/2023-08-05_one_year_into_phd/</link>
      <description>I started my PhD program about a year ago. In my first year I have:
Taken 4 “normal” 3-credit-hour classes Participated in 3 seminars Switched advisors Attended 2 conferences (PLDI @ FCRC, JuliaCon) Presented my work at JuliaCon It’s been a lot of work, and there’s been a lot of stress. I’m in a much better place now than when I started, and over all I’m happy where I’m at and where I’m headed.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lambdaland.org/posts/2023-08-05_one_year_into_phd/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is CodeClan to you?</title>
      <link>https://trizuliak.com/blog/what-is-codeclan-to-you</link>
      <description>What people think about CodeClan. Collection of testimonials about Scottish digital skills academy.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://trizuliak.com/blog/what-is-codeclan-to-you</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should everything be blazingly fast?</title>
      <link>https://www.einenlum.com/articles/should-everything-be-blazingly-fast</link>
      <description>Fast seems to be the new trend. Are we sure it&amp;#39;s always worth it?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.einenlum.com/articles/should-everything-be-blazingly-fast</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overlooked on HN: Databases That Process Data Faster Than Memory Bandwidth</title>
      <link>https://taras.glek.net/post/overlooked-hn-databases-that-process-data-faster-than-memory-bandwidth/</link>
      <description>13 GiB/s per core!
Sneller posted a blog on HN
 on how they use AVX-512 to decompress data at 13 gigabytes per second per core.
This a fantastic ad for their “lets turn logs on S3 into cheap database” product. This is a solution I wanted multiple times, will definitely consider them next time the need comes up.
Faster than RAM
Now this post did not get overlooked, but what did get overlooked is that the post engaged the clickhouse CTO. He posted a link to a presentation on how Clickhouse uses compression to process in-memory data faster than RAM bandwidth
.
As a result of discussion in these comments, clickhouse might get even faster.</description>
      <author> (Taras Glek)</author>
      <guid>https://taras.glek.net/post/overlooked-hn-databases-that-process-data-faster-than-memory-bandwidth/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bun vs Yarn: A Comparison of Package Installation</title>
      <link>https://scinos.dev/posts/2023-07-30-bun-vs-yarn-a-comparison-of-package-installation/</link>
      <description>Bun vs Yarn:, An In-Depth Comparison for Package Management in Node.js Projects. This detailed analysis explores the efficiency and functionality of Bun as a potential alternative to Yarn. Using a real-world medium-large project, the author investigates claims of Bun&amp;#39;s superior speed, uncovers several issues, and provides insights that could inform your choice between these two package managers. A transparent and nuanced look at what each tool offers, perfect for developers seeking an informed decision.</description>
      <author> (Sergio Cinos)</author>
      <guid>https://scinos.dev/posts/2023-07-30-bun-vs-yarn-a-comparison-of-package-installation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Code Organization in a Post-Hexagonal World</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/08/08/thoughts-on-code-organization-in-a-post-hexagonal-world/</link>
      <description>JasperFx Software&amp;#160;is up and running, and we’d love to work with you to help make your software development efforts more successful. I’m one of a number of folks who are actively questio…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/08/08/thoughts-on-code-organization-in-a-post-hexagonal-world/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go 1.21 Release Notes - The Go Programming Language</title>
      <link>https://go.dev/doc/go1.21</link>
      <description>The latest Go release, version 1.21, arrives six months after Go 1.20.
  Most of its changes are in the implementation of the toolchain, runtime, and libraries.
  As always, the release maintains the Go 1 promise of compatibility;
  in fact, Go 1.21 improves upon that promise.
  We expect almost all Go programs to continue to compile and run as before.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://go.dev/doc/go1.21</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Framework August 2023 Security and Quality Rollup Updates - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-framework-august-2023-security-and-quality-rollup-updates/</link>
      <description>August 2023 Security and Quality Rollup Updates for .NET Framework</description>
      <author> (Salini Agarwal)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-framework-august-2023-security-and-quality-rollup-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee and Open Source Conversation - Phil Haack</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=B_XIZcHbkSg</link>
      <description>Phil Haack is a co-founder and CTO of A Serious Business, Inc. building serious products for serious people. Very serious. We are the creators of Abbot, a Co...</description>
      <author> (YouTube Movies &amp;amp; TV
  
  
  
    YouTube Movies &amp;amp; TV
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=B_XIZcHbkSg</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Quick Reviews</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=58aXHiinJOs</link>
      <description>Powered by Restream https://restream.io</description>
      <author> (Jay Shetty Podcast
  
  
  
    Jay Shetty Podcast
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=58aXHiinJOs</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2022 – 17.7 Now Available - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2022-17-7-now-available/</link>
      <description>We’re delighted to announce the General Availability (GA) of Visual Studio 2022 version 17.7 today. This release is a testament to our continued commitment to creating an enriched developer experience, powered by community feedback, and driven by the needs of the diverse developer landscape.</description>
      <author> (Taysser Gherfal)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2022-17-7-now-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: Skip the Waitlist to Test ChatGPT Plugins with Our Chat Copilot -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/08/08/chat-copilot.aspx</link>
      <description>Meanwhile, OpenAI ends the waitlist.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel08/08/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/08/08/chat-copilot.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core updates in .NET 8 Preview 7 - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/asp-net-core-updates-in-dotnet-8-preview-7/</link>
      <description>.NET 8 Preview 7 is now available! Check out what&amp;#39;s new in ASP.NET Core in this update.</description>
      <author> (Daniel Roth)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/asp-net-core-updates-in-dotnet-8-preview-7/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing .NET 8 Preview 7 - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-8-preview-7/</link>
      <description>.NET 8 Preview 7 is now available with improvements to type containers, JSON source generation, and CodeGen as well as new support for HTTPS proxy, WPF open folder dialog, and iOS hybrid globalization.</description>
      <author> (Richard Lander)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-8-preview-7/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blocked by Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://jrhawley.ca/2023/08/07/blocked-by-cloudflare</link>
      <description>Well, it finally happened to me. I was blocked out of a website I use for work because of Cloudflare. And I have no idea if or when I&amp;#39;ll be...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jrhawley.ca/2023/08/07/blocked-by-cloudflare</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET August 2023 Updates – .NET 7.0.10, .NET 6.0.21 - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/august-2023-updates/</link>
      <description>Check out latest August 2023 updates for .NET 7.0 and .NET 6.0</description>
      <author> (Rahul Bhandari (MSFT))</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/august-2023-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall the Nightowl App, now.</title>
      <link>https://robins.one/notes/uninstall-the-nightowl-app-now.html</link>
      <description>Intro</description>
      <author> (Taylor Robinson)</author>
      <guid>https://robins.one/notes/uninstall-the-nightowl-app-now.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing .NET MAUI in .NET 8 Preview 7: Keyboard Accelerators - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-maui-in-dotnet-8-preview-7/</link>
      <description>.NET MAUI in .NET 8 Preview 7 has more new quality improvements for developers, experimental new AOT for iOS, and exciting new Visual Studio support.</description>
      <author> (David Ortinau)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-maui-in-dotnet-8-preview-7/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - huggingface/candle: Minimalist ML framework for Rust</title>
      <link>https://github.com/huggingface/candle</link>
      <description>Minimalist ML framework for Rust. Contribute to huggingface/candle development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (huggingface)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/huggingface/candle</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Reactive Streaming Applications with Containers on AWS</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YrD2c46sTIw</link>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;#39;m James! Do you have a container based application that needs to process records from a queue? And is your application running 24 hours a day, 7 days a...</description>
      <author> (James Eastham
  
  
  
    James Eastham
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YrD2c46sTIw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 17:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Computer Should Say What You Tell It To Say</title>
      <link>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2023/08/your-computer-should-say-what-you-tell-it-say-1</link>
      <description>WEI? I’m a frayed knotTwo pieces of string walk into a bar.The first piece of string asks for a drink.The bartender says, “Get lost. We don’t serve pieces of string.”The second string ties a knot in his middle and messes up his ends. Then he orders a drink. The bartender says, “Hey, you aren’t a...</description>
      <author> (Cory Doctorow and Jacob Hoffman-Andrews)</author>
      <guid>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2023/08/your-computer-should-say-what-you-tell-it-say-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 17:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rest in peace Bram Moolenaar, author of Vim and hero of many developers</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2023/08/bram-moolenaar-creator-of-the-beloved-vim-text-editor-has-passed-away/</link>
      <description>The open source software legend left us on August 3 at age 62.</description>
      <author> (Samuel Axon
    -  8/8/2023, 6:18 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2023/08/bram-moolenaar-creator-of-the-beloved-vim-text-editor-has-passed-away/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 16:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make AI your co-pilot</title>
      <link>https://mastersofscale.com/make-ai-your-co-pilot-john-maeda/</link>
      <description>Can you truly take advantage of AI before speaking its language? Microsoft’s VP of Design and AI, Dr. John Maeda discusses AI’s common misconceptions and its misunderstood opportunities. A veteran of AI development, John shares valuable insights for entrepreneurs about how to engage with the new technology — from overcoming trepidation to making AI work harder for you — and AI’s potential to help leaders make better decisions.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mastersofscale.com/make-ai-your-co-pilot-john-maeda/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 16:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Community Standup - Implementation of the .NET WebAssembly Jiterpreter</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ZedzpGgLcy0</link>
      <description>A technical talk by Katelyn Gadd about the design and implementation of the .NET WebAssembly Jiterpreter.Community Links: https://www.theurlist.com/blazor-st...</description>
      <author> (IAmTimCorey
  
  
  
    IAmTimCorey
  




  Verified



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ZedzpGgLcy0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QCon San Francisco Workshop: Building a database from the ground up</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/199873-A/qcon-san-francisco-workshop-building-a-database-from-the-ground-up?Key=c51e4299-0e3a-4322-83d9-89ec754250fe</link>
      <description>I&amp;amp;rsquo;m going to QCon San Francisco and will be teaching a full day workshop where we&amp;amp;rsquo;ll start from a C compiler and&amp;amp;nbsp; an empty file and end up w...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/199873-A/qcon-san-francisco-workshop-building-a-database-from-the-ground-up?Key=c51e4299-0e3a-4322-83d9-89ec754250fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside STL: The unordered_map, unordered_set, unordered_multimap, and unordered_multiset - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230808-00/?p=108572</link>
      <description>A hash table.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230808-00/?p=108572</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parametric, Nonparametric, Robust, and Defensive statistics</title>
      <link>https://aakinshin.net/posts/parametric-nonparametric-robust-defensive/</link>
      <description>Recently, I started writing about defensive statistics. The methodology allows having parametric assumptions, but it adjusts statistical methods so that they continue working even in the case of huge deviations from the declared assumptions. This idea sound...</description>
      <author> (Andrey Akinshin)</author>
      <guid>https://aakinshin.net/posts/parametric-nonparametric-robust-defensive/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting my library cards onto my phone the hard way — iliana.fyi</title>
      <link>https://iliana.fyi/blog/ios-wallet-library-card/</link>
      <description>Our local libraries, The Seattle Public Library and the King County Library System, issue pieces of plastic with barcodes printed on the back assigned to your borrower account. These cards are not strictly necessary in 2023; most everything at Seattle libraries is self-service, including circulation, and these self-service entrypoints usually have a way to type in a library barcode manually. But having the barcode is far more convenient, and I’d like to have it without having to keep yet another plastic card I rarely use in my wallet.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iliana.fyi/blog/ios-wallet-library-card/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Cybersafe Schools: Bringing security tools for free to small K-12 school districts in the US</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/project-cybersafe-schools/</link>
      <description>Announced as part of the Back to School Safely: K-12 Cybersecurity Summit at the White House on August 7, Project Cybersafe Schools will support eligible K-12 public school districts with a package of Zero Trust cybersecurity solutions — for free, and with no time limit</description>
      <author> (Zaid Zaid)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/project-cybersafe-schools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grape - Create interactive coding videos from your browser.</title>
      <link>https://www.grape.codes/</link>
      <description>An online IDE for creators and viewers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.grape.codes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Book That Changed How I Write Code</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sIH_SR4xPg8</link>
      <description>I read this book called “Test-Driven Development by Example”, it’s a foundational book for TDD. Kent Beck guides us through a deep-dive journey into this pra...</description>
      <author> (A to Zen Life
  
  
  
    A to Zen Life
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sIH_SR4xPg8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Dapper CRUD API From Scratch In .NET 7 - For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Idi_X0cTDjk</link>
      <description>&amp;#128204; Check out my Pragmatic Clean Architecture course: https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/pragmatic-clean-architecture&amp;#128640; Join 770+ engineers in my  Patreon commun...</description>
      <author> (LambdaTest
  
  
  
    LambdaTest
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Idi_X0cTDjk</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Videos From Azure Blob Storage in Blazor Server</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=y9EO1A2wCKI</link>
      <description>Playing videos in web browsers is nowadays a fairly common task. But how do we do this in Blazor Server? And what if our videos are in Azure Blob Storage? We...</description>
      <author> (Sabine Hossenfelder
  
  
  
    Sabine Hossenfelder
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=y9EO1A2wCKI</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started: Solution Architecture</title>
      <link>https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-solution-architecture/</link>
      <description>Get started with the art of Solution Architecture</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dometrain.com/course/getting-started-solution-architecture/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craftrise verileri sızdırılmış</title>
      <link>https://memoryhackers.org/konular/craftrise-verileri-sizdirilmis.270536/</link>
      <description>Craftrise hacklenmiş verileri sızdırılmış bilgisi olan var mı?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://memoryhackers.org/konular/craftrise-verileri-sizdirilmis.270536/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>why &amp;#39;age int&amp;#39; is better than &amp;#39;int age&amp;#39;</title>
      <link>https://benhoyt.com/writings/name-before-type/</link>
      <description>A variable&amp;#39;s name is more important than its type, so the name should be more prominent and come first in declarations.</description>
      <author> (Ben Hoyt)</author>
      <guid>https://benhoyt.com/writings/name-before-type/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:03:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ferromagnetic half levitation of LK-99-like synthetic samples</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.03110</link>
      <description>We successfully synthesized polycrystalline LK-99-like ceramic samples with a
solid-state-sintering method. Powder X-ray diffraction shows that the main
contents are $\mathrm{Pb_{10-x}Cu_x(PO_4)_6O}$ and $\mathrm{Cu_2S}$, consistent
with recent reports [arXiv:2307.12037; arXiv:2308.01192]. In some small flaky
fragments, we successfully observed ``half levitation&amp;#39;&amp;#39; atop a
$\mathrm{Nd_2Fe_{14}B}$ magnet. Using magnetization measurements on such small
pieces, as well as on a large piece which does not exhibit the half levitation,
we show that the samples ubiquitously contain weak yet definitive soft
ferromagnetic components. We argue that, together with the pronounced shape
anisotropy of the small fragments, the soft ferromagnetism is sufficient to
explain the observed half levitation in strong vertical magnetic fields. Our
measurements do not indicate the presence of the Meissner effect, nor zero
resistance, in our samples, leading us to believe that our samples do not
exhibit superconductivity.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 6 Aug 2023])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.03110</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending IdentityUser With Custom Properties in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/aspdotnet-extending-identityuser/</link>
      <description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll learn all possibilities of extending IdentityUser with custom properties and changing the primary key type.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/aspdotnet-extending-identityuser/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EI013: AI Processing Service (Part 7)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=7k7PoR6uu9I</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Hassan Habib
  
  
  
    Hassan Habib
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=7k7PoR6uu9I</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Zoom’s terms of service and practices apply to AI features | Zoom Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.zoom.us/zooms-term-service-ai/</link>
      <description>It’s important to us at Zoom to empower our customers with innovative and secure communication solutions. We’ve updated our terms of service (in section</description>
      <author> (Smita Hashim)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.zoom.us/zooms-term-service-ai/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:03:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raku: A Language for Gremlins • Buttondown</title>
      <link>https://buttondown.email/hillelwayne/archive/raku-a-language-for-gremlins/</link>
      <description>By Gremlins, For Gremlins™</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://buttondown.email/hillelwayne/archive/raku-a-language-for-gremlins/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadertoy</title>
      <link>https://www.shadertoy.com/view/DlBcz1</link>
      <description>Build shaders, share them, and learn from the best community.</description>
      <author> (Beautypi)</author>
      <guid>https://www.shadertoy.com/view/DlBcz1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Would Rather See My Books Get Pirated Than This (Or: Why Goodreads and Amazon Are Becoming Dumpster Fires) | Jane Friedman</title>
      <link>https://janefriedman.com/i-would-rather-see-my-books-pirated/</link>
      <description>Amazon and Goodreads must take steps to combat the flood of AI-generated content that will mislead readers and damage author reputations.</description>
      <author> (http://facebook.com/jane.friedman)</author>
      <guid>https://janefriedman.com/i-would-rather-see-my-books-pirated/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>