<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>2 Years Of Lessons From Running My Own Bookstore - RyanHoliday.net</title>
      <link>https://ryanholiday.net/2-years-of-lessons-from-running-my-own-bookstore/</link>
      <description>It is only from doing hard things, the Stoics said, that we learn what we’re capable of. A little over three years ago, my wife and I had the craziest idea we’ve ever had in our lives: to open a bookstore in Bastrop, Texas. Opening a small business is always hard. But opening a small business during a pandemic in a small town in rural Texas? To call it a challenge would be an understatement. We’ve learned a lot…about business, about books, and about what we’re capable of. Last year, I wrote a piece on the lessons we’d learned in our first year of business at The Painted Porch. Now, another year has passed and we have learned a few more…and re-learned some of the ones we thought we’d gotten the first time. I share them here so you can perhaps learn a little from my experiences and hopefully go create something cool of your own out of it. [1] Anything can be a good business if you treat it like a business. Too many indie bookstores are started because people think they’ll be fun…or because they love books. No, you have to be serious. I learned this as a writer: treat it like a job. [2] The bookstore of course is not just a bookstore. It is my office. It is my employee’s office. It is where I record podcasts and film YouTube videos. I rent part of the building to another business (a really cool record store called Astro Records). When you are thinking about taking a big risk, look for little ways to take some risk off the table. Find multiple uses, multiple options so that if one fails, you can still succeed. [3] On the Daily Stoic podcast, Matthew McConaughey gave me a better framework for making big decisions. He told me he’s known in Hollywood as a Quick No, Long Yes. His No’s are quick. But before he says Yes to something, “I give myself about 2 weeks in each frame of mind—Yes I’m in, No I’m out—and then I measure what keeps me up at night.” [4] Keep your eye on the prize. What is success to you? What metrics actually matter to you? Remembering why you did something and how you measure success helps you calibrate your decisions properly. I’m happy enough to be putting books out in the world, making this community better, having a physical space, challenging myself, etc…as long as I don’t lose lots of money, that’s a win. [5] Forget the politics. It’s been interesting to watch people in our small town care a lot about what other people in the small town think. Except this small town isn’t big enough to support a bookstore. When you’re starting out doing things, you get strong opinions from people in your local scene etc. But that’s not who you should be trying to impress, or who matters in the long run. Look outward, onwards. Don’t be stuck thinking small, don’t let the scene you chanced into constrain you. [6] Don’t be afraid to be political though. We delayed opening during the worst days of COVID. We kept up safety protocols even after the state of Texas washed its hands of its responsibilities last year. We did it even though people got mad at us for it, even though it probably cost us business. My conscience is clean and that’s what counts. Keeping your community and your staff safe is good for business in the long run anyway. [7] Beware of mission creep. Our original plan was that we’d have only a couple hundred books, only my absolute favorite books, only the books I put in my Reading List Email. It would only be those books. But the problem is, I’m always reading and discovering new favorite books. So the temptation to add and add and add is always there. In the military, they call this mission creep. It’s hard to predict exactly how things are going to unfold, so there tends to be a gradual broadening of objectives as a mission or battle progresses. If you are setting out on a project, just something to be aware of. [8] For everything you add, take something away. There’s a great story of Mark Parker who, just after he became CEO of Nike, called Steve Jobs for advice. “Just one thing,” Jobs said. “Nike makes some of the best products in the world. Products that you lust after. But you also make a lot of crap. Just get rid of the crappy stuff and focus on the good stuff.” “He was absolutely right,” Parker said. “We had to edit.” Because we’ve always done it this way, is not a good reason. Or in our case, because we’ve always carried this book or because it sold well in the past, is not a good reason. We have to edit. [9] Whenever I am at the store, people are excited to see me and ask a bunch of questions. Whenever my wife is there people ask her, “Where are your kids?” No one has EVER asked me that. It’s just a reminder that entrepreneurship is easier for some than others and the whole idea of just pulling yourselves up by your bootstraps is nonsense. Be aware of your advantages and privileges. [10] Speaking of which…something that’s been hard to navigate is all the people who come to the bookstore to see me. On the one hand, it is awesome. But on the other hand, if I give everyone twenty minutes, my day is gone. This means I sometimes have to be rude…but if I am not, then I am rude to my writing, to my family, to myself. [11] If you’re successful, your people should be successful. Nothing feels better than distributing profits or raises to the team. If you don’t take pleasure in that, you’re doing it wrong, prioritizing the wrong things. [12] A few weeks ago, an employee made a bad call [...]</description>
      <author> (mattragland)</author>
      <guid>https://ryanholiday.net/2-years-of-lessons-from-running-my-own-bookstore/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techniques for Setting up Peripherals via PIO and DMA</title>
      <link>https://serhack.me/articles/techniques-setting-up-pheripherals-dma-pio/</link>
      <description>Learn about the hardware aspects for Programmed Input Output and Direct Memory Access.</description>
      <author> (SerHack)</author>
      <guid>https://serhack.me/articles/techniques-setting-up-pheripherals-dma-pio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ideas have a 2 week shelf life</title>
      <link>https://stevecorona.com/ideas-have-a-2-week-shelf-life</link>
      <description>I have a new rule that I’m making for myself and holding others to. If you haven’t worked on something in the past two weeks, you’re not allowed to talk about it.</description>
      <author> (Stephen Corona)</author>
      <guid>https://stevecorona.com/ideas-have-a-2-week-shelf-life</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to be a technology charlatan</title>
      <link>https://scottlocklin.wordpress.com/2023/03/23/how-to-be-a-technology-charlatan/</link>
      <description>I’ve mentioned many times that I do not think technology is advancing in a serious way. By “a serious way” I mean something like what happened between 1820 and 1970. That kind of …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://scottlocklin.wordpress.com/2023/03/23/how-to-be-a-technology-charlatan/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the 2/3 rule for multi-factor authentication</title>
      <link>https://roman.computer/mfa/</link>
      <description>I propose the &amp;quot;2/3 rule&amp;quot; for multi-factor authentication: to access a system, a user must pass at least two out of three possible methods for authentication. Unlike standard 2-factor authentication, this strategy protects against both false positives (granting access to a hacker) and false negatives (denying access to a legitimate user).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://roman.computer/mfa/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs and Declarative Software Development</title>
      <link>http://aumitleon.dev/llms-and-declaritive-software-development</link>
      <description>Leveraging LLMs and the naturalness of software to build software declaratively.</description>
      <author> (Aumit Leon)</author>
      <guid>http://aumitleon.dev/llms-and-declaritive-software-development</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparks of Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) in GPT-4</title>
      <link>https://ibragimov.org/2023/03/24/sparks-of-agi.html</link>
      <description>Microsoft research recently published a paper where they review the original version of GPT-4, prior to all tuning, like removing bias, filtering, etc, that OpenAI did for the public version. In this article I will summarise the most interesting aspects and experiments why they think GPT-4 has sparks of AGI. And this time, I didn’t use ChatGPT to summarise it, as I enjoyed reading it myself :)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ibragimov.org/2023/03/24/sparks-of-agi.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I won&amp;#39;t buy a YubiKey</title>
      <link>https://garrit.xyz/posts/2023-03-21-i-wont-buy-a-yubikey</link>
      <description>Generalist developer writing about fullstack development, system administration and free software.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://garrit.xyz/posts/2023-03-21-i-wont-buy-a-yubikey</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS-only Widgets Are Inaccessible</title>
      <link>https://adrianroselli.com/2023/03/css-only-widgets-are-inaccessible.html</link>
      <description>Usually. I originally titled this InacCSS-onlyible. I even made this typographically, er, distinct image. Then I realized it was silly and will instead use the neologism in a talk so I can hear the groans IRL. Interactive widgets powered with only CSS are relatively common as people are playing with…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://adrianroselli.com/2023/03/css-only-widgets-are-inaccessible.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retry flaky tests with dotnet test and PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://conductofcode.io/post/retry-flaky-tests-with-dotnet-test-and-powershell/</link>
      <description>Introducing test.ps1, a script for running flaky tests - Keeps track of failing tests and retries them - Notifies the test framework of the current retry iteration - Makes it possible to accept a certain percentage of failing tests - Outputs the test result in a coherent way</description>
      <author> (Henrik Lau Eriksson)</author>
      <guid>https://conductofcode.io/post/retry-flaky-tests-with-dotnet-test-and-powershell/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techniques for label conditioning in Gaussian denoising diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://beckham.nz/2023/01/27/ddpms_guidance.html</link>
      <description>Techniques for label conditioning in Gaussian denoising diffusion models</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://beckham.nz/2023/01/27/ddpms_guidance.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a DOS ChatGPT client in 2023</title>
      <link>https://yeokhengmeng.com/2023/03/building-a-dos-chatgpt-client-in-2023/</link>
      <description>With the recent attention on ChatGPT and OpenAI’s release of their APIs, many developers have developed clients for modern platforms to talk to this super smart AI chatbot. However I’m pretty sure almost nobody has written one for a vintage platform like MS-DOS.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yeokhengmeng.com/2023/03/building-a-dos-chatgpt-client-in-2023/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Started a Shitstorm or Contemporary Journalism Is Embarrassing</title>
      <link>https://filthydreams.org/2023/03/25/i-started-a-shitstorm-or-contemporary-journalism-is-embarrassing/</link>
      <description>“Why is that a story? No offense…” my cousin James, a nurse in Pittsburgh, asked after I told him that while on the phone I received an interview request from The New York Times, a publicatio…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://filthydreams.org/2023/03/25/i-started-a-shitstorm-or-contemporary-journalism-is-embarrassing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putnam on reason, reductionism, and relativism</title>
      <link>http://edwardfeser.blogspot.com/2023/03/putnam-on-reason-reductionism-and.html</link>
      <description>Naturalism holds that what is real is what can be accounted for in terms acceptable to science.&amp;#160; More or less the orthodoxy in contemporary ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://edwardfeser.blogspot.com/2023/03/putnam-on-reason-reductionism-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;ve been programming full time for the past 5 years. Am I a senior engineer yet?</title>
      <link>https://cuffaro.com/2023-03-26-am-i-a-senior-engineer-yet/</link>
      <description>experiences</description>
      <author> (mike)</author>
      <guid>https://cuffaro.com/2023-03-26-am-i-a-senior-engineer-yet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software is not defined by the language it&amp;#39;s written in</title>
      <link>https://garrit.xyz/posts/2023-03-26-software-is-not-defined-by-the-language-it%27s-written-in</link>
      <description>Generalist developer writing about fullstack development, system administration and free software.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://garrit.xyz/posts/2023-03-26-software-is-not-defined-by-the-language-it%27s-written-in</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Artificial in AI - Pravesh Koirala</title>
      <link>https://praveshkoirala.com/2023/03/16/the-artificial-in-ai/</link>
      <description>We may have figured out how to create a brain, before we figured out how it actually works. Full disclosure, the quote above is not mine. I heard it from someone who heard it from someone who read it somewhere on the Internet. But this perfectly summarizes how the release of GPT-4 has made me</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://praveshkoirala.com/2023/03/16/the-artificial-in-ai/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just update rules between neurons</title>
      <link>https://www.jtolio.com/2023/03/just-update-rules-between-neurons/</link>
      <description>A while ago, I came across this statement about Bing’s chatbot.</description>
      <author> (JT Olio)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jtolio.com/2023/03/just-update-rules-between-neurons/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Incremental and Disruptive innovations</title>
      <link>https://www.antonoriza.com/incremental-disruptive-innovations/</link>
      <description>The other day while I was scrolling through my LinkedIn feed I read the following quote:
Quote &amp;#171;The electric light did not come from the continuous improvement of candles&amp;#187; -Oren Harari This idea is relevant in the process of creating products and services, specifically it exemplifies the “incremental” versus “disruptive” improvement concepts.
The term “creation” is clear but in the current world a lot of people just copy/duplicate someone else’s product/service and implement it in their country or region targeting it as “innovation”.</description>
      <author> (Juan Antonio Oriza Armas)</author>
      <guid>https://www.antonoriza.com/incremental-disruptive-innovations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience Replay | Entangled Logs</title>
      <link>https://entangledlogs.com/archives/2023/xp_replay/</link>
      <description>As you wander in the woods, the sun begins to sink below the horizon. You are suddenly filled with joy as you remember similar scenes from your past. Maybe you visited this place with your loved ones when you were young or recently. Being here triggers memories that are special to you. If this doesn’t resonate with you, think of a time when you saw someone’s eyes light up as they experienced something new for the first time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://entangledlogs.com/archives/2023/xp_replay/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banking Crisis 2023: Who else is in trouble? - What the Hell is Beeping?</title>
      <link>https://davidschenz.com/banking-crisis-2023-who-else-is-in-trouble/</link>
      <description>Our previous article on the banking crisis looked at Silicon Valley Bank&amp;#39;s (SVB) 2022 10-K to determine the reason for their failure. Our analysis revealed</description>
      <author> (David Schenz)</author>
      <guid>https://davidschenz.com/banking-crisis-2023-who-else-is-in-trouble/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A note to my former self: You&amp;#39;re not supposed to take care of everything</title>
      <link>http://blog.killerstorm.dev/2023/03/a-note-to-my-former-self-youre-not.html</link>
      <description>In 2012-2013, I led the development of an open-source project called &amp;quot;Colored Coins&amp;quot;, which defined a protocol for user-issued fungible toke...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>http://blog.killerstorm.dev/2023/03/a-note-to-my-former-self-youre-not.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Disposable Software</title>
      <link>https://www.paritybits.me/disposable/</link>
      <description>The ratio of compute(disposable software) to  compute(maintained software) will double every 18 months.

Or maybe

The average deployable lifespan of new sof...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.paritybits.me/disposable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 21:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Things Orgs Do That Kill Productivity w/ Netflix, FloSports &amp;amp; Refactoring.club</title>
      <link>https://devinterrupted.substack.com/p/stupid-things-orgs-do-that-kill-productivity</link>
      <description>From the archives: As we progress through Season 3, we thought it would be nice to look back at some of our best episodes that haven’t been posted to our Substack page. Enjoy! At LinearB, we like to think we spend all our time figuring out how to unlock developer potential. To find ways to let devs do more of the work they love and reduce the amount of time they spend dealing with needless hurdles, idling and churn.</description>
      <author> (Dev Interrupted)</author>
      <guid>https://devinterrupted.substack.com/p/stupid-things-orgs-do-that-kill-productivity</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 17:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDC Vault</title>
      <link>https://www.gdcvault.com/</link>
      <description>Having trouble viewing our new site? Try clearing your browser&amp;#39;s cache.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.gdcvault.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 09:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>systemd 100% cpu hang?</title>
      <link>https://forum.proxmox.com/threads/systemd-100-cpu-hang.124767/</link>
      <description>Ok I&amp;#39;ve been at this for the past several hours, I&amp;#39;ve tried everything and at this stage I don&amp;#39;t know what to do next.
This morning I woke up with my NUC fans spinning quite high. When I tried to connect to ssh or shell I had no joy. So I tried a reboot. To my surprise my proxmox host was never...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://forum.proxmox.com/threads/systemd-100-cpu-hang.124767/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 07:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor WASM Dockerizing</title>
      <link>https://ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-dockerizing/</link>
      <description>In this post I will teach you how to dockerize stand alone blazor wasm app in .NET. All with live working demo.</description>
      <author> (Abdul Rahman Shabeek Mohamed)</author>
      <guid>https://ilovedotnet.org/blogs/blazor-wasm-dockerizing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 05:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice authentication</title>
      <link>https://www.ato.gov.au/general/online-services/voice-authentication/</link>
      <description>Use voice authentication to quickly and securely verify your identity when you phone us.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ato.gov.au/general/online-services/voice-authentication/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 04:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hassle-free web app development with Cloudflare Quick Tunnels</title>
      <link>https://jonasclaes.be/hassle-free-web-app-development-with-cloudflare-quick-tunnels/</link>
      <description>Discover how to publish your local web server securely with Cloudflare Tunnels. Get the performance, security, and flexibility you need while sharing your projects easily. TryCloudflare simplifies the process, letting you test and share without domain/DNS hassles.</description>
      <author> (Jonas Claes

Mar 24, 2023
• 2 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://jonasclaes.be/hassle-free-web-app-development-with-cloudflare-quick-tunnels/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does hifi audio sound like?</title>
      <link>https://www.julian.com/guide/hifi/train</link>
      <description>What hifi audio sounds like.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.julian.com/guide/hifi/train</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic vs Connectionist Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://vaclavkosar.com/ml/Symbolic-vs-Connectionist-Machine-Learning</link>
      <description>Reasoning and reducing hallucinations in large language models by hybridizing with algorithms.</description>
      <author> (Vaclav Kosar)</author>
      <guid>https://vaclavkosar.com/ml/Symbolic-vs-Connectionist-Machine-Learning</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At What Point Dedication Becomes an Obsession? - This Blog Contains Words</title>
      <link>https://axython.com/2023/03/24/at-what-point-dedication-becomes-an-obsession/</link>
      <description>Something interesting I was thinking today. Dedication is something important and usually cheered and looked as a positive force, while obsession is looked as not...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://axython.com/2023/03/24/at-what-point-dedication-becomes-an-obsession/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Kotlin/Wasm</title>
      <link>https://seb.deleuze.fr/introducing-kotlin-wasm/</link>
      <description>This blog post is a refined transcription of the presentation Zalim Bashorov and I gave at Wasm I/O 2023 to introduce Kotlin/Wasm. I will later add a video of the recording when available.
Zalim Hi, everyone! I’m Zalim. I’m writing Kotlin in Kotlin at JetBrains and leading Kotlin/Wasm. We are going to have a quick journey around Kotlin/Wasm, we will see what the possibilities are, and also have a look at the inside.</description>
      <author> (S&amp;#233;bastien Deleuze)</author>
      <guid>https://seb.deleuze.fr/introducing-kotlin-wasm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The age of average — Alex Murrell</title>
      <link>https://www.alexmurrell.co.uk/articles/the-age-of-average</link>
      <description>In the early 1990s, two Russian artists named Vitaly Komar and Alexander Melamid hired a market research firm to survey the public on what they wanted in a work of art. Across 11 countries they then set about painting a piece that reflected the results. Each piece was intended to be a unique a colla</description>
      <author> (Mar 20
            
            Written By Alex Murrell)</author>
      <guid>https://www.alexmurrell.co.uk/articles/the-age-of-average</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tooled. —&amp;#160;ethanmarcotte.com</title>
      <link>https://ethanmarcotte.com/wrote/tooled/</link>
      <description>The work, and who gets to do it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ethanmarcotte.com/wrote/tooled/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airbnb is worse than a casino addiction</title>
      <link>https://davekiss.com/blog/airbnb-is-worse-than-a-casino-addiction</link>
      <description>Airbnb is worse than a casino addiction. It’s a sucker’s bet. It’s rigged. The house almost always wins. Everybody knows this. And yet, we all still tempt fate, itching for that once-in-a-lifetime, deal-of-the-century, jackpot experience that we’ll never forget.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davekiss.com/blog/airbnb-is-worse-than-a-casino-addiction</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvesting Logs for Fun and Profit</title>
      <link>https://beny23.github.io/posts/harvesting_logs_for_fun_and_profit/</link>
      <description>From a security point of view, application logs are two-sided. On the one hand, it is really important to have good observability, to find out what is happening and what has happened. On the other hand, we don’t want to leak sensitive information. In this post I am going to look at the kinds of things you might find in your logs. The juicy bits are Personal Identifying Information (PII) or security credentials.</description>
      <author> (Authorisation Tokens)</author>
      <guid>https://beny23.github.io/posts/harvesting_logs_for_fun_and_profit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agile Is A Glass Cannon</title>
      <link>https://www.tomdalling.com/blog/software-processes/agile-is-a-glass-cannon/</link>
      <description>A recent shower thought of mine is that agile software development
might be similar to the strategic concept of a glass
cannon in gaming —
specifically, that it’s a high-risk high-reward strategy where the risk can be
mitigated by skill/experience.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tomdalling.com/blog/software-processes/agile-is-a-glass-cannon/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My workflow</title>
      <link>https://g14n.info/2023/03/my-workflow/</link>
      <description>Principles and policies I use to organize my tasks. It also includes my own way to handle a kanban board which uses an interesting approach, the metadata.</description>
      <author> (Gianluca Casati)</author>
      <guid>https://g14n.info/2023/03/my-workflow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Unix Commands</title>
      <link>https://alexsaveau.dev/blog/projects/performance/files/fuc/fast-unix-commands</link>
      <description>Fast Unix Commands (FUC) is a project that aims to create the world’s fastest Unix commands. Currently, this means rm and cp replacements named rmz and cpz (the ‘z’ stands for “zippy”). When better performance cannot be achieved, the next highest priority is efficiency. In practice, rmz appears to be the fastest file deleter available while cpz wins in most cases, only losing in flat directory hierarchies.</description>
      <author> (Alex Saveau)</author>
      <guid>https://alexsaveau.dev/blog/projects/performance/files/fuc/fast-unix-commands</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Two-Part code review</title>
      <link>https://bran.name/two-part-code-review.html</link>
      <description>Published 2023-03-23</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bran.name/two-part-code-review.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On being bored as a tech enthusiast</title>
      <link>https://blog.ignaciobrasca.com/opinion/2023/02/01/on-being-bored.html</link>
      <description>Childhood dream and boredom as the world changes underneath</description>
      <author> (Ignacio Brasca)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ignaciobrasca.com/opinion/2023/02/01/on-being-bored.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 22:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>