<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>*Privacy Not Included: A Buyer’s Guide for Connected Products</title>
      <link>https://foundation.mozilla.org/en/privacynotincluded/articles/its-official-cars-are-the-worst-product-category-we-have-ever-reviewed-for-privacy/</link>
      <description>All 25 car brands we researched earned our *Privacy Not Included warning label – making cars the worst category of products that we have ever reviewed</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://foundation.mozilla.org/en/privacynotincluded/articles/its-official-cars-are-the-worst-product-category-we-have-ever-reviewed-for-privacy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 01:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tales from the .NET Migration Trenches - Empty Proxy</title>
      <link>https://www.jimmybogard.com/tales-from-the-net-migration-trenches-empty-proxy/</link>
      <description>Posts in this series:


 * Intro
 * Cataloging
 * Empty Proxy


In the previous post, we looked at techniques for determining the size and scope of our .NET migration effort, as well as clarifying what our goals should be. But before we start migrating anything, we wanted to &amp;quot;establish a beachhead&amp;quot; and work</description>
      <author> (Jimmy Bogard
                
                    Sep 6, 2023
                        • 4 min read)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jimmybogard.com/tales-from-the-net-migration-trenches-empty-proxy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 01:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>373: Installing the .NET 9 Alpha</title>
      <link>https://player.fireside.fm/v2/UDzB5o3V+fVq58Dpn/twitter</link>
      <description>Powerful podcast hosting and analytics. By podcasters, for podcasters.</description>
      <author> (Fireside Labs, LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://player.fireside.fm/v2/UDzB5o3V+fVq58Dpn/twitter</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK pulls back from clash with Big Tech over private messaging</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/770e58b1-a299-4b7b-a129-bded8649a43b</link>
      <description>Ministers will not immediately enforce online safety bill powers to scan apps after WhatsApp threatened shutdown</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ft.com/content/770e58b1-a299-4b7b-a129-bded8649a43b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 23:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully automated data driven authoritarianism ain’t what it’s cracked up to be</title>
      <link>https://crookedtimber.org/2023/07/25/51610/</link>
      <description>Last September, Abe Newman, Jeremy Wallace and I had a&amp;#160;piece&amp;#160;in&amp;#160;Foreign Affairs’ 100th anniversary issue. I can’t speak for my co-authors’ motivations, but my own reason for writing was vexation th…</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100006446086669)</author>
      <guid>https://crookedtimber.org/2023/07/25/51610/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:08:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future headwinds</title>
      <link>https://radoncnotes.com/2023/09/06/the-future-headwinds/</link>
      <description>Photo by Tomas Ryant on Pexels.com I have had several interesting conversations with a range of individuals over the past few weeks. The hard part is not convincing them to do something. The most d…</description>
      <author> (RadOnc Notes)</author>
      <guid>https://radoncnotes.com/2023/09/06/the-future-headwinds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:08:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Wasm, Part 3: You Are Here - Chris Dickinson</title>
      <link>https://www.neversaw.us/2023/09/04/understanding-wasm/part3/you-are-here/</link>
      <description>Understanding WASM, Part 3: You Are Here</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.neversaw.us/2023/09/04/understanding-wasm/part3/you-are-here/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:08:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js includes built-in support for .env files</title>
      <link>https://philna.sh/blog/2023/09/05/nodejs-supports-dotenv/</link>
      <description>With the recent release of version 20.6.0, Node.js now has built-in support for .env files. You can now load environment variables from a .env file into...</description>
      <author> (Phil Nash)</author>
      <guid>https://philna.sh/blog/2023/09/05/nodejs-supports-dotenv/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:08:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ryjo.codes - A JSON Validator in C</title>
      <link>https://ryjo.codes/articles/a-json-validator-in-c.html</link>
      <description>This article describes an implementation of a json parser in C.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ryjo.codes/articles/a-json-validator-in-c.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:08:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Request Latency with Profiling</title>
      <link>https://richardstartin.github.io/posts/wallclock-profiler</link>
      <description>It can be hard to figure out why response times are high in Java applications. In my experience, people either apply a process of elimination to a set of recent commits, or might sometimes use profiles of the system to explain changes in metrics. Making guesses about recent commits can be frustrating for a number of reasons, but mostly because even if you pinpoint the causal change, you still might not know why it was a bad change and are left in limbo. In theory, using a profiler makes root cause analysis a part of the triage process, so adopting continuous profiling should make this whole process easier, but using profilers can be frustrating because you’re using the wrong type of profile for analysis. Lots of profiling data focuses on CPU time, but the cause of your latency problem may be related to time spent off CPU instead. This post is about Datadog’s Java wallclock profiler, which I worked on last year, and explores how to improve request latency without making any code changes, or even seeing the code for that matter.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://richardstartin.github.io/posts/wallclock-profiler</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:08:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make your own PCB Hacker Card</title>
      <link>https://jams.hackclub.com/jam/hacker-card</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s build a business card -- but with a twist -- it can transmit a URL on tap and light up! You&amp;#39;ll learn the basics of designing a PCB, and you can get the cards made for free, with Hack Club&amp;#39;s OnBoard.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jams.hackclub.com/jam/hacker-card</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Upgrade Assistant Boosts MAUI as .NET 8 Nears GA -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/09/06/upgrade-assistant.aspx</link>
      <description>Microsoft upgraded its .NET Upgrade Assistant tool with improvements to .NET MAUI functionality and other new features as it gets ready to ship .NET 8 next month.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel09/06/2023)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2023/09/06/upgrade-assistant.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s Read the Turbo Source: What Happens When You Click a Link?</title>
      <link>https://www.akshaykhot.com/turbo-internals/</link>
      <description>Reading the source code is one of the best ways to learn how a feature, framework, or a program works. In this post, we&amp;#39;ll explore the source code of Hotwire&amp;#39;s Turbo library to understand exactly what happens when you click a link. I hope you&amp;#39;ll appreciate Turbo much more after this deep dive.</description>
      <author> (Akshay Khot)</author>
      <guid>https://www.akshaykhot.com/turbo-internals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s New in Teams Toolkit for Visual Studio 17.7</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YeGRgScvil8</link>
      <description>John Miller is back to talk more about building Microsoft Teams apps with .NET and this time will share what&amp;#39;s new in Teams Toolkit for Visual Studio 17.7. I...</description>
      <author> (dotnet
  
  
  
    dotnet
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YeGRgScvil8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can I trust the code that GitHub Copilot generates?</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=89ZyoEGwDOI</link>
      <description>Can I trust the code that GitHub Copilot generates? Damian Brady shares his thoughts on how to evaluate and use the code GitHub Copilot generates.Learn more:...</description>
      <author> (Developers Digest
  
  
  
    Developers Digest
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=89ZyoEGwDOI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Effective Remote Working</title>
      <link>https://mikemcquaid.com/more-effective-remote-working/</link>
      <description>COVID-19 was many people’s first introduction to the working-from-home experience. I’ve been lucky enough to have been working from home exclusively since 2009 and at US-based companies (e.g. GitHub) since 2012. I’ve also been an EU-based open-source maintainer since 2007 and maintaining the globally-distributed Homebrew package manager since 2009. These experiences have helped me learn some tips on how to be more effective working remotely that I’d like to share with you:</description>
      <author> (Mike McQuaid)</author>
      <guid>https://mikemcquaid.com/more-effective-remote-working/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dunghill Anti-Pattern - Why utility classes and modules smell?</title>
      <link>https://mattilehtinen.com/articles/dunghill-anti-pattern-why-utility-classes-and-modules-smell/</link>
      <description>Learn why utility classes or helper files can become problematic in your software project. Get practical tips for organizing utility functions, as well as alternatives to utility classes.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mattilehtinen.com/articles/dunghill-anti-pattern-why-utility-classes-and-modules-smell/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Should Founders Pay Themselves?</title>
      <link>https://www.descrumble.com/blog/how-much-should-founders-pay-themselves</link>
      <description>Key principles that guide how much to pay yourself, ensuring a balance between personal needs and business growth.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.descrumble.com/blog/how-much-should-founders-pay-themselves</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luasnip and Treesitter for Smarter Snippets</title>
      <link>https://cj.rs/blog/luasnip-and-treesitter-for-smarter-snippets/</link>
      <description>An example on Go error handling.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cj.rs/blog/luasnip-and-treesitter-for-smarter-snippets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Internet of PHP</title>
      <link>https://timotijhof.net/posts/2023/an-internet-of-php/</link>
      <description>Statistics and anecdotes about PHP at scale.</description>
      <author> (Timo Tijhof)</author>
      <guid>https://timotijhof.net/posts/2023/an-internet-of-php/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How one Book changed my view about Writing Online</title>
      <link>https://brianchristner.io/how-one-book-changed-my-view-about-writing-online/</link>
      <description>Interested to learn how to write better online? I found the ultimate book to give you all the secrets written by someone with over 500m+ page views, six books, and three businesses, and is clever as hell.</description>
      <author> (Brian Christner)</author>
      <guid>https://brianchristner.io/how-one-book-changed-my-view-about-writing-online/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Write a Secure JWT Library If You Absolutely Must</title>
      <link>https://scottarc.blog/2023/09/06/how-to-write-a-secure-jwt-library-if-you-absolutely-must/</link>
      <description>I am famously not a fan of JSON Web Tokens (JWT). Like most cryptography and security experts familiar with JWT, I would much rather you use something else if you can. I even proposed a secure alte…</description>
      <author> (Scott Arciszewski)</author>
      <guid>https://scottarc.blog/2023/09/06/how-to-write-a-secure-jwt-library-if-you-absolutely-must/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Nemo, revisited</title>
      <link>https://www.lukatela.com/pointNemoRevisited/index.html</link>
      <description>Point Nemo is defined as that point on the world&amp;#39;s oceans
that is furthest away from any land.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lukatela.com/pointNemoRevisited/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How-to Evaluate a Product Roadmap, for Engineers</title>
      <link>https://stephen.fm/how-to-evaluate-a-product-roadmap/</link>
      <description>Aka, how do I know if a product manager knows what they&amp;#39;re doing?


There are thousands of articles, courses, and guides on how to build a roadmap for product managers. Even with all these resources, roadmaps often end up being a point of contention between product managers and their stakeholders.</description>
      <author> (Harvard Business Review)</author>
      <guid>https://stephen.fm/how-to-evaluate-a-product-roadmap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please Kindly Leave Stdout Alone When Printing Your Beautiful Logo</title>
      <link>https://citrinefox.com/posts/2023-09-02-leave-stdout-alone/</link>
      <description>It was many years ago. At my to-be-previous job, we wanted to try some new modeling things. We grabbed the then-latest TensorFlow docker image (Since the model was based on TensorFlow—I forget which one though) and it spun up smoothly. The container even printed a pretty logo in colorful ASCII art as shown in the cover image.
The experiments went well. We eventually packed some more dependencies and an sshd (and some sort of init, of course) in, and asked IT to put the image on a shared GPU box.</description>
      <author> (Hojin Koh)</author>
      <guid>https://citrinefox.com/posts/2023-09-02-leave-stdout-alone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hybrid Architecture of Kinopio for iOS</title>
      <link>https://pketh.org/kinopio-ios.html</link>
      <description>Using Kinopio iOS running on my scratched up iPhone 12 mini</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pketh.org/kinopio-ios.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Push and Pull</title>
      <link>https://kellanem.com/notes/push-and-pull</link>
      <description>A model I return to a lot when talking about engineering processes is Push and Pull. Often when we design a new process or system we struggle to get buy-in. That lack of buy-in can often be traced to having forgotten the Push, the Pull, or both.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kellanem.com/notes/push-and-pull</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:08:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation extractable versions of Groth’s zk-SNARK revisited - International Journal of Information Security</title>
      <link>https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10207-023-00750-7</link>
      <description>Zero-knowledge succinct non-interactive arguments of knowledge (zk-SNARKs) are the most efficient proof systems in terms of proof size and verification. Currently, Groth’s scheme from EUROCRYPT 2016, $$	extsf{Groth16}$$ Groth 16 , is the state-of-the-art and is widely deployed in practice. $$	extsf{Groth16}$$ Groth 16 is originally proven to achieve knowledge soundness, which does not guarantee the non-malleability of proofs. There has been considerable progress in presenting new zk-SNARKs or modifying $$	extsf{Groth16}$$ Groth 16 to efficiently achieve strong Simulation extractability, which is shown to be a necessary requirement in some applications. In this paper, we revise the Random oracle based variant of $$	extsf{Groth16}$$ Groth 16 proposed by Bowe and Gabizon, BG18, the most efficient one in terms of prover efficiency and CRS size among the candidates, and present a more efficient variant that saves 2 pairings in the verification and 1 group element in the proof. This supersedes our preliminary construction, presented in CANS 2020 (Baghery et al. in CANS 20, volume 12579 of LNCS, Springer, Heidelberg. pp 453-461, 2020), which saved 1 pairing in the verification, and was proven in the generic group model. Our new construction also improves on BG18 in that our proofs are in the algebraic group model with Random Oracles and reduces security to standard computational assumptions in bilinear groups (as opposed to using the full power of the generic group model (GGM)). We implement our proposed simulation extractable zk-SNARK (SE zk-SNARK) along with BG18 in the Arkworks library, and compare the efficiency of our scheme with some related works. Our empirical experiences confirm that our SE zk-SNARK is more efficient than all previous simulation extractable (SE) schemes in most dimensions and it has very close efficiency to the original $$	extsf{Groth16}$$ Groth 16 .</description>
      <author> (R&amp;#224;fols, Carla)</author>
      <guid>https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10207-023-00750-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 20:03:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. Abandons, for Now, Legislation That Would Have Banned End-to-End Encryption</title>
      <link>https://daringfireball.net/linked/2023/09/06/uk-encryption-win</link>
      <description>Link to: https://www.ft.com/content/770e58b1-a299-4b7b-a129-bded8649a43b</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://daringfireball.net/linked/2023/09/06/uk-encryption-win</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 20:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scheduled or Delayed Messages in Wolverine</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/09/06/scheduled-or-delayed-messages-in-wolverine/</link>
      <description>Wolverine has first class support for delayed or scheduled message delivery. While I don’t think I’d recommend using Wolverine as a one for one replacement for a Hangfire or Quartz.Net,…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/09/06/scheduled-or-delayed-messages-in-wolverine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 19:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - leandromoreira/linux-network-performance-parameters: Learn where some of the network sysctl variables fit into the Linux/Kernel network flow. Translations: &amp;#127479;&amp;#127482;</title>
      <link>https://github.com/leandromoreira/linux-network-performance-parameters</link>
      <description>Learn where some of the network sysctl variables fit into the Linux/Kernel network flow. Translations: &amp;#127479;&amp;#127482; - GitHub - leandromoreira/linux-network-performance-parameters: Learn where some of the net...</description>
      <author> (leandromoreira)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/leandromoreira/linux-network-performance-parameters</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 19:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elevating Debugging with Auto-decompilation and External Sources - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/elevating-debugging-with-auto-decompilation-and-external-sources/</link>
      <description>Visual Studio has been supporting external sources debugging and decompilation for some time now. However, with the release of Visual Studio 17.6, the debugger took a significant leap forward by introducing Auto-decompilation for .NET libraries making the External sources debugging in Visual Studio much more streamlined and effortless. Its integrated decompiler, it decompiles external code in real-time and seamlessly incorporates it into the debugger as needed.</description>
      <author> (Harshada Hole)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/elevating-debugging-with-auto-decompilation-and-external-sources/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 19:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autumn and Fall</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2825/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2825/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 19:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing Bad C# Advice | Q&amp;amp;A | .NET &amp;amp; C# &amp;#128308; LIVE</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=quboFzWEFno</link>
      <description>Check out my courses: https://dometrain.comSupport the stream: https://streamlabs.com/nick_chapsasBecome a Patreon and get source code access: https://www.pa...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=quboFzWEFno</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 17:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Time-Saving Tips in Visual Studio 2022 (with Tim Corey)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=urI8_beoziE</link>
      <description>Join Tim Corey and Dalia as they dive deep into 10 Time-Saving Tips in Visual Studio 2022 that will enhance your daily development workflow. From brand-new f...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=urI8_beoziE</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 16:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this duplo train track under too much tension?</title>
      <link>https://puzzling.stackexchange.com/questions/122232/is-this-duplo-train-track-under-too-much-tension</link>
      <description>My kids were making this train track of duplo the other day, and this is what they have put together. They are still very young, and for them, this is something big: they were really proud that the...</description>
      <author> (LezzupLezzup
        
            4,36111 gold badge77 silver badges4343 bronze badges)</author>
      <guid>https://puzzling.stackexchange.com/questions/122232/is-this-duplo-train-track-under-too-much-tension</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 16:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - eigilnikolajsen/commit-mono: Commit Mono is an anonymous and neutral programming typeface focused on creating a better reading experience.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/eigilnikolajsen/commit-mono</link>
      <description>Commit Mono is an anonymous and neutral programming typeface focused on creating a better reading experience. - GitHub - eigilnikolajsen/commit-mono: Commit Mono is an anonymous and neutral program...</description>
      <author> (eigilnikolajsen)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/eigilnikolajsen/commit-mono</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 16:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New EU Rules: Smartphones and Tablets will follow new ecodesign requirements by June 2025! - Right to Repair Europe</title>
      <link>https://repair.eu/news/new-eu-rules-smartphones-and-tablets-will-follow-new-ecodesign-requirements-by-june-2025/</link>
      <description>As of June 2025 smartphones and tablets will have to follow the new EU ecodesign rules. Read the article for our take on repairability aspects.</description>
      <author> (Cristina Ganapini)</author>
      <guid>https://repair.eu/news/new-eu-rules-smartphones-and-tablets-will-follow-new-ecodesign-requirements-by-june-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 15:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You’ve Got a New Car, It’s a Data Privacy Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/mozilla-new-cars-data-privacy-report-1850805416</link>
      <description>Bad news: your car is a spy. Every major car brand failed a recent privacy and security test from Mozilla. You’re probably driving around in a &amp;quot;privacy nightmare&amp;quot; that may collect information as sensitive as your race, health status, and sexual activity. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gizmodo.com/mozilla-new-cars-data-privacy-report-1850805416</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 15:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Network Programming in C# 12 &amp;amp; .NET 8 - Chris Woodruff&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/practical-network-programming-csharp/</link>
      <description>I am thrilled to announce my new adventure into the world of book writing with my upcoming title, &amp;quot;Practical Network Programming Using C#.&amp;quot; A few months ago, I received a request about deep diving into network programming, particularly with C#. I am very passionate about this area of software development, so I agreed, and Packt will publish the book.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/practical-network-programming-csharp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 14:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How would you say &amp;quot;She said goodbye too many times before.&amp;quot; in Latin?</title>
      <link>https://latin.stackexchange.com/questions/21491/how-would-you-say-she-said-goodbye-too-many-times-before-in-latin/21492#21492</link>
      <description>The refrain of the Maroon 5&amp;#39;s song &amp;amp;quot;This Love&amp;amp;quot; contains the verse &amp;amp;quot;She said goodbye too many times before.&amp;amp;quot;. How would you translate that verse into Latin? My attempt would be &amp;amp;...</description>
      <author> (Draconis♦Draconis
        
            63.8k66 gold badges113113 silver badges253253 bronze badges)</author>
      <guid>https://latin.stackexchange.com/questions/21491/how-would-you-say-she-said-goodbye-too-many-times-before-in-latin/21492#21492</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 14:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting whether a tree-like data structure contains a cycle - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230906-00/?p=108726</link>
      <description>Combining two things we already know.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230906-00/?p=108726</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 14:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Retrieval Augmented Generation with .NET - .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/demystifying-retrieval-augmented-generation-with-dotnet/</link>
      <description>Build a chat-based console app with Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) from scratch.</description>
      <author> (Stephen Toub - MSFT)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/demystifying-retrieval-augmented-generation-with-dotnet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 13:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dictionary - A Primer On When And How To Use in C#</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/09/06/c-dictionary-a-primer-on-when-and-how-to-use/</link>
      <description>Dictionaries in C# are heavily used by all levels of software developers. Let&amp;#39;s look at some dictionary use cases and comparisons to other collections!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2023/09/06/c-dictionary-a-primer-on-when-and-how-to-use/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 13:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core in Action, Third Edition: Lock, Andrew: 9781633438620: Amazon.com: Books</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/ASP-NET-Core-Action-Third-Andrew/dp/1633438627?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202309</link>
      <description>ASP.NET Core in Action, Third Edition [Lock, Andrew] on Amazon.com. *FREE* shipping on qualifying offers. ASP.NET Core in Action, Third Edition</description>
      <author> (Andrew LockAndrew Lock + Follow More books from this author)</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/ASP-NET-Core-Action-Third-Andrew/dp/1633438627?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202309</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 10:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft .NET Code Analysis: Properly Formatting Class Files</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/09/06/microsoft-net-code-analysis-properly-formatting-class-files/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of consistent formatting in Microsoft .NET class files for improved code readability and collaboration among developers. It provides tips on how to set up forma…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave
		

		
			I live in San Diego, Ca USA			
				View all posts by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/09/06/microsoft-net-code-analysis-properly-formatting-class-files/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 10:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need to know about configuration and secret management in .NET</title>
      <link>https://stenbrinke.nl/blog/configuration-and-secret-management-in-dotnet/</link>
      <description>A handy pocketguide that covers everything a .NET developer needs to know about configuration and secret management!</description>
      <author> (Sander ten Brinke)</author>
      <guid>https://stenbrinke.nl/blog/configuration-and-secret-management-in-dotnet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 10:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fast.ai - Can LLMs learn from a single example?</title>
      <link>https://www.fast.ai/posts/2023-09-04-learning-jumps/</link>
      <description>We’ve noticed an unusual training pattern in fine-tuning LLMs. At first we thought it’s a bug, but now we think it shows LLMs can learn effectively from a single example.</description>
      <author> (Jeremy Howard and Jonathan Whitaker)</author>
      <guid>https://www.fast.ai/posts/2023-09-04-learning-jumps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 10:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differences Between Any and Exists Methods in C# - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-differences-between-any-and-exists-methods/</link>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss the Any and Exists methods in C#, and analyze their properties, differences, and use cases.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-differences-between-any-and-exists-methods/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 09:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EI025: SQL Processing Service (Part 5)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Doapulf7rvg</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (Hassan Habib
  
  
  
    Hassan Habib
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=Doapulf7rvg</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 06:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-tenancy with ASP.NET Core and FinBuckle.Multitenant</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/multi-tenancy-with-aspnet-core-and-finbuckle-multitenant</link>
      <description>Multi-tenancy is a complex topic with a generally understood definition, yet the devil is in the details. From a high level, Multi-tenancy is the idea that a...</description>
      <author> (About Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/multi-tenancy-with-aspnet-core-and-finbuckle-multitenant</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 06:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build your UI as a finite state machine</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/09/build-your-ui-as-finite-state-machine.html</link>
      <description>As an architect I’m regularly involved in code reviews. One of the lessons I learned from reviewing so many codebases is that most codebases...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2023/09/build-your-ui-as-finite-state-machine.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 06:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event Counters - Running Locally</title>
      <link>https://pmichaels.net/event-counters-local/</link>
      <description>I’ve recently been playing with Event Counters in .Net.  These are basically a way to record a set of metrics against a given program.  In this post, I’ll cover…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pmichaels.net/event-counters-local/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 06:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>