<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Overkill Objects for Everyday Life</title>
      <link>https://neil.computer/notes/overkill-objects-for-everyday-life/</link>
      <description>I routinely make a fool of myself when I tell friends I want a Martin Baker ejection seat as a chair in my living room. Of course, with the pyrotechnic charge removed. Seriously, I would totally buy it if it weren&amp;#39;t $5,000 on eBay and I&amp;#39;ve got a watchlist</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://neil.computer/notes/overkill-objects-for-everyday-life/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 19:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Prime Is an Economy-Distorting Lie</title>
      <link>https://mattstoller.substack.com/p/amazon-primes-free-shipping-promise</link>
      <description>A new antitrust case shows that Prime inflates prices across the board, using the false promise of &amp;#39;free shipping&amp;#39; that is anything but free.</description>
      <author> (Matt Stoller)</author>
      <guid>https://mattstoller.substack.com/p/amazon-primes-free-shipping-promise</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 18:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drunk Post: Things I&amp;#39;ve learned as a Sr Engineer</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/ExperiencedDevs/comments/nmodyl/drunk_post_things_ive_learned_as_a_sr_engineer/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m drunk and I&amp;#39;ll probably regret this, but here&amp;#39;s a drunken rank of things I&amp;#39;ve learned as an engineer for the past 10 years. * The best way...</description>
      <author> (kormapls)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/ExperiencedDevs/comments/nmodyl/drunk_post_things_ive_learned_as_a_sr_engineer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 18:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Conway&amp;#39;s Game of Life</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bCRI9fEl9UU</link>
      <description>hello</description>
      <author> (Rust
  
  
    

    
      
    Rust
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bCRI9fEl9UU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 17:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the best engineering advice I stole from non-technical people</title>
      <link>https://bellmar.medium.com/all-the-best-engineering-advice-i-stole-from-non-technical-people-eb7f90ca2f5f</link>
      <description>As I focus on becoming a better manager of engineers, I have been reflecting more and more on the advice that produced a 10X boost in my…</description>
      <author> (https://bellmar.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://bellmar.medium.com/all-the-best-engineering-advice-i-stole-from-non-technical-people-eb7f90ca2f5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 17:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please Commit More Blatant Academic Fraud</title>
      <link>https://jacobbuckman.com/2021-05-29-please-commit-more-blatant-academic-fraud/</link>
      <description>This week, I was thrilled to read about the first well-documented case of explicit academic fraud in the artificial intelligence community. I hope that this is the beginning of a trend, and that other researchers will be inspired by their example and follow up by engaging in even more blatant...</description>
      <author> (Jacob Buckman)</author>
      <guid>https://jacobbuckman.com/2021-05-29-please-commit-more-blatant-academic-fraud/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 15:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add support for customising the creation of Kestrel listen sockets by deanward81 &amp;#183; Pull Request #32827 &amp;#183; dotnet/aspnetcore</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/aspnetcore/pull/32827</link>
      <description>Fixes #32794. As mentioned in the issue it is currently not possible to configure the underlying listen socket used by Kestrel. In certain circumstances it is desirable to be able to configure sock...</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/aspnetcore/pull/32827</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 13:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‎CloudSkills.fm: 097: Programming in Go with Michael Levan on Apple Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/cloudskills-fm/id1448194100?i=1000501333009</link>
      <description>‎Show CloudSkills.fm, Ep 097: Programming in Go with Michael Levan - Dec 4, 2020</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/cloudskills-fm/id1448194100?i=1000501333009</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 11:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‎The .NET Core Podcast: Blazor Catch-up with Chris Sainty on Apple Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-net-core-podcast/id1433496275?i=1000504727439</link>
      <description>‎Show The .NET Core Podcast, Ep Blazor Catch-up with Chris Sainty - Jan 8, 2021</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-net-core-podcast/id1433496275?i=1000504727439</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 11:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio lawmakers want to abolish vaccine requirements—all vaccine requirements</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/05/ohio-lawmakers-want-to-abolish-vaccine-requirements-all-vaccine-requirements/?utm_social-type=owned</link>
      <description>Someone would only have to verbally decline vaccination and cite &amp;quot;reasons of conscience.&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> (Beth Mole
    -  5/27/2021, 4:45 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/05/ohio-lawmakers-want-to-abolish-vaccine-requirements-all-vaccine-requirements/?utm_social-type=owned</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 11:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To .NET Interactive</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=02gEHg_m3CU</link>
      <description>Join us as Maria Naggaga, Senior Program Manager for .NET Interactive and ASP.NET demonstrates how .NET Interactive takes the power of .NET and embeds it int...</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
    

    
      
    .NET Foundation
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=02gEHg_m3CU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 11:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have I Been Pwned teams with FBI, gives open-source access to code</title>
      <link>https://www.scmagazine.com/password-management/have-i-been-pwned-teams-with-fbi-gives-open-source-access-to-code/</link>
      <description>The FBI will provide breached passwords to Have I Been Pwned when they are discovered during investigations, in an effort to better inform victims of cybercrime of compromise.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.scmagazine.com/password-management/have-i-been-pwned-teams-with-fbi-gives-open-source-access-to-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 10:06:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Refused to Refund $7,000 After Shipping an Empty Box Instead of a Sony a1</title>
      <link>https://fstoppers.com/news/amazon-refused-refund-7000-after-shipping-empty-box-instead-sony-a1-564979</link>
      <description>A couple in Alabama were left shocked after Amazon delivered an empty box instead of the Sony a1 worth $7,000 that they ordered — and then refused to give them a refund. As reported by PetaPixel and The Denver Channel (skip to 1:03), Bill and Kelly Chiles ordered the Sony a1 back in mid-March and waited patiently for it to arrive. Upon delivery, they opened their package and were confused to find two boxes for the Sony a1, both of which were empty. Upon contacting Amazon, the company insisted that the product had been delivered and refused to offer a refund.</description>
      <author> (http://www.facebook.com/andydayphotography)</author>
      <guid>https://fstoppers.com/news/amazon-refused-refund-7000-after-shipping-empty-box-instead-sony-a1-564979</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 10:06:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Short Hike for Nintendo Switch - Nintendo Game Details</title>
      <link>https://www.nintendo.com/games/detail/a-short-hike-switch/</link>
      <description>Hike, climb, and soar through the peaceful mountainside landscapes of Hawk Peak Provincial Park.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nintendo.com/games/detail/a-short-hike-switch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 07:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve the rate of thread injection for blocking due to sync-over-async by kouvel &amp;#183; Pull Request #53471 &amp;#183; dotnet/runtime</title>
      <link>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/53471</link>
      <description>Fixes #52558</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/dotnet/runtime/pull/53471</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 06:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon devices will soon automatically share your Internet with neighbors</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/05/amazon-devices-will-soon-automatically-share-your-internet-with-neighbors/</link>
      <description>Amazon&amp;#39;s experiment wireless mesh networking turns users into guinea pigs.</description>
      <author> (Dan Goodin
    -  5/29/2021, 12:10 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/05/amazon-devices-will-soon-automatically-share-your-internet-with-neighbors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 05:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using HTMX with ASP.NET Core: Inline editing</title>
      <link>https://www.jerriepelser.com/blog/htmx-inline-editing/</link>
      <description>I demonstrate how you can add an inline editing experience for a list of items using ASP.NET Core and HTMX</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jerriepelser.com/blog/htmx-inline-editing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 04:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Added endpoint and password ingestion by mdawsonuk &amp;#183; Pull Request #17 &amp;#183; HaveIBeenPwned/PwnedPasswordsAzureFunction</title>
      <link>https://github.com/HaveIBeenPwned/PwnedPasswordsAzureFunction/pull/17</link>
      <description>This Pull Request adds an Azure Function endpoint at &amp;amp;lt;url&amp;amp;gt;/range/append which will take a JSON POST payload with three values - sha1Hash, ntlmHash and prevalence -  that were specified in you...</description>
      <author> (HaveIBeenPwned)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/HaveIBeenPwned/PwnedPasswordsAzureFunction/pull/17</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 04:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trials begin on lozenge that rebuilds tooth enamel -&amp;#160;UW School of Dentistry</title>
      <link>https://dental.washington.edu/trials-begin-on-lozenge-that-rebuilds-tooth-enamel/</link>
      <description>A new breath mint that rebuilds your tooth enamel while it whitens your teeth has been created by UW Researchers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dental.washington.edu/trials-begin-on-lozenge-that-rebuilds-tooth-enamel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 01:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn X in Y Minutes: Scenic Programming Language Tours</title>
      <link>https://learnxinyminutes.com/</link>
      <description>Highlight your language:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://learnxinyminutes.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 00:06:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some recent papers in isogeny crypto</title>
      <link>https://ellipticnews.wordpress.com/2021/04/06/some-recent-papers-in-isogeny-crypto/</link>
      <description>There have been quite a few papers on isogeny crypto posted in the last few months. Here is a brief summary of some of them. I thank the members of my research group for fruitful discussions about …</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://ellipticnews.wordpress.com/2021/04/06/some-recent-papers-in-isogeny-crypto/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 22:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsing Signals on Remote Work From CEOs</title>
      <link>https://markmaunder.com/2021/05/parsing-signals-on-remote-work-from-ceos/</link>
      <description>Recent remarks of numerous chief executives suggest the culture of workplace face time remains alive and well. At The Wall Street Journal’s CEO Council Summit this month, JP Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co.’s Jamie Dimon said remote work doesn’t work well “for those who want to hustle.” Goldman Sachs CEO David Solomon has called it “an...</description>
      <author> (https://markmaunder.com/author/mark/)</author>
      <guid>https://markmaunder.com/2021/05/parsing-signals-on-remote-work-from-ceos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:08:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Guilty, Crazy Secret That Helps Me Write - RyanHoliday.net</title>
      <link>https://ryanholiday.net/the-guilty-crazy-secret-that-helps-me-write/</link>
      <description>GEORGE: I can’t get it out of my head. I just keep singing it over and over. It just comes out. I have no control over it. I’m singing it on elevators, buses. I sing it in front of clients. It’s taking over my life. JERRY: You know, Schumann went mad from that. He went crazy from one note. He couldn’t get it out of his head. I think it was an A. He kept repeating it over and over again. He had to be institutionalized. GEORGE: Really? What if it doesn’t stop? JERRY gestures “That’s the breaks.” – Seinfeld “The Jacket” I won’t say that I present the picture of mental health or anything, but most people would be surprised to find out I harbor a habit that hints at deep insanity. I listen to the same song over and over again. Alone in my office, or on my iPod, or on my phone, I play them on repeat over and over and over again. Loudly. In my iTunes library there are&amp;#160;certain songs of an embarrassing nature&amp;#160;that I have played more than 300 or 400 times in a row (that is a full 24 hours each). I’ve gone through so many computers over the last few years that I don’t have an accurate tally, but if I were to add them up, the numbers and the songs would seem preposterous, even to me. They are my version of the backyard shed, covered in incomprehensible gibberish in&amp;#160;A Beautiful Mind, or the wall in&amp;#160;Carrie Mathison’s&amp;#160;apartment after a manic fit. And then I wake from my stupor and discard the songs like used condoms and pretend it never happened. As a result, I no longer enjoy “music,” a fact that the 16-year-old version of myself–the one who was in a band and had hard drives full of rare music–would have found unthinkable. God knows, I never thought I’d find myself 142 listens in on a Taylor Swift song on a Tuesday morning. But there is a method to the madness. I found that this secret habit has been the fuel for&amp;#160;my creative output. See,&amp;#160;part of writing–or really any creative endeavor from brainstorming to marketing–requires tuning everything out. There are a couple ways to do this. You have your noise canceling headphones or ambient noise machines. You can put your phone on “Airplane Mode” or tell everyone to leave you alone. The problem with these reductive techniques is that they leave everything a little empty. In my experience, it’s not about quiet, it’s about finding your zone. I think melodic music, played on repeat, puts you in a heightened emotional state–while simultaneously dulling your awareness to most of your surroundings. It puts you in a creative zone. The important facilities are turned on, while all the others are turned off. Sometimes “good” songs can help you with that. But Bruce Springsteen only has so many songs that work for this (Try “I’m On Fire”). You exhaust them soon enough and have to start listening to songs on the Top 40. And you stop caring who wrote them–as long as it brings you closer to that state. Michael Lewis (Liar’s Poker, The Blind Side, The Big Short)&amp;#160;has spoken about this too. Writing a book–or really any major creative project–puts you in an “agitated mental state.” It’s hard to sleep, it’s hard to concentrate, it’s hard to be present in everyday. But you can’t afford that when you’re&amp;#160;actually working. He fixes that by&amp;#160;doing the following: I pull down the blinds. I put my headset on and play the same soundtrack of twenty songs over and over and I don’t hear them. It shuts everything else out. So I don’t hear myself as I’m writing and laughing and talking to myself. I’m not even aware I’m making noise. I’m having a physical reaction to a very engaging experience. It is not a detached process. You might ask, can you accomplish this by listening to music like a normal person? I would have thought so too, but the answer is no. Repeat on the same song or the same two or three songs allows the songs to fade into themselves–to become a more or less a continuous stream. The reason I gravitate towards radio singles is that they normally have big, catchy choruses. The idea is that after enough listens to song becomes a perpetual chorus. Time stops. Distractions stop. Extraneous thinking stops. (Proof of which is the fact that you’re not bothered by the fact that the song is looping every three minutes and thirty seconds.) All that’s left is the work at hand. All that’s left is that little voice inside your head that you’re attempting to hear and translate onto the page. All that’s left is&amp;#160;the book or the paper you’re reading. All that’s left is problem you’re trying to crack when you go for a walk. All that’s left is the workout you’re trying to complete. The bullshit–well, it disappears for a fleeting second. Creative work isn’t about pleasure. It’s not always fun. It’s about reaching something inside yourself–something that society and everyday life make extraordinarily difficult. This is one way to do it. The fact that it basically ruined music for me is a cost I am willing to pay. I’ll take my fix from anyone–and I’m not ashamed to say that I have. Even if that means I have to listen to the Black Eyed Peas or some other god-awful group. Every writer (or painter or thinker or adman) finds their own way. This is mine. Maybe it will work for you. Or maybe you’ll try it and never look at me the same way again. The post originally ran on ThoughtCatalog.com. Comments can be seen there. Tweet Facebook Twitter Google+ Pinterest LinkedIn</description>
      <author> (by Ryan Holiday)</author>
      <guid>https://ryanholiday.net/the-guilty-crazy-secret-that-helps-me-write/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:08:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>willfennel.com – Learning on the fly, impostor syndrome, and Vim dumbassery</title>
      <link>https://willfennel.com/posts/2021/05/29/learning-impostor-syndrome-and-vim-dumbassery.html</link>
      <description>One of the things I love about working in IT is that you can often learn on the go. It’s possible to learn something so quickly during the job, that you can come in with no experience at all, and become productive enough to add value to a project in a small timeframe.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://willfennel.com/posts/2021/05/29/learning-impostor-syndrome-and-vim-dumbassery.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:08:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s rewild the earth with NFTs</title>
      <link>https://maraoz.com/2021/05/29/rewild/</link>
      <description>Manuel Araoz&amp;#39;s personal website.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://maraoz.com/2021/05/29/rewild/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:08:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Yak Shaving</title>
      <link>https://antfu.me/posts/about-yak-shaving</link>
      <description>Anthony Fu&amp;#39;s Portfolio</description>
      <author> (Anthony Fu)</author>
      <guid>https://antfu.me/posts/about-yak-shaving</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:08:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital currencies, DeFi and the impact of the next Carrington event</title>
      <link>https://dylancollins.com/2021/05/29/digital-currencies-defi-and-the-impact-of-the-next-carrington-event/</link>
      <description>‘But have you hedged yourself in crypto?’ is the kind of question I am being asked a lot lately. Ignoring the technical and economic miracles/mirages of DeFi, I started to scratch an it…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dylancollins.com/2021/05/29/digital-currencies-defi-and-the-impact-of-the-next-carrington-event/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:08:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet Explorer: A Brief History</title>
      <link>https://benslivka.com/2021/05/27/internet-explorer-a-brief-history/</link>
      <description>Why post this now? On May 20th, 2021, Microsoft announced the end of Internet Explorer. So this is a perfect time to reflect back on my role in the creation of the world’s most popular web br…</description>
      <author> (Author: benslivka)</author>
      <guid>https://benslivka.com/2021/05/27/internet-explorer-a-brief-history/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:07:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to Gemini ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://pitr.ca/2021-05-29-gemini-ecosystem</link>
      <description>29 May 2021 on Peter Vernigorov’s blog</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pitr.ca/2021-05-29-gemini-ecosystem</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:06:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shameless Work Influencers Are the Bane of LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://index.medium.com/shameless-work-influencers-are-the-bane-of-linkedin-5f458bb046aa</link>
      <description>The professional networking platform showcases everything gone wrong with the attention economy</description>
      <author> (https://matthewmcfarlane4.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://index.medium.com/shameless-work-influencers-are-the-bane-of-linkedin-5f458bb046aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 20:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remains of 215 children found at former residential school in B.C.</title>
      <link>https://www.aptnnews.ca/national-news/remains-of-215-children-found-at-former-residential-school-in-british-columbia/</link>
      <description>The remains of 215 children have been found buried on the site of a former residential school in Kamloops, B.C.</description>
      <author> (The Canadian Press)</author>
      <guid>https://www.aptnnews.ca/national-news/remains-of-215-children-found-at-former-residential-school-in-british-columbia/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 20:06:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>