<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>[new blog](https://garcia.in)</title>
      <link>https://blog.brunogarcia.com/2020/12/new-bloghttpsgarciain.html</link>
      <description>Dear Blogger.com, we need to talk. Since I met markdown , I&amp;#39;ve been wanting to tell you. It&amp;#39;s going to work. I&amp;#39;ll now blog on https://garcia.in</description>
      <author> (Posted by


Bruno Garcia)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.brunogarcia.com/2020/12/new-bloghttpsgarciain.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Prequel Trilogy **SPECIAL EDITION**</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5zCSSd8QCVk</link>
      <description>The Knights of Renesmee present the ultimate lockdown movie marathon.SCENE SELECTION:0:00 **THE PHANTOM MENACE**5:00 NEMOIDIAN DEATH METAL7:44 Queen Amidala ...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5zCSSd8QCVk</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 21:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACE: Apple Type-C Port Controller Secrets | Part 1</title>
      <link>https://blog.t8012.dev/ace-part-1/</link>
      <description>Exposing Apple&amp;#39;s Vendor Defined Messaging protocol, AppleVDM, built on USB-PD.</description>
      <author> (Rick Mark







Aun-Ali Zaidi







h0m3us3r







mrarm)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.t8012.dev/ace-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 21:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git email flow vs Github flow</title>
      <link>https://blog.brixit.nl/git-email-flow-versus-github-flow/</link>
      <description>Comparing the Github and Gitlab pull request workflow to the Git built-in email workflow.</description>
      <author> (Martijn Braam)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.brixit.nl/git-email-flow-versus-github-flow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 20:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSX Party</title>
      <link>https://psxparty.kosmi.io/</link>
      <description>Online Multiplayer PSX Emulator using WebRTC!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://psxparty.kosmi.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon still hasn’t fixed its problem with bait-and-switch reviews</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/12/amazon-still-hasnt-fixed-its-problem-with-bait-and-switch-reviews/</link>
      <description>Amazon has done little to stop sellers from gaming its search algorithm.</description>
      <author> (Timothy B. Lee
    -  12/30/2020, 4:55 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/12/amazon-still-hasnt-fixed-its-problem-with-bait-and-switch-reviews/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 18:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Markdown Linting to my Blog’s Build Process with GitHub Actions and markdownlint</title>
      <link>https://seankilleen.com/2020/12/adding-markdown-linting-to-my-blogs-build-process-with-github-actions-and-markdownlint/</link>
      <description>I’ll confess, reader. My markdown formatting was messy. I don’t like messy, so I decided to fix it and automate it.</description>
      <author> (Sean Killeen)</author>
      <guid>https://seankilleen.com/2020/12/adding-markdown-linting-to-my-blogs-build-process-with-github-actions-and-markdownlint/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 17:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are the C and C++ compilers giving me error messages about int when my code doesn&amp;#39;t mention int? | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20201230-00/?p=104618</link>
      <description>You’re trying to get your code to compile without errors, and you’re working through the error list, and then you get to some error message that complains about int when your code never mentions int: void f() {  const char* p = get_user_name();</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20201230-00/?p=104618</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 16:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messengers of hope</title>
      <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41587-020-00807-1</link>
      <description>Emergency Use Authorizations for two mRNA COVID-19 vaccines represent a turning point in the pandemic. They also herald a new era for vaccinology.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41587-020-00807-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 15:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Commands to Live By</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/better-programming/git-commands-to-live-by-349ab1fe3139</link>
      <description>The cheat sheet that goes beyond Git basics</description>
      <author> (https://osharaki.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/better-programming/git-commands-to-live-by-349ab1fe3139</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 15:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Maps changes a route after the drama of young people lost on a ghost road</title>
      <link>https://tekdeeps.com/google-maps-changes-a-route-after-the-drama-of-young-people-lost-on-a-ghost-road/</link>
      <description>Google MapsA point on the Russian Highway of Bones.Google Maps has been forced to change a route in the Russian Far East after a young man, Sergei</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tekdeeps.com/google-maps-changes-a-route-after-the-drama-of-young-people-lost-on-a-ghost-road/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 12:05:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>START with a Monolith, NOT Microservices</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z_pj1mUDKdw</link>
      <description>Start with a Monolith! Why? Finding boundaries is a difficult thing to do and even harder to get right. Having to define those boundaries up-front for a micr...</description>
      <author> (TechWorld with Nana
  
  
    

    
      
    TechWorld with Nana
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z_pj1mUDKdw</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 11:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding comments to your static blog with Mastodon</title>
      <link>https://carlschwan.eu/2020/12/29/adding-comments-to-your-static-blog-with-mastodon/</link>
      <description>One of the biggest disadvantages of static site generators is that they are static and can&amp;amp;rsquo;t include comments.
There are multiples solutions to solve this problem. You could add a third party blog engine like Disqus, but this has the drawback of including a third-party tool with a bad privacy record in your website. Another solution would be to host an open-source alternative but this comes at the cost of a higher maintenance burden.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://carlschwan.eu/2020/12/29/adding-comments-to-your-static-blog-with-mastodon/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 09:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visa Advertising Solutions (VAS) Opt Out</title>
      <link>https://marketingreportoptout.visa.com/OPTOUT/request.do</link>
      <description>U.S. cardholders may opt out of Visa using their card transaction data for VAS, a suite of aggregated data products in the US. To learn more, visit Visa Global Privacy Notice.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marketingreportoptout.visa.com/OPTOUT/request.do</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 06:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scriban - Visual Studio Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=xoofx.scriban</link>
      <description>Extension for Visual Studio Code - Syntax Coloring for Scriban Text Templating Language</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=xoofx.scriban</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 04:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Podcast: Maddy Leger on Xamarin in a .NET 5 World - Episode 120</title>
      <link>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/maddy-leger-on-xamarin-in-a-net-5-world-episode-120</link>
      <description>In this episode, Jeffrey is joined by Maddy Leger, a Program Manager at Microsoft on the Xamarin team! &amp;amp;nbsp; Maddy has been with the Xamarin team since 2018 working on Xamarin tooling. When she first joined Microsoft and worked with the Xamarin team as an intern, she realized the impact that she could have in creating amazing developer tools and frameworks, which inspired her to pursue a role as Program Manager. You can connect with her on Twitter and GitHub @maddyleger1! &amp;amp;nbsp; In Jeffrey and Maddy’s conversation, they discuss Xamarin in a .NET 5 world. Maddy shares her vision for where Xamarin is headed and what she hopes will be the new normal for C# developers five years from now; what the state-of-the-art is now for Xamarin; what a Xamarin developer setup looks like in the .NET 5 world for mobile, Mac, and Windows; and what developers with existing Xamarin apps should they be paying attention to (or change) with .NET 5 coming out. &amp;amp;nbsp; Topics of Discussion: [:38] Be sure to visit  for past episodes and show notes. [1:07] About The Azure DevOps Podcast and Jeffrey’s offer to speak at virtual user groups. [1:20] Clear Measure is hiring! Be sure to check out the link in the show notes. [1:43] About today’s guest, Maddy Leger! [2:17] Jeffrey welcomes Maddy Leger to the podcast. [2:25] Maddy speaks about her career journey thus far and what led to her working on the Xamarin team at Microsoft. [5:20] Overtime, the story for developing on non-Windows computers has been fragmented. Maddy speaks about this and what the story looks like right now. [6:25] Maddy shares her vision for where Xamarin is headed and what she hopes will be the new normal for C# developers five years from now. [7:09] What the state-of-the-art is now for Xamarin. [9:30] If you just want things to work and just have an app to access some data, what level of share code is Xamarin currently? [10:50] Maddy speaks about what a Xamarin developer setup looks like in the .NET 5 world for mobile. [13:38] A word from Azure DevOps Podcast’s sponsor: Clear Measure. [14:25] Maddy speaks on the Mac story as a Xamarin developer and when you need to have a Mac on the .NET 5 side. [18:06] For developers now, do they need a Mac of some type? Or does the iPhone suffice? [19:07] Azure DevOps has hosted Mac Agents. If you’re using that, do you need a local Mac? [20:35] In the .NET 5 world, what is state-of-the-art when it comes to the teams’ development, DevOps environment, building, testing, packaging, and deploying? What should they choose? And what pieces do they put together? [22:30] What are the libraries and tools for automated testing and testing locally? What does that look like these days? [24:15] What do deployments to a DevOps environment look like in the world of .NET 5 in Xamarin? [27:04] For developers with existing Xamarin apps that they’ve been managing, what should they be paying attention to or change with .NET 5 coming out? What would they miss out on if they don’t move to .NET 5? [29:01] Jeffrey thanks Maddy for joining the podcast! &amp;amp;nbsp; Mentioned in this Episode:   (Sponsor)  — Available on Amazon!  — Click here to download the .NET DevOps for Azure ebook!   — Follow to stay informed about future events!         &amp;amp;nbsp; Want to Learn More? Visit  for show notes and additional episodes. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://azuredevopspodcast.clear-measure.com/maddy-leger-on-xamarin-in-a-net-5-world-episode-120</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 04:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy - Transparency Report - Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/legal/transparency/</link>
      <description>Apple is committed to your privacy and being transparent about government requests for customer data globally. This report provides information on government requests received.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/legal/transparency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 04:04:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NetConf Virtual Event | What’s new in EF Core 5.0</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Redmond/events/274973827</link>
      <description>Mon, Jan 25, 2021, 4:00 PM: Entity Framework Core is the preferred data access API for over 70% of .NET Core web developers. The latest version provides more functionality than ever before. In this se</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Redmond/events/274973827</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 04:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s new in PHP 8 - stitcher.io</title>
      <link>https://stitcher.io/blog/new-in-php-8</link>
      <description>PHP 8 is available now!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stitcher.io/blog/new-in-php-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 04:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Genomics Reveals a Single-Species Ecosystem Deep Within Earth</title>
      <link>https://science.sciencemag.org/content/322/5899/275.full</link>
      <description>DNA from low-biodiversity fracture water collected at 2.8-kilometer depth in a South African gold mine was sequenced and assembled into a single, complete genome. This bacterium, Candidatus Desulforudis audaxviator , composes &amp;gt;99.9% of the microorganisms inhabiting the fluid phase of this particular fracture. Its genome indicates a motile, sporulating, sulfate-reducing, chemoautotrophic thermophile that can fix its own nitrogen and carbon by using machinery shared with archaea. Candidatus Desulforudis audaxviator is capable of an independent life-style well suited to long-term isolation from the photosphere deep within Earth&amp;#39;s crust and offers an example of a natural ecosystem that appears to have its biological component entirely encoded within a single genome.</description>
      <author> (Dylan Chivian)</author>
      <guid>https://science.sciencemag.org/content/322/5899/275.full</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 04:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDA Cruise Ships Under Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://www.databreaches.net/aida-cruise-ships-under-cyber-attack/</link>
      <description>Jim Walker reports: AIDA cruise ships, including the&amp;#160;Aidamar&amp;#160;and the&amp;#160;Aidaperla,&amp;#160;are suffering what has been described as an “immense” IT problem,...</description>
      <author> (About the author: Dissent)</author>
      <guid>https://www.databreaches.net/aida-cruise-ships-under-cyber-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 04:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Years Later | Not Even Wrong</title>
      <link>https://www.math.columbia.edu/~woit/wordpress/?p=12069</link>
      <description>Almost exactly twenty years ago I started writing a short article about the problems with string theory.  I had been thinking about doing this for quite a while, and the timing of entering the twenty-first century seemed appropriate for evaluating something that had long been advertised as “a piece of 21st-century physics that had fallen by accident into the 20th”.  The piece was done in a week or two, after which I sent it around to a group of physicists to ask for comments.  The reaction was mostly positive, although at least one well-known theorist told me that publicly challenging string theorists in this way would be counter-productive.</description>
      <author> (Posted on)</author>
      <guid>https://www.math.columbia.edu/~woit/wordpress/?p=12069</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 03:01:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Macs for 2020: #1 – iMac G3</title>
      <link>https://sixcolors.com/post/2020/12/20-macs-for-2020-1-imac-g3/</link>
      <description>You can divide Mac history in a bunch of different ways. But perhaps the clearest line of demarcation is the mid-1998 release of the original iMac. The first era of the Mac, begun in 1984, was endi…</description>
      <author> (by Jason Snell &amp;amp; Dan Moren)</author>
      <guid>https://sixcolors.com/post/2020/12/20-macs-for-2020-1-imac-g3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 02:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colin Stebbins Gordon</title>
      <link>https://csgordon.github.io/books.html</link>
      <description>Below is a loosely-categorized collection of links to CS textbooks in a variety of areas that are
freely available online, usually because they are one of the following:</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://csgordon.github.io/books.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>