<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Kagi Search Stats</title>
      <link>https://kagi.com/stats?stat=leaderboard</link>
      <description>Better search results with no ads. Welcome to Kagi (pronounced kah-gee), a paid search engine that gives power back to the user.</description>
      <guid>https://kagi.com/stats?stat=leaderboard</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tried making artificial sunlight at home</title>
      <link>https://victorpoughon.fr/i-tried-making-artificial-sunlight-at-home/</link>
      <description>Some time ago, I saw  where they make artificial sunlight at home with a 500W LED and a gigantic (1.2m) parabolic reflector. I've been fascinated by this pro...</description>
      <guid>https://victorpoughon.fr/i-tried-making-artificial-sunlight-at-home/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Needs a Snow Sequoia</title>
      <link>https://reviews.ofb.biz/safari/article/1300.html</link>
      <description>The same year Apple launched the iPhone, it unveiled a massive upgrade to Mac OS X known as Leopard, sporting “300 New Features.” Two years later, it did something almost unheard of: it released Snow Leopard, an upgrade all about how little it added and how much it took away. Apple needs to make it snow again.</description>
      <guid>https://reviews.ofb.biz/safari/article/1300.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Death of the Software Engineer by a Thousand Prompts</title>
      <link>https://verdikapuku.com/posts/the-death-of-the-software-engineer-by-a-thousand-prompts/</link>
      <description>This is Verdi's personal website. He writes about interesting ideas or projects.</description>
      <guid>https://verdikapuku.com/posts/the-death-of-the-software-engineer-by-a-thousand-prompts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laurent Kempé - Dockerizing your .NET C# MCP Server for AI Clients like Claude Desktop</title>
      <link>https://laurentkempe.com/2025/03/27/dockerizing-your-dotnet-csharp-mcp-server-for-ai-clients-like-claude-desktop/</link>
      <description>My previous post showed how easy it is to develop a .NET C# MCP server and write a client able to communicate with it. Now, the question is how we can distribute our MCP server to be used by AI clients. In this post, we’ll leverage the knowledge acquired from my previous posts to explore how to dockerize your .NET C# MCP server.</description>
      <guid>https://laurentkempe.com/2025/03/27/dockerizing-your-dotnet-csharp-mcp-server-for-ai-clients-like-claude-desktop/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Money Habits of the Successfully Rich: Insights from “The Millionaire Next Door”</title>
      <link>https://enlight8.com/2025/03/25/8-money-habits-of-the-successfully-rich-from-the-millionaire-next-door/</link>
      <description>I’ve always been curious about the money habits of successful, wealthy people. Often, these habits are what lead them to become extremely rich. We need specific habits to help us succeed and build our wealth to achieve our financial goals and we can adopt some of these effective practices by learning from those who are…</description>
      <guid>https://enlight8.com/2025/03/25/8-money-habits-of-the-successfully-rich-from-the-millionaire-next-door/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering GPT-4o's Image Gen Process</title>
      <link>https://www.philipnielsen.info/blog/blog_posts/4o-image.md</link>
      <description>OpenAI's 4o Image Generation capability launched two days ago on March 25th, 2025. The quality of the images it creates is the best among all contemporary models by a large margin. However, what is most interesting is the way it seems to generate the image: first it quickly creates a blurry version of the final image, then sharpens it from top to bottom, as if loading an image on a dial-up connection. This shouldn't be possible using a standard latent diffusion model, which would generate the whole image at once. What could they be doing different? As why is it better?</description>
      <guid>https://www.philipnielsen.info/blog/blog_posts/4o-image.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never in a million years...</title>
      <link>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2025/never-million-years</link>
      <description>...would I have imagined my video on whether a pigeon is faster than the Internet would end up on a popular Italian quiz show, L'Eredita. Specifically, in the March 26th episode (playable in Italy, or with an account).</description>
      <guid>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2025/never-million-years</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The "No, But" Engineer</title>
      <link>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/no-but-engineer/</link>
      <description>When you're improvising a comedy scene, the golden rule is to respond with "yes, and" to everything your partners say and do. This unwavering acceptance can produce riotous bouts of laughter. In an engineering team, it just creates unholy messes.</description>
      <guid>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/no-but-engineer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron's Blog</title>
      <link>https://aaron-blog.onrender.com/post/the-beauty-in-not-knowing</link>
      <description>3/26/20251 mins read</description>
      <guid>https://aaron-blog.onrender.com/post/the-beauty-in-not-knowing</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golang on the PlayStation 2</title>
      <link>https://rgsilva.com/blog/ps2-go-part-1/</link>
      <description>The PS2 is more than capable of doing some wild things, including running Linux. I always wondered if we could just write baremetal Go code on it, so I decided to give it a try.</description>
      <guid>https://rgsilva.com/blog/ps2-go-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs - A Ghost in the Machine | zacksiri.dev</title>
      <link>https://zacksiri.dev/posts/llms-a-ghost-in-the-machine/</link>
      <description>The landscape of Large Language Models (LLMs) is evolving rapidly, with powerful and open models being released at an unprecedented pace. As these technologies advance, so does the potential to integrate them into our existing systems. Traditionally, we've built systems with distinct layers such as the Application layer and Data Persistence layer.</description>
      <guid>https://zacksiri.dev/posts/llms-a-ghost-in-the-machine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>do what i mean (dwim) - alp1n3</title>
      <link>https://alp1n3.dev/blog/0020-do-what-i-mean/</link>
      <description>a collection of cybersecurity-related notes &amp; projects.</description>
      <guid>https://alp1n3.dev/blog/0020-do-what-i-mean/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Safari bug that punishes you for using content blockers | BenHollis.net</title>
      <link>https://benhollis.net/blog/2025/01/04/the-safari-bug-that-punishes-you-for-using-content-blockers/</link>
      <description>Running content blockers in your browser is a good idea–yes, you block ads, but you also block malware, cryptominers, tracking, and more. In general, the experience of using the web with a good content blocker should be noticeably faster, as you skip downloading and executing many megabytes of code, images, and videos that provides you with no benefit. I’ve run content blocking extensions since they were first introduced and I’ve never looked back.

Safari 15, released in September 2021, was the first version to support extensions, including content blocking extensions. This was a huge improvement to mobile browsing on iOS, which doesn’t offer any choice of browser besides Safari. Safari finally had a way to fight back against intrusive ads just like other browsers. I chose to use 1Blocker, which was highly reviewed by Apple aficionados at the time, though I’m sure there are other good alternatives.

</description>
      <guid>https://benhollis.net/blog/2025/01/04/the-safari-bug-that-punishes-you-for-using-content-blockers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The False Promise of ORMs | Mike Pray</title>
      <link>https://mikepray.dev/posts/false-promise-of-orms/</link>
      <description>ORMs promise to abstract databases and SQL. At any normal scale, this promise fails and the ORM becomes a powerful multiplier of pointless complexity</description>
      <guid>https://mikepray.dev/posts/false-promise-of-orms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing MCP Tools: A Command-Line Inspector for Model Context Protocol Servers</title>
      <link>https://blog.fka.dev/blog/2025-03-26-introducing-mcp-tools-cli/</link>
      <description>Discover MCP Tools, a powerful CLI for interacting with Model Context Protocol servers using stdio transport. Learn how to discover and call tools, list resources, and interact with MCP-compatible services.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.fka.dev/blog/2025-03-26-introducing-mcp-tools-cli/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the hype | Alberto Sadde</title>
      <link>https://www.albertosadde.com/blog/beyond-the-hype/</link>
      <description>The Siren Song of New Tech Every morning, I open Twitter to find my feed transformed into an AI wonderland.</description>
      <author> (Alberto Sadde)</author>
      <guid>https://www.albertosadde.com/blog/beyond-the-hype/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take This On-Call Rotation and Shove It</title>
      <link>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/take-oncall-and-shove-it/</link>
      <description>At some companies, it is expected that certain engineers will serve as part of a formal on-call rotation. On paper, this seems like a reasonable way to ensure the reliability of the product. In practice, it is a miserable burden and you probably won't even get paid for it.</description>
      <guid>https://www.scottsmitelli.com/articles/take-oncall-and-shove-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Open Source Journey - Ashpreet Bedi</title>
      <link>https://www.ashpreetbedi.com/articles/oss-journey</link>
      <description>My journey building one of the most popular Agent Libraries</description>
      <guid>https://www.ashpreetbedi.com/articles/oss-journey</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Execution is everything... or nothing?</title>
      <link>https://nial.se/blog/execution-is-nothing/</link>
      <description>One striking feature of modern artificial intelligence, especially in large language models like ChatGPT, Claude, and Gemini, is their ability to instantly generate surprisingly advanced software engineering solutions. One interpretation of this phenomenon is that we are in the midst of a wave of commoditization. A specific subset of cognitive work, once scarce and expensive, has become infinitely accessible at minimal cost. With the rise of “vibe coding”, where AI tools are used transform a basic idea into a functional app or website almost instantly for fun, it seems that any basic concept for a digital product can now be cloned on the spot. The barrier to entry has dropped dramatically, while the bar for uniqueness has risen just as fast. Any simple enough product can be replicated instantly. Are we witnessing the rapid commoditization of cognitive work, with software engineering at the forefront?</description>
      <guid>https://nial.se/blog/execution-is-nothing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracing the thoughts of a large language model</title>
      <link>https://www.anthropic.com/research/tracing-thoughts-language-model</link>
      <description>Anthropic's latest interpretability research: a new microscope to understand Claude's internal mechanisms</description>
      <guid>https://www.anthropic.com/research/tracing-thoughts-language-model</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 21:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LTS for .NET MAUI is a Lie!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=w3jD-UpxRF4</link>
      <description>Unlike general .NET, .NET MAUI does not have a LTS/STS cycle. You will always want to be on the latest major .NET version for your .NET MAUI apps. Why, how, what, where? Learn a bit more in this video!

💝 Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/GeraldVersluis/join

🛑  Don't forget to subscribe to my channel for more cool content: https://www.youtube.com/GeraldVersluis/?sub_confirmation=1

🔗 Links
.NET MAUI Support Policy: https://dotnet.microsoft.com/platform/support/policy/maui

⏱ Timestamps
0:00 - Nope, no LTS
0:21 - Still no LTS for .NET MAUI
1:25 - Why LTS doesn't work for .NET MAUI
2:15 - .NET MAUI Support Policy Page
3:43 - Did I Mention .NET MAUI has no LTS?

🎥 Video edited with Camtasia (ref): https://techsmith.z6rjha.net/AJoeD

🙋‍♂️ Also find my...
Blog: https://blog.verslu.is
Twitch: https://twitch.tv/jfversluis
All the rest: https://jfversluis.dev</description>
      <author> (Gerald Versluis)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=w3jD-UpxRF4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 15:01:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Servo vs Ladybird</title>
      <link>https://thelibre.news/servo-vs-ladybird/</link>
      <description>I believe that Ladybird has more funding and better support for the web, but Servo wins in performance. Though, they're hard to compare directly!</description>
      <guid>https://thelibre.news/servo-vs-ladybird/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 14:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Code + Model Context Protocol (MCP) Servers Beginner's Guide | What, Why, How</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=iS25RFups4A</link>
      <description>What the heck is an MCP (Model Context Protocol) Server, why do you care, how does it help you, how does it help software development, and how do you get it setup in VS Code with GitHub Copilot. Let's do it!

Links:
Get VS Code Insiders: https://code.visualstudio.com/insiders/
Get GitHub Copilot: http://aka.ms/copilot-free
Model Context Protocol: https://github.com/modelcontextprotocol
MCP Servers: https://github.com/modelcontextprotocol/servers
MCP C# SDK: https://github.com/modelcontextprotocol/csharp-sdk
What are MCPs Video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m0YrxLnFPzQ

Chapters:
00:00 - Intro
00:40 - What is Model Context Protocol?
02:40 - Model Context Protocol &amp; Servers on GitHub
03:47 - Enabling MCP in VS Code
05:23 - Configuring MCP Servers in VS Code
09:35 - Real world MCP Servers with GitHub
17:53 - Using command palette with MCP
19:30 - Creating your own MCP Server &amp; Wrap-up

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCENTmbKaTphpWV2R2evVz2A/join

👕 Buy some swag! - https://jamesmontemagno.myspreadshop.com/
☕️ Buy me a coffee - https://www.buymeacoffee.com/jamesmontemagno

Follow:
👨‍💻 GitHub: https://github.com/jamesmontemagno
🦜 X: https://x.com/jamesmontemagno
📄 Website: https://www.montemagno.com
📰 Newsletter: https://newsletter.montemagno.com/

Disclaimer: This channel, videos, and streams are created in my spare time and are a product of me... James Montemagno! They are NOT officially affiliated or endorsed by Microsoft (my employer) in any way. Opinions and views are my own.

What is on my hat? It is the CLE clothing logo because I am from Cleveland! Checkout their awesome CLE merch: https://cleclothingco.myshopify.com/

What is that art on my wall? It is an original piece from the French street artist Gregos of La Butte Montmartre: https://www.instagram.com/p/BceZ1oNHiQx/

My Setup:
📷 Canon M50 Mark II - https://amzn.to/3P8R7lp
💡 Nanoleaf Elements Lights - https://amzn.to/3umwJVW
🎙 Blue Spark Microphone - https://amzn.to/3qgtYkq
🎙 Blue Pop Filter - https://amzn.to/3jEWM3r
🤳 Rode Microphone Arm - https://amzn.to/2Z68AlE
🎧 Sony MDR7306 Headphones - https://amzn.to/372jxta
📲 Stream Deck - https://amzn.to/373Uk1n
🖱 MX Master 2S Mouse - https://amzn.to/3d7J2gj
⌨️ Tecware Phantom Keyboard - https://amzn.to/3aUP4y9

Using links I provide I may receive a commission if you buy something which helps support the channel.

#vscode #githubcopilot  #mcpserver #mcp #mcps #claude  #claudecode #modelcontextprotocol #dotnet</description>
      <author> (James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=iS25RFups4A</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 14:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Website Hacker News Is Afraid to Discuss (You’re Reading It)</title>
      <link>https://daringfireball.net/2025/03/the_website_hacker_news_is_afraid_to_discuss</link>
      <description>What bothers me isn’t so much that Daring Fireball is shitlisted at Hacker News. What bothers me is that it’s unexplained.</description>
      <guid>https://daringfireball.net/2025/03/the_website_hacker_news_is_afraid_to_discuss</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 13:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build your first Azure Function with .NET Aspire support</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=g-fKXzrNOhI</link>
      <description>Azure Functions can now use .NET Aspire to integrate serverless technology into projects leveraging .NET Aspire. See how easy it is to create a new Function with .NET Aspire orchestration or integrate it into your existing Functions with just a few clicks in Visual Studio.

Documentation: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet/aspire/serverless/functions
Get Visual Studio: https://www.visualstudio.com/

Connect with .NET: 
Blog:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/blog
Twitter: https://aka.ms/dotnet/twitter
TikTok:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/tiktok
Mastodon:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/mastodon
LinkedIn:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/linkedin
Facebook:  https://aka.ms/dotnet/facebook
Docs: https://learn.microsoft.com/dotnet
Forums: https://aka.ms/dotnet/forums
🙋‍♀️Q&amp;A: https://aka.ms/dotnet-qa
👨‍🎓Microsoft Learn: https://aka.ms/learndotnet

#dotnet #dotnetaspire #azurefunctions #visualstudio</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=g-fKXzrNOhI</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 13:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waymo has had dozens of crashes—almost all were a human driver's fault</title>
      <link>https://www.understandingai.org/p/human-drivers-keep-crashing-into</link>
      <description>Human drivers keep crashing into Waymos that aren't even moving.</description>
      <guid>https://www.understandingai.org/p/human-drivers-keep-crashing-into</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>