<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Code is a Skill - Trisha Gee</title>
      <link>https://trishagee.com/2020/09/07/reading-code-is-a-skill/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;m inspired to write this post because Someone Is Wrong On The Internet. Of course a more accurate statement would be &amp;quot;I disagree with some aspects of what someone on the internet said, even though they have an entirely valid point of view&amp;quot;. But that&amp;#39;s less catchy. I saw a Tweet I agreed vehemently with, … Continue reading &amp;quot;Reading Code is a Skill&amp;quot;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://trishagee.com/2020/09/07/reading-code-is-a-skill/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 15:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New VS Code Theme You HAVE NEVER Heard Of! - YouTube</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DYZs3sGS8Aw</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DYZs3sGS8Aw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 14:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CertUtil program will decode Windows error codes, and in a variety of formats</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210921-00/?p=105713</link>
      <description>Some time ago, I noted that The NET HELPMSG command will decode Windows error codes, at least the simple ones. Stefan Kanthak pointed out that there’s another built-in program for converting numbers to error messages, and it handles a lot more error numbers and formats than NET HELPMSG does.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210921-00/?p=105713</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 14:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tunguska sized airburst destroyed Tall el-Hammam a Middle Bronze Age city in the Jordan Valley near the Dead Sea - Scientific Reports</title>
      <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-021-97778-3</link>
      <description>We present evidence that in ~ 1650 BCE (~ 3600&amp;#160;years ago), a cosmic airburst destroyed Tall el-Hammam, a Middle-Bronze-Age city in the southern Jordan Valley northeast of the Dead Sea. The proposed airburst was larger than the 1908 explosion over Tunguska, Russia, where a ~ 50-m-wide bolide detonated with ~ 1000&amp;#215; more energy than the Hiroshima atomic bomb. A city-wide ~ 1.5-m-thick carbon-and-ash-rich destruction layer contains peak concentrations of shocked quartz (~ 5–10&amp;#160;GPa); melted pottery and mudbricks; diamond-like carbon; soot; Fe- and Si-rich spherules; CaCO3 spherules from melted plaster; and melted platinum, iridium, nickel, gold, silver, zircon, chromite, and quartz. Heating experiments indicate temperatures exceeded 2000&amp;#160;&amp;#176;C. Amid city-side devastation, the airburst demolished 12+ m of the 4-to-5-story palace complex and the massive 4-m-thick mudbrick rampart, while causing extreme disarticulation and skeletal fragmentation in nearby humans. An airburst-related influx of salt (~ 4&amp;#160;wt.%) produced hypersalinity, inhibited agriculture, and caused a ~ 300–600-year-long abandonment of ~ 120 regional settlements within a &amp;gt; 25-km radius. Tall el-Hammam may be the second oldest city/town destroyed by a cosmic airburst/impact, after Abu Hureyra, Syria, and possibly the earliest site with an oral tradition that was written down (Genesis). Tunguska-scale airbursts can devastate entire cities/regions and thus, pose a severe modern-day hazard.</description>
      <author> (Silvia, Phillip J.)</author>
      <guid>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-021-97778-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 14:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing WebApplicationBuilder to the Generic Host: Exploring .NET Core 6 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/exploring-dotnet-6-part-2-comparing-webapplicationbuilder-to-the-generic-host/</link>
      <description>In this post I take a first look at the new WebApplication and WebApplicationBuilder types in .NET 6, and compare them to the Generic Host from .NET 5.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/exploring-dotnet-6-part-2-comparing-webapplicationbuilder-to-the-generic-host/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 13:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECDSA and Custom XML Signatures in .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.scottbrady91.com/c-sharp/ecdsa-xml-dotnet</link>
      <description>Drag your XML signing into the 2020&amp;#39;s with modern cryptography by signing XML with ECDSA.</description>
      <author> (https://www.scottbrady91.com/About)</author>
      <guid>https://www.scottbrady91.com/c-sharp/ecdsa-xml-dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to sign XML using RSA in .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.scottbrady91.com/c-sharp/xml-signing-dotnet</link>
      <description>How to sign XML in .NET and .NET Core using an RSA key while avoiding common XML security pitfalls.</description>
      <author> (https://www.scottbrady91.com/About)</author>
      <guid>https://www.scottbrady91.com/c-sharp/xml-signing-dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide to Autoencoders with TensorFlow &amp;amp; Keras | Rubik&amp;#39;s Code</title>
      <link>https://rubikscode.net/2021/09/21/guide-to-autoencoders-with-tensorflow/</link>
      <description>In this article, we explore Autoencoders, their structure, variations (convolutional autoencoder) &amp;amp; we present 3 implementations using TensorFlow and Keras.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rubikscode.net/2021/09/21/guide-to-autoencoders-with-tensorflow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 07:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWASP 20th Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://20thanniversary.owasp.org/</link>
      <description>OWASP 20th Anniversary on the main website for The OWASP Foundation. OWASP is a nonprofit foundation that works to improve the security of software.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://20thanniversary.owasp.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-09-21</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/09/app-developer-links-2021-09-21/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/09/app-developer-links-2021-09-21/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 07:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I started SaaS companies in 2013 and 2021. Here&amp;#39;s how things have changed</title>
      <link>https://blog.airplane.dev/i-started-a-saas-company-in-2013-and-2021-heres-how-its-changed/</link>
      <description>In 2013, I co-founded Heap, a product analytics company that I helped grow to over 200 people and $X0,000,000 in ARR before I left in 2020. In 2021, I co-founded Airplane, a developer platform for quickly creating internal tools. Here&amp;#39;s what I&amp;#39;ve observed as being different in SaaS</description>
      <author> (Ravi Parikh)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.airplane.dev/i-started-a-saas-company-in-2013-and-2021-heres-how-its-changed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 07:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Last Week in .NET #60]- Sourcing Your Packages</title>
      <link>https://georgestocker.com/2021/09/20/last-week-in-net-60-sourcing-your-packages/</link>
      <description>&amp;#128227;.NET Core 3.1.19 has been released Big news here is that Alpine 3.14 and Debian 11 “bullseye” are now supported. If you ever want to containerize your .NET applications, you’ll want to use A…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://georgestocker.com/2021/09/20/last-week-in-net-60-sourcing-your-packages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 03:01:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation is not cost of living</title>
      <link>https://www.singlelunch.com/2021/09/20/inflation-is-not-cost-of-living/</link>
      <description>Part of my series debunking bad economics on the internet TLDR: Housing, education and healthcare costs aren’t the dollar’s fault, even though they’re a huge problem It’s a …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.singlelunch.com/2021/09/20/inflation-is-not-cost-of-living/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:29:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the platform</title>
      <link>https://elisehe.in/2021/08/22/using-the-platform</link>
      <description>Developer and interaction designer.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://elisehe.in/2021/08/22/using-the-platform</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:29:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sudo in system()</title>
      <link>https://cenains.blog/2021/08/31/sudo-in-system/</link>
      <description>In Linux there are so many permission mechanisms, depending on exactly what you want to do, it dazzles the mind. There is suid, dbus policies, polkit, Linux capabilities, files attributes, PAM modu…</description>
      <author> (Paulo Neves)</author>
      <guid>https://cenains.blog/2021/08/31/sudo-in-system/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:29:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Price to Income Ratio (US &amp;amp; UK) - 73 Year Chart | Longtermtrends</title>
      <link>https://www.longtermtrends.net/home-price-median-annual-income-ratio/</link>
      <description>Historically, an average house in the U.S. cost around 5 times the yearly household income. The ratio in this chart divides the Case-Shiller Home Price Index by the US median annual household income.</description>
      <author> (Silvan Frank)</author>
      <guid>https://www.longtermtrends.net/home-price-median-annual-income-ratio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:29:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rejections, Resilience, and Rejoicing: Getting a Tenure-Track Position</title>
      <link>https://bastian.rieck.me/blog/posts/2021/tenure_track/</link>
      <description>Soon, a new chapter in my career as a researcher beckons: I will
join the Institute of AI for Health,
an institute of the Helmholtz Zentrum M&amp;#252;nchen,
to lead my own research group, the AIDOS LAB.
I intend to use this position to reify my vision of topology-based
methods for addressing challenges in biomedicine and healthcare. In this
post, I want to briefly detail the long, rocky, and certainly winding
road that led me to this position.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bastian.rieck.me/blog/posts/2021/tenure_track/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:29:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 RCEs in npm for $15,000</title>
      <link>https://robertchen.cc/blog/2021/09/20/npm-rce</link>
      <description>Complexity breeds vulnerability; optimization demands compensation: an exploration of a series of vulnerabilities reported against NPM.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robertchen.cc/blog/2021/09/20/npm-rce</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:29:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When McDonalds Came to Denmark – Matt Bruenig Dot Com</title>
      <link>https://mattbruenig.com/2021/09/20/when-mcdonalds-came-to-denmark/</link>
      <description>Every few months, a prominent person or publication points out that McDonalds workers in Denmark receive $22 per hour, 6 weeks of vacation, and sick pay. This compensation comes on top of the general slate of social benefits in Denmark, which includes child allowances, health care, child care, paid leave, retirement, and education through college, among other things.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mattbruenig.com/2021/09/20/when-mcdonalds-came-to-denmark/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:29:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emacs Typing Tutor</title>
      <link>https://connorberry.com/2021/08/20/emacs-typing-tutor/</link>
      <description>Last night I re-read this Steve Yegge article about learning to type as a programmer. I can touch type, but I don’t usually manage to break 60 WPM. The article made me curious if regular prac…</description>
      <author> (connorberry)</author>
      <guid>https://connorberry.com/2021/08/20/emacs-typing-tutor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:29:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical frontend architecture - jaredgorski.org</title>
      <link>https://jaredgorski.org/writing/14-practical-frontend-architecture/</link>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ve been upgrading our frontend tech stack at Liferay Cloud this past year. Nifty tools we&amp;#39;ve adopted include:React: easy componentization, commonly used,...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jaredgorski.org/writing/14-practical-frontend-architecture/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:29:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotNET</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/dotnet</link>
      <description>.NET is a free, cross-platform, open source developer platform for building many different types of applications. With .NET, you can use multiple languages, editors, and libraries to build for web, cloud, mobile, desktop, games, and IoT. This is the official YouTube channel for the .NET team at Microsoft.</description>
      <author> (•
  
  
    
      11,684 views
    
      2 months ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/dotnet</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:28:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splitting Your Data and Application APIs</title>
      <link>https://htmx.org/essays/splitting-your-apis/</link>
      <description>TLDR: If you split your API into Data and Application APIs, as advocated here,
you should consider changing your Application API from JSON to Hypermedia (HTML) &amp;amp; using a hypermedia-oriented library like
htmx to reap the benefits of the hypermedia model (simplicity, reliability, flexibility, etc.)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://htmx.org/essays/splitting-your-apis/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:28:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s Encrypt&amp;#39;s Root Certificate is expiring!</title>
      <link>https://scotthelme.co.uk/lets-encrypt-old-root-expiration/</link>
      <description>On 30th September 2021, the root certificate that Let&amp;#39;s Encrypt are currently using, the IdentTrust DST Root CA X3 certificate, will expire. You may or may not need to do anything about this Root CA expiring, but I&amp;#39;m betting a few things will probably break on that day so here&amp;#39;s</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/scott.helme)</author>
      <guid>https://scotthelme.co.uk/lets-encrypt-old-root-expiration/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 22:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackerNews Readings</title>
      <link>https://hacker-recommended-books.vercel.app/category/0/all-time/page/0/0</link>
      <description>AlbertCoryonAug 13, 2021</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hacker-recommended-books.vercel.app/category/0/all-time/page/0/0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:19:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iOS 15</title>
      <link>https://www.apple.com/ios/ios-15/</link>
      <description>iOS 15 is packed with new features to help you stay connected, find focus, use intelligence, and explore the world.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.apple.com/ios/ios-15/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:19:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Serverless Conf September 2021 - Events</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learntv/azure-serverless-conf-september-2021/</link>
      <description>No matter where you are located, we want you to join us for the free, virtual developer event focused on building event-driven apps using Azure Serverless technologies. These technologies include Functions, Cosmos DB, Azure SQL DB, and Logic Apps. We look forward to unplugging with you, learning from experts, and connecting with the community. See you on Learn TV!</description>
      <author> (t-rchin)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/events/learntv/azure-serverless-conf-september-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:19:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Docs in a clean-room browser - Ekioh</title>
      <link>https://www.ekioh.com/devblog/google-docs-in-a-clean-room-browser/</link>
      <description>A detailed description of how we made Google Docs run inside the new Flow Browser. The number of websites that work in Flow is increasing regularly.</description>
      <author> (Posted on September 17, 2021		
	 by Piers Wombwell)</author>
      <guid>https://www.ekioh.com/devblog/google-docs-in-a-clean-room-browser/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:19:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing the Similarity Between Two Machine Learning Datasets -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/09/20/dataset-similarity.aspx</link>
      <description>At first thought, computing the similarity/distance between two datasets sounds easy, but in fact the problem is extremely difficult, explains Dr. James McCaffrey of Microsoft Research.</description>
      <author> (By James McCaffrey09/20/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/09/20/dataset-similarity.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:19:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>little-endian</title>
      <link>https://wizardzines.com/comics/little-endian/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://wizardzines.com/comics/little-endian/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:19:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As A Solo Developer, I Decided To Offer Phone Support, And This Is What Happened | Plumshell</title>
      <link>http://plumshell.com/2017/11/30/as-a-solo-app-developer-i-decided-to-offer-phone-support-and-this-is-what-happened/</link>
      <description>This year, around February, I started offering telephone support for Taxnote, which I hadn’t done up until then, because the idea made me anxious. I intended to quit if, at any time, I thought it was tough for me to do; but, so far, I have continued with it for over half a year, so I’ll update you on the things I’ve learned from doing it. I wrote my phone number in the help section of the Japanese version only, since I live in Japan and it is a JP number. I might try it in English too in the future, if I can make it work with an international calling facility like Skype. How often do I get calls? For the time being, my telephone number is written on the help section of the Taxnote accounting application, and the recently released text-to-speech application named Voicepaper. For example, when it comes to Taxnote, when you tap on the “Help” section on the settings screen, it shows “Inquiry by phone call” right at the top; in other words, it’s made so that people who go to the help</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://plumshell.com/2017/11/30/as-a-solo-app-developer-i-decided-to-offer-phone-support-and-this-is-what-happened/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:18:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Development Then and Now: Steep Decline into Mediocrity</title>
      <link>https://levelup.gitconnected.com/software-development-then-and-now-steep-decline-into-mediocrity-5d02cb5248ff</link>
      <description>We were once protected from interruption; now we are forbidden to focus</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@tommyudo431)</author>
      <guid>https://levelup.gitconnected.com/software-development-then-and-now-steep-decline-into-mediocrity-5d02cb5248ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:18:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickHouse/clickhouse-inc.md at master &amp;#183; ClickHouse/ClickHouse</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ClickHouse/ClickHouse/blob/master/website/blog/en/2021/clickhouse-inc.md</link>
      <description>ClickHouse&amp;#174; is a free analytics DBMS for big data. Contribute to ClickHouse/ClickHouse development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/ClickHouse/ClickHouse/blob/master/website/blog/en/2021/clickhouse-inc.md</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:18:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Table Storage with ASP.NET Core - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/azure-table-storage-aspnetcore/</link>
      <description>Azure Table storage is a cloud-based NoSQL datastore. We can use it to store large amounts of structured, non-relational data.</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/azure-table-storage-aspnetcore/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is C# getting out of hand?</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Op0yNNLg1zc</link>
      <description>Subscribe: http://bit.ly/ChapsasSubBecome a Patreon and get source code access: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsasHello everybody I&amp;#39;m Nick and in this video...</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas
  
  
  
    Nick Chapsas
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Op0yNNLg1zc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does this mean? The caller specified wait timed out before the operation completed because a host termination is in queued</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210920-00/?p=105711</link>
      <description>So your program is running along, minding its own business, and then it crashes with exception 0x80070bfe = “The caller specified wait timed out before the operation completed because a host termination is in queued”, or possibly 0x80070bfd = “The caller specified wait timed out before the operation completed.”</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210920-00/?p=105711</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Memento: An NFT art project</title>
      <link>https://www.cryptologie.net/article/542/project-memento-an-nft-art-project/</link>
      <description>Believe it or not, even though I was one of the participant in the standardization of ERC-721, the Ethereum standard for NFCs, I had never read the final standard, yet alone written an ERC-721 smart contract. At the time I was against the standard, at least in its form, due to its collision with the ERC-20 standard (you can&amp;#39;t create a smart contract that is both a compliant ERC-20 token and a comp ...</description>
      <author> (david wong)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cryptologie.net/article/542/project-memento-an-nft-art-project/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate PDF files using an html template and Playwright - G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/generate-pdf-files-using-an-html-template-and-playwright.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to generate a PDF document using an html template and Playwright.</description>
      <author> (G&amp;#233;rald Barr&amp;#233;)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/generate-pdf-files-using-an-html-template-and-playwright.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to customize your HTTP DDoS protection settings</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/http-ddos-managed-rules/</link>
      <description>We’re excited to announce the availability of the HTTP DDoS Managed Ruleset. This new feature allows Cloudflare customers to independently tailor their HTTP DDoS protection settings.</description>
      <author> (Omer Yoachimik)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/http-ddos-managed-rules/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>272: .NET 6 RC1, .NET MAUI Updates, &amp;amp; iPhone 13 Event Recap</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/272</link>
      <description>What a week! We have you covered with everything happening with .NET 6, .NET MAUI, and a full breakdown of the iPhone 13 event.</description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/272</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-09-20</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/09/app-developer-links-2021-09-20/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/09/app-developer-links-2021-09-20/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomic reference counting (with Zig code samples)</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/194753-B/atomic-reference-counting-with-zig-code-samples?Key=63c58a36-e1df-46ce-a0f9-ba00bbdc631d</link>
      <description>Referencing counting is probably the oldest memory management technique in existence. It is widely used, easily to understand and explain and in most cases d...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/194753-B/atomic-reference-counting-with-zig-code-samples?Key=63c58a36-e1df-46ce-a0f9-ba00bbdc631d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Microsoft Teams meetings in ASP.NET Core using Microsoft Graph</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2021/09/20/creating-microsoft-teams-meetings-in-asp-net-core-using-microsoft-graph/</link>
      <description>This article shows how to create Microsoft Teams online meetings in ASP.NET Core using Microsoft Graph. Azure AD is used to implement the authentication using Microsoft.Identity.Web and the authent…</description>
      <author> (damienbod)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2021/09/20/creating-microsoft-teams-meetings-in-asp-net-core-using-microsoft-graph/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singularity – Microsoft’s Experimental OS</title>
      <link>https://codingkaiser.blog/2021/07/23/operating-systems-are-more-exciting-than-you-think/</link>
      <description>What would happen if we will write a new OS from scratch right now? can we do it better? can we improve security and robustness? can we prevent unexpected interactions between applications? “what w…</description>
      <author> (by Eliran)</author>
      <guid>https://codingkaiser.blog/2021/07/23/operating-systems-are-more-exciting-than-you-think/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET MAUI: Preview 8 Available, but GA Postponed to Q2 2022 </title>
      <link>https://www.infoq.com/news/2021/09/dotnet-maui-ga-postponed/</link>
      <description>Microsoft postponed the release of .NET MAUI. Release and global availability of .NET MAUI were targeted together with .NET 6 for November 2021. 

According to the latest news from Microsoft, .NET MAUI will not be ready for production with .NET 6 global availability in November this year. The new planned date is set for Q2 of 2022.</description>
      <author> (Almir Vuk)</author>
      <guid>https://www.infoq.com/news/2021/09/dotnet-maui-ga-postponed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCPS Ransomware Update December 22</title>
      <link>https://www.fcps.edu/blog/fcps-ransomware-update-december-22</link>
      <description>Dear FCPS Community and Staff,</description>
      <author> (By Communication and Community Relations)</author>
      <guid>https://www.fcps.edu/blog/fcps-ransomware-update-december-22</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 17:52:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There are six internet links on my office on wheels. Seven when Starlink arrives.</title>
      <link>https://ghuntley.com/internet/</link>
      <description>Is this the best internet in Australia?</description>
      <author> (Geoffrey Huntley)</author>
      <guid>https://ghuntley.com/internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 15:56:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>