<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Introvert</title>
      <link>https://iamintrovert.co/</link>
      <description>Story of your uninterrupted time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://iamintrovert.co/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 03:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Over 1 Million Girls Safe &amp; Cute Since 2013</title>
      <link>https://www.blingsting.com/</link>
      <description>BLINGSTING was created in 2013 by Andi Atteberry with a vision to reinvent personal protection products as stylish safety accessories that women would love to wear and carry – making self-protection relevant and accessible.</description>
      <author> (Jill)</author>
      <guid>https://www.blingsting.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 03:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's not what programming languages do, it's what they shepherd you to</title>
      <link>http://nibblestew.blogspot.com/2020/03/its-not-what-programming-languages-do.html</link>
      <description>How many of you have listened, read or taken part in a discussion about programming languages that goes like the following:   Person A: "Pro...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://nibblestew.blogspot.com/2020/03/its-not-what-programming-languages-do.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 02:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy complex application, seamlessly | Qovery</title>
      <link>https://www.qovery.com/</link>
      <description>Qovery is the first Container as a Service (CaaS) platform that allows any developer to deploy an application in just a few seconds.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.qovery.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 02:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go serverless: Real-time applications with Azure SignalR Service | Azure Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FmxAf8TfFkc</link>
      <description>Modern applications light up with real-time information. Anthony Chu joins Donovan Brown to show how to deliver live updates from Azure Functions to web, mobile, and desktop apps with Azure SignalR Service. Learn how to send real-time messages over WebSockets from your serverless apps with a few lines of code.

3:00 - Demo

Build real-time Apps with Azure Functions and Azure SignalR Service
https://aka.ms/azfr/622/01

SignalR Service bindings for Azure Functions
https://aka.ms/azfr/622/02

What is speech translation?
https://aka.ms/azfr/622/03

CaptionR (GitHub)
https://aka.ms/azfr/622/04

Enable automatic updates in a web application using Azure Functions and SignalR Service
https://aka.ms/azfr/622/05

Azure SignalR Service
https://aka.ms/azfr/622/06

Create a free account (Azure)
https://aka.ms/azfr/622/free

#microsoft #microsoftazure</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Azure)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FmxAf8TfFkc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 01:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Whisk(e)y Day</title>
      <link>https://www.internationalwhiskyday.org/</link>
      <description>On this date let every whisk(e)y lover annually raise a dram - whereever in the world he or she may be - to honour the many unsung heroes of the past and present, who have been crafting the King o'Drinks for centuries and will hopefully continue to do so till the end of time.</description>
      <author> (Drew not Weird)</author>
      <guid>https://www.internationalwhiskyday.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 01:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlueTrace</title>
      <link>https://bluetrace.io/</link>
      <description>BlueTrace, a privacy-preserving technology for community-driven contact tracing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bluetrace.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic Hot Cross Buns | Donna Hay</title>
      <link>https://www.donnahay.com.au/recipes/classic-hot-cross-buns</link>
      <description>Quick and easy dinner or decadent dessert - recipes for any occasion.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.donnahay.com.au/recipes/classic-hot-cross-buns</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peach - Helping you be productive and focused on your laptop.</title>
      <link>https://peachapp.net/</link>
      <description>Helping you be productive and focused on your laptop. Organize your work into different Desktops, and switch quickly between them. Keep important apps on your screen at all times.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://peachapp.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God be with you till we meet again</title>
      <link>http://www.lettersofnote.com/2020/03/god-be-with-you-till-we-meet-again.html</link>
      <description>  On September 29th, 1918, months before the end of World War I , a freshly assigned physician at Camp Devens  military base in Massachusett...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.lettersofnote.com/2020/03/god-be-with-you-till-we-meet-again.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 23:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teijin Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.teijin.com/</link>
      <description>Technology-driven global group operating in the fields of advanced fibers, plastics, composites, healthcare, and IT businesses.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.teijin.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 23:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‎Flow Leak</title>
      <link>https://apps.apple.com/ca/app/flow-leak/id1299310220</link>
      <description>‎Online security is extremely important in our rapidly growing technological world. Oftentimes passwords will inevitably be leaked online because some online websites that we signed up for was hacked. We often don't even know when account information are exposed and will continue to use the same pass…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://apps.apple.com/ca/app/flow-leak/id1299310220</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 22:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play by Play: Modern Web Security Patterns</title>
      <link>https://www.pluralsight.com/courses/play-by-play-modern-web-security-patterns</link>
      <description>This course will help you establish proper patterns and protocols to help keep yourself on the more secure side of web security rather than unsecure. </description>
      <author> (Lars Klint)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pluralsight.com/courses/play-by-play-modern-web-security-patterns</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 22:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow Leak - Apps on Google Play</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rockia.flowleak&amp;hl=en_US</link>
      <description>Online security is extremely important in our rapidly growing technological world. Oftentimes passwords will inevitably be leaked online because some online websites that we signed up for was hacked. We often don't even know when account information are exposed and will continue to use the same password for other online services and websites.

Flow Leak can help you:
* Check if any email account info was exposed from previous data breaches
* Verify if any passwords have already been leaked
* Provide notifications for future breaches

Note that this app does not check your current account status. It will only check if your account shows up in online leaked databases.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rockia.flowleak&amp;hl=en_US</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 22:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating an epidemic</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gxAaO2rsdIs</link>
      <description>Experiments with toy SIR models
Home page: https://www.3blue1brown.com
Brought to you by you: http://3b1b.co/sir-thanks

Simulations by Harry Stevens at the Washington Post:
https://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2020/world/corona-simulator/

Simulations by Kevin Simler at Melting Asphalt:
https://meltingasphalt.com/interactive/outbreak/

Excellent visualization of each country's current growth from Minutephysics and Aatish Bhatia:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=54XLXg4fYsc

If you want to hear a mathematician/epidemiologist's summary of COVID-19, I found this MSRI  talk very worthwhile:
https://youtu.be/MZ957qhzcjI

Marcel Salathé on Contact Tracing:
https://twitter.com/marcelsalathe/status/1242430736944201730

------------------

These animations are largely made using manim, a scrappy open-source python library:  https://github.com/3b1b/manim

The source code for this video is visible here:
https://github.com/3b1b/manim/blob/shaders/from_3b1b/active/sir.py

If you want to check it out, I feel compelled to warn you that it's not the most well-documented tool, and it has many other quirks you might expect in a library someone wrote with only their own use in mind.

Opening music:
Candlepower by Chris Zabriskie is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/)
Source: http://chriszabriskie.com/divider/
Artist: http://chriszabriskie.com/

Other music by Vincent Rubinetti.
Download the music on Bandcamp:
https://vincerubinetti.bandcamp.com/album/the-music-of-3blue1brown

Stream the music on Spotify:
https://open.spotify.com/album/1dVyjwS8FBqXhRunaG5W5u

If you want to contribute translated subtitles or to help review those that have already been made by others and need approval, you can click the gear icon in the video and go to subtitles/cc, then "add subtitles/cc".  I really appreciate those who do this, as it helps make the lessons accessible to more people.

------------------

3blue1brown is a channel about animating math, in all senses of the word animate.  And you know the drill with YouTube, if you want to stay posted on new videos, subscribe: http://3b1b.co/subscribe

Various social media stuffs:
Website: https://www.3blue1brown.com
Twitter: https://twitter.com/3blue1brown
Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/3blue1brown
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/3blue1brown_animations/
Patreon: https://patreon.com/3blue1brown
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/3blue1brown</description>
      <author> (3Blue1Brown)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gxAaO2rsdIs</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 21:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mycroft – Open Source Voice Assistant - Mycroft</title>
      <link>https://mycroft.ai/</link>
      <description>Mycroft is an open source voice assistant, that can be installed on Linux, Raspberry Pi, or on the Mark 1 hardware device. Our opensource skills are written in Python and we have a very friendly developer community. Come join us!</description>
      <author> (Derick Schweppe)</author>
      <guid>https://mycroft.ai/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 21:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Am a Happy Janitor – Part 1: Finding garbage | .NET Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/i-am-a-happy-janitor-part-1-finding-garbage/</link>
      <description>Indeed what I do is very much like the job of the janitors – like the ones who clean your building, or janitors you see at a food court, or yourself when you are taking care of garbage at your house.</description>
      <author> (Maoni StephensFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/i-am-a-happy-janitor-part-1-finding-garbage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 21:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screencasting Tips and Tools, Part 1 | Big Machine</title>
      <link>https://bigmachine.io/career/screencasting-tips-and-tools-part-1/</link>
      <description>Just starting out screencasting? Or maybe it’s been a while? I have some tips, tricks and tools for you. I threw this video together in a bit of a hurry and the audio is a bit rougher than I’d like but I figured it would be better to have the information out there sooner. Polish [...]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bigmachine.io/career/screencasting-tips-and-tools-part-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 21:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New grad vs senior dev</title>
      <link>https://ericlippert.com/2020/03/27/new-grad-vs-senior-dev/</link>
      <description>A student who I used to tutor in CS occasionally sent me a meme yesterday which showed “NEW GRAD vs SENIOR DEVELOPER”; the new grad is all caps yelling NO! YOU CAN’T JUST USE BRUT…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ericlippert.com/2020/03/27/new-grad-vs-senior-dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 20:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us – Spotify for Artists</title>
      <link>https://artists.spotify.com/contact</link>
      <description>Get more out of Spotify with tools &amp; tips for artists and their teams.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://artists.spotify.com/contact</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 18:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keith Elder on about.me</title>
      <link>https://about.me/keith.elder</link>
      <description>I am a Sr. Technology Evangelist, public speaker, and Software Engineer / Architect in Hattiesburg, Mississippi. Read my blog.</description>
      <author> (Keith Elder)</author>
      <guid>https://about.me/keith.elder</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Made an Audio Deepfake of Myself (and Obama!)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NBOm5bPJJU4</link>
      <description>I made an audio deepfake of my voice along with Obama and Trump! 


Samples:
* Donkey: https://soundcloud.com/galacticglum/sets/donkey-audio-deepfake-cnn-tts
* Obama: https://soundcloud.com/galacticglum/sets/obama-audio-deepfake-cnn-tts
* Trump: https://soundcloud.com/galacticglum/sets/trump-audio-deepfake-cnn-tts

 Powered by a text-to-speech model using Deep Convolutional networks with transfer learning. Based on Efficiently Trainable Text-to-Speech System Based on Deep Convolutional Networks with Guided Attention (https://arxiv.org/abs/1710.08969) and dc_tts (https://github.com/Kyubyong/dc_tts), an implementation of the methods described by the paper. 

Currently, I'm working on cleaning up the source code and rewriting it to a newer version of Tensorflow. I hope to eventually release a consolidated CLI to streamline usage of the TTS model.

Transfer learning based approach:
Given a really well-trained model (this means a model that has been trained on both A LOT of data for A LOT of time), we can significantly reduce the training of 'derivative' voices if we simply 'transfer' the weights from the pretrained model. Further training off this model is simply fine-tuning it to fit the specific voice; rather than the more generic base. You can think of this as training the model to do an impression of the target voice. It's pretty cool, I know!

Further Notes:
All the models you heard in this were trained on roughly 10-15 minutes of data samples (consisting of clips that range between 2-10 seconds). All the datasets were manually made by splitting audio recordings into small clips and then transcribing them. I experimented with many different voices for this video (e.g. Donkey and Shrek) and I found that the best results come from when extreme tone is minimized. This is why the Donkey results were never very good. As well as the fact the there is constantly music and other noise in Donkey scenes. TL;DR: if you're trying this at home, remember to get CLEAN data (e.g. no noise in the background, trimmed silence, consistent tone).

The Obama model was trained on 130 samples (12 minutes and 55 seconds total time) sourced from "The President's Speech in Cairo: A New Beginning." Likewise, The Trump model was trained on 136 samples (12 minutes and 11.8 seconds total time).



 ————————————————————————————————— 
Join our Discord! https://discord.gg/hnpccXy

Twitch: https://twitch.tv/galacticglum/
Twitter: https://twitter.com/galacticglum/
Patreon: https://patreon.com/galacticglum/

—————————————————————————————————

I use Adobe Premiere Pro 2020 CC for editing my videos and Adobe After Effects 2020 CC for animation.

I primarily use the Canon T6i with a 50mm f/1.8 STM lens and a 60mm f/2.8 macro 2:1 lens. I use the Logitech C920 as my webcam.

—————————————————————————————————

Music (in order of usage):

* pretzelshop pop - dosbomb. - https://soundcloud.com/dosbomber/pretzelshoppop 
* Track Name: "Give Me Somebody"
Music By: Dj Quads @ https://soundcloud.com/aka-dj-quads
Original upload HERE - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JzCs_tF3kzI
* ｏｎｌｉｎｅ 世界 - dosbomb. - https://soundcloud.com/dosbomber/online
* hairloss hotline. - dosbomb. - https://soundcloud.com/dosbomber/hairlosshotline
* Cello Suite No.1 in G major, BWV 1007 - Collin Carr - https://musopen.org/music/3998-cello-suite-no-1-in-g-major-bwv-1007/
* Violin Concerto in G minor, RV 315 'Summer' - III. Presto - John Harrison - https://musopen.org/music/14910-the-four-seasons-op-8/
* need somebody (feat. iamalex) - engelwood - https://soundcloud.com/engelwoodmusic/need-somebody-feat-iamalex</description>
      <author> (GalacticGlum)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NBOm5bPJJU4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Upcoming Streams Page to My Gatsby Site (Live Stream)</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I6Dty2eiEfQ</link>
      <description>Since I am starting to do live streams, I am adding an Upcoming Streams page to my Gatsby site. I also use the react-livestream package to embed a live feed of my stream on the page.

https://www.jamesqquick.com
https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
https://www.learnbuildteach.com/

Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code!!
https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/

Build a Quiz App with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/

Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/jamesqquick</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I6Dty2eiEfQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 16:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom needs to clean up its privacy act</title>
      <link>https://blogs.harvard.edu/doc/2020/03/27/zoom/</link>
      <description>As quarantined millions gather virtually on conferencing platforms, the best of those, Zoom, is doing very well. Hats off. But Zoom is also—correctly—taking a lot of heat for its privacy policy, wh…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.harvard.edu/doc/2020/03/27/zoom/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 16:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Tools From the Warren for President Tech Team</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@teamwarren/open-source-tools-from-the-warren-for-president-tech-team-f1f27d2c7551</link>
      <description>We’re taking the important step of open-sourcing some of the most important projects of the Elizabeth Warren campaign for anyone to use.</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@teamwarren)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@teamwarren/open-source-tools-from-the-warren-for-president-tech-team-f1f27d2c7551</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 15:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLab</title>
      <link>https://sharplab.io/#v2:EYLgZgpghgLgrgJwgZwLQygg5hG6CeADhACaoB2EA7gDQkgDUAPgAIAMABCwIwAsA3AFgAUCwDMXAEwcAwhwDeIjso5KV4rrw4BZABQBKBWpUqA9KY4AVTDhgcYRCB0pUQxkxwAiASwDGMbwB7ckx8AB5vchgaDkiYAD57GHIOAF5nagMhYQ8VdxNzADdMNxzcjmKECrSMqi8/AODQiKiYuPis9wBfES6gA=</link>
      <description>C#/VB/F# compiler playground.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sharplab.io/#v2:EYLgZgpghgLgrgJwgZwLQygg5hG6CeADhACaoB2EA7gDQkgDUAPgAIAMABCwIwAsA3AFgAUCwDMXAEwcAwhwDeIjso5KV4rrw4BZABQBKBWpUqA9KY4AVTDhgcYRCB0pUQxkxwAiASwDGMbwB7ckx8AB5vchgaDkiYAD57GHIOAF5nagMhYQ8VdxNzADdMNxzcjmKECrSMqi8/AODQiKiYuPis9wBfES6gA=</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 15:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity &amp; Access Control for modern Applications and APIs using ASP.NET Core 3 - NDC Copenhagen 2020</title>
      <link>https://ndccopenhagen.com/workshop/identity-access-control-for-modern-applications/</link>
      <description>Modern application design has changed quite a bit in recent years.&lt;section&gt;“Mobile-first” and “cloud-ready” are the types of applications you are expected to develop. Also, to keep pace with these demands, Microsoft has revamped their complete web stack with ASP.NET Core to meet these architectural demands.&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ndccopenhagen.com/workshop/identity-access-control-for-modern-applications/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 14:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP Classic Journeys: no-store</title>
      <link>https://www.mobilize.net/blog/asp-classic-journeys-no-store?hss_channel=tw-4083531</link>
      <description>VBUC is a great tool to modernize your ASP Classic Websites. Sometimes when you migrate from ASP Classic we find little subtle details that require attention. One of this subtle details this Cache No-Store setting. Some recommendations on what to do. </description>
      <author> (Mauricio Rojas)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mobilize.net/blog/asp-classic-journeys-no-store?hss_channel=tw-4083531</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 14:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rubino's Best Gear Page's Amazon Page</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/shop/daniel_rubino?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202003</link>
      <description>Shop recommended products from Rubino's Best Gear Page on Amazon.com. Learn more about Rubino's Best Gear Page's favorite products.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.amazon.com/shop/daniel_rubino?tag=linksfordevs-20&amp;lfd=202003</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 13:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential Free Software for Remote Work – Purism</title>
      <link>https://puri.sm/posts/our-essential-list-of-free-software-for-remote-work/</link>
      <description>Purism — Private and Secure Hardware, Software, and Services</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://puri.sm/posts/our-essential-list-of-free-software-for-remote-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 12:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's not what programming languages do, it's what they shepherd you to</title>
      <link>https://nibblestew.blogspot.com/2020/03/its-not-what-programming-languages-do.html</link>
      <description>How many of you have listened, read or taken part in a discussion about programming languages that goes like the following:   Person A: "Pro...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nibblestew.blogspot.com/2020/03/its-not-what-programming-languages-do.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 11:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 184</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-184/</link>
      <description>This has been an absolutely flat-out week between running almost 3 hours of our free Cyber-Broken talk with Scott Helme, doing an hour of code with Ari each day (and helping get up to speed with remote schooling) then running our Hack Yourself First workshop on Aussie time zones the</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-184/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 08:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"I thought it would be more of an old Soviet kind" — Jon Galloway on the Russian visa process, Sovietness, and tech conferences </title>
      <link>https://dev.to/_jugrugroup/i-thought-it-would-be-more-of-an-old-soviet-kind-jon-galloway-on-the-russian-visa-process-sovietness-and-tech-conferences-1pel</link>
      <description>There are many people who find traveling to Russia an extreme and exotic adventure. Some say snow cov...</description>
      <author> (JUG Ru Group)</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/_jugrugroup/i-thought-it-would-be-more-of-an-old-soviet-kind-jon-galloway-on-the-russian-visa-process-sovietness-and-tech-conferences-1pel</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2019 version 16.6 Preview 2 Brings New Features Your Way | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2019-version-16-6-preview-2/</link>
      <description>Visual Studio 2019 version 16.6 Preview 2 releases today. In this release comes more Git integration, several productivity features &amp; more!</description>
      <author> (Jacqueline WiddisProgram Manager, Release TeamFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2019-version-16-6-preview-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Production Debugging for .NET meets Infrastructure as Code | Ozcode</title>
      <link>https://oz-code.com/production-debugging/production-debugging-dotnet-meets-infrastructure-as-code/</link>
      <description>Deploy Ozcode Production Debugger to Azure using Pulumi, next-gen IaC, to enable easy debugging of your .NET Apps and services. Learn more &gt;</description>
      <author> (Simon Timms)</author>
      <guid>https://oz-code.com/production-debugging/production-debugging-dotnet-meets-infrastructure-as-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanitize HTML snippets with AngleSharp</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/sanitize-html-snippet-with-anglesharp.htm</link>
      <description>Some websites allow user to include html when they post comments. This may looks like:


Add comment section on Scott Hanselman's blog

The website must remove all elements and attributes that are not allowed to avoid injection problems. In this post we'll see how to use AngleSharp to parse the html snippet and remove dangerous attributes and elements.

AngleSharp is a .NET library that gives you the…</description>
      <author> (Gérald Barré)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/sanitize-html-snippet-with-anglesharp.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 06:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Code Tired | Adding Tuple Support to .NET Classes in C#</title>
      <link>https://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Adding-Tuple-Support-to-NET-Classes-in-C</link>
      <description>Don't Code Tired - Jason Roberts on Software Development and .NET -</description>
      <author> (Jason)</author>
      <guid>https://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Adding-Tuple-Support-to-NET-Classes-in-C</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 06:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell 7.1 Team Investments and Preview.1 Release | PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/powershell-7-1-team-investments-and-preview-1-release/</link>
      <description>The PowerShell 7 release marks a huge milestone for PowerShell, the community, and the team!
Today we released the first preview for PowerShell 7.1! This release includes a number of changes that did not make it in time for the 7.0 release.</description>
      <author> (Steve LeePrincipal Software Engineer Manager, PowerShellFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/powershell-7-1-team-investments-and-preview-1-release/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 06:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimising C# for a serverless environment</title>
      <link>https://blogs.endjin.com/2020/03/optimising-c-for-a-serverless-environment/</link>
      <description>We recently used Azure Functions to process marine vessel telemetry from around the world. We optimised our processing for a serverless environment which meant that the compute would cost less than £10 / month. This post summarises some of the techniques we used! #AzureFunctions #bigcompute #bigdata</description>
      <author> (Carmel Eve)</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.endjin.com/2020/03/optimising-c-for-a-serverless-environment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 06:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What about it!?  is creating Youtube Videos about SpaceX, Space and Science in general! | Patreon</title>
      <link>https://www.patreon.com/whataboutit</link>
      <description>Become a patron of What about it!?  today:
            Read 118 posts by What about it!?  and get access to exclusive
            content and experiences on the world’s largest membership
            platform for artists and creators.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.patreon.com/whataboutit</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 04:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>