<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How Blizzard&amp;#39;s reputation collapsed in just 3 years</title>
      <link>https://www.pcgamer.com/how-blizzards-reputation-collapsed-in-just-3-years/</link>
      <description>From free speech scandals and massive layoffs to a discrimination lawsuit: A history of Blizzard&amp;#39;s recent controversies and major departures.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/pcgamermagazine)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pcgamer.com/how-blizzards-reputation-collapsed-in-just-3-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 09:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - cy384/ssheven: A modern SSH client for Mac OS 7/8/9</title>
      <link>https://github.com/cy384/ssheven</link>
      <description>A modern SSH client for Mac OS 7/8/9. Contribute to cy384/ssheven development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/cy384/ssheven</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 07:07:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech spec experts seek allies to tear down ISO standards paywall</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.com/2021/07/31/iso_paywall_battle/</link>
      <description>Open letter drafted against what&amp;#39;s seen as unjustified profiteering</description>
      <author> (Thomas Claburn in San Francisco
            Sat&amp;#160;31&amp;#160;Jul&amp;#160;2021 // 13:06&amp;#160;UTC)</author>
      <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2021/07/31/iso_paywall_battle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 06:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 6 corporations control 90% of the media outlets in America. The illusion of choice and objectivity | Tech News | Startups News</title>
      <link>https://techstartups.com/2020/09/18/6-corporations-control-90-media-america-illusion-choice-objectivity-2020/</link>
      <description>Elite is a word we use in our daily conversations but few people probably know the origin and the history of the word.&amp;#160;Elites (French &amp;#233;lite, from Latin eligere, to select or to sort out) are a small group of powerful …</description>
      <author> (Nickie Louise)</author>
      <guid>https://techstartups.com/2020/09/18/6-corporations-control-90-media-america-illusion-choice-objectivity-2020/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 04:05:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Ways to Get S#!+ Done—and We Still Don’t</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/to-do-apps-failed-productivity-tools/</link>
      <description>You want to be productive. Software wants to help. But even with a glut of tools claiming to make us all into taskmasters, we almost never master our tasks.</description>
      <author> (Cond&amp;#233; Nast)</author>
      <guid>https://www.wired.com/story/to-do-apps-failed-productivity-tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:06:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTTP | MDN</title>
      <link>https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTTP</link>
      <description>Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) is an application-layer protocol for transmitting hypermedia documents, such as HTML. It was designed for communication between web browsers and web servers, but it can also be used for other purposes. HTTP follows a classical client-server model, with a client opening a connection to make a request, then waiting until it receives a response. HTTP is a stateless protocol, meaning that the server does not keep any data (state) between two requests.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTTP</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:06:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cory Doctorow: Past Performance is Not Indicative of Future Results</title>
      <link>https://locusmag.com/2020/11/cory-doctorow-past-performance-is-not-indicative-of-future-results/</link>
      <description>In “Full Employment”, my July 2020 column, I wrote, “I am an AI skeptic. I am baffled by anyone who isn’t. I don’t see any path from continuous improvements to the (ad…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://locusmag.com/2020/11/cory-doctorow-past-performance-is-not-indicative-of-future-results/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 23:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Presenting Vendor Paradox</title>
      <link>https://danielmiessler.com/blog/the-presenting-vendor-paradox/</link>
      <description>There&amp;#39;s a paradox in information security where the community wants two things at once: 1. High quality research and talks, and 2. Unbiased research and</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://danielmiessler.com/blog/the-presenting-vendor-paradox/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t become an Enterprise/IT Architect…</title>
      <link>https://ea.rna.nl/2021/07/31/dont-become-an-enterprise-it-architect/</link>
      <description>With increasing IT volumes in the world, landscape change is getting harder and harder, and we need to adapt to that fact. Upper management is very slow to adapt and the Enterprise/IT Architect/Str…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ea.rna.nl/2021/07/31/dont-become-an-enterprise-it-architect/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:07:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verkle trees</title>
      <link>https://vitalik.ca/general/2021/06/18/verkle.html</link>
      <description>2021 Jun 18 
See all posts</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vitalik.ca/general/2021/06/18/verkle.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:07:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers leak full EA data after failed extortion attempt</title>
      <link>https://therecord.media/hackers-leak-full-ea-data-after-failed-extortion-attempt/</link>
      <description>The hackers who breached Electronic Arts last month have released the entire cache of stolen data after failing to extort the company and later sell the stolen files to a third-party buyer.</description>
      <author> (Catalin Cimpanu)</author>
      <guid>https://therecord.media/hackers-leak-full-ea-data-after-failed-extortion-attempt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:07:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Dvorak Die &amp;quot;A Bitter Man&amp;quot;?</title>
      <link>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2021/07/did-dvorak-die-a-bitter-man/</link>
      <description>Yet more MSc yak-shaving. I’m currently reading Melissa Schilling’s book “Strategic management of technological innovation”. In a passage talking about customers’ resi…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2021/07/did-dvorak-die-a-bitter-man/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:07:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Poincar&amp;#233; Conjecture</title>
      <link>https://www.privatdozent.co/p/the-poincare-conjecture</link>
      <description>Poincar&amp;#233; began working on what is now considered to be&amp;#160;the foundation of topology and algebraic topology in the 1890s&amp;#160;with the work&amp;#160;Analysis Situs&amp;#160;(1895) and five later supplements (1899; 1900, 1902a, 1902b, 1904).</description>
      <author> (J&amp;#248;rgen Veisdal)</author>
      <guid>https://www.privatdozent.co/p/the-poincare-conjecture</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:07:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to Linux</title>
      <link>https://metaredux.com/posts/2021/07/31/back-to-linux.html</link>
      <description>Background Note: I’ve started writing this article about one year ago (September 2020), but I dropped it at some point. Its final version is way less ambitious than my original plans for it. Still, better than nothing. A long time ago I wrote about my frustrations with Linux that led me to abandon the OS after having spent quite a lot of time on it. After this article I made one failed attempt to convert to Windows and eventually I settled on macOS for almost a decade. While I was reasonably happy with macOS for most of the time, it never felt like home and I kept longing to revisit Linux. I was also missing having a custom-built desktop PC for a while, so I was very tempted to get one and run Linux on it. For various reasons (e.g. a lot of work-related travel and excessive laziness) I never got to doing so. Until now. 2020 has been a horrible year on many levels, but it presented me with an unique opportunity to follow through with my plans, as I was finally grounded at home. In this article I’ll share my experience revisiting Linux and rediscovering the joy of being in control of your operating system and your hardware. The Downfall of macOS I won’t go into much details here, as I hope everyone has noticed the shift in macOS to be something more like iOS. That’s good for most users, but not really for software engineers. Apple used to spend a lot of time courting developers to their OS some 15 years ago, but now they only seem to care about macOS and iOS devs. They rarely update the Unix tools that ship with macOS, they still haven’t created a package manager (everyone’s basically using homebrew), etc. At this point it’s clear to me that macOS is not meant to be an OS for tinkerers, but rather for consumers. That’s not a bad thing, it just doesn’t sit very well with me. On a more practical note, here are a few things that have bothered me with macOS in recent years: Pushing aggressively for the use of the App Store, which limits what applications can do. The OS tries hard to dissuade you from using any externally procured applications. Bringing some applications and weird features from iOS to macOS (has anyone ever used the launchpad?). The need to reinstall XCode after each macOS upgrade. Almost every major OS upgrade breaks Homebrew or some tool that I use (like Karabiner, a keyboard remapping utility). macOS ships by default with Emacs 22. That’s not a typo. As noted above there are plenty of outdated Unix tools that ship with macOS. Cheap tricks to obscure some problems, like hiding the remaining battery life estimation. I can go on, but I’ll stop at this point. I hope you get the idea. The New Hardware Here’s the hardware that I got: CPU AMD RYZEN 7 3700X GPU ASUS DUAL Radeon RX 5500 XT EVO OC 8G Motherboard AORUS X570 ULTRA SSD 960GB M.2 2280 Corsair Force Series MP510 RAM 32GB (2x16GB) DDR4 3200MHz Corsair Vengeance LPX Case Fractal Design Define 7 PSU Fractal Design Ion+ 660W Platinum As you can see there’s nothing fancy about it. I wanted to build a decent workstation, not a gaming rig. Still, I opted to get a decent discrete GPU, as there were a few PC games that I was hoping to eventually play (StarCraft II, Tomb Raider, Diablo III, etc). I went for the Radeon mostly because of the AMD’s (supposedly great) open-source GPU driver for Linux. In hindsight this was a big mistake, but I’ll expand on this topic later. Note: I knew that an Intel CPU with built-in GPU was the safest option in terms of driver support, but I really wanted a Ryzen CPU and a reasonably powerful discreet GPU. The Distro I decided to play it safe and I went with Ubuntu 20.04, which was the latest release at the time. Historically I preferred Arch Linux and Fedora, but I wanted to minimize the setup efforts. When I was younger I loved spending lots of time to tweak every aspect of my setup (e.g. building a custom kernel, tuning the compilation flags for my packages, obtaining proprietary drivers from third-party repos, etc), but now I’m older, lazier and more practical. I still enjoy tinkering with my setup a lot, but I don’t want to be forced to tinker (the Gentoo way). The Drivers Everything worked out of the box, but unfortunately not everything worked well. I was getting some intermittent issues with my wi-fi and X.org kept crashing due to some issues with the GPU drivers. A quick Google search revealed I wasn’t the only person facing these GPU issues. No matter what I tried (and I tried a lot of things - updated kernels, Mesa, random patches I found here and there, etc) I couldn’t solve the GPU issue and my computer kept crashing 1-2 times per day. As you can imagine this was quite frustrating. Funny enough, after each change the crashes would get more frequent or less frequent. Never completely disappear, though. The wi-fi problem was much easier to address - I just switched to ethernet and never bothered to investigate it. Hardware support was the main reason I left Linux a decade ago and sadly the situation there hasn’t improved much. Perhaps the situation is better with Nvidia GPUs, but I was hoping avoid dealing with a proprietary driver.1 The Apps Little has changed in the past 10 years, not to mention I don’t use that many apps - mostly a browser, Emacs and a terminal. In short - everything was better than I remembered it, but nothing was fantastic. GNOME and its apps (e.g. Nautilus) still have plenty of rough edges, but they get the job done. Albert was a great alternative to Alfred. That’s probably the only new app that I used this time around. Some proprietary apps that I need for work like Zoom, Slack and Dropbox didn’t work/look great, but this is what I expected anyways. Still, they were working better than I remembered them to. The Development Experience Absolutely divine. Proper package manager. Proper service management. Docker at its home. It doesn’t get better than this. I’m 100% certain that Linux offers the best development experience for most software engineers. When there aren’t hardware issues to affect it negatively, that is. Epilogue “Back to Linux” is a bit of a misnomer, because of the long period in which this article stayed on my backburner. By the time I wrapped it, I’m no longer using Linux, at least not natively. Due to the GPU driver issues, in the end I’ve opted to switch to Windows 10 and WSL (basically a Linux VM running in Windows). One year later I’m still a happy camper. With Windows 10 I got the best of both worlds: no driver issues proper Linux development experience As a bonus - I also got the opportunity to play a lot more games.2 Windows still has its quirks, but the experience with it certainly beats the experience I had with Linux. All proprietary apps work great, the drivers are solid and I’m essentially working in Linux all of the time. The only thing from macOS I’m really missing is the nice collaboration/sync between all Apple devices - e.g. you take a picture on your phone and it immediately goes to your computer. You get an SMS on your phone and it’s also on your computer. Not a big deal, but this walled Apple garden kept me on macOS even though I was getting more and more frustrated with it. I hate walled gardens! In short, hardware support remains the biggest weakness of Linux as desktop operating system, just as always. It’s super disappointing that even after carefully choosing hardware for Linux compatibility I still ended up with a GPU that didn’t work reliably. On the bright side - it was a ton of fun to assemble a new PC, after all those years. You should have seen how happy I was when the thing booted from the first try! And it was nice to check in on the progress made in the world of Linux and to find a reason to give Windows another chance. That’s all I have for you today. Keep hacking! And I happen to be a huge AMD fan.&amp;#160;↩ Not sure if that’s really a bonus though.&amp;#160;↩</description>
      <author> (Bozhidar Batsov)</author>
      <guid>https://metaredux.com/posts/2021/07/31/back-to-linux.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:07:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UV Radiation</title>
      <link>https://www.cdc.gov/nceh/features/uv-radiation-safety/index.html</link>
      <description>Learn how to protect yourself from UV radiation.</description>
      <author> (CDC)</author>
      <guid>https://www.cdc.gov/nceh/features/uv-radiation-safety/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:07:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - AdrienTorris/awesome-blazor: Resources for Blazor, a .NET web framework using C#/Razor and HTML that runs in the browser with WebAssembly.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/AdrienTorris/awesome-blazor#podcasts</link>
      <description>Resources for Blazor, a .NET web framework using C#/Razor and HTML that runs in the browser with WebAssembly. - GitHub - AdrienTorris/awesome-blazor: Resources for Blazor, a .NET web framework usin...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/AdrienTorris/awesome-blazor#podcasts</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 20:06:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold, silver and brass medals</title>
      <link>https://cosmosmagazine.com/science/chemistry/olympic-medal-composition</link>
      <description>What are the Olympic medals made of? It seems an obvious answer but the silver medal is the only one that is actually pure silver.</description>
      <author> (30 July 2021
/

Ellen Phiddian)</author>
      <guid>https://cosmosmagazine.com/science/chemistry/olympic-medal-composition</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 19:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of AI tools have been built to catch covid. None of them helped.</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/07/30/1030329/machine-learning-ai-failed-covid-hospital-diagnosis-pandemic/</link>
      <description>Some have been used in hospitals, despite not being properly tested. But the pandemic could help make medical AI better.</description>
      <author> (by Will Douglas Heaven archive page)</author>
      <guid>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/07/30/1030329/machine-learning-ai-failed-covid-hospital-diagnosis-pandemic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 19:04:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers - NDC Oslo 2021 | Software Developers Conference</title>
      <link>https://ndcoslo.com/cfp</link>
      <description>NDC Oslo 2021 is a 5-Day Event for Software Developers, 29 Nov - 3 Dec in Oslo Spektrum.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ndcoslo.com/cfp</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 17:06:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Activity | Firefox Public Data Report</title>
      <link>https://data.firefox.com/dashboard/user-activity</link>
      <description>The state of the Firefox userbase, including user totals, usage hours, and version adoption. Use our public data to improve your Firefox support!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://data.firefox.com/dashboard/user-activity</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 17:06:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OfficeSuite</title>
      <link>https://www.officesuite.com/</link>
      <description>Fully compatible with Microsoft Office 365. Get OfficeSuite for 29.99 per year - create and edit Word, Excel, PowerPoint and PDF files on Windows PC, Android and iOS. Download Free Trial.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.officesuite.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 17:06:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edit Your C++ Code while Debugging with Hot Reload in Visual Studio 2022</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/edit-your-c-code-while-debugging-with-hot-reload-in-visual-studio-2022/</link>
      <description>In Visual Studio 2022 Preview 2, we are happy to announce that Hot Reload is now supported for C++. Hot Reload for C++, powered by Edit and Continue, is a new way of editing your code during debugging.</description>
      <author> (David Li)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/edit-your-c-code-while-debugging-with-hot-reload-in-visual-studio-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 17:06:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5000x faster CRDTs: An Adventure in Optimization</title>
      <link>https://josephg.com/blog/crdts-go-brrr/</link>
      <description>July 31 2021</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://josephg.com/blog/crdts-go-brrr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 16:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosting SQLite databases on Github Pages - (or any static file hoster)</title>
      <link>https://phiresky.netlify.app/blog/2021/hosting-sqlite-databases-on-github-pages/</link>
      <description>I was writing a tiny website to display statistics of how much sponsored content a Youtube creator has over time when I noticed that I often write a small tool as a website that queries some data from a database and then displays it in a graph, a table, or similar. But if you want to use a</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://phiresky.netlify.app/blog/2021/hosting-sqlite-databases-on-github-pages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 13:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>