<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Airbreak: Jailbreak your CPAP machine</title>
      <link>https://airbreak.dev/</link>
      <description>Tools to turn your CPAP device into an emergency ventilator</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://airbreak.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 22:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swagger UI</title>
      <link>https://grpchttpapi.azurewebsites.net/swagger/index.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://grpchttpapi.azurewebsites.net/swagger/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 22:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tom nook's laptop</title>
      <link>https://tomnookslaptop.bert.org/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tomnookslaptop.bert.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 21:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Webpage</title>
      <link>https://news.russellsaw.io/</link>
      <description>There are nearly two million confirmed cases of coronavirus in 185 countries and almost 120,000 people have died.

The United States now has about three times as many confirmed cases as any other country.

This series of maps and charts tracks the spread of the virus since it emerged in China in December last year.

Confirmed cases around the world

cases 1,920,648

deaths 119,716

recoveries 456,910

Group 4

Please upgrade your browser to see the full interactive

Figures last updated 14 Apr 2020

The virus is spreading rapidly in many countries and the death toll is still climbing - but the majority of people are recovering from the infection.

The country with the highest number of cases is the US, according to figures collated by Johns Hopkins University. With about 580,000 confirmed cases, it has nearly seven times the official number recorded in China.

China's official death toll from the outbreak is just over 3,300 - but the US, Italy, Spain, France and UK have each recorded more than 10,000 deaths.

Critics of the Chinese government, however, have questioned whether the country's official numbers can be trusted.

This information is regularly updated but may not reflect the latest totals for each country.

Cases

Deaths

USA

581,370

23,568

Spain

170,099

17,756

Italy

159,516

20,465

France

136,779

14,967

Germany

130,072

3,194

UK

88,621

11,329

China

83,302

3,345

Iran

73,303

4,585

Turkey

61,049

1,296

Belgium

30,589

3,903

Netherlands

26,554

2,823

Switzerland

25,688

1,138

Canada

25,680

780

Brazil

23,723

1,355

Russia

18,328

148

Portugal

16,934

535

Austria

14,041

368

Israel

11,586

116

Sweden

10,948

919

Ireland

10,647

365

South Korea

10,564

222

India

10,453

358

Peru

9,784

216

Japan

7,645

143

Ecuador

7,529

355

Chile

7,525

82

Poland

6,934

245

Romania

6,633

331

Norway

6,605

134

Australia

6,366

61

Denmark

6,318

285

Czech Republic

6,059

143

Pakistan

5,707

96

Mexico

5,014

332

Saudi Arabia

4,934

65

Philippines

4,932

315

Malaysia

4,817

77

Indonesia

4,557

399

United Arab Emirates

4,521

25

Serbia

4,054

85

Panama

3,472

94

Luxembourg

3,292

69

Qatar

3,231

7

Dominican Republic

3,167

177

Ukraine

3,102

93

Finland

3,064

59

Belarus

2,919

29

Singapore

2,918

9

Colombia

2,852

112

Thailand

2,613

41

Argentina

2,277

98

South Africa

2,272

27

Egypt

2,190

164

Greece

2,145

99

Algeria

1,983

313

Morocco

1,763

126

Moldova

1,712

35

Iceland

1,711

8

Croatia

1,650

25

Hungary

1,458

109

Iraq

1,378

78

New Zealand

1,366

9

Bahrain

1,361

6

Estonia

1,332

28

Kuwait

1,300

2

Slovenia

1,212

55

Azerbaijan

1,148

12

Kazakhstan

1,091

14

Lithuania

1,062

24

Armenia

1,039

14

Bosnia and Herzegovina

1,037

39

Uzbekistan

998

4

Puerto Rico

903

45

North Macedonia

854

38

Cameroon

848

12

Bangladesh

803

39

Slovakia

769

2

Oman

727

4

Cuba

726

21

Tunisia

726

34

Diamond Princess cruise ship

712

12

Bulgaria

685

32

Afghanistan

665

21

Cyprus

662

12

Latvia

655

5

Andorra

646

29

Lebanon

632

20

Ivory Coast

626

6

Costa Rica

612

3

Ghana

566

8

Niger

548

13

Burkina Faso

515

27

Uruguay

483

8

Albania

467

23

Kyrgyzstan

430

5

Honduras

397

25

Taiwan

393

6

Réunion

391

Jordan

391

7

Malta

384

3

San Marino

371

36

Bolivia

354

28

Nigeria

343

10

Mauritius

324

9

Guinea

319

Palestinian Territories

308

2

Djibouti

298

2

Senegal

291

2

Kosovo

283

7

Montenegro

274

3

Georgia

272

3

Vietnam

265

Isle of Man

242

2

DR Congo

235

20

Guernsey

219

6

Sri Lanka

218

7

Jersey

217

3

Kenya

208

9

Mayotte

207

3

Venezuela

189

9

Faroe Islands

184

Guatemala

167

5

Paraguay

159

7

Martinique

157

6

Guadeloupe

145

8

El Salvador

137

6

Brunei

136

1

Guam

133

5

Gibraltar

129

Rwanda

127

Mali

123

10

Cambodia

122

Trinidad and Tobago

113

8

Madagascar

106

Monaco

93

1

Aruba

92

French Guiana

86

Liechtenstein

79

1

Togo

77

3

Ethiopia

74

3

Jamaica

73

4

Barbados

72

4

Myanmar

62

4

Somalia

60

2

Congo

60

5

Liberia

59

6

Bermuda

57

5

Gabon

57

1

French Polynesia

55

Cayman Islands

54

1

Uganda

54

Sint Maarten

52

9

United States Virgin Islands

51

1

Bahamas

49

8

Tanzania

49

3

Guyana

47

6

Zambia

45

2

Haiti

40

3

Guinea-Bissau

38

Benin

35

1

Eritrea

34

Saint Martin

32

2

Mongolia

30

Sudan

29

4

Libya

26

1

Syria

25

2

Antigua and Barbuda

23

2

Chad

23

Equatorial Guinea

21

Mozambique

21

Maldives

20

Laos

19

Angola

19

2

New Caledonia

18

Belize

18

2

Zimbabwe

17

3

Fiji

16

Dominica

16

Malawi

16

2

Namibia

16

Saint Lucia

15

Eswatini

15

Grenada

14

Nepal

14

Curaçao

14

1

Botswana

13

1

Saint Kitts and Nevis

12

St Vincent and the Grenadines

12

Montserrat

11

Greenland

11

Seychelles

11

Central African Republic

11

Northern Mariana Islands

11

2

Sierra Leone

10

Cape Verde

10

1

Suriname

10

1

Turks and Caicos Islands

10

1

Nicaragua

9

1

Gambia

9

1

MS Zaandam cruise ship

9

2

Vatican

8

Mauritania

7

1

Saint Barthelemy

6

Western Sahara

6

Bhutan

5

Burundi

5

1

Falkland Islands

5

Timor-Leste

4

Sao Tome and Principe

4

South Sudan

4

British Virgin Islands

3

Anguilla

3

Papua New Guinea

2

Saint Pierre and Miquelon

1

Yemen

1

Source: Johns Hopkins University, national public health agencies. France now includes cases confirmed and suspected in retirement and nursing homes.

The outbreak was declared a global pandemic by the World Health Organization (WHO) on 11 March. This is when an infectious disease is passing easily from person to person in many parts of the world at the same time.

The WHO said it took more than three months to reach the first 100,000 confirmed cases worldwide, but it took less than a week for the number to double from 500,000 to a million. It then took seven days to reach 1.5 million.

The true figure for the number of people with coronavirus is thought to be much higher as many of those with milder symptoms have not been tested and counted.

China has now lifted many of the stringent measures it took to bring the disease under control. Last week, authorities eased travel restrictions in Wuhan, the city where the outbreak began in late 2019.

South Korea, where a major outbreak began in February, has also seen the number of new cases fall in recent weeks.

Governments across the world have halted flights, locked down towns and cities and urged people to stay at home.

European countries have seen steep rises in cases and deaths, but slowing infection rates are raising hopes that strict social distancing measures are curbing the spread of the virus.

Italy has the highest toll outside the US, with more than 20,000 deaths so far, but recent data shows the infection rate is slowing.

The country was the first in Europe to record a large number of deaths and has been in lockdown since 9 March.

Some quarantine measures are now starting to be relaxed with certain shops, such as booksellers and stationery stores, reopening. The amount of activity depends on the region - for example, Lombardy in the north, which was the centre of Italy's coronavirus crisis, is keeping shops shut.

Spain's death toll is not far behind, with more than 18,000 - the third highest of any country. There are now around 172,000 confirmed cases in Spain, but data shows the rate of new cases is falling with the latest figures showing the country's lowest increase in infections since 20 March.

The Spanish government is also beginning to ease the strict lockdown that has been in place in the country since 14 March. People in manufacturing, construction and some services are being allowed to return to work, but must stick to strict safety guidelines. The rest of the population must still remain at home.

In the UK, there have been more than 88,000 confirmed cases and more than 11,000 deaths.

Like Spain, deaths in the UK grew rapidly at first, doubling faster than every two days. That rate of increase has now slowed.

The UK's first emergency field hospital, built in London's ExCel Centre, is now open. The NHS Nightingale hospital, as it has been called, has space for 4,000 intensive care beds. Others are planned across the UK.

With more than 580,000 cases, the US has the highest number of confirmed infections in the world.

In fact, New York state alone has more cases than any other country, with 195,000 so far. But Andrew Cuomo, the state's governor, says New York City is now witnessing a flattening curve of cases as the effects of social distancing measures begin to be seen.

The number of deaths from the virus in the US now stands at more than 23,000, and the rate is doubling about every three days at present.

Nearly all Americans are now living under some form of lockdown as states increase efforts to curb the outbreak.

President Trump has said he wants the economy to reopen with a "big bang" - but that would have to wait until the US was on the downward slope in terms of infections.

Federal coronavirus guidelines, such as social distancing, will be in place across the country until at least 30 April.

The outbreak is having a major economic impact, with figures showing the number of people making a new claim for unemployment benefits surging to a record high of more than 6.6 million in the week ending 4 April. In all, roughly 16 million Americans have lost their jobs since states began to bring in lockdown measures.

The majority of countries in Europe now have strict lockdowns in place, with many only allowing citizens to leave their homes to buy essential items or exercise. In Paris, authorities have even banned exercise during the day to reduce the number of people out on the streets.

India's government told the country's 1.3 billion residents to stay at home last month and there are similar restrictions on movement and social contact across the world in countries like Argentina, New Zealand, Saudi Arabia and South Africa.

Data on planned journeys in major cities, from the travel app Citymapper, shows how people in places like London, Madrid, Istanbul and New York are now moving around far less than they were a few weeks ago.

The data shows that while Milan in northern Italy has been locked down for several weeks now, many other cities have been restricting movement for a much shorter period.

While movement is also down in the South Korean capital Seoul, the city hasn't ground to a halt like European capitals despite facing huge numbers of coronavirus cases - a sign of the country's decision to focus on widespread testing and contact tracing rather than imposing a lockdown.

In Russia, the Kremlin had insisted that there was "de facto no epidemic" in the country but President Putin has urged people to stay at home, which explains the significant drop in movement in Moscow.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://news.russellsaw.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 17:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub is now free for teams</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/2020-04-14-github-is-now-free-for-teams/</link>
      <description>Every developer and team can now get private repositories with unlimited collaborators at no cost with GitHub Free, and we reduced prices for some of our paid plans.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.blog/2020-04-14-github-is-now-free-for-teams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 17:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zippia Poll: Half of American workers would rather work from home forever - Zippia</title>
      <link>https://www.zippia.com/advice/coronavirus-remote-work-survey/</link>
      <description>Two thirds of all American workers are able to work from home 75% of baby boomers want to work from home forever Half of all Americans want to continue working from home following the coronavirus The coronavirus, or COVID-19, has more people than ever working from home. With many states and cities closing down nonessential …</description>
      <author> (by Kathy Morris)</author>
      <guid>https://www.zippia.com/advice/coronavirus-remote-work-survey/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 15:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Visual Studio Code Git Extensions in 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N8L6RJ5uZoE</link>
      <description>By finding the right Visual Studio Code Git extensions, you can really power up your Git workflow right inside of your editor. Although VS Code has some great built-in functionality for Git, you can add some real power to your workflow.

Git History - https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=donjayamanne.githistory
Git Blame - https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=waderyan.gitblame
Git Project Manager - https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=felipecaputo.git-project-manager
Open in Github, Bitbucket, Gitlab, VisualStudio.com - https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=ziyasal.vscode-open-in-github
Github Pull Requests - https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=GitHub.vscode-pull-request-github
Git Extension Pack - https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=donjayamanne.git-extension-pack
Git Lens - https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=eamodio.gitlens


https://www.jamesqquick.com
https://www.jamesqquick.com/uses/ (hardware, software, etc.)
https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
https://www.learnbuildteach.com/

Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code!!
https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/

Build a Quiz App with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/

Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/jamesqquick</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N8L6RJ5uZoE</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 15:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to automatically choose a free port in ASP.NET Core 3.0</title>
      <link>https://andrewlock.net/how-to-automatically-choose-a-free-port-in-asp-net-core/</link>
      <description>In this post I show how to tell ASP.NET Core to use a random free port on startup, instead of a static value. I also show how to retrieve the value.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://andrewlock.net/how-to-automatically-choose-a-free-port-in-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 13:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Blazor Bindings - State Management and Data</title>
      <link>https://chrissainty.com/mobile-blazor-bindings-state-management-and-data/</link>
      <description>In this post, I talk about the state management and data options for Mobile Blazor Bindings. I then apply these to a real app to see how they work in practice.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://chrissainty.com/mobile-blazor-bindings-state-management-and-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 09:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NextDNS is my new favourite DNS service</title>
      <link>https://angristan.xyz/2020/04/nextdns/</link>
      <description>AKA Anycast-Pi-hole-as-a-Service... but even better!</description>
      <author> (Stanislas Lange)</author>
      <guid>https://angristan.xyz/2020/04/nextdns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 08:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIP John Conway</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2293/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2293/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 08:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xkcd: RIP John Conway</title>
      <link>https://m.xkcd.com/2293/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://m.xkcd.com/2293/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 08:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Conway</title>
      <link>https://terrytao.wordpress.com/2020/04/12/john-conway/</link>
      <description>I was greatly saddened to learn that John Conway died yesterday from COVID-19, aged 82. My own mathematical areas of expertise are somewhat far from Conway’s; I have played for instance with …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://terrytao.wordpress.com/2020/04/12/john-conway/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 07:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organizational Accounts for ASP .NET Core 3.1</title>
      <link>https://wakeupandcode.com/organizational-accounts-for-asp-net-core-3-1/</link>
      <description>This is the fifteenth of a new series of posts on ASP .NET Core 3.1 for 2020. In this series, we’ll cover 26 topics over a span of 26 weeks from January through June 2020, titled</description>
      <author> (by Shahed C)</author>
      <guid>https://wakeupandcode.com/organizational-accounts-for-asp-net-core-3-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:03:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queuing Background Jobs with Coravel - CodeOpinion</title>
      <link>https://codeopinion.com/queuing-background-jobs-with-coravel/</link>
      <description>In one of my live streams on my YouTube Channel, I took a look at using Coravel to refactor some code that was sending out an email. Emailing is a good example of something that can be created as a background job that frees up your web application to return a result quicker to the …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://codeopinion.com/queuing-background-jobs-with-coravel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQL Server 2017 adds support for Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8 and Ubuntu 18.04</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server/sql-server-2017-adds-support-for-red-hat-enterprise-linux-8-and/ba-p/1303573</link>
      <description>SQL Server team has been adding support for "current" Linux distributions at fast clip last few months. The team announced support for RHEL 8 and Ubuntu 18.04 for SQL Server 2019 over last quarter. The team is happy to announce that SQL Server 2017 has now added support for Red Hat Enterprise Linux ...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/201111)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/sql-server/sql-server-2017-adds-support-for-red-hat-enterprise-linux-8-and/ba-p/1303573</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Code Tired | Simplifying Parameter Null and Other Checks with the Pitcher Library</title>
      <link>https://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Simplifying-Parameter-Null-and-Other-Checks-with-the-Pitcher-Library</link>
      <description>Don't Code Tired - Jason Roberts on Software Development and .NET -</description>
      <author> (Jason)</author>
      <guid>https://dontcodetired.com/blog/post/Simplifying-Parameter-Null-and-Other-Checks-with-the-Pitcher-Library</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing a New Interactive Element: In-Game Purchases (Includes Random Items)</title>
      <link>https://www.esrb.org/blog/in-game-purchases-includes-random-items/</link>
      <description>To help inform consumers of what's offered in a game the ESRB will now begin assigning a new Interactive Element: In-Game Purchases (Includes Random Items).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.esrb.org/blog/in-game-purchases-includes-random-items/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Introduction to GraphQL: Subscriptions</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/introduction-to-graphql-subscriptions</link>
      <description>GraphQL subscription aims to help you build real-time functionality into your apps, while still allowing only the data you need to be returned from live events.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/introduction-to-graphql-subscriptions</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring your own machine to Visual Studio Online | Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/bring-your-own-machine-to-visual-studio-online/</link>
      <description>Leverage your own environments for anywhere access with our self-hosted improvements in Visual Studio Online.</description>
      <author> (Allison Buchholtz-AuProgram Manager II, Visual Studio OnlineFollow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/bring-your-own-machine-to-visual-studio-online/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try gh, GitHub's new CLI</title>
      <link>https://johnpapa.net/try-githubs-new-cli-gh/</link>
      <description>Try the new gh CLI. It's GitHub on the command line, and it’s now available in beta.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://johnpapa.net/try-githubs-new-cli-gh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters Weekly 159 -  Managing Database Migrations</title>
      <link>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/04/monsters-weekly/ep159/</link>
      <description>When dealing with changes to a database schema, it’s important to manage those changes in a way that is repeatable across your team and various environments. Watch as Simon and James us DbUp to add da</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aspnetmonsters.com/2020/04/monsters-weekly/ep159/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typing functions in TypeScript</title>
      <link>https://2ality.com/2020/04/typing-functions-typescript.html</link>
      <description>This blog post explores static typing for functions in TypeScript.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://2ality.com/2020/04/typing-functions-typescript.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Google Book: Building Secure and Reliable Systems - High Scalability - </title>
      <link>http://highscalability.com/blog/2020/4/9/free-google-book-building-secure-and-reliable-systems.html</link>
      <description> 
  

 Google added another book into their excellent SRE series: Building Secure and Reliable Syst...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://highscalability.com/blog/2020/4/9/free-google-book-building-secure-and-reliable-systems.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: Let’s Build a Financial Dashboard with React</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/webinar-build-a-financial-dashboard-react</link>
      <description>We’re running a live, 45-minute webinar on building financial dashboards. Here’s what we’ll cover.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/webinar-build-a-financial-dashboard-react</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.6.0 Release Notes · The Zig Programming Language</title>
      <link>https://ziglang.org/download/0.6.0/release-notes.html</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ziglang.org/download/0.6.0/release-notes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Certificates from Azure Key Vault in ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2020/04/09/using-certificates-from-azure-key-vault-in-asp-net-core/</link>
      <description>This post shows how you can create and use X509 certificates in Azure Key Vault. The certificates are created using Azure CLI and are used inside an ASP.NET Core application. Code: StsServerIdentit…</description>
      <author> (April 9, 2020 ·							by damienbod ·							in .NET Core, Azure, Web														· 1 Comment)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2020/04/09/using-certificates-from-azure-key-vault-in-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document Your Pain - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/sysadmin/devops/document-your-pain/</link>
      <description>In this article, Grant Fritchey explains how leaving the database out of DevOps hurts you and your organization and why you should document the pain it causes.</description>
      <author> (Grant Fritchey)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/sysadmin/devops/document-your-pain/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Data Dive with Kusto for Azure Data Explorer and Log Analytics</title>
      <link>https://blog.jeremylikness.com/blog/kusto-azure-data-explorer-log-analytics/</link>
      <description>Kusto is a service for storing and analyzing big data. It uses a unique syntax to analyze data. This post walks through how to craft a Kusto query by using Azure Data Explorer to analyze telemetry captured in Log Analytics from Application Insights.</description>
      <author> (Empowering developers to be their best.📅 Apr 10, 2020
🕘 8 min read
💬 1557 words)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jeremylikness.com/blog/kusto-azure-data-explorer-log-analytics/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 04:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Corbyn Labour officials worked to lose general election to oust leader, leaked dossier finds</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/labour-leak-report-corbyn-election-whatsapp-antisemitism-tories-yougov-poll-a9462456.html</link>
      <description>Call for investigation into ‘possible misuse of funds’ by senior officials on party’s right wing</description>
      <author> (Jon Stone
    
    
      Policy Correspondent
    
    
    
    
    
      @joncstone)</author>
      <guid>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/labour-leak-report-corbyn-election-whatsapp-antisemitism-tories-yougov-poll-a9462456.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 04:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TurboPower Software Company</title>
      <link>http://www.turbopower.com/</link>
      <description>We're sorry to say that TurboPower Software Company closed its 
              retail business on January 7, 2003. We would like to express our 
              sincere appreciation to our customers and the software development 
              community that supported us so well for nearly 18 years.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.turbopower.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 04:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rename files in linux / bash using mv command without typing the full name two times</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/premek/6e70446cfc913d3c929d7cdbfe896fef</link>
      <description>Rename files in linux / bash using mv command without typing the full name two times - mv.sh</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/premek/6e70446cfc913d3c929d7cdbfe896fef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 04:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://malleable.systems/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://malleable.systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 04:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Alba for Integration Testing ASP.Net Core Web Services</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2020/04/13/using-alba-for-integration-testing-asp-net-core-web-services/</link>
      <description>There’s a video of David Giard and I talking about Alba at CodeMash a couple years ago on YouTube if you’re interested. Alba is a helper library for doing automated testing against ASP.…</description>
      <author> (by jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2020/04/13/using-alba-for-integration-testing-asp-net-core-web-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 04:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>File transfer app with Blazor: Introduction - Mircea Oprea</title>
      <link>https://mirceaoprea.net/blog/file-transfer-app-with-blazor-introduction/</link>
      <description>This series will show you how to build a file sharing web application with ASP.NET Core 3.1 (using Blazor) and hosting it on AWS. The application will allow users to upload a file, their email address and a friend’s or colleague’s email address, and deliver the file to the desired person. The purpose of the …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mirceaoprea.net/blog/file-transfer-app-with-blazor-introduction/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 23:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>