<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>How to Grow a Micro Startup With Programmatic SEO</title>
      <link>https://marclou.beehiiv.com/p/how-to-grow-a-micro-startup-with-programmatic-seo</link>
      <description>You don&amp;#39;t need an audience or a marketing budget to get visitors. Here&amp;#39;s how to grow a micro startup for free when you&amp;#39;re a solopreneur who loves coding.</description>
      <author> (Marc Lou)</author>
      <guid>https://marclou.beehiiv.com/p/how-to-grow-a-micro-startup-with-programmatic-seo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refurb weekend: Data General/One (and the worst LCD in the world)</title>
      <link>http://oldvcr.blogspot.com/2024/03/refurb-weekend-data-generalone-and.html</link>
      <description>I mentioned earlier that while I prefer specializing in non-x86 laptops, that doesn&amp;#39;t mean I don&amp;#39;t collect interesting or unusual x86 laptop...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://oldvcr.blogspot.com/2024/03/refurb-weekend-data-generalone-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HOWTO] Calculate distance between two points (coordinates) on Microsoft SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://blog.rufer.be/2024/03/31/howto-calculate-distance-between-two-points-coordinates-on-microsoft-sql-server/</link>
      <description>Microsoft SQL Server offers the STDistance method to calculate the shortest distance between two geography points with high accuracy.</description>
      <author> (Published by Marc Rufer)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.rufer.be/2024/03/31/howto-calculate-distance-between-two-points-coordinates-on-microsoft-sql-server/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satisfaction and progress in open-ended work</title>
      <link>https://blog.andymatuschak.org/post/159979927467/satisfaction-and-progress-in-open-ended-work</link>
      <description>When we’re in execution mode, we swim in signs of our progress. A day’s work stands crisply in some endless checklist: four problems solved; three features added; check and check. Am I on track? Did I...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.andymatuschak.org/post/159979927467/satisfaction-and-progress-in-open-ended-work</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview - FontMagic</title>
      <link>https://arayofsunshine.dev/fontmagic/getting-started</link>
      <description>FontMagic is a font (ttf, woff, woff2) processing software that can be used on macOS and Windows platforms.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://arayofsunshine.dev/fontmagic/getting-started</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XD1 Log entries. Begin... &amp;#183; Backups and bitrot</title>
      <link>https://xd1.dev/2024/03/backups-and-bitrot</link>
      <description>Last night I killed my linux installation. It refused to come back to life even after chrooting and reinstalling everything. Something broke irreparably, to the best of my knowledge.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xd1.dev/2024/03/backups-and-bitrot</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental Health in Software Engineering</title>
      <link>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/mental-health-in-software-engineering/</link>
      <description>I want to talk about something we don&amp;#39;t discuss enough in our field: the mental health of software engineers, especially those of us who&amp;#39;ve taken on the</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/vadim.kravcenko.dev)</author>
      <guid>https://vadimkravcenko.com/shorts/mental-health-in-software-engineering/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
      Tips for LLM Pretraining and Evaluating Reward Models
    </title>
      <link>https://sebastianraschka.com/blog/2024/research-papers-in-march-2024.html</link>
      <description>
        It’s another month in AI research, and it’s hard to pick favorites.
      </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sebastianraschka.com/blog/2024/research-papers-in-march-2024.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daylight Saving Time is a perfect test for UI designer</title>
      <link>https://tonsky.me/blog/dst/</link>
      <description>Unique challenges that DST presents for clock/watch designers</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/nikitonsky)</author>
      <guid>https://tonsky.me/blog/dst/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory access patterns and performance | Benjamin Dicken</title>
      <link>https://benjdd.com/posts/memory-access-patterns-and-performance/</link>
      <description>How does a programs memory access pattern and the underlying virtual memory system affect performance?</description>
      <author> (Benjamin Dicken)</author>
      <guid>https://benjdd.com/posts/memory-access-patterns-and-performance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Mode Differentiation is Kind of Like a Lens II</title>
      <link>https://www.philipzucker.com/reverse-mode-differentiation-is-kind-of-like-a-lens-ii/</link>
      <description>Reverse mode automatic differentiation is kind of like a lens. Here is the type for a non-fancy lens</description>
      <author> (philzook58)</author>
      <guid>https://www.philipzucker.com/reverse-mode-differentiation-is-kind-of-like-a-lens-ii/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franklin Pezzuti Dyer</title>
      <link>https://franklin.dyer.me/post/222</link>
      <description>Lately I&amp;#39;ve been continuing my adventures in dependent type theory and computer-verified proofs by working with the Idris language. I&amp;#39;ve really enjoyed using Agda, but I think that Idris has started to appeal to me more because it feels like it strikes nice balance between practicality and more &amp;quot;academic&amp;quot; use cases, e.g. as a proof assistant. But I still consider myself a beginner at all of this stuff, so instead of arguing for the merits of Idris I&amp;#39;d like to talk about a specific interesting problem that I&amp;#39;ve solved recently. (You can find all of the code that I&amp;#39;ve written for this post in this Github repo.)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://franklin.dyer.me/post/222</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceRouter: Hyperscale and Minimal Cost Service Mesh at Meta</title>
      <link>https://www.micahlerner.com/2024/03/28/servicerouter-hyperscale-and-minimal-cost-service-mesh-at-meta.html</link>
      <description>ServiceRouter: Hyperscale and Minimal Cost Service Mesh at Meta</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.micahlerner.com/2024/03/28/servicerouter-hyperscale-and-minimal-cost-service-mesh-at-meta.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining the internals of async-task from the ground up</title>
      <link>https://notgull.net/async-task-explained-part1/</link>
      <description>async-task is one of the most complicated crates in the smol ecosystem. But, fundamentally, it’s just a future on the heap.</description>
      <author> (notgull)</author>
      <guid>https://notgull.net/async-task-explained-part1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a backend database: SQL vs Document vs Columnar</title>
      <link>https://www.thomashansen.me/choosing-backend-database/</link>
      <description>In the evolving landscape of databases, the lines distinguishing one type from another have blurred as features converge. How do you pick the right one for your needs? Here&amp;#39;s a venn diagram showing which features are shared and which are unique.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.thomashansen.me/choosing-backend-database/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xorvoid</title>
      <link>https://xorvoid.com/on_garbage_collection.html</link>
      <description>So, this article is trending on the top of Hacker News. And while I&amp;#39;m pretty ambivalent about it, I&amp;#39;ve decided to
not comment on the parts I think are short-sighted. Instead, its given me motivation to finally write up my feelings on
the issue. I&amp;#39;ve been a systems programmer for a long-time and at this point, and I&amp;#39;m quite sick of the Manual Memory Management vs Garbage Collection flamewars. Let&amp;#39;s elevate the discourse.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xorvoid.com/on_garbage_collection.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutting down the letsblock.it project and its official instance &amp;#183; letsblockit/letsblockit &amp;#183; Discussion #663</title>
      <link>https://github.com/letsblockit/letsblockit/discussions/663</link>
      <description>The letsblock.it project enables users to remove low-quality content and useless nags, to tailor their online experience and focus on what matters. It has been running for more than two years now a...</description>
      <author> (letsblockit)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/letsblockit/letsblockit/discussions/663</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyRGB</title>
      <link>https://susam.net/myrgb.html</link>
      <description>A simple RGB color guessing game.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://susam.net/myrgb.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helix</title>
      <link>https://helix-editor.com/news/release-24-03-highlights/</link>
      <description>A post-modern modal text editor.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://helix-editor.com/news/release-24-03-highlights/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook/Meta class action discovery</title>
      <link>https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/24520332-merged-fb</link>
      <description>FILED   UNDER   SEAL   May   31,   2023   Via   CM/ECF   Re:   Klein   v.   Meta   Platforms,   Inc.,   No.   3:20-cv-08570-JD   (N.D.   Cal.)   Dear   Judge   Donato:   Advertiser   Plaintiffs   (“Advertisers”)   respectfully   request   that   the   Court   find   that   a   prima   facie   case   exists   under   the   crime-fraud   exception   with   respect   to   certain   communications   currently   being   withheld   by   Defendant   Meta   Platforms,   Inc.   (“Facebook”)   as   attorney-client   privileged.   The   communications   at   issue   relate   to   Facebook’s   so-called   In-App   Action   Panel   (“IAAP”)   program,   which   existed   between   June   2016   and   approximately   May   2019.   The   IAAP   program,   launched   at   the   request   of   Mark   Zuckerberg,   used   a   cyberattack   method   called   “SSL   man-in-the-middle”   to   intercept   and   decrypt   Snapchat’s—and   later   YouTube’s   and   Amazon’s—SSL-protected   analytics   traffic   to   inform   Facebook’s   competitive   decisionmaking.   As   described   below,   Facebook’s   IAAP   program   conduct   was   not   merely   anticompetitive,   but   criminal—the   program   violated   18   U.S.C.   &amp;#167;   2511(a)   and   (d),   the   so-called   “Wiretap   Act,”   with   no   applicable   exception.   Facebook’s   attorneys   were   pervasively   involved   in   the   design,   execution,   and   expansion   of   this   program.   On   May   15,   2023,   Advertisers   sent   Facebook   a   nineteen-page   single-spaced   letter   providing   screenshots,   quotations   from   documents,   and   evidentiary   citations   setting   forth   the   company’s   applicable   conduct;   analyzing   that   conduct   under   18   U.S.C.   &amp;#167;   2511,   et   seq.   and   under   the   Ninth   Circuit’s   crime-fraud   test,   see   In   re   Grand   Jury   Investigation,   810   F.3d   1110,   1113   (9th   Cir.   2016);   and   seeking   a   prompt   meet-and-confer.1   Over   the   next   two   weeks,   Advertisers   sent   additional   letters   and   emails.   On   May   31,   the   parties   met   and   conferred   and   reached   impasse.   I.   Facebook’s   IAAP   Program   Targets   Competition   By   Wiretapping   Competitors   On   June   9,   2016,   Mark   Zuckerberg   emailed   three   of   the   company’s   top   executives   a   message   titled   “Snapchat   analytics.”   PX   2255   (PALM-016564834)   at   3.   According   to   Zuckerberg:   Whenever   someone   asks   a   question   about   Snapchat,   the   answer   is   usually   that   because   their   traffic   is   encrypted   we   have   no   analytics   about   them.   .   .   .   Given   how   quickly   they’re   growing,   it   seems   important   to   figure   out   a   new   way   to   get   reliable   analytics   about   them.   Perhaps   we   need   to   do   panels   or   write   custom   software.   You   should   figure   out   how   to   do   this.   Id.   Javier   Olivan,   now   Facebook’s   COO,   promptly   replied,   “fully   agree[ing]   that   this   was   one   of   the   most   important   market   analysis   questions   we   need   to   answer.”   Id.   However,   Olivan   “ha[d]   been   looking   into   this   with   the   onavo   team”   and   the   technology   to   look   inside   Snapchat’s   SSL-   protected   analytics   traffic   “[wa]s   really   complicated,”   likely   “requir[ing]   legal   approval.”   Id.   Five   minutes   later,   Olivan   forwarded   Zuckerberg’s   email   to   Facebook’s   Onavo   team,   asking   for   “out   of   the   box   thinking”   on   a   task   that   “is   really   important.”   Id.   at   2.   Olivan   suggested   potentially   paying   users   to   “let   us   install   a   really   heavy   piece   of   software   (that   could   even   do   man   in   the   middle,   etc.).”   Id.   Later   that   morning,   Onavo   founder   Guy   Rosen   replied:   “we   are   going   to   figure   out   a   plan   for   a   lockdown   effort   during   June   to   bring   a   step   change   to   our   Snapchat   visibility.   This   is   an   opportunity   for   our   team   to   shine.”   Id.   at   1.   Two   days   later,   Olivan   forwarded   the   whole   email   thread   to   then-General   Counsel   Colin   Stretch,   saying   “[w]e   should   move   as   fast   as   possible   on   this   (budget   will   not   be   an   issue   assuming   Colin   greenlights   this   type   of   research   on   the   thread   @   Colin   1   Advertisers   stand   ready   to   provide   full   briefing,   exhibits,   and/or   Advertisers’   letters   to   Facebook   at   the   Court’s   request.   Case   3:20-cv-08570-JD   Document   735   Filed   03/23/24   Page   1   of   5</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/24520332-merged-fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collection Initializer Performance in C# - Get An 87% Boost!</title>
      <link>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/31/collection-initializer-performance-in-c-double-your-performance-with-what/</link>
      <description>Check out these benchmarks measuring collection initializer performance in C#. How the heck did I speed up C# collection initialization by 87%?!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/devleaderca)</author>
      <guid>https://www.devleader.ca/2024/03/31/collection-initializer-performance-in-c-double-your-performance-with-what/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 14:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running OCR against PDFs and images directly in your browser</title>
      <link>https://simonwillison.net/2024/Mar/30/ocr-pdfs-images/</link>
      <description>I attended the Story Discovery At Scale data journalism conference at Stanford this week. One of the perennial hot topics at any journalism conference concerns data extraction: how can we …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://simonwillison.net/2024/Mar/30/ocr-pdfs-images/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 13:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Microcosm of the interactions in Open Source projects</title>
      <link>https://robmensching.com/blog/posts/2024/03/30/a-microcosm-of-the-interactions-in-open-source-projects/</link>
      <description>Originally a thread on Twitter about the xz/liblzma vulnerability, when I finished typing it, I realized I had a real world slice of Open Source interaction that deserved more attention.</description>
      <author> (Rob Mensching)</author>
      <guid>https://robmensching.com/blog/posts/2024/03/30/a-microcosm-of-the-interactions-in-open-source-projects/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 13:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xz/liblzma: Bash-stage Obfuscation Explained</title>
      <link>https://gynvael.coldwind.pl/?lang=en&amp;id=782</link>
      <description>Yesterday Andres Freund emailed oss-security@ informing the community of the discovery of a backdoor in xz/liblzma, which affected OpenSSH server (huge respect for noticing and investigating this). Andres&amp;#39; email is an amazing summary of the whole drama, so I&amp;#39;ll skip that. While admittedly most juicy and interesting part is the obfuscated binary with the backdoor, the part that caught my attention – and what this blogpost is about – is the initial part in bash and the simple-but-clever obfuscation methods used there. Note that this isn&amp;#39;t a full description of what the bash stages do, but rather a write down of how each stage is obfuscated and extracted.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://gynvael.coldwind.pl/?lang=en&amp;id=782</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 08:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>git.tukaani.org - xz.git/summary</title>
      <link>https://git.tukaani.org/?p=xz.git;a%3Dblobdiff;f%3DCMakeLists.txt;h%3Dd2b1af7ab0ab759b6805ced3dff2555e2a4b3f8e;hp%3D76700591059711e3a4da5b45cf58474dac4e12a7;hb%3D328c52da8a2bbb81307644efdb58db2c422d9ba7;hpb%3Deb8ad59e9bab32a8d655796afd39597ea6dcc64d</link>
      <description />
      <author> (Lasse Collin)</author>
      <guid>https://git.tukaani.org/?p=xz.git;a%3Dblobdiff;f%3DCMakeLists.txt;h%3Dd2b1af7ab0ab759b6805ced3dff2555e2a4b3f8e;hp%3D76700591059711e3a4da5b45cf58474dac4e12a7;hb%3D328c52da8a2bbb81307644efdb58db2c422d9ba7;hpb%3Deb8ad59e9bab32a8d655796afd39597ea6dcc64d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 05:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technologist vs spy: the xz backdoor debate</title>
      <link>https://lcamtuf.substack.com/p/technologist-vs-spy-the-xz-backdoor</link>
      <description>Well — we just witnessed one of the most daring infosec capers of my career. Here’s what we know so far: some time ago, an unknown party evidently noticed that liblzma (aka xz) — a relatively obscure open-source compression library — was a dependency of</description>
      <author> (lcamtuf)</author>
      <guid>https://lcamtuf.substack.com/p/technologist-vs-spy-the-xz-backdoor</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 04:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roll-Invert-Unroll: An Easier Way to Replace a Duvet Cover</title>
      <link>https://danverbraganza.com/writings/an-easier-way-to-replace-a-duvet-cover</link>
      <description>This way of putting a cover onto a duvet might save you effort and time!</description>
      <author> (Danver Braganza)</author>
      <guid>https://danverbraganza.com/writings/an-easier-way-to-replace-a-duvet-cover</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 01:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talking Hot Dog gives new meaning to &amp;#39;Ham radio&amp;#39;</title>
      <link>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2024/talking-hot-dog-gives-new-meaning-ham-radio</link>
      <description>...except it was a beef frank. Make your wurst jokes in the comments.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jeffgeerling.com/blog/2024/talking-hot-dog-gives-new-meaning-ham-radio</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on El Salvador</title>
      <link>https://mattlakeman.org/2024/03/30/notes-on-el-salvador/</link>
      <description>In 1995, El Salvador had an intentional homicide rate of 139 per 100,000, the highest in the world and one of the highest rates recorded in modern history. Like all educated middle-class Americans,…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mattlakeman.org/2024/03/30/notes-on-el-salvador/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Fuhrer | Frontend Engineer</title>
      <link>https://adamfuhrer.com/selling-physical-art-online/</link>
      <description>A Toronto-based frontend engineer with a passion for art &amp;amp; creative coding.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://adamfuhrer.com/selling-physical-art-online/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons of a first time founder</title>
      <link>https://nikubaba.com/blog/lessons-of-a-first-time-founder/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nikubaba.com/blog/lessons-of-a-first-time-founder/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The de-nerdification of programming</title>
      <link>https://vivekhaldar.com/articles/the-de-nerdification-of-programming/</link>
      <description>Programming with LLMs, and building systems with LLMs, has completed the long de-nerdification of the field.
The programmers at the dawn of computing were nerds. They had no abstractions. They dealt with raw hardware – switches, circuits, currents. Binary code. Punched cards. Assembly language was a respite.
The next step up were high-level languages like FORTRAN and C. Imagine having mnemonics like FOR and variable declarations, after futzing with assembly.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vivekhaldar.com/articles/the-de-nerdification-of-programming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tell the LLM the business context</title>
      <link>https://jameshfisher.com/2024/03/30/tell-the-llm-the-business-context/</link>
      <description>Employees do better when they have more business context. The same is true of LLMs! To do its best work, the LLM needs to know why it’s being prompted, where its input came from, how its output will be used, and how its output will be judged. Many prompters try to tell the LLM how to achieve some task, but it’s often better to just give it the business context.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jameshfisher.com/2024/03/30/tell-the-llm-the-business-context/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbage Collection for Systems Programmers</title>
      <link>https://bitbashing.io/gc-for-systems-programmers.html</link>
      <description>Yet another programming blog. Thoughts on software and related misadventures.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bitbashing.io/gc-for-systems-programmers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Django: Write-up on optimizing the system check framework - Adam Johnson</title>
      <link>https://adamj.eu/tech/2024/03/23/django-optimizing-system-checks/</link>
      <description>Django’s system check framework provides fantastic protection for configuration mishaps. It’s like a targeted linter that runs when you start Django commands. It takes advantage of runtime setup to inspect the true state rather than infer it from the source.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://adamj.eu/tech/2024/03/23/django-optimizing-system-checks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Reasonable Effectiveness of Using Old Phones as Servers</title>
      <link>https://jarbus.net/blog/phone-server/</link>
      <description>I installed linux on a OnePlus6T. Setup took less than an hour, technical issues included.
Why $90 for 8GB RAM, 128GB storage, 2.8GHz 8-core CPU Linux on the OnePlus 6T is well documented Low power consumption Tiny footprint No additional cables Built-in battery backup WiFi, bluetooth, speaker, screen, etc Negligible environmental impact sans shipping I wanted to play with Linux on ARM I don’t need a dedicated cable to power or connect it.</description>
      <author> (jarbus)</author>
      <guid>https://jarbus.net/blog/phone-server/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My laptop is faster than your Elastic cluster</title>
      <link>https://haybatov.com/blog/saved-searches/</link>
      <description>How well a single laptop can handle a task of an Elastic cluster? Surprisingly well.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://haybatov.com/blog/saved-searches/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say something that will surprise people and be useful</title>
      <link>https://jonpauluritis.com/articles/say-something-that-will-surprise-people-and-be-useful/</link>
      <description>As I understand it, there are just certain things in my life that I can&amp;#39;t stop doing. I&amp;#39;ve been writing in some fashion since I was 12. Writing seems to be an experience that is growing richer and I appear to be improving. There are other things in my life though which follow the same pattern- despite having every reason in the world to stop... I just can&amp;#39;t stop doing.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jonpauluritis.com/articles/say-something-that-will-surprise-people-and-be-useful/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Ideal Libre Computer+Phone</title>
      <link>https://mpeyton.com/posts/my_ideal_libre_computer_phone/</link>
      <description>I have a very clear idea of what my “ideal” computer would be. It would incorporate all of the best aspects of the different computers (including smartphones!) I already use today, into a single machine.
The What First, it would have the form factor of a typical smartphone. This would allow me to carry it everywhere, and use it both one-handed and two-handed. I might even have it be a “hotdog-style foldable” to allow for comfier reading.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mpeyton.com/posts/my_ideal_libre_computer_phone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xz and my thoughts on supply chain attacks against FOSS</title>
      <link>http://blog.duti.me/blog/xz-thoughts/</link>
      <description>Note: These are just an assortment of random thoughts. Don’t expect structure or good / well thought out reasoning.</description>
      <author> (Antonio Cheong)</author>
      <guid>http://blog.duti.me/blog/xz-thoughts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>