<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>A new kind of GridView right in your console: Introducing the early preview of ConsoleGuiTools | PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/introducing-consoleguitools-preview/</link>
      <description>Yes. This is yet another post about GridViews. We love them. You love them. What’s not to like?
If you’re not familiar with Out-GridView, it can be used to interactively view objects as a table allowing sorting and filtering. Many PowerShell users like to use it within a pipeline for interactive selection of objects that get processed later in the pipeline.</description>
      <author> (Tyler LeonhardtSoftware Engineer, PowerShell TeamFollow Tyler)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/introducing-consoleguitools-preview/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 07:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stateful Programming Models in Serverless Functions | QCon San Francisco 2020</title>
      <link>https://qconsf.com/sf2019/presentation/serverless-advantages-patterns-and-challenges</link>
      <description>Most will agree that Serverless is the future of cloud computing. But when most people think of Serverless, they think of FaaS (Functions as a Service), and when they think of FaaS, they think of functions that are ephemeral, stateless, and short-lived. But does this always need to be the case? Is it possible write functions that are stateful and long-running on top of ephemeral, Serverless compute platforms? In this session, we'll explore two stateful programming models: workflows and actors. We'll discuss how they can simplify development and how they enable stateful and long-running application patterns within ephemeral, Serverless compute environments. We'll also explain why we're making a bit bet on these programming models in the Azure Functions service.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://qconsf.com/sf2019/presentation/serverless-advantages-patterns-and-challenges</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 07:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus: The Black Swan of 2020</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/sequoia-capital/coronavirus-the-black-swan-of-2020-7c72bdeb9753</link>
      <description>Here is a note that we sent to Sequoia founders and CEOs today to provide guidance on how to ensure the health of their business while…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@sequoia)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/sequoia-capital/coronavirus-the-black-swan-of-2020-7c72bdeb9753</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 06:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYBP (Maybe You’ve Been Pwned)</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/vrchat/mybp-maybe-youve-been-pwned-30a4809ad5e1</link>
      <description>System’s back, and this time he’s talkin’ about security, HaveIBeenPwned, and how to choose a good password. There’s a tl;dr at the end.</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@curtis_49146)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/vrchat/mybp-maybe-youve-been-pwned-30a4809ad5e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 05:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 in US healthcare: who pays for testing?</title>
      <link>https://politics.stackexchange.com/questions/50624/covid-19-in-us-healthcare-who-pays-for-testing</link>
      <description>If, as a US citizen or resident, I had flu-like symptoms and if I was not covered by Medicaid/Medicare and didn't have health insurance, who would be liable for paying for COVID-19 test diagnostics...</description>
      <author> (Italian Philosophers 4 Monica)</author>
      <guid>https://politics.stackexchange.com/questions/50624/covid-19-in-us-healthcare-who-pays-for-testing</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 05:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Miller | SpeakerHub</title>
      <link>https://speakerhub.com/speaker/adam-miller</link>
      <description>I am an enthusiastic and often animated speaker with a passion for automation and open source.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://speakerhub.com/speaker/adam-miller</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 03:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use PowerShell ISE Mode in Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://www.thomasmaurer.ch/2020/03/how-to-use-powershell-ise-mode-in-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <description>If you are writing PowerShell code, you might have realized that there weren't really improvements to the PowerShell Integrated Scripting Environment (PowerShell ISE) in the last couple of releases. With PowerShell becoming more popular on cross-platform systems, Visual Studio Code (VS Code) becomes the editor of choice. However, by default Visual Studio Code has a</description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://www.thomasmaurer.ch/2020/03/how-to-use-powershell-ise-mode-in-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 03:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Car Ownership is Fair.</title>
      <link>http://fair.com/</link>
      <description>Fair: A new way to shop, get approved and pay for your next car - all on your phone.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://fair.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 03:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade Mount for UniFi AC Pro AP</title>
      <link>https://store.ui.com/products/uap-ac-pro-to-nanohd-upgrade-mount?variant=14489682477145</link>
      <description>The UniFi nanoHD AP RetroFit Mount makes upgrading to the UniFi nanoHD AP quick and convenient. The RetroFit Mount allows you to mount the UniFi nanoHD AP over existing UniFi AP mounting brackets, with no additional tools needed. Available in three-packs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://store.ui.com/products/uap-ac-pro-to-nanohd-upgrade-mount?variant=14489682477145</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 02:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not being an asshole will make you more money</title>
      <link>https://www.atlassquats.com/post/not-being-an-asshole-will-make-you-more-money</link>
      <description>All too often in the course of building my business, I bump into the existence of countless assholes. From dealing with aggressive and manipulative salesmen to investors offering term sheets a monkey wouldn't be dumb enough to sign. It frankly sucks. Sucks hard. I really don't understand why. So many people are straigh</description>
      <author> (Greg)</author>
      <guid>https://www.atlassquats.com/post/not-being-an-asshole-will-make-you-more-money</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 02:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>localghost.io</title>
      <link>http://localghost.io/articles/introducing-assembly-differ-2020-03-06/</link>
      <description>Hi! ever wanted created a dll and nuget package and wanted to get a report of all of the assembly changes? Well now there is a dotnet tool for that!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://localghost.io/articles/introducing-assembly-differ-2020-03-06/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 02:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest mistakes I've made with Lunch Money (so far)</title>
      <link>https://lunchbag.ca/lunch-money-mistakes/</link>
      <description>It's been 6 months since the official launch of Lunch Money and I've been sharing milestones, both big and small. But that's hardly the full picture.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lunchbag.ca/lunch-money-mistakes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 02:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UPS Store National Email Program</title>
      <link>https://www.theupsstore.com/email</link>
      <description>Join The UPS Store email program and enjoy 25% off your next online print purchase.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.theupsstore.com/email</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 01:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARN IT is a direct attack on end-to-end encryption</title>
      <link>https://blog.cryptographyengineering.com/2020/03/06/earn-it-is-an-attack-on-encryption/</link>
      <description>Yesterday a bipartisan group of U.S. Senators introduced a new bill called the EARN IT act. On its face, the bill seems like a bit of inside baseball having to do with legal liability for informati…</description>
      <author> (Matthew Green)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cryptographyengineering.com/2020/03/06/earn-it-is-an-attack-on-encryption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Storage for $2 / TB / Mo</title>
      <link>https://blog.sia.tech/cloud-storage-for-2-tb-mo-8a34043e93bb?gi=8df5c4d18671</link>
      <description>Explore the model that shows why Sia storage will stay below $2/TB/Mo for the long term.</description>
      <author> (https://blog.sia.tech/@davidvorick)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sia.tech/cloud-storage-for-2-tb-mo-8a34043e93bb?gi=8df5c4d18671</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Media Disclosure Statement | TurgenSec</title>
      <link>https://turgensec.com/virgin-media-disclosure-statement/</link>
      <description>This is our statement in response to the two most common questions sent to us by journalists following our disclosure to Virgin Media of a breach on 28th of February. This included personal information corresponding to approximately nine hundred thousand UK residents.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://turgensec.com/virgin-media-disclosure-statement/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 23:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The beautiful machine</title>
      <link>http://fabiensanglard.net/the_beautiful_machine/index.html</link>
      <description>March 6, 2020</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://fabiensanglard.net/the_beautiful_machine/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 23:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zip Files: History, Explanation and Implementation</title>
      <link>https://www.hanshq.net/zip.html</link>
      <description>I have been curious about data compression and the Zip file format in particular for a long time. At some point I decided to address that by learning how it works and writing my own Zip program. The implementation turned into an exciting programming exercise; there is great pleasure to be had from creating a well oiled machine that takes data apart, jumbles its bits into a more efficient representation, and puts it all back together again. Hopefully it is interesting to read about too.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanshq.net/zip.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 22:38:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Media breach 'linked customers to porn'</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-51768577</link>
      <description>Researchers say a breached Virgin Media database contained more details than the company suggested.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/bbcnews)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-51768577</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 22:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zynga faces class action suit over massive Words With Friends hack</title>
      <link>https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2020/03/05/zynga-faces-class-action-suit-over-massive-words-with-friends-hack/</link>
      <description>It’s charging subpar password security and lousy user notification: Zynga has yet to notify users to warn them of the breach, the suit says.</description>
      <author> (by
			Lisa Vaas)</author>
      <guid>https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2020/03/05/zynga-faces-class-action-suit-over-massive-words-with-friends-hack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 22:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Variables: var and let and const</title>
      <link>https://www.prestonlamb.com/blog/javascript-variables-var-and-let-and-const</link>
      <description>There are three ways to create variables in a JavaScript application: using var, using let, or using const. This will not be a post trying to convince you which one you should use, or arguing about what is best. It’s just good to know about the differences and what it means when you use the different options.</description>
      <author> (Preston Lamb)</author>
      <guid>https://www.prestonlamb.com/blog/javascript-variables-var-and-let-and-const</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 21:31:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caffeine Boosts Problem-Solving Ability  but Not Creativity, Study Indicates</title>
      <link>https://news.uark.edu/articles/52447/caffeine-boosts-problem-solving-ability-but-not-creativity-study-indicates</link>
      <description>While the drug is known to increase focus, alertness and motor skills, its effect on creative thinking had not been studied previously.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://news.uark.edu/articles/52447/caffeine-boosts-problem-solving-ability-but-not-creativity-study-indicates</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 21:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>renderman (RenderMan) | Keybase</title>
      <link>https://keybase.io/renderman</link>
      <description>renderman (RenderMan) is now on Keybase, an open source app for encryption and cryptography.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://keybase.io/renderman</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 21:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build apps for free with Azure Cosmos DB Free Tier | Azure Cosmos DB Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/build-apps-for-free-with-azure-cosmos-db-free-tier/</link>
      <description>This blog post was co-authored by Nikisha Reyes-Grange, Senior Product Marketing Manager, Azure Marketing.
Introducing Azure Cosmos DB Free Tier
Looking to build a new app, develop and test, or run small production workloads with Azure Cosmos DB? Our new Free Tier makes it easy to get started with no cost and save money as you build and grow new apps.</description>
      <author> (Deborah ChenProgram Manager, Azure Cosmos DBFollow Deborah)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/build-apps-for-free-with-azure-cosmos-db-free-tier/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 20:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home | Jovica Turčinović</title>
      <link>https://www.turcinovic.com/</link>
      <description>Hi, I am Jovica. I have been engaged in software design since 1993. I am an experienced Microsoft .NET Developer in:
- .NET programming language, SQL (SQL Server, MySql, DAL), Knockout JS, Umbraco CMS, EPiServer CMS, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), Software Architecture, Software Design Patterns, Software Testing, Project Organization</description>
      <author> (Jovica Turčinović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.turcinovic.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 19:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As we work to protect public health, we also need to protect the income of hourly workers who support our campus - Microsoft on the Issues</title>
      <link>https://blogs.microsoft.com/on-the-issues/2020/03/05/covid-19-microsoft-hourly-workers/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has asked its employees who can work from home to do so due to the impact of COVID-19. Despite this meaning a reduced need for many of the hourly workers vital to our daily operations, we’ve decided that Microsoft will continue to pay their regular pay during this period. We hope other large companies will take a similar approach to counteract the economic effect COVID-19 will have on hourly workers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.microsoft.com/on-the-issues/2020/03/05/covid-19-microsoft-hourly-workers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 18:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is Facebook's mysterious "Lan Tim 2"?</title>
      <link>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2020/03/who-is-facebooks-mysterious-lan-tim-2/</link>
      <description>Facebook has an interesting feature. It will let you see which companies have associated your off-Facebook activity with your Facebook account. If you visit: you’ll see what companies are sni…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2020/03/who-is-facebooks-mysterious-lan-tim-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLIDE : In Defense of Smart Algorithms over Hardware Acceleration for Large-Scale Deep Learning Systems</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/1903.03129</link>
      <description>Deep Learning (DL) algorithms are the central focus of modern machine
learning systems. As data volumes keep growing, it has become customary to
train large neural networks with hundreds of millions of parameters to maintain
enough capacity to memorize these volumes and obtain state-of-the-art accuracy.
To get around the costly computations associated with large models and data,
the community is increasingly investing in specialized hardware for model
training. However, specialized hardware is expensive and hard to generalize to
a multitude of tasks. The progress on the algorithmic front has failed to
demonstrate a direct advantage over powerful hardware such as NVIDIA-V100 GPUs.
This paper provides an exception. We propose SLIDE (Sub-LInear Deep learning
Engine) that uniquely blends smart randomized algorithms, with multi-core
parallelism and workload optimization. Using just a CPU, SLIDE drastically
reduces the computations during both training and inference outperforming an
optimized implementation of Tensorflow (TF) on the best available GPU. Our
evaluations on industry-scale recommendation datasets, with large fully
connected architectures, show that training with SLIDE on a 44 core CPU is more
than 3.5 times (1 hour vs. 3.5 hours) faster than the same network trained
using TF on Tesla V100 at any given accuracy level. On the same CPU hardware,
SLIDE is over 10x faster than TF. We provide codes and scripts for
reproducibility.</description>
      <author> (Authors:Beidi Chen, Tharun Medini, James Farwell, Sameh Gobriel, Charlie Tai, Anshumali Shrivastava)</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/1903.03129</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My New Role as Senior Program Manager for .NET Data</title>
      <link>https://blog.jeremylikness.com/blog/new-role-dotnet-data-pm/</link>
      <description>I recently accepted a new role at Microsoft as Senior Program Manager for .NET Data. This post explains the history behind the decision, what I'll be doing and how you can help.</description>
      <author> (Empowering developers to be their best.📅 Mar 6, 2020
🕘 5 min read
💬 898 words)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jeremylikness.com/blog/new-role-dotnet-data-pm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuckDuckGo is good enough for regular use | www.bitlog.com</title>
      <link>https://www.bitlog.com/2020/03/06/duckduckgo-is-good-enough-for-regular-use/</link>
      <description>I haven't tried a new search engine since I tried Bing in 2009. It was time to find out how good DuckDuckGo is in 2020. What was the biggest difference that I found?</description>
      <author> (by jakevoytko)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bitlog.com/2020/03/06/duckduckgo-is-good-enough-for-regular-use/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>piCorePlayer</title>
      <link>https://www.picoreplayer.org/</link>
      <description>pCP is a high quality audio player via Squeezelite. The use of a DAC will greatly improve sound quality (up to to 384 kHz /24 bit). The player can be controlled via touch screen, phone, tablet, iPad, computer or IR/USB remote control. If you add more players you can enjoy a advanced multi-room audio system that can play in sync or play different streams in separate zones.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.picoreplayer.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mopidy</title>
      <link>https://mopidy.com/</link>
      <description>The extensible music server</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mopidy.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Odyssey of Stark and Melody</title>
      <link>https://xoofx.com/blog/2020/03/05/stark-melody-dotnet-sel4/</link>
      <description>What would it take these days to build a prototype of a new language and operating system built on top of it, just for fun? This idea started to emerge during the 2018 winter holidays:...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xoofx.com/blog/2020/03/05/stark-melody-dotnet-sel4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stark - Language And Frontend Compiler - Prototype 2019</title>
      <link>https://xoofx.com/blog/2020/03/06/stark-language-frontend-compiler/</link>
      <description>This is the first part of the blog post series about The Odyssey of Stark and Melody and more specifically, about the development of the syntax of the Stark language and its front-end compiler, based...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xoofx.com/blog/2020/03/06/stark-language-frontend-compiler/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>