<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>This is the Skill you NEED as a software engineer</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sFKTYi6aLIE</link>
      <description>💌 Free Developer Insights: https://guiferreira.me/newsletter

#softwareengineering</description>
      <author> (Gui Ferreira)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=sFKTYi6aLIE</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean Architecture With .NET 9 and CQRS - Project Setup + FREE template</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=VKc88NWf4lw</link>
      <description>Get the CA template for free: https://dub.sh/ca-setup
Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Get the source code here: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic



Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=VKc88NWf4lw</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - koreader/koreader: An ebook reader application supporting PDF, DjVu, EPUB, FB2 and many more formats, running on Cervantes, Kindle, Kobo, PocketBook and Android devices</title>
      <link>https://github.com/koreader/koreader</link>
      <description>An ebook reader application supporting PDF, DjVu, EPUB, FB2 and many more formats, running on Cervantes, Kindle, Kobo, PocketBook and Android devices - koreader/koreader</description>
      <guid>https://github.com/koreader/koreader</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apps lighter than a React button</title>
      <link>https://nuejs.org/blog/large-scale-apps/</link>
      <description>Nue is HTML, CSS, and JavaScript taken to their absolute peak.</description>
      <guid>https://nuejs.org/blog/large-scale-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Vertical Slice Architecture, Not Layers!</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=o82JG0fY_oY</link>
      <description>Happy April!
Subscribe to my weekly newsletter: https://nickchapsas.com

Become a Patreon and get special perks: https://www.patreon.com/nickchapsas

Hello, everybody. I'm Nick, and in this video, I will show you how to create the best Vertical Slices. Vertical Slices are much better than Clean Architecture, because with vertical slices, there is nothing to clean. You're welcom

Workshops: https://bit.ly/nickworkshops

Don't forget to comment, like and subscribe :)

Social Media:
Follow me on GitHub: https://github.com/Elfocrash
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/nickchapsas
Connect on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick-chapsas

#csharp #dotnet</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=o82JG0fY_oY</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Optimization Guide</title>
      <link>https://goperf.dev/</link>
      <description>Patterns and Techniques for Writing High-Performance Applications with Go</description>
      <guid>https://goperf.dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 08:01:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-04-01-final-final-FINAL-V2.go</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=UjrtJgzwJzU</link>
      <description>Some very important news on the future of the show in this episode. You'll get answers to important questions like:

  What does the future of the show look like? Who are the next, big ticket, guests? What's a SegFault? Why does my knee hurt? Why do fools fall in love? Does this look infected to you?  Any many more. So definitely make a point of listening to this episode... all the way to the end, too.

 There's no transcription for this episode, as it's all breaking news and I didn't have the time to get one completed before the time of release.

 Show Notes Welcome friends to The Modern .NET Show; the premier .NET podcast, focusing entirely on the knowledge, tools, and frameworks that all .NET developers should have in their toolbox. We are the go-to podcast for .NET developers worldwide, and I am your host: Jamie "GaProgMan" Taylor.

 In this episode, I'll talk you through a slight change of direction for the show. But more on that in a moment. Let's listen to the intro music for a little longer before I wrap up this intro.

 Anyway, without further ado, let's sit back, open up a terminal, type in `go mod init github.com/golang-show` and we'll dive into...

 Supporting the Show If you find this episode useful in any way, please consider supporting the show by either leaving a review (check our review page for ways to do that), sharing the episode with a friend or colleague, buying the host a coffee, or considering becoming a Patron of the show.

 Full Show Notes There are no full show notes for this episode, friends. I'm sorry for that, but it's the nature of the game when you're releasing breaking news.

 I'll try and get a transcription completed in the next few days, so watch out for that.

 Music Used In This Episode This contains some copyright free music during the interstitials. Each of the pieces of music (linked below) were created by some incredibly highly skilled invididuals. If you liked the music we used, check out links to the them below:

  "Ascend (sped up)" by Alex-Productions "Golden" by HoobeZa "Mellow" by HoobeZa  Supporting the show:  Leave a rating or review Buy the show a coffee Become a patron  Getting in Touch:  Via the contact page Joining the Discord  Remember to rate and review the show on  Apple Podcasts, Podchaser, or wherever you find your podcasts, this will help the show's audience grow. Or you can just share the show with a friend.

 And don't forget to reach out via our Contact page. We're very interested in your opinion of the show, so please get in touch.

 You can support the show by making a monthly donation on the show's Patreon page at: https://www.patreon.com/TheDotNetCorePodcast.

 Music created by Mono Memory Music, licensed to RJJ Software for use in The Modern .NET Show</description>
      <author> (Jamie Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=UjrtJgzwJzU</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 08:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the hell out of the LLM as soon as possible | sgnt.ai</title>
      <link>https://sgnt.ai/p/hell-out-of-llms/</link>
      <description>Don’t let an LLM make decisions or implement business logic: they suck at that.</description>
      <guid>https://sgnt.ai/p/hell-out-of-llms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 07:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orogeny</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/3070/</link>
      <description></description>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/3070/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 03:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-4o draws itself as a consistent type of guy</title>
      <link>https://newsletter.danielpaleka.com/p/gpt-4o-draws-itself-as-a-consistent</link>
      <description>When asked to draw itself as a person, the ChatGPT Create Image feature introduced on March 25, 2025, consistently portrays itself as a white male in his 20s with brown hair, often sporting facial hair and glasses.</description>
      <guid>https://newsletter.danielpaleka.com/p/gpt-4o-draws-itself-as-a-consistent</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work is Life Too | Himanshu Mishra (@OrkoHunter)</title>
      <link>https://orkohunter.net/blog/work-is-life-too/</link>
      <description>Personal website and blog of Himanshu Mishra (@OrkoHunter)</description>
      <guid>https://orkohunter.net/blog/work-is-life-too/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Attacks on Naive Tree Hashes</title>
      <link>https://jacko.io/tree_hashing.html</link>
      <description>If you're building a tree hash,​also known as a Merkle tree and you want it to have the same
security properties as a cryptographic hash like SHA-3 or BLAKE3, there are a
couple of "attacks" you need to know about. Here's a naive recursive tree hash
based on SHA-3 in Python, which turns out to be vulnerable to these
attacks:​Dividing the length by 2 at each level of the tree like this is a
shortcut, but the resulting tree structure isn't great, because we have to
know the final input length to figure out where any of the leaf or subtree
boundaries are. That's no problem in these examples, but in practice most
hash functions need to be able to "stream" long inputs in a loop
without knowing the final length until the end. A better splitting rule for
real tree hashes is to make the left side as large as possible as long as
it's a power-of-2. See the BLAKE3 paper, particularly sections 2.1 and
5.1.2, and also Binary Numeral Trees.</description>
      <guid>https://jacko.io/tree_hashing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader self-awareness. Learn 5 tips and 2 tools (FRIS®, RMP) to support leader development.</title>
      <link>https://trojanczyk.eu/leader-self-awareness/</link>
      <description>Learn practical tips and tools (FRIS®, RMP) to support leader development. Leader self-awareness is your key to effective leadership and a cohesive team.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/adam.trojanczyk)</author>
      <guid>https://trojanczyk.eu/leader-self-awareness/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving 18 years of comments out of Disqus and into my 11ty static site :: Sacha Chua</title>
      <link>https://sachachua.com/blog/2025/03/moving-18-years-of-comments-out-of-disqus-and-into-my-11ty-static-site/</link>
      <description>One challenge: there are a lot of comments. How
many? I got curious about analyzing the XML, and
then of course I wanted to do that from Emacs. I
used pipx install yq to install yq so that I
could use the xq tool to query the XML, much like
jq works.</description>
      <guid>https://sachachua.com/blog/2025/03/moving-18-years-of-comments-out-of-disqus-and-into-my-11ty-static-site/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Checks™: Release Without Fear</title>
      <link>https://blog.jacobstechtavern.com/p/release-without-fear</link>
      <description>My novel release strategies for app startups</description>
      <guid>https://blog.jacobstechtavern.com/p/release-without-fear</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future Favors the Curious » Mike Industries</title>
      <link>https://mikeindustries.com/blog/archive/2025/03/the-future-favors-the-curious</link>
      <description>If you’re a designer in the market for a job right now, you probably feel behind the AI wave already, and you’re wondering if the skills you’ve honed in your career are even useful anymore. One of the benefits of …</description>
      <guid>https://mikeindustries.com/blog/archive/2025/03/the-future-favors-the-curious</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunsetting openSNP - a personal retrospective</title>
      <link>https://tzovar.as/sunsetting-opensnp/</link>
      <description>As this blog post is being published, we are sending out emails to all openSNP users with some news: OpenSNP will be turned off – and with that also delete all the data stored on it – on April 30, 2025. Given that the project has been part of my...</description>
      <guid>https://tzovar.as/sunsetting-opensnp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpacking Dijkstra’s Note on “Why Numbering Should Start at Zero”</title>
      <link>https://fabiendubosson.com/blog/unpacking-dijkstra-note-on-why-numbering-should-start-at-zero/</link>
      <description>Edsger W. Dijkstra wrote a famous note titled “Why numbering should start at zero” This three-page handwritten document is often cited in discussions about why indexing in programming languages should start at zero. While his reasoning is relatively straightforward, the document lacks the structure and examples needed to fully grasp it—at least for me—without resorting to pen and paper. As a result, I decided to read it thoroughly and unpack his reasoning into explicit arguments, expressed in my own words and illustrated with examples.</description>
      <guid>https://fabiendubosson.com/blog/unpacking-dijkstra-note-on-why-numbering-should-start-at-zero/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIND9 as fully recursive resolver in 2025</title>
      <link>https://szafka.net/blog/bind9-as-resolver.html</link>
      <description>Recently, we have been engaged in consulting work and providing DNS training for
a major IT corporation, boasting an employee count exceeding 10,000.
Thankfully, not every staff member attended the course.</description>
      <guid>https://szafka.net/blog/bind9-as-resolver.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forty-Seven </title>
      <link>https://nazhamid.com/journal/forty-seven/</link>
      <description>I turned another year older.</description>
      <guid>https://nazhamid.com/journal/forty-seven/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garmin Connect+ and the Beginning of the End</title>
      <link>https://boehs.org/node/garmin-connect-plus</link>
      <description>Oh how the mighty have fallen</description>
      <guid>https://boehs.org/node/garmin-connect-plus</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Best Sleep Tracker</title>
      <link>https://karpathy.bearblog.dev/finding-the-best-sleep-tracker/</link>
      <description>Finding the best sleep tracker with data</description>
      <guid>https://karpathy.bearblog.dev/finding-the-best-sleep-tracker/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm Leaving Sentry</title>
      <link>https://lucumr.pocoo.org/2025/3/31/leaving/</link>
      <description>Endings and new beginnings.</description>
      <guid>https://lucumr.pocoo.org/2025/3/31/leaving/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Made My Credit Cardholder Discounts Searchable</title>
      <link>https://danverbraganza.com/writings/credit-card-discounts-searchable</link>
      <description>How I gather my credit card offers in one place so I don't miss out</description>
      <guid>https://danverbraganza.com/writings/credit-card-discounts-searchable</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your Own Linter</title>
      <link>https://lukasschwab.me/blog/gen/bring-your-own-linter.html</link>
      <description>This is a practical guide for integrating a custom linter into your
Go project.</description>
      <guid>https://lukasschwab.me/blog/gen/bring-your-own-linter.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:03:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web’s biggest problem. Introduction to Web 1.1 – Reinventing the Web</title>
      <link>https://reinventingtheweb.com/2025/03/02/webs-biggest-problem/</link>
      <description>The World Wide Web started as a web of documents. That was back in the early ’90s. Web pages were static HTML documents—simple, read-only pages that just presented information. There was no interactivity. Then, in 1995, JavaScript was added to browsers, changing everything.</description>
      <guid>https://reinventingtheweb.com/2025/03/02/webs-biggest-problem/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to simplify nested SQL in applications with esProc</title>
      <link>https://c.esproc.com/article/1742979889140?p=1&amp;m=0</link>
      <description>In data analysis or reporting applications, various complex SQL statements are sometimes encount ..</description>
      <guid>https://c.esproc.com/article/1742979889140?p=1&amp;m=0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fix the Missing Custom Models bug</title>
      <link>https://www.lucasaguiar.xyz/posts/fix-custom-models-open-webui/</link>
      <description>This is a quick fix to a problem I experienced with Open WebUI, which was that custom models were not showing in the models list. There was nothing in the documentation or in the issues pointing to a solution. I decided to open a new issue 4 days ago and today the user @dcolley gave the missing information and it worked.
For some reason, custom models are not working when you use Direct Connections.</description>
      <guid>https://www.lucasaguiar.xyz/posts/fix-custom-models-open-webui/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Silica Gel Took Over the World</title>
      <link>https://www.scopeofwork.net/silica-gel/</link>
      <description>Silica gel packets seem like the only thing keeping our packaged food crispy and our belongings free of mildew. How on earth did they all get here?</description>
      <guid>https://www.scopeofwork.net/silica-gel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I thought I'd never get addicted to my phone but here I am</title>
      <link>https://shub.club/writings/phone-addiction/</link>
      <description>I hate reels</description>
      <guid>https://shub.club/writings/phone-addiction/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Binary Distribution Rebuilds – Simon Josefsson's blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.josefsson.org/2025/03/31/on-binary-distribution-rebuilds/</link>
      <description>I rebuilt (the top-50 popcon) Debian and Ubuntu packages, on amd and arm64, and compared the results a couple of months ago. Since then the Reproduce.Debian.net effort has been launched. Unlike my small experiment, that effort is a full-scale rebuild with more architectures. Their goal is to reproduce what is published in the Debian archive.</description>
      <guid>https://blog.josefsson.org/2025/03/31/on-binary-distribution-rebuilds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you want to browse the internet, you must first invent the universe</title>
      <link>https://ashutoshbsathe.github.io/blog/internet-universe/</link>
      <description>An unnecessarily detailed description of what happens every time you google something</description>
      <guid>https://ashutoshbsathe.github.io/blog/internet-universe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fall of the Open Source Initiative (OSI): The OSI Election is Rigged, Biased Against People Who Oppose the Openwashing of GPL-Violating Bots Operated by Microsoft for Profit (OSI Gets Paid to Promote This)</title>
      <link>https://techrights.org/n/2025/03/10/The_Fall_of_the_Open_Source_Initiative_OSI_The_OSI_Election_is_.shtml</link>
      <description>they reckon that pretence of calm would serve them best, helped by puff pieces</description>
      <guid>https://techrights.org/n/2025/03/10/The_Fall_of_the_Open_Source_Initiative_OSI_The_OSI_Election_is_.shtml</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets Work Exponentially</title>
      <link>https://www.allenleee.com/blog/secret</link>
      <description>Known vs Unknown</description>
      <guid>https://www.allenleee.com/blog/secret</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dipping my toes in OpenBSD, in Amsterdam</title>
      <link>https://ewintr.nl/posts/2025/dipping-my-toes-in-openbsd-in-amsterdam/</link>
      <description>Sometimes the water is cold at first.</description>
      <guid>https://ewintr.nl/posts/2025/dipping-my-toes-in-openbsd-in-amsterdam/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapping ranking models with an LLM judge - Emir's blog</title>
      <link>https://emiruz.com/post/2025-03-30-bootstrap-ranking-llm-judge/</link>
      <description>I use 500 Hacker News (HN) titles and an LLM to derive an article ranking
model from a user supplied preference description. The LLM supplies the
labelled data, whilst Ridge regression and cheap sentence transformer
embedding provides the features. The surrogate has 0.74 Spearman correlation
with the LLM labels, which is remarkable given that the experiment is entirely
unoptimised.</description>
      <guid>https://emiruz.com/post/2025-03-30-bootstrap-ranking-llm-judge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emjay - implementing function calls</title>
      <link>https://andreabergia.com/blog/2025/03/emjay-implementing-function-calls/</link>
      <description>In this post, I am following up on the explanation of my simple JIT compiler glorified calculator Emjay and I will show you how I implemented function calls.
Why the complexity? Link to heading Imagine we are JIT-compiling the following program:</description>
      <guid>https://andreabergia.com/blog/2025/03/emjay-implementing-function-calls/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop syncing everything</title>
      <link>https://sqlsync.dev/posts/stop-syncing-everything/</link>
      <description>Discover Graft, an open-source transactional storage engine built to solve the challenges of syncing data at the edge. Inspired by lessons from SQLSync, Graft enables lazy, partial, and strongly consistent replication—allowing edge applications to sync only the data they need, exactly when they need it.</description>
      <guid>https://sqlsync.dev/posts/stop-syncing-everything/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a search engine from scratch, in Rust: introduction</title>
      <link>https://jdrouet.github.io/posts/202503161800-search-engine-intro/</link>
      <description>Or how to build a secure, blazingly fast search engine that works everywhere, from your browser to your phone, without compromising on features or performance.</description>
      <guid>https://jdrouet.github.io/posts/202503161800-search-engine-intro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honey has now lost 4 million Chrome users after shady tactics were revealed</title>
      <link>https://9to5google.com/2025/03/31/honey-extension-users-dropped-chrome-march-2025/</link>
      <description>After being exposed for shady tactics in late 2024, Honey has now lost over 4 million users from its peak numbers.</description>
      <guid>https://9to5google.com/2025/03/31/honey-extension-users-dropped-chrome-march-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 22:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s White Stuff Growing on Your Cheese That Isn’t Mold</title>
      <link>https://www.thephcheese.com/theres-white-stuff-growing-on-your-cheese-that-isnt-mold</link>
      <description>Two weeks ago, one of my best friends and ex-cheese comrades, Chelsea, brought our old mentor/boss-lady, the illustrious Kim Martin, into the shop. Neither of them had visited us before, and it was…</description>
      <guid>https://www.thephcheese.com/theres-white-stuff-growing-on-your-cheese-that-isnt-mold</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 21:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sergey's Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.sergey.fyi/articles/reliability-vs-capability</link>
      <description>Sergey Filimonov's blog</description>
      <guid>https://www.sergey.fyi/articles/reliability-vs-capability</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 21:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There is no Vibe Engineering</title>
      <link>https://serce.me/posts/2025-31-03-there-is-no-vibe-engineering</link>
      <description>This article explores the relationship between vibe coding and software engineering.</description>
      <guid>https://serce.me/posts/2025-31-03-there-is-no-vibe-engineering</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee and Open Source Conversation - Dennis Doomen</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=J__ByENjFs4</link>
      <description>Dennis is a Microsoft MVP and Principal Consultant at Dutch Microsoft consultancy firm Aviva Solutions. With 27 years of experience under his belt as a software architect and/or lead developer, he specializes in designing full-stack enterprise solutions based on .NET as well as providing coaching on all aspects of designing, building, documenting, deploying and maintaining software systems in an agile world. He is the author of Fluent Assertions, an assertion library to make your unit tests look great, Liquid Projections, a set of libraries for building Event Sourcing projections and he has been maintaining coding guidelines for C# since 2001. You can find him on Twitter, Mastodon and BlueSky.

You can follow Dennis on Social Media
https://bsky.app/profile/dennisdoomen.com
https://x.com/ddoomen
https://www.linkedin.com/in/dennisdoomen
https://github.com/dennisdoomen
https://www.dennisdoomen.com/

PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO THE PODCAST

- Spotify: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-spotify
- Apple Podcasts: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-apple
- Google Podcasts: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-google
- RSS: http://isaacl.dev/podcast-rss

You can check out more episodes of Coffee and Open Source on https://www.coffeeandopensource.com

Coffee and Open Source is hosted by Isaac Levin (https://twitter.com/isaacrlevin)</description>
      <author> (Isaac Levin)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=J__ByENjFs4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle attempt to hide serious cybersecurity incident from customers in Oracle SaaS service</title>
      <link>https://doublepulsar.com/oracle-attempt-to-hide-serious-cybersecurity-incident-from-customers-in-oracle-saas-service-9231c8daff4a</link>
      <description>Being a provider of cloud SaaS (Software-as-a-service) solutions requires certain cybersecurity responsibilities — including being…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@networksecurity)</author>
      <guid>https://doublepulsar.com/oracle-attempt-to-hide-serious-cybersecurity-incident-from-customers-in-oracle-saas-service-9231c8daff4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 2.5 Pro vs. Claude 3.7 Sonnet: Coding Comparison</title>
      <link>https://composio.dev/blog/gemini-2-5-pro-vs-claude-3-7-sonnet-coding-comparison/</link>
      <description>This blog-post compares the coding capabilites of new Gemini 2.5 Pro experimental and Claude 3.7 Sonnet (thinking)</description>
      <guid>https://composio.dev/blog/gemini-2-5-pro-vs-claude-3-7-sonnet-coding-comparison/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The demoscene as a UNESCO heritage in Sweden</title>
      <link>https://www.goto80.com/the-demoscene-as-a-unesco-heritage-in-sweden</link>
      <description>The demoscene has become a national UNESCO-heritage in Sweden, thanks to an application that Ziphoid and me did last year. This has already happened in several European countries, as part of the international Art of Coding initiative to make the demoscene a global UNESCO heritage. I think this makes</description>
      <guid>https://www.goto80.com/the-demoscene-as-a-unesco-heritage-in-sweden</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back in the studio and coding</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2IIpBO0XrFI</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Let's talk tech, write some code, and have fun</description>
      <author> (Fritz's Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2IIpBO0XrFI</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interesting links of the week 2025-14</title>
      <link>https://samestuffdifferentday.net/2025/03/31/Interesting-links-of-the-week-2025-14/</link>
      <description>Here are the best and most interesting articles, blog posts, videos, podcasts, and GitHub repositories I’ve run into over the last week (March 24, 2024 - March 30, 2025). Enjoy!</description>
      <author> (Michael Eaton)</author>
      <guid>https://samestuffdifferentday.net/2025/03/31/Interesting-links-of-the-week-2025-14/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the Token Bucket Algorithm? #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=18pQooORm2c</link>
      <description>💌 Free Developer Insights: https://guiferreira.me/newsletter</description>
      <author> (Gui Ferreira)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=18pQooORm2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>