<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Why Dark didn&amp;#39;t choose Rust</title>
      <link>https://blog.darklang.com/why-dark-didnt-choose-rust/</link>
      <description>Welcome again HN! Dark is a programming language, structured editor, and infrastructure—all in one—whose goal is to make it 100x easier to build backend services. Check out the website, our What is Dark post, and How Dark deploys in 50ms for more. Thanks for checking us out! This</description>
      <author> (Paul Biggar)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.darklang.com/why-dark-didnt-choose-rust/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 02:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Targets Critical &amp;#39;Cuties&amp;#39; Tweets With Copyright Takedown Requests * TorrentFreak</title>
      <link>https://torrentfreak.com/netflix-targets-critical-cuties-tweets-with-copyright-takedown-requests-201105/</link>
      <description>Netflix has sent many takedown requests targeting tweets that are critical of the movie &amp;#39;Cuties&amp;#39; or urged people to cancel their subscription.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://torrentfreak.com/netflix-targets-critical-cuties-tweets-with-copyright-takedown-requests-201105/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 01:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OS hacking: Let&amp;#39;s debug a GCC crash on SerenityOS</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3NXge5RChcs</link>
      <description>SerenityOS is open source on GitHub: https://github.com/SerenityOS/serenity
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/awesomekling
Sponsor me on GitHub: https://github.com/sponsors/awesomekling
Support me on Patreon: https://patreon.com/serenityos
Donate via Paypal: https://paypal.me/awesomekling

SerenityOS is a Unix-like operating system that I&amp;#39;m implementing from scratch. http://www.serenityos.org/</description>
      <author> (Andreas Kling)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3NXge5RChcs</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 01:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Password Security with Troy Hunt | Authlogics</title>
      <link>https://authlogics.com/troyhunt/</link>
      <description>Authlogics Password Security Management ensures Active Directory password compliance with NIST SP 800-63B and that they haven&amp;#39;t been breached online.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://authlogics.com/troyhunt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning how to learn (Pt. 1)</title>
      <link>https://oldmanrahul.com/2020/11/04/re-use-trained-muscles/</link>
      <description>Make it a game of stacking brain muscles.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://oldmanrahul.com/2020/11/04/re-use-trained-muscles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underjord | The BEAM marches forward</title>
      <link>https://underjord.io/the-beam-marches-forward.html</link>
      <description>The BEAM is the virtual machine that Erlang and Elixir runs on. It is widely cited as a battle-tested piece of software though I don&amp;#39;t know in which wars it has seen action. It has definitely paid its dues in the telecom space as well as globally scaled projects such as Whatsapp and Discord. It is well suited to tackle soft-realtime distributed systems with heavy concurrency. It has been a good platform chugging along. And with a small team at Ericsson responsible for much of its continuing development it has been managed in a deeply pragmatic way. Erlang has always been a bit of a secret and silent success. Almost no-one uses it if you look at market shares. But among the ones that use it there seems to be a very positive consensus. And then Elixir came and caused a bit of a boom. I think the BEAM has benefited from Elixir and Elixir wouldn&amp;#39;t exist without the BEAM. With that bit of background I&amp;#39;d like to shine a light on some cool developments that I think makes the BEAM more interesting or even uniquely interesting in the future.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://underjord.io/the-beam-marches-forward.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The problem of centralisation</title>
      <link>https://jae.moe/blog/nov2020-centralization/</link>
      <description>Developer &amp;amp; Sysadmin</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jae.moe/blog/nov2020-centralization/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Don&amp;#39;t Need to Boycott Wayland</title>
      <link>https://refi64.com/posts/dont-boycott-wayland.html</link>
      <description>This is a response to the &amp;quot;Boycott Wayland&amp;quot; gist, stating that we should boycott Wayland because something something Red Hat evil and breakage and...global menus? Well, there were quite a few exaggerations and misrepresentations in the gist, which will be shown and explained here.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://refi64.com/posts/dont-boycott-wayland.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop telling me to exercise: dealing with a mild short-term depression</title>
      <link>https://rasulkireev.com/dealing-with-mild-depression/</link>
      <description>In this post, I wanted to share some of my reflections on the depressive state that I went through. I&amp;#39;d like to share some of my thoughts that were running through my head and what helped me get over.</description>
      <author> (Rasul KireevHome)</author>
      <guid>https://rasulkireev.com/dealing-with-mild-depression/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everybody be Coil. You... Be Coil - Tink - L&amp;#233;onie Watson</title>
      <link>https://tink.uk/everybody-be-coil/</link>
      <description>Online advertising is, in my opinion, intrusive, invasive, and, in the case of accessibility, frequently destructive. Yet since it first emerged in 1994, online advertising has been one of the few ways content creators have had to be compensated for their efforts. Until now.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tink.uk/everybody-be-coil/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life and Death of a Linux Process</title>
      <link>https://natanyellin.com/posts/life-and-death-of-a-linux-process/</link>
      <description>This post contains a rough sketch of the life and death of a process on Linux. It is a first-order approximation only. A later post will refine this further and provide a more precise description, adding details about pid namespaces, obscure syscalls, and little known flags.
Birth Every time a process is created, really another process split itself using the fork or clone syscall. After forking, processes usually run the execve syscall to swap the currently executing binary with another one.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://natanyellin.com/posts/life-and-death-of-a-linux-process/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t make me think about whether I should pay you</title>
      <link>https://www.krewast.de/artikel/dont-make-me-think-about-whether-i-should-pay-you/</link>
      <description>I recently watched a few videos on YouTube about the latest and greatest LEGO sets. I didn’t do it because I’m super interested in LEGO (that was a while ago) but because the YouTube algorithm decided that I had to. I naturally obeyed. The results were as expected: I felt old and none of those sets triggered any kind of “I need to have this” response. Until I saw this:</description>
      <author> (krewast - Bastian Kres Webentwicklung)</author>
      <guid>https://www.krewast.de/artikel/dont-make-me-think-about-whether-i-should-pay-you/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compose for Desktop UI Framework</title>
      <link>https://www.jetbrains.com/lp/compose/</link>
      <description>Modern high performance reactive UI framework for desktop platforms by JetBrains</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jetbrains.com/lp/compose/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Productive Productivity System</title>
      <link>https://mrbalihai.github.io/2020/11/05/a-productive-productivity-system.html</link>
      <description>I’ve tried many different systems and tools over the years: Getting Things Done (GTD), todo.txt, Taskwarrior, Org Mode to name a few. One thing I’ve discovered is that productivity systems are like dieting; you feel really motivated when starting out but after a few weeks the enthusiasm starts to wane and you quickly start to fall out of practice. I’ve been trying GTD on and off for several years now but failed to really gel with it meaningfully. The one I’ve had the most success with so far is Bullet Journaling. I want to add that I’m not Bullet Journaling on the same level as all these creative hand drawn Instagram masterpieces you see; my approach is very much messy, minimal and functional. I follow most of the principles outlined on the Bullet Journal Website: a dot for a task, a dash for a note, a small circle for an event, each day has it’s own heading, once a task is complete I put a cross through the dot, if I carry forward a task the dot becomes an arrow, if the task is no longer relevant I put a line through it. I suspect the reason this has worked so well for me is because it’s the first time I’ve tried hand-written notes rather than a digital system and perhaps if I had tried hand written lists with GTD it would have been equally successful.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mrbalihai.github.io/2020/11/05/a-productive-productivity-system.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 216</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-216/</link>
      <description>Alrighty, quickie intro before I rush off to hit the tennis court, catch up with old friends, onto the wake park before BBQ and, of course, &amp;#127866;. I&amp;#39;m doing a quick snapshot on how we&amp;#39;re travelling down here COVID wise, I lament the demise (followed by resurrection) of my Ubiquiti network,</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/troyahunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-216/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The winner of the election is... Big Tech</title>
      <link>https://creativegood.com/blog/20/winner-of-election-big-tech.html</link>
      <description>To remove Silicon Valley&amp;#39;s chokehold, ban the algorithm.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://creativegood.com/blog/20/winner-of-election-big-tech.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye USA</title>
      <link>https://larrysalibra.com/goodbye-usa/</link>
      <description>The story of how I left America.</description>
      <author> (2020-10-06)</author>
      <guid>https://larrysalibra.com/goodbye-usa/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to allow executable .exe files to be downloaded with ASP.NET Core and UseStaticFiles middleware</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/how-to-allow-executable-exe-files-to-be-downloaded-with-aspnet-core-and-usestaticfiles-middleware</link>
      <description>In the long process of upgrading this blog and moving it to Azure I&amp;#39;ve been ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/how-to-allow-executable-exe-files-to-be-downloaded-with-aspnet-core-and-usestaticfiles-middleware</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 23:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Complete Analysis Of The Bkz Lattice Reduction Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://www.cryptologie.net/links/link/2393</link>
      <description>Your name</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cryptologie.net/links/link/2393</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 23:05:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning and Scientific Computing with Python </title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/AI-Show/Machine-Learning-and-Scientific-Computing-with-Python</link>
      <description>In this episode we will talk about the Python community and the scientific Python ecosystem. So if you always wanted to know what is so great about Python for Machine learning and its community this e</description>
      <author> (by Seth Juarez)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/AI-Show/Machine-Learning-and-Scientific-Computing-with-Python</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 23:05:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setup Git with Multiple Configs</title>
      <link>https://itnext.io/setup-git-with-multiple-configs-9b4111d6928c</link>
      <description>Conditional global configuration of git based on url</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@englundgiant)</author>
      <guid>https://itnext.io/setup-git-with-multiple-configs-9b4111d6928c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 23:05:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programmatic Problem Solving with Nicole Archambault  | Hanselminutes with Scott Hanselman</title>
      <link>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/programmatic-problem-solving-with-nicole-archambault-XEc6xDkr</link>
      <description>Nicole Archambault believes we can scale back on learning to code and we should ramp up on learning problem solving. She believes this so much she&amp;#39;s launched a whole online course - Newbie Coder Problem Solving School - that teaches tons of problem solving skills...with not a single line of code! Is this possible? A good idea? We find out this week!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hanselminutes.simplecast.com/episodes/programmatic-problem-solving-with-nicole-archambault-XEc6xDkr</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 23:05:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Azure Arc Enabled PostgreSQL Hyperscale?</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Data-Exposed/What-is-Azure-Arc-Enabled-PostgreSQL-Hyperscale--Data-Exposed</link>
      <description>In this episode with Jean-Yes Devant, we&amp;#39;ll introduce Azure Arc enabled PostgreSQL Hyperscale and provide an overview of its capabilities. We&amp;#39;ll also share how you can get started with Azure Arc enabl</description>
      <author> (by Marisa Brasile)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Data-Exposed/What-is-Azure-Arc-Enabled-PostgreSQL-Hyperscale--Data-Exposed</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 23:05:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrapping JavaScript Libraries with C# in Blazor WebAssembly</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/wrapping-javascript-libraries-with-csharp-in-blazor-webassembly/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to learn about Wrapping JavaScript Libraries with C#. We&amp;#39;ll show you how to do that by wrapping the Toastr lib.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/wrapping-javascript-libraries-with-csharp-in-blazor-webassembly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 23:05:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Data fetching with GraphQL and Blazor</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Real-time-Data-fetching-with-GraphQL-and-Blazor</link>
      <description>GraphQL supports the ability to subscribe to event streams to enable somewhat real-time scenarios for both clients and servers. In this episode of the On .NET show, HotChocolate author Michael Staib r</description>
      <author> (by Cecil Phillip)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/Real-time-Data-fetching-with-GraphQL-and-Blazor</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 23:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamilton Halloween</title>
      <link>https://www.paraesthesia.com/archive/2020/11/05/hamilton-halloween/</link>
      <description>This year my daughter was obsessed with Hamilton, so the whole family hit Halloween in Revolutionary War style.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.paraesthesia.com/archive/2020/11/05/hamilton-halloween/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 21:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python, a VS Code Mainstay, Slithers Past Java in Popularity Index -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/11/05/python-passes-java.aspx</link>
      <description>  Python, surely the most important programming language to users of Visual Studio Code (except for perhaps C#), has for the first time passed Java to secure the No. 2 spot in the latest TIOBE Index ranking of popularity.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel11/05/2020)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2020/11/05/python-passes-java.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 21:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video falsely claims possible voter fraud in Detroit. It actually shows a WXYZ photographer loading camera gear.</title>
      <link>https://www.wxyz.com/news/video-claiming-to-show-possible-voter-fraud-in-detroit-is-actually-a-wxyz-photographer-loading-camera-gear</link>
      <description>A video making the rounds on social media and other platforms that claims to show voter fraud and a wagon being loaded outside of the TCF Center in Detroit is actually video of a WXYZ photographer loading his camera and other gear into a wagon for work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.wxyz.com/news/video-claiming-to-show-possible-voter-fraud-in-detroit-is-actually-a-wxyz-photographer-loading-camera-gear</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 20:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NewReleases.io</title>
      <link>https://newreleases.io/</link>
      <description>Stop wasting your time checking if some software is updated. Get Email, Slack, Telegram, Discord, Hangouts Chat, Microsoft Teams, Mattermost or Webhook notifications.</description>
      <author> (Janoš Guljaš)</author>
      <guid>https://newreleases.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 20:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>janos/compromised</title>
      <link>https://github.com/janos/compromised</link>
      <description>Compromised/Pwned Passwords API On-premisses. Contribute to janos/compromised development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (janos)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/janos/compromised</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 20:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uno Platform</title>
      <link>https://platform.uno/</link>
      <description>Pixel-Perfect Multi-Platform Applications with C# and WinUI for Windows, WebAssembly, iOS, macOS, Android and Linux</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://platform.uno/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 19:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nextjs Crash Course with Fauna, Tailwind CSS, React Hook Form, and SWR</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1GpbdX8aJCU</link>
      <description>Nextjs has quickly become my favorite framework for creating fullstack applications especially when paired with the right tools. In this video, we are going to create a CRUD app for tracking code snippets using FaunaDB for data, Tailwind CSS for styling, React Hook Form for handling forms, and SWR for fetching and caching data.

Source Code - https://github.com/jamesqquick/nextjs-crash-course-fauna-swr-react-hook-form-tailwind

Sign up for Fauna for Free - https://bit.ly/jqqfauna
_____________________________________________

Newsletter &amp;#128478;
Interested in exclusive content and discounts? &amp;#129327; Sign up for the newsletter!
https://www.jamesqquick.com
_____________________________________________

Connect with me &amp;#128512;
Live streams on Twitch - https://twitch.tv/jamesqquick
Follow me on Twitter - https://www.twitter.com/jamesqquick
Join the &amp;#128172; Discord Server &amp;#128172; - https://discord.gg/vM2bagU
_____________________________________________

COURSES  &amp;#128187;
Learn how to build Fullstack apps with React and Serverless Functions - https://www.jamesqquick.com/courses/react-and-serverless-fullstack-developmnent
Learn everything you need to know about Visual Studio Code - https://www.udemy.com/learn-visual-studio-code/
Build a Quiz App  - https://www.udemy.com/build-a-quiz-app-with-html-css-and-javascript/</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1GpbdX8aJCU</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 19:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scripts for Managing Azure Container Registry</title>
      <link>https://www.paraesthesia.com/archive/2020/11/05/scripts-for-managing-azure-container-registry/</link>
      <description>A few helpful scripts for working with creating and managing Azure Container Registry instances.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.paraesthesia.com/archive/2020/11/05/scripts-for-managing-azure-container-registry/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 19:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten Number System - Numberphile</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9p55Qgt7Ciw</link>
      <description>Featuring author Alex Bellos - check his books (including the Language Lover&amp;#39;s Puzzle Book) on Amazon: https://amzn.to/3oU0wjT
More links &amp;amp; stuff in full description below ↓↓↓

More Alex on Numberphile: http://bit.ly/Bellos_Playlist

Alex&amp;#39;s own website with links to all his stuff: http://www.alexbellos.com

Numberphile is supported by the Mathematical Sciences Research Institute (MSRI): http://bit.ly/MSRINumberphile

We are also supported by Science Sandbox, a Simons Foundation initiative dedicated to engaging everyone with the process of science. https://www.simonsfoundation.org/outreach/science-sandbox/

And support from Math For America - https://www.mathforamerica.org/ 

NUMBERPHILE
Website: http://www.numberphile.com/
Numberphile on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/numberphile
Numberphile tweets: https://twitter.com/numberphile
Subscribe: http://bit.ly/Numberphile_Sub 

Videos by Brady Haran

Patreon: http://www.patreon.com/numberphile

Numberphile T-Shirts and Merch: https://teespring.com/stores/numberphile


Brady&amp;#39;s videos subreddit: http://www.reddit.com/r/BradyHaran/

Brady&amp;#39;s latest videos across all channels: http://www.bradyharanblog.com/ 

Sign up for (occasional) emails: http://eepurl.com/YdjL9

With thanks to Patreon supporters, including: Arjun Chakroborty, Ben Delo, Jeff Straathof, Ken Baron, Yana Chernobilsky, Andy B, James Bissonette, Jubal John, Jeremy Buchanan, Steve Crutchfield, Adam Savage, Ben White, Andrei M Burke, RAD Donato, Matthew Schuster, Nat Tyce, Ron Hochsprung, Mitch Harding, Ubiquity Ventures, Mateusz Swiatkowski, John Zelinka, Gnare , Tom Marshall, Jes&amp;#250;s Salsero, Jordan W Oja, Tracy Parry, Ian George Walker, Arnas , Bernd Sing, Valentin , Alfred Wallace, Charles Southerland, Kristian Joensen, Bodhisattva Debnath, Alex Khein, Kermit Norlund, That Asymptote, Mirik Gogri</description>
      <author> (Numberphile)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9p55Qgt7Ciw</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 18:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Live TV | Live developer streams every day</title>
      <link>https://dotnet.microsoft.com/live</link>
      <description>Live TV from the .NET team and the .NET community.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dotnet.microsoft.com/live</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 18:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SvgPathEditor</title>
      <link>https://yqnn.github.io/svg-path-editor/</link>
      <description>Online editor to create and manipulate SVG paths</description>
      <author> (Yann Armelin)</author>
      <guid>https://yqnn.github.io/svg-path-editor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 18:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Override webpage resources with local copies using Microsoft Edge DevTools - Microsoft Edge Development</title>
      <link>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-edge/devtools-guide-chromium/javascript/overrides</link>
      <description>The Overrides feature is a feature within the Sources tool of Microsoft Edge DevTools that allows you to copy webpage resources to your hard drive.  When you refresh the webpage, DevTools do not load the resource but replace it with your local copy instead.</description>
      <author> (MSEdgeTeam)</author>
      <guid>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-edge/devtools-guide-chromium/javascript/overrides</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 18:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US formally exits Paris pact aiming to curb climate change</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-climate-climate-change-paris-united-states-1331bc30021756454dda8eb7ff3c1075</link>
      <description>BERLIN (AP) — The United States on Wednesday formally left the Paris Agreement, a global pact it helped forge five years ago to avert the threat of catastrophic climate change. The move,... </description>
      <author> (By FRANK JORDANS and SETH BORENSTEIN)</author>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-climate-climate-change-paris-united-states-1331bc30021756454dda8eb7ff3c1075</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 17:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python overtakes Java to become the second-most popular programming language</title>
      <link>https://www.techrepublic.com/article/python-overtakes-java-to-become-the-second-most-popular-programming-language/</link>
      <description>For the first time in the history of TIOBE&amp;#39;s index, Java has slipped out of the top two, leaving Python to occupy the spot behind reigning champion, C.</description>
      <author> (Brandon Vigliarolo)</author>
      <guid>https://www.techrepublic.com/article/python-overtakes-java-to-become-the-second-most-popular-programming-language/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 17:04:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# in Simple Terms - Arrays and Collections</title>
      <link>https://exceptionnotfound.net/csharp-in-simple-terms-13-arrays-and-collections/</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s learn about arrays, lists, ranges, indices, List&amp;lt;T&amp;gt;, Dictionary&amp;lt;TKey, TValue&amp;gt;, Stack&amp;lt;T&amp;gt;, and more!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/exceptionnotfnd/)</author>
      <guid>https://exceptionnotfound.net/csharp-in-simple-terms-13-arrays-and-collections/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 17:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetconf.net/swag</link>
      <description>Join the .NET Conf 2020 free virtual event November 10-12 to learn about the newest developments across the .NET platform, open source, and dev tools. Mark your calendar!</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetconf.net/swag</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 17:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz-Birkenau - Wirtualne zwiedzanie</title>
      <link>http://panorama.auschwitz.org/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://panorama.auschwitz.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 17:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building applications with C# and a Challenge!</title>
      <link>https://tattoocoder.com/building-applications-with-c-and-a-challenge/</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s seems not too long ago I was laying down the words for &amp;quot;So Many Ways to Learn .NET in 2020&amp;quot;, but of course it was March yesterday too. This list is still very valid; 101 videos (youtube | channel9), Microsoft docs, the various shows now available on the new https:</description>
      <author> (Shayne Boyer)</author>
      <guid>https://tattoocoder.com/building-applications-with-c-and-a-challenge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 17:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#39;s the point of APTTYPE_CURRENT? I mean, of course I&amp;#39;m current. | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20201105-00/?p=104422</link>
      <description>The Co&amp;#173;Get&amp;#173;Apartment&amp;#173;Type function tells you what kind of apartment you are executing in. One of the values in the APTTYPE enumeration is APTTYPE_CURRENT. Receiving this value is like walking up to an information desk and asking, “Where am I?” and the person at the desk says,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20201105-00/?p=104422</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 16:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickHouse Capacity Estimation Framework</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/clickhouse-capacity-estimation-framework/</link>
      <description>We use ClickHouse widely at Cloudflare. It helps us with our internal analytics workload, bot management, customer dashboards, and many other systems.</description>
      <author> (Oxana Kharitonova)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/clickhouse-capacity-estimation-framework/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 15:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A first look at the JIT</title>
      <link>https://blog.erlang.org/a-first-look-at-the-jit/</link>
      <description>Now that we’ve had a look at BEAM and the interpreter we’re going to
explore one of the most exciting additions in OTP 24: the just-in-time
compiler, or “JIT” for short.

</description>
      <author> (A Blog from the Erlang/OTP team)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.erlang.org/a-first-look-at-the-jit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 15:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Conf 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetconf.net/swag?hss_channel=tw-2384354214</link>
      <description>Join the .NET Conf 2020 free virtual event November 10-12 to learn about the newest developments across the .NET platform, open source, and dev tools. Mark your calendar!</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetconf.net/swag?hss_channel=tw-2384354214</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 15:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson: The gambler, by Tom Bower book review</title>
      <link>https://www.the-tls.co.uk/articles/boris-johnson-tom-bower-book-review-rory-stewart/</link>
      <description>Book review - British Politics - The TLS | Boris Johnson: The gambler by Tom Bower, reviewed by Rory Stewart</description>
      <author> (By rory stewart)</author>
      <guid>https://www.the-tls.co.uk/articles/boris-johnson-tom-bower-book-review-rory-stewart/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 12:04:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FFMPEG.WASM</title>
      <link>https://ffmpegwasm.github.io/</link>
      <description>ffmpeg.wasm is a pure WebAssembly / JavaScript port of FFmpeg. It enables video &amp;amp; audio record, convert and stream right inside browsers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ffmpegwasm.github.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 10:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2020-11-05</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/11/app-developer-links-2020-11-05/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/11/app-developer-links-2020-11-05/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 09:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randy Pausch Last Lecture: Achieving Your Childhood Dreams</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ji5_MqicxSo</link>
      <description>Carnegie Mellon Professor Randy Pausch (Oct. 23, 1960 - July 25, 2008) gave his last lecture at the university Sept. 18, 2007, before a packed McConomy Auditorium. In his moving presentation, &amp;quot;Really Achieving Your Childhood Dreams,&amp;quot; Pausch talked about his lessons learned and gave advice to students on how to achieve their own career and personal goals. 

For more on Randy, visit: http://www.cmu.edu/randyslecture

Learn how to support the Randy Pausch Memorial Bridge, visit: http://www.cmu.edu/homepage/images/extras/emails/pausch/pausch_bridge.html</description>
      <author> (Carnegie Mellon University)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ji5_MqicxSo</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 08:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TypeScript Dictionary</title>
      <link>https://www.carlrippon.com/typescript-dictionary/</link>
      <description>Different ways to strongly-type a dictionary / hash / map in TypeScript.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.carlrippon.com/typescript-dictionary/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 06:04:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate a GitHub Actions workflow file from dotnet CLI</title>
      <link>https://timheuer.com/blog/generate-github-actions-workflow-from-cli/</link>
      <description>Generate a GitHub Actions workflow file quickly from the dotnet CLI using this new helper tool.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://timheuer.com/blog/generate-github-actions-workflow-from-cli/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 06:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing TypeScript 4.1 RC | TypeScript</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-4-1-rc/</link>
      <description>Today we are making the Release Candidate (RC) of TypeScript 4.1 available. To get started using the RC, you can get it through NuGet, or use npm with the following command: npm install typescript@rc You can also get editor support by Downloading for Visual Studio 2019/2017 Following directions for Visual Studio Code and Sublime Text.</description>
      <author> (Daniel Rosenwasser Program Manager, TypeScript Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-4-1-rc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 06:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lazy-Loading Your React App</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/lazy-loading-your-react-app</link>
      <description>Improve the performance of your React app with React.lazy and Suspense.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/lazy-loading-your-react-app</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 06:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Switch from Redux to Recoil</title>
      <link>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-to-switch-redux-to-recoil</link>
      <description>Like Redux, Recoil is state management library in React. Let’s look at the differences and how to make the switch when you’re ready.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-to-switch-redux-to-recoil</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 06:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Middleware Stack in Modular AWS SDK for JavaScript | Amazon Web Services</title>
      <link>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/middleware-stack-modular-aws-sdk-js/</link>
      <description>One of the major changes in v3 is introduction of the middleware stack, which customizes the SDK behavior by modifying the middleware. In this blog post we&amp;#39;d like to describe how you can use this feature in detail.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/developer/middleware-stack-modular-aws-sdk-js/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 06:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seller Floods Forums With Stolen Data - Binary Defense</title>
      <link>https://www.binarydefense.com/threat_watch/seller-floods-forums-with-stolen-data/</link>
      <description>A data breach broker is selling databases containing user information from 14 different companies that were claimed to have been breached in 2020. When companies are breached, threat actors will typically download accessible databases, including user account records, which are then sold to other threat actors directly or via a data breach broker. Over the […]</description>
      <author> (Jake Aurand)</author>
      <guid>https://www.binarydefense.com/threat_watch/seller-floods-forums-with-stolen-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 05:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Rocks! vNext</title>
      <link>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1712</link>
      <description>.NET Rocks! is a weekly talk show for anyone interested in programming on the Microsoft .NET platform. The shows range from introductory information to hardcore geekiness.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dotnetrocks.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=1712</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 05:04:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Source Code Leak</title>
      <link>https://resynth1943.net/articles/github-source-code-leak/</link>
      <description>What do Microsoft &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;really&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; think about open-source?</description>
      <author> (resynth1943)</author>
      <guid>https://resynth1943.net/articles/github-source-code-leak/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 03:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>