<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Aimoresc.NET - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/142/aimoresc.net</link>
      <description>The app includes the following features:
- My personal blog where I regularly update with new tech articles.
- My updated resume with all the projects I worked on and professional experience.
- Photo map showing the places I&amp;#39;ve visited.
- Last but not least my contact information with the socia…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/142/aimoresc.net</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 17:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Azure App Service SSL Certificate with Azure Key Vault</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/managing-ssl-certificate-with-azure-keyvault/</link>
      <description>In my last blog post I wrote about working with SSL certificate in Azure App Service. In this article I will explain how to manage Azure App Service SSL certificates with Azure Key Vault Service. If you’re running SAAS applications on Azure App Service with custom domains and SSL certificates it is quite complicated. Here is a screenshot of an App Service running a SAAS app with custom domain and SSL certificates.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/managing-ssl-certificate-with-azure-keyvault/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 15:05:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maoli - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/143/maoli</link>
      <description>Maoli is C# helper library for common brazilian business rules (CEP, CPF and CNPJ), compatible with .NET Framework 4.0+ and .NET Standard 1.1.

Currently implements:

CEP validation
CPF validation
CNPJ validation</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/143/maoli</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 12:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI OpenCV Dolly Zoom Camera</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aujQVz2TPN0</link>
      <description>This is a quick example of a dolly zoom camera that I created in Python. I was inspired to create this after watching countless movies that use dolly zoom. I...</description>
      <author> (G DriveHarshal)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aujQVz2TPN0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 11:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETworkManager - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/75/networkmanager</link>
      <description>A powerful tool for managing networks and troubleshoot network problems!

- Network Interface - Information, Configure
- IP-Scanner
- Port-Scanner
- Ping
- Traceroute
- DNS Lookup
- Remote Desktop
- PuTTY
- SNMP - Get, Walk, Set (v1, v2c, v3)
- Wake on LAN
- HTTP Headers
- Subnet Calcu…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/75/networkmanager</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 08:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The High QA Guy</title>
      <link>http://www.highqaguy.com/</link>
      <description>Make sure anyone can use your website stoned.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.highqaguy.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 06:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeekTable	 - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/73/seektable</link>
      <description>Free web-based BI tool for self-service data analysis with pivot tables, charts &amp;amp; datagrids. Supports CSV, SQL and NoSQL data sources (MongoDb, ElasticSearch), report can be shared by email or published to web with a shareable link.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/73/seektable</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 05:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home — Spyder IDE</title>
      <link>https://www.spyder-ide.org/</link>
      <description>Website for Spyder, the Scientific Python Development Environment</description>
      <author> (Spyder Team)</author>
      <guid>https://www.spyder-ide.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 05:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Tailwind CSS</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Web-Wednesday/What-is-Tailwind-CSS</link>
      <description>Tailwind CSS is self-described as a utility first CSS framework. Rather than focusing on the functionality of the item being styled, Tailwind is centered around how it should be displayed. This makes </description>
      <author> (by GeekTrainer, Jen Looper)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Web-Wednesday/What-is-Tailwind-CSS</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 05:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operational best practices for web apps on Azure App Service | Azure Friday</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Operational-best-practices-for-web-apps-on-Azure-App-Service</link>
      <description>Byron Tardif joins Scott Hanselman to discuss some operational best practices for running your web apps on Azure App Service.</description>
      <author> (by Scott Hanselman, Rob Caron)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Azure-Friday/Operational-best-practices-for-web-apps-on-Azure-App-Service</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 05:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men&amp;#39;s Suitmeister Rainbow Summer Suit &amp;amp; Tie Set</title>
      <link>https://www.kohls.com/product/prd-3748458/mens-suitmeister-rainbow-summer-suit-tie-set.jsp</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.kohls.com/product/prd-3748458/mens-suitmeister-rainbow-summer-suit-tie-set.jsp</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the future, even your RAM will have firmware; and the subject of POWER10 blobs</title>
      <link>https://www.devever.net/~hl/omi</link>
      <description>Industry trends: serial memory attachment. One of the most interesting
things which will happen in the near future in computing is the adoption of
serial memory interfaces. For pretty much the entire history of modern
computing, RAM has been attached to a system via a high-speed parallel
interface. Making parallel interfaces fast is hard and requires extremely
rigorous control of timing skew between pins, therefore the routing of PCB
traces between a CPU and RAM slots must be done with great precision. At the
speeds of modern parallel RAM interfaces like DDR4, what is theoretically a
digital interface in practice must be viewed as practically analog (to the
point that part of a CPU DDR4 controller is called the “PHY”). Moreover, the
maximum distance between a CPU and its RAM slots is extremely tight. The
positioning of RAM slots on a motherboard is largely constrained by these
physics considerations. For these reasons you have never seen anything like the
flexibility with RAM attachment that you can get with, for example, PCIe or
SAS. PCIe and SAS are serial architectures which support cabling and even
switching, allowing entire additional chassis of PCIe and SAS devices to be
attached to a system via cables.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.devever.net/~hl/omi</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 04:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Engines Don&amp;#39;t Work and They Are Not Good</title>
      <link>https://www.chrbutler.com/search-engines-dont-work</link>
      <description>“A good question is much more difficult than a brilliant answer.”</description>
      <author> (— Christopher Butler, Feb 5, 2021, Durham, NC)</author>
      <guid>https://www.chrbutler.com/search-engines-dont-work</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Missed Opportunities of Static Types</title>
      <link>http://sigusr2.net/on-the-missed-opportunities-of-static-types.html</link>
      <description>Recently, a colleague spent a bunch of time working on a bug. When
attempting to perform some action, the system would provide feedback
that everything was going as planned, and then &amp;quot;go dark,&amp;quot; seemingly
out of no where. It&amp;#39;s important to realize that this is a complex
distributed system, and that there is a network connection between the
&amp;quot;part that worked&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;the part that went dark.&amp;quot; But, there wasn&amp;#39;t a
change to the connection logic, and it worked before, so that
&amp;quot;couldn&amp;#39;t possibly be it.&amp;quot; (Yes. I already told you where this is going—Ed)</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://sigusr2.net/on-the-missed-opportunities-of-static-types.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Life Advice: Never Give Up - Replay Attacks Against HTTPS</title>
      <link>https://vnhacker.blogspot.com/2015/12/bad-life-advice-never-give-up-replay.html</link>
      <description>(joint work with Thiago&amp;#160;Valverde and Quan Nguyen -- see also Thiago&amp;#39;s post  on his blog)   I was once advised by a self-help book that I sho...</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>https://vnhacker.blogspot.com/2015/12/bad-life-advice-never-give-up-replay.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to choose a market where your startup can win</title>
      <link>https://diego-os.com/startup-ideas/how-to-choose-a-market-where-your-startup-can-win/</link>
      <description>Our main competitor is Microsoft, but we are very smart, so I’m sure our product will win. Famous last words.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://diego-os.com/startup-ideas/how-to-choose-a-market-where-your-startup-can-win/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to automatically set up a development machine with Ansible</title>
      <link>https://stribny.name/blog/ansible-dev/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://stribny.name/blog/ansible-dev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I stay motivated to publish despite being a lazy bastard</title>
      <link>https://www.simplecto.com/how-i-stay-motivated-publish-despite-being-lazy-bastard/</link>
      <description>I briefly break down my process for staying on top of my writing ideas despite begin a lazy bastard. Procrastinate without guilt.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.simplecto.com/how-i-stay-motivated-publish-despite-being-lazy-bastard/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Staff Software Engineering Reading List</title>
      <link>https://huth.me/blog/my-staff-software-engineering-reading-list/</link>
      <description>After reading Four books professional developers should read, by Phil Eaton, I was inspired to write my own engineering reading list.
Originally I thought of this as a “staff engineering” reading list, because I probably wouldn’t have appreciated these earlier in my career. When starting out, my reading was mostly about the specifics of using Ruby on Rails, HTML, and CSS. Which was great, and worked well for me.
But while the books in this list have been useful for me as an engineering leader, anybody at any level can get a lot out of them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://huth.me/blog/my-staff-software-engineering-reading-list/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veloren</title>
      <link>https://veloren.net/</link>
      <description>The Veloren devblog website</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://veloren.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the world becoming better? - Inverted Passion</title>
      <link>https://invertedpassion.com/is-the-world-becoming-better/</link>
      <description>This essay is inspired by the book Factfulness where the key idea explored is that the world has witnessed significant progress over the last few decades, but most people are unaware of that fact because they hold distorted views.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://invertedpassion.com/is-the-world-becoming-better/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Myself Quantum Mechanics, Part one. | </title>
      <link>https://danielepaliotta.com/qm-1/</link>
      <description>A long series on learning quantum mechanics from scratch</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://danielepaliotta.com/qm-1/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the 23andMe and VGAC Merger</title>
      <link>https://blog.m5e.de/post/on-the-23andme-and-vgac-merger/</link>
      <description>On the 4th February 2021 23andMe and VG Acquisition Corp announced that they will merge, bringing 23andMe into the public.
As VGAC is already tradable in the public market, the shares have skyrocketed to 19 USD. But this is crazy&amp;amp;hellip;
Why this is crazy? First you should know that the initiators of a SPAC commonly have additional rights to e.g. buy additional shares. They also mostly pay 10 USD per share.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.m5e.de/post/on-the-23andme-and-vgac-merger/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware the Cult of Numeracy</title>
      <link>https://blog.awaxman.com/beware-the-cult-of-numeracy/</link>
      <description>While data can be a fantastic tool to understand behavior and measure impact, we should be mindful of its limitations.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.awaxman.com/beware-the-cult-of-numeracy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS Code Dev Team Eyes Long-Requested Testing Support -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/05/vs-code-1-53.aspx</link>
      <description>  Of course, testing is possible in VS Code via numerous extensions, but Microsoft is seeking to spearhead a more structured, comprehensive approach.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel02/05/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/02/05/vs-code-1-53.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 23:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&amp;#39;s Crack Zodiac - Episode 5 - The 340 Is Solved!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-1oQLPRE21o</link>
      <description>On December 3rd, 2020, an international three-person team of codebreakers made a breakthrough with the Zodiac Killer&amp;#39;s unsolved 340-character cipher.By Decem...</description>
      <author> (David Oranchak
  
  
    

    
      
    David Oranchak
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-1oQLPRE21o</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 23:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl LV on Cloudflare’s Radar</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-super-bowl-lv/</link>
      <description>Super Bowl LV, the most watched US sports broadcast, is just around the corner. All through Super Bowl weekend and especially while the game between the Tampa Bay Buccaneers and the Kansas City Chiefs is on we expect a visible impact on Internet usage.</description>
      <author> (Marc Lamik)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-super-bowl-lv/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 23:05:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Vaccine - LessWrong</title>
      <link>https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/niQ3heWwF6SydhS7R/making-vaccine</link>
      <description>Back in December, I asked how hard it would be to make a vaccine for oneself.
Several people pointed to radvac. It was a best-case scenario: an open-source
vaccine design, made for self-experimenters, dead simple to make with
readily-available materials, well-explained reasoning about the design, and with
the name of one of the world’s more competent biologists (who I already knew of
beforehand) stamped on the whitepaper. My girlfriend and I made a batch a week
ago and took our first booster yesterday.

This post talks a bit about the process, a bit about our plan, and a bit about
motivations. Bear in mind that we may have made mistakes - if something seems
off, leave a comment.

THE PROCESS
All of the materials and equipment to make the vaccine cost us about $1000. We
did not need any special licenses or anything like that. I do have a little
wetlab experience from my undergrad days, but the skills required were pretty
minimal.

One vial of custom peptide - that little pile of white powder at the bottom.The
large majority of the cost (about $850) was the peptides. These are the main
active ingredients of the vaccine: short segments of proteins from the COVID
virus. They’re all &amp;lt;25 amino acids, so far too small to have any likely function
as proteins (for comparison, COVID’s spike protein has 1273 amino acids).
They’re just meant to be recognized by the immune system: the immune system
learns to recognize these sequences, and that’s what provides immunity.

Each of six peptides came in two vials of 4.5 mg each. These are the half we
haven&amp;#39;t dissolved; we keep them in the freezer as backups.The peptides were
custom synthesized. There are companies which synthesize any (short) peptide
sequence you want - you can find dozens of them online. The cheapest options
suffice for the vaccine - the peptides don’t need to be “purified” (this just
means removing partial sequences), they don’t need any special modifications,
and very small amounts suffice. The minimum order size </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/niQ3heWwF6SydhS7R/making-vaccine</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 23:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fecal transplant turns cancer immunotherapy non-responders into responders</title>
      <link>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-02/uop-ftt012921.php</link>
      <description>A phase II clinical trial shows that changing the gut microbiome through fecal transplant can transform cancer patients who never responded to immunotherapy into patients who do.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-02/uop-ftt012921.php</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 22:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac utility Homebrew finally gets native Apple Silicon and M1 support</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/02/mac-utility-homebrew-finally-gets-native-apple-silicon-and-m1-support/?utm_social-type=owned</link>
      <description>There aren&amp;#39;t bottles for every package yet, but the work is in progress.</description>
      <author> (Samuel Axon
    -  2/5/2021, 1:47 PM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/02/mac-utility-homebrew-finally-gets-native-apple-silicon-and-m1-support/?utm_social-type=owned</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 22:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoHistory for EF Core - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/77/autohistory-for-ef-core</link>
      <description>A plugin for Microsoft.EntityFrameworkCore to support automatically recording data changes history. Comes in handy when you want to create a log of data changes over time. Think blog post revisions, etc.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/77/autohistory-for-ef-core</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 22:06:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firewalls Don&amp;#39;t Stop Dragons Podcast - Don&amp;#39;t Get Caught With Your Drawbridge Down!</title>
      <link>https://podcast.firewallsdontstopdragons.com/</link>
      <description>Don&amp;#39;t Get Caught With Your Drawbridge Down!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://podcast.firewallsdontstopdragons.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 21:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elements of Computing Systems, Second Edition</title>
      <link>https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/elements-computing-systems-second-edition</link>
      <description>A new and extensively revised edition of a popular textbook used in universities, coding boot camps, hacker clubs, and online courses.
                The best way to understand how computers work is to build one from scratch, and this textbook leads learners through twelve chapters and projects that gradually build the hardware platform and software hierarchy for a simple but powerful computer system. In the process, learners gain hands-on knowledge of hardware, architecture, operating systems, programming languages, compilers, data structures and algorithms, and software engineering. Using this constructive approach, the book introduces learners to a significant body of computer science knowledge and demonstrates how theoretical and applied techniques taught in other computer science courses fit into the overall picture. The outcome of these efforts is known as Nand to Tetris: a journey that starts with the most elementary logic gate, called Nand, and ends, twelve projects later, with a general-purpose computer system capable of running Tetris.
                    The first edition of this popular textbook inspired Nand to Tetris classes in universities, coding boot camps, hacker clubs, and online course platforms. This second edition has been extensively revised. It has been restructured into two distinct parts—part I, Hardware, and part II, Software—with six projects in each part. All chapters and projects have been rewritten, with an emphasis on separating abstraction from implementation, and many new sections, figures, and examples have been added. Substantial new appendixes offer focused presentation on technical and theoretical topics.</description>
      <author> (By Noam Nisan and  Shimon Schocken)</author>
      <guid>https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/elements-computing-systems-second-edition</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 20:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major corporations say they will stop donating to members of Congress who tried to overturn the election</title>
      <link>https://popular.info/p/three-major-corporations-say-they</link>
      <description>On January 6, a violent mob stormed the Capitol of the United States, disrupting the joint session to confirm Joe Biden&amp;#39;s victory. The incident left five people dead, including a member of the Capitol police who was crushed to death in the mele.</description>
      <author> (Judd Legum)</author>
      <guid>https://popular.info/p/three-major-corporations-say-they</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 20:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gift Egwuenu (Gift Egwuenu)</title>
      <link>https://mvp.microsoft.com/en-us/PublicProfile/5004152?fullName=Gift%20Egwuenu</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mvp.microsoft.com/en-us/PublicProfile/5004152?fullName=Gift%20Egwuenu</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 20:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Maze Weekly #63 - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-63/</link>
      <description>Not many technologies are exciting as soon as they come out. Blazor was and still is an exciting toy to play with, and we’re thrilled to see it grow and that people are adopting it steadily. So give it a chance. Or pick some of the awesome topics we’ve prepared for you this time. Take […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/code-maze-weekly-63/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 19:06:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>