<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AltStore PAL</title>
      <link>https://rileytestut.com/blog/2024/04/17/introducing-altstore-pal/</link>
      <description>This is a day I’ve been looking forward to for over 10 years.</description>
      <author> (riley)</author>
      <guid>https://rileytestut.com/blog/2024/04/17/introducing-altstore-pal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did the Medici make their money?</title>
      <link>https://www.karlsnotes.com/how-did-the-medici-make-their-money/</link>
      <description>How did the Medici manage to earn vast sums of money from banking, when lending money with interest was forbidden?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.karlsnotes.com/how-did-the-medici-make-their-money/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Blasterhacks Taught Me About Leadership</title>
      <link>https://elijahpotter.dev/articles/what_blasterhacks_taught_me_about_leadership</link>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s easier than you think.</description>
      <author> (Elijah Potter)</author>
      <guid>https://elijahpotter.dev/articles/what_blasterhacks_taught_me_about_leadership</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I like Android &amp;#129302;</title>
      <link>https://merecivilian.com/why-i-like-android/</link>
      <description>Things I like about Android that do not exist on iOS and iPadOS</description>
      <author> (Published by MereCivilian on Apr 26, 2024 &amp;#183; 
                        android)</author>
      <guid>https://merecivilian.com/why-i-like-android/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Request Response Messaging Pattern With MassTransit</title>
      <link>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/request-response-messaging-pattern-with-masstransit</link>
      <description>When building distributed systems with .NET, direct calls between services can create tight coupling. The request-response messaging pattern can allow distributed services to communicate in a loosely coupled way.</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog/request-response-messaging-pattern-with-masstransit</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anneal autopsy</title>
      <link>https://nickmccleery.github.io/posts/06-anneal-autopsy/</link>
      <description>Post-mortem reflections on a failed engineering software start-up.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nickmccleery.github.io/posts/06-anneal-autopsy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I search in 2024</title>
      <link>https://newsletter.vickiboykis.com/archive/how-i-search-in-2024/</link>
      <description>We are now in a very weird liminal space in information retrieval for consumers, particularly those attuned to trends in search and working on the bleeding...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://newsletter.vickiboykis.com/archive/how-i-search-in-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t get hit with the pendulum: DevOps shifted too far left</title>
      <link>https://blog.christianposta.com/devops-shifted-too-far-left/</link>
      <description>You probably wouldn’t be surprised if I told you modern networking based on open source projects like Istio, SPIFFE, Cilium and others (See my paper about the CAKES stack) are typically consumed by what we now call “platform engineering” teams. You’ve probably heard the term platform engineering or seen some nice write-ups on it (like the one from my industry colleague Daniel Bryant).

</description>
      <author> (Twitter)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.christianposta.com/devops-shifted-too-far-left/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code signing on Windows with Azure Trusted Signing &amp;#183; Melatonin</title>
      <link>https://melatonin.dev/blog/code-signing-on-windows-with-azure-trusted-signing/</link>
      <description>Trash your overpriced third party certs! Set that clumsy dongle on fire! Get ready to sign on the dotted line for $9.99.</description>
      <author> (sudara)</author>
      <guid>https://melatonin.dev/blog/code-signing-on-windows-with-azure-trusted-signing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOLVED]: node_modules/metro-hermes-compiler/src/emhermesc.js:77 throw ex; Error: EMFILE: too many open files</title>
      <link>https://topherpedersen.blog/2024/04/26/solved-node_modules-metro-hermes-compiler-src-emhermesc-js77-throw-ex-error-emfile-too-many-open-files/</link>
      <description>If you’re a React-Native developer and you’re running into this error when attempting to run your Metro bundler, “too many open files,” the fix is really simple: You need to install watchman.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://topherpedersen.blog/2024/04/26/solved-node_modules-metro-hermes-compiler-src-emhermesc-js77-throw-ex-error-emfile-too-many-open-files/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Machines</title>
      <link>http://funcall.blogspot.com/2024/04/state-machines.html</link>
      <description>A blog about computers, functional languages, Lisp, and Scheme.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://funcall.blogspot.com/2024/04/state-machines.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I made a new backplane for my Terramaster F2-221 NAS | codedbearder</title>
      <link>https://codedbearder.com/posts/f3-backplane/</link>
      <description>In a previous post I wrote about how I setup NixOS on my Terramaster F2-221 instead of using the included TOS provided by Terramaster. This in itself was quite simple as the NAS contains Intel J3355, a standard X86_64 CPU. However the NAS only has 2 SATA connectors, both of which were being used for the 4TB hard drives, so I had to resort to plugging in an external USB SSD for storing the operating system. This quickly became a little annoying to make room for this external SSD behind the NAS and make sure it’s always plugged in when something is moved around in the shelf where I keep it, so I wanted to see if I could come up with a better solution.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://codedbearder.com/posts/f3-backplane/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-Scooters: First Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://maxmautner.com/2024/04/26/electric-scooters.html</link>
      <description>I’m obsessed with technologies that improve my freedom of movement. Cars are incredible floating living rooms, bicycles make one feel like you can fly, and walking/running are the healthiest form of self-propelled movement imaginable. They all have tradeoffs though: cost (fuel, storage/real estate, depreciation) safety (both to the operator &amp;amp; those around them) maximum speed maxmium acceleration ease of operation comfort (sweating, protection from inclement weather) In spite of existing for many years now, I had not tried using an electric push scooter up until recently. My curiousity with these scooters converted to obsession when it was pointed out to me how similar e-bikes are to scooters. In fact scooters even have kits to install seatposts that make them look like e-bikes/mopeds. So I research and narrowed down to a reasonable entry-level purchase, a Segway Air T-15: With a coupon code and free shipping, the total price came out to be $186.34. This is about the cheapest you can go for such a vehicle, with the following constraits: 12 miles per hour maximum speed (20kph) ~8 mile maximum range @ the max speed (13km) 23 pounds It was delivered to my residence in suburban San Francisco in 3 calendar days: I promptly unboxed it and rode it to get a coffee: And another coffee: My first impressions are: it is a lot of fun it could be very dangerous it won’t reach 100% penetration of usage (same is true of cars, bicycles) it has very limited ability to carry cargo besides a human (backpack/messenger bag maybe) it can be parked anywhere–for better or worse combined with transit, this can take me anywhere (although the battery prohibits bringing it on planes) the charger is so small, not a problem to bring with you to often double your range by charging at your office (for example) the cost is ridiculous cheap. Not a problem to buy another if stolen or maintenance becomes burdensome lithium-ion battery fire is something to research more closely–this is a serious safety problem theft risk is lower, as you can fold or bring it into a wide variety of places &amp;amp; you do not have to carry a lock Electric scooters deliver on personal financial savings in a massive way relative to other transportation options. In contrast to expensive car parking, you can securely store and charge your scooter inside of your residence: I tested out grocery shopping with a backpack at my local grocery store: Carrying a days worth of groceries in my backpack was not a problem and did not cause stability issues as I rode home. In the weeks after purchase I used my scooter in combination with my local commuter train. Folding it made it trivial to carry on to the train, although at 23 pounds this model is much lighter than typical scooters I saw in my research (more common is 40 pounds or more). Overall, I would highly recommend electric scooters with the caveat that safety is possibly the biggest hurdle to overcome: I hope to address in a future blogpost about what safety precautions can be taken both personally and societally to elevate electric scooters as a preferred transportation option. Hope this helps!</description>
      <author> (Max Mautner)</author>
      <guid>https://maxmautner.com/2024/04/26/electric-scooters.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;lt;span class=&amp;quot;dquo&amp;quot;&amp;gt;“&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;Reading” Articles via Podcast&amp;#160;Software</title>
      <link>https://blog.nawaz.org/posts/2024/Apr/reading-articles-via-podcast-software/</link>
      <description>Posted on Fri 26 April 2024</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.nawaz.org/posts/2024/Apr/reading-articles-via-podcast-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I search in 2024</title>
      <link>https://vickiboykis.com/2024/04/25/how-i-search-in-2024/</link>
      <description>The unbundling of Big Search is here</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vickiboykis.com/2024/04/25/how-i-search-in-2024/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC0 Textures &amp;amp; Models | Share Textures</title>
      <link>https://www.sharetextures.com/</link>
      <description>ShareTextures.com Free PBR Textures and models archive include wood, stone, wall, ground, metal and more. Download free models and textures up to 4K resolution.</description>
      <author> (Share Textures)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sharetextures.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LogLog Games</title>
      <link>https://loglog.games/blog/leaving-rust-gamedev/</link>
      <description>Disclaimer: This post is a very long collection of thoughts and problems I&amp;#39;ve had over the years, and also addresses some of the arguments I&amp;#39;ve been repeatedly told. This post expresses my opinion the has been formed over using Rust for gamedev for many thousands of hours over many years, and multiple finished games. This isn&amp;#39;t meant to brag or indicate success, but rather just show there has been more than enough effort put into Rust, to dispel the the commonly said &amp;quot;once you gain enough experience it&amp;#39;ll all make sense&amp;quot; argument.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://loglog.games/blog/leaving-rust-gamedev/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding state to the update notification pattern, part 8 - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240426-00/?p=109705</link>
      <description>Comparing the two algorithms.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240426-00/?p=109705</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:00:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Formation Site</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2925/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2925/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:00:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;90% of Java services have critical or severe security vulnerabilities&amp;quot;... or about the quirks of security reporting – JVM Weekly vol. 80</title>
      <link>https://vived.substack.com/p/90-of-java-services-have-critical</link>
      <description>Today, only one topic, but that&amp;#39;s because I wanted to share my broader thoughts on the latest Datadog report.</description>
      <author> (Artur Skowronski)</author>
      <guid>https://vived.substack.com/p/90-of-java-services-have-critical</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collection Performance: Is LINQ Always the Most Performant Choice?</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/04/26/collection-performance-is-linq-always-the-most-performant-choice/</link>
      <description>The article explores the performance implications of using LINQ for collection queries, finding that a conventional foreach() loop outperforms LINQ by 1.75 times in identifying items matching a giv…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2024/04/26/collection-performance-is-linq-always-the-most-performant-choice/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:01:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Abstractions: an Increase API design principle — Increase</title>
      <link>https://increase.com/articles/no-abstractions</link>
      <description>This post explains one of the core design principle of Increase’s API, dubbed No Abstractions, which we’ve found useful as our product and company scale.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://increase.com/articles/no-abstractions</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 09:00:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Class Event Subscriptions in Marten</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/04/25/first-class-event-subscriptions-in-marten/</link>
      <description>This feature has been planned for Marten for years, but finally happened this month because a JasperFx Software client had a complicated multi-tenanted integration need for this as part of a compli…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/04/25/first-class-event-subscriptions-in-marten/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing a functionality with GitHub Copilot for Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-developer-community/implementing-a-functionality-with-github-copilot-for-visual/ba-p/4123406</link>
      <description>Here&amp;#39;s a new article and short video where Gwyn &amp;quot;GPS&amp;quot; Pe&amp;#241;a-Siguenza demonstrates how to create a new functionality in a .NET application with the..</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/103560)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-developer-community/implementing-a-functionality-with-github-copilot-for-visual/ba-p/4123406</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 13 Params Collections</title>
      <link>https://reflectionit.nl/blog/2024/csharp-13-params-collections</link>
      <description>With the version 17.10.0 Preview 3.0 of Visual Studio Preview you can test some new C# 13 features. In this blog I will explain the params Collection feature as documented in this proposal. To use this feature you have to set the LangVersion in your csproj file to preview.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://reflectionit.nl/blog/2024/csharp-13-params-collections</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Type pattern matching in C# and TypeScript</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/04/type-pattern-matching-in-c-and.html</link>
      <description>Although C# remains an object-oriented programming language, it has incorporated more and more functional techniques over the years. One of ...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/04/type-pattern-matching-in-c-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing identity: Exploring application types and authentication flows | Microsoft Entra Identity Platform</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/app-types-and-auth-flows/</link>
      <description>Building on the foundations of our IAM basics blog post, discover the world of application types and authentication flows.</description>
      <author> (Adam Matthews)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/app-types-and-auth-flows/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>