<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>FlatBuffers: FlexBuffers</title>
      <link>https://google.github.io/flatbuffers/flexbuffers.html</link>
      <description>FlatBuffers was designed around schemas, because when you want maximum performance and data consistency, strong typing is helpful.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://google.github.io/flatbuffers/flexbuffers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 15:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A little bit of plain Javascript can do a lot</title>
      <link>https://jvns.ca/blog/2020/06/19/a-little-bit-of-plain-javascript-can-do-a-lot/</link>
      <description>I’ve never worked as a professional frontend developer, so even though I’ve been writing HTML/CSS/JS for 15 years for little side projects, all of the projects have been pretty small, sometimes I don’t write any Javascript for years in between, and I often don’t quite feel like I know what I’m doing.
Partly because of that, I’ve leaned on libraries a lot! Ten years ago I used to use jQuery, and since maybe 2017 I’ve been using a lot of vue.</description>
      <author> (Julia Evans)</author>
      <guid>https://jvns.ca/blog/2020/06/19/a-little-bit-of-plain-javascript-can-do-a-lot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 14:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How is NSA breaking so much crypto?</title>
      <link>https://freedom-to-tinker.com/2015/10/14/how-is-nsa-breaking-so-much-crypto/</link>
      <description>There have been rumors for years that the NSA can decrypt a significant fraction of encrypted Internet traffic. In 2012, James Bamford published an article quoting anonymous former NSA officials stating that the agency had achieved a “computing breakthrough” that gave them “the ability to crack current public encryption.” The Snowden documents also hint at some extraordinary capabilities: they show that NSA has built extensive infrastructure to intercept and decrypt VPN traffic and suggest that the agency can decrypt at least some HTTPS and SSH connections on demand.</description>
      <author> (Alex Halderman and Nadia Heninger)</author>
      <guid>https://freedom-to-tinker.com/2015/10/14/how-is-nsa-breaking-so-much-crypto/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 14:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning My MacBook After 16800 Hours of Use!</title>
      <link>https://quanticdev.com/articles/cleaning-macbook-after-16800-hours-of-use/</link>
      <description>I estimated that I had used my mac for approximately 10 hours a day, 5 days a week, 48 weeks a year, for 7 years straight, for a total for whopping 16800 hours. I have written the first versions of most of the software components of my startup using this computer. And all this time, this machine worked without a hiccup. It was never repaired, and I never opened the back cover. However, its battery is getting swollen, so it is a good time to upgrade to a newer machine. Before recycling the machine, I decided to open it for once and vacuum the fans to see if it makes a difference. Oh boy, did it make a difference! You can find the fan test in the video if you want to check it out.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://quanticdev.com/articles/cleaning-macbook-after-16800-hours-of-use/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 13:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor @chrissainty on GitHub Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sponsors/chrissainty</link>
      <description>I'm a software engineer 💻 who's passionate about open source. I'm also a writer ✍, speaker 🗣, and creator &amp; maintainer of Blazored 🔥</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sponsors/chrissainty</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 11:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing Notes and Townhall Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1mudOqz5EKc</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1mudOqz5EKc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 08:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Rector - Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sarah_Rector</link>
      <description>Sarah Rector (March 3, 1902 – July 22, 1967) was an African American member of the Muscogee (Creek) Nation, best known for being the "Richest Colored Girl in the world" or the "millionaire girl a member of the race".[1][2]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sarah_Rector</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 08:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teach Yourself Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://teachyourselfcs.com/</link>
      <description>All the resources you need to give yourself a world class computer science education</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://teachyourselfcs.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 07:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jsmouret/grpc-over-webrtc</title>
      <link>https://github.com/jsmouret/grpc-over-webrtc</link>
      <description>gRPC over WebRTC. Contribute to jsmouret/grpc-over-webrtc development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/jsmouret/grpc-over-webrtc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 06:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ramsey County corrections officers of color say they were barred from guarding Derek Chauvin</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/minority-officers-kept-from-monitoring-chauvin-in-jail/571391442/</link>
      <description>As Derek Chauvin arrived, all officers of color were ordered to a separate floor, and a supervisor told one of them that they would be a potential "liability," according to charges filed by eight Ramsey County corrections officers.</description>
      <author> (Liz Sawyer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.startribune.com/minority-officers-kept-from-monitoring-chauvin-in-jail/571391442/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 06:04:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite CLI Tools</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/switowski/my-favorite-cli-tools-4p4g</link>
      <description>Previously, I wrote about my favorite Mac apps. But I spend half of my time in the terminal, and I ha...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/switowski/my-favorite-cli-tools-4p4g</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 06:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear types are merged in GHC</title>
      <link>https://www.tweag.io/blog/2020-06-19-linear-types-merged/</link>
      <description>Looking back at the journey which brought us there, and forward to what still lies ahead.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tweag.io/blog/2020-06-19-linear-types-merged/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 02:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banjo Obayomi - Grimoire:  A Data Centric Blogging Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iOEK_FqBHb0</link>
      <description>In this talk, I will describe how I built a new blogging platform focused on creating interactive data stories. By the end, you will understand the tools and techniques used to build a serverless first platform and a new place to communicate with data.
---
Banjo is a Senior Research Engineer at Two Six Labs, where he develops platform solutions for productizing various researched-based projects. Banjo is passionate about operationalizing data aka DataOps and has started a podcast and meetup around data.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iOEK_FqBHb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nate Rose - Innovating on OUR STEM Education</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ooF4sxflT6c</link>
      <description>What is an IQ? Why do we take the SATs? How did it end up even being a metric of childhood success? Senior Software Engineer walks through 100 years of modern education and how it has been systematically flawed for underrepresented communities. NSBE Jr. Bay Area takes on this challenge by innovating outside of the parameters of the education system.

My talk challenges the status quo of common core, standardized tests and looks to technologists, innovators and entrepreneurs as a call to action to remodel education for people of color.
---
Nate Rose is a Senior Software Engineer with a background in DevOps, Data Engineering, and Distributed Cloud Infrastructure Systems. Outside of engineering at Ripple, he does research in neurotechnology, casually overfits ML models and works with building education equity through non-profits like AI4ALL and NSBE.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ooF4sxflT6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 02:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angie Jones - Keynote: The Reality of Developing an Artificial World</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rF3_4SexVlY</link>
      <description>Our world is changing. Artificial intelligence is being employed in just about all walks of life - from virtual assistants to self-driving cars. How does this new way of life impact software development?

In this talk, Angie will share her personal journey in learning how to test the AI-based applications that we develop, and highlight just how important it is to society that we get this right.
---
Angie Jones is a Senior Developer Advocate who specializes in test automation strategies and techniques. She shares her wealth of knowledge by speaking and teaching at software conferences all over the world, writing tutorials and technical articles on angiejones.tech, and leading the online learning platform, Test Automation University.

As a Master Inventor, Angie is known for her innovative and out-of-the-box thinking style which has resulted in more than 25 patented inventions in the US and China. In her spare time, Angie volunteers with Black Girls Code to teach coding workshops to young girls in an effort to attract more women and minorities to tech.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rF3_4SexVlY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 02:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Okhakumhe - Intellectual Property rights in the technology sector</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iWj_iCCcKdU</link>
      <description>The slave who made the whiskey, Jack Daniel, was not given recognition until 2016. This recognition was 150 years late. This is not an isolated incident as there are several instances in the past where inventions and ideas by black people were stolen.

So much has changed all over the world, especially in countries where the rights of black people have always been a subject of constant discourse. A 2016 study found that black Americans “apply for patents at nearly half the rate of whites". This shows that a lot still needs to done to protect the intellectual property rights of black people in tech.

In my session, I will address the subject of what intellectual property rights are, how they can be protected and what the black community can do to help facilitate this protection. I will speak on the jurisdictional nature of intellectual property rights and why it is important for black people in tech to apply for triadic or international patents.
---
Mark is a trained lawyer and mediator actively building a career in tech &amp; innovation, corporate practice, intellectual property, dispute resolution, and impact investment.

He enjoys speaking to people on emerging areas of law, Impact Investment, branding and personal development, startups, and Sustainable Development Goals (SDG), especially SDGs 1, 4, 7, 11 and 16.

As a humanitarian, he volunteered at one of Nigeria's correctional facilities as an ad-hoc lecturer with the National Open Univerisity. He also volunteered with the Legal Aid Council of Nigeria to take on pro bono cases, and DEVATOP to tackle human trafficking.

He was a judge at the regional rounds of the Philip Jessup International Law Moot Competition. More recently, he was part of the #AfricaVsVirus Ideathon and also the COVID-19 Challenge organised by UNICEF.

He has advised various tech startups on matters of compliance and IP protection. He is open to all types of engagements including speaking, volunteer, and full or part-time career opportunities.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iWj_iCCcKdU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 02:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackfacts and The Wakanda Technology Platform   Technology By Us For Us About Us</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ELmtRSuM7FM</link>
      <description>The subject of 'Inclusion' in the Tech Industry is a hot topic today.

In 1990, when my employer at the time declined to offer to reimburse me for programming classes I was thinking of taking, the only thing I asked them for was to amend my employment agreement to not claim ownership of anything I built, or in other words, not get in my way.

They agreed, and I taught myself to code by reading books and launched a programming career that has now spanned close to three decades.

When I was able to quit that job a couple of years later from revenue from a product I wrote in my basement apartment, I realized the wide open opportunities available in the world of technology, and committed myself to creating technologies to help 'Bring Communities of Color Into the Information Age.'

Today, I have built a technology platform that powers my 23-years-running website Blackfacts.com, designed to provide Black schools, organizations and businesses with content and technology services on a global basis.

This talk will describe and demonstrate some of the components of the platform, called the Wakanda Technology Platform, inspired by a sub-text of the fictional nation of Wakanda, who was able to protect its culture and people because they were in possession of superior technology.
---
Ken Granderson
Digital Visionary, Pioneer and Entrepreneur

Dale Dowdie
Co-Founder/CEO</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ELmtRSuM7FM</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 02:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town Hall</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kf10WMZP2ds</link>
      <description>#BlackLivesMatter: What Next

Lance Goudy
Goudy Management Group, CEO

Kimeka Campbell
Young Professionals of Color--Greater Harrisburg

Michael Brown
Senior Software Engineer at Microsoft

Nicole Tinson

Franklin Rosado</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kf10WMZP2ds</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 02:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning Interviews - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tldhogjeAnE</link>
      <description>Danny Thompson will prerecord a series of interviews, which will stream consecutively during this time.

Guests:
- Marcelo Rocha DaSilva
- Joe Santos
- Justin Samuels</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tldhogjeAnE</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 01:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning Interviews - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HKW_ZqqNVQU</link>
      <description>Danny Thompson will prerecord a series of interviews, which will stream consecutively during this time.

Guests:
- Christina Beckford
- Natalie Davis
- Erika Myles
- Lerin Hampton
- Lawrence Lockhart
- Sultan DevCareers over 70 Laptops given away</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HKW_ZqqNVQU</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 01:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does culturally responsive teaching mean in an online environment?</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7nYMoAs98Es</link>
      <description>Culturally responsive teaching (CRT) is an instructional approach that seeks to ensure academic success while developing students' sense of culture and social-political awareness. CRT allows students to see themselves in the curriculum and assignments provided by the teacher. In the online and traditional classroom, CRT provides opportunities for students to learn how to value their culture. During this time in America, it is especially important for students to have opportunities to express themselves while using online technology.
---
Dr. Tressa Matthews
Clever Math LLC , Co-Founder
Dr. Tressa Matthews has been teaching math to middle and high school students for 18 years. She has a Bachelor's in Industrial and Operations Engineering from the University of Michigan. After two years in corporate America, she decided to pursue her passion for secondary mathematics. After earning a Masters and Doctorate in Education, Dr. Matthews co-founded Clever Math to provide online educational services for students and parents. She has a passion for building supportive classroom environments for African-American students which became the basis for her doctoral research.

Dr.  Jennifer Banks
Clever Math, LLC Co-Founder
Jennifer D. Banks, Ph.D. is currently the Mathematics and Science Coordinator for Washtenaw County. For nearly 20 years, Dr. Banks has served as a teacher and instructional leader at various levels. Jennifer is passionate about empowering educators and learners, to ensure that all students have equitable access and opportunities to learn and engage in high-quality rigorous mathematics. Over the past ten years, she has intently worked to expand K-12 educators' understanding of culturally responsive instruction, specifically in the area of mathematics. Dr. Banks holds a bachelors' Industrial and Operations Engineer and worked in the corporate sector for 4 years. She has been recognized by various community organizations for her work in expanding access to STEM education, including the Rhonda Walker Foundation and DAPCEP. She currently serves on the Michigan Early Mathematics Taskforce and is a lecturer for the University of Michigan. Furthermore, she is the Co-Founder of Clever Math, LLC.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7nYMoAs98Es</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shukri Abdullahi - Through Programming I became a better Artist</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJJcMpsYWUI</link>
      <description>Code is my new favorite artistic medium. Creating art was once the only activity that put me in a flow state that was until I started coding. Programming like art is full of processes, speed bumps, errors, eustress, and joy. My skills as an artist have proven to be an asset in programming. While programming has cultivated artistic improvements.

What: More artists should learn to code.
Why: You’re skills as an artist are an asset in the programming world and vice versa programming can cultivate artistic improvements.
How: Personal Anecdote detailing skills.
---
Shukri Abdullahi is a Self-Taught Programmer and Multi-disciplinary Artist based in New York.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJJcMpsYWUI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Us, Without Us: Addressing Tech’s Shortcomings in Creating Equity for Black People</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qzc6D8NZo-4</link>
      <description>Many consider technology to be the “great equalizer”, but it’s evident that Black people are not benefiting at the same rates as others. This session will discuss how the forces that limit Black people’s ability to navigate the physical also prevent us from exerting agency via the digital. Together, we’ll discuss the ways that anti-Blackness is replicated in technology, the discrepancies faced by Black communities due to the digital divide, and the changes required for us to have a more equitable future. Because we can never fully benefit if technology continues to be made for us, without us.
---
Jacqueline Gibson
Software Engineer focusing on accessibility at Microsoft

Jacqueline is a Digital Equity Advocate &amp; Software Engineer building change from the code up. She's interested in leveraging technology for social good, particularly identifying ways in which current technology maintains social inequities and working to eliminate these biases. She strives to understand what is necessary to create systems that everyone, regardless of ability, can use with ease.

She graduated with dual degrees in Computer Science and African &amp; African Diaspora Studies from the University of Texas at Austin. She's currently developing tools to create accessible applications for Android, Windows, and web as part of Microsoft's Accessibility Insights team.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qzc6D8NZo-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSS Box</title>
      <link>https://rssbox.herokuapp.com/</link>
      <description>Get RSS feeds for services</description>
      <author> (Stefan Sundin)</author>
      <guid>https://rssbox.herokuapp.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawood Iddris - The future of tech and how to keep in touch while it evolves</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_eJzPgThuM8</link>
      <description>Building and leading communities, one of the common pitfall many people fall in whiles trying to gain grounds in technology has to do with learning every new thing they hear of. It is quite clear that these people think they are doing the right thing until they realize years have passed by and yet they can't build a single project with their knowledge gained. As several people share their stories with me about the same problem, I notice I was in their shoes for my first two years career. In this session, we will address how people who find their self in this category can progress while staying up to date with all new technologies.
---
Dawoodiddris is a software developer, passionately creating products and changing lives with his soft and technical skills by training others in event, workshops and providing platforms for coders to think beyond the limit.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_eJzPgThuM8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashley Janelle - Why You're Not Landing That UX Role</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PA1Rho75qzQ</link>
      <description>As a UX Coach, the question I am asked the most is "How do I actually land that UX role?". While the question is broad, I've identified a few areas where aspiring UX Designers really struggle getting their foot in the door at companies of their choice. In my talk, attendees will walk away being able to not only identify their key problem areas, but have action items around overcoming those obstacles to land their dream role.
---
As a seasoned User Experience and User Interface Designer, Ashley Janelle focuses on designing customer centered experiences that target her users everyday challenges. At Caterpillar Inc., Ashley taps into user needs while designing solutions that allow them to save time, money, and increase their productivity.

As a UX coach and course creator, she’s developed an online course, “Learn UX Online in 16 Weeks” to help aspiring UX designers go from beginner to experienced UX Designers to land jobs at top companies. Using her UX expertise and passion for working with people, Ashley’s not only helped others land their dream roles, but build the confidence to become successful UX Designers.


https://www.ashleyjanelle.com</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PA1Rho75qzQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorting and information theory</title>
      <link>https://guille.site/sorting-bounds.html</link>
      <description>Category: math</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://guille.site/sorting-bounds.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse-engineering and comparing two Game Boy audio amplifier chips</title>
      <link>http://www.righto.com/2020/06/reverse-engineering-and-comparing-two.html</link>
      <description>  The Nintendo Game Boy contains an audio amplifier chip for sound through a speaker or headphones. In this post, I reverse-engineer this ch...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.righto.com/2020/06/reverse-engineering-and-comparing-two.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head Up, Head Down</title>
      <link>https://martinrue.com/head-up-head-down/</link>
      <description>There are few things more enjoyable to me than the mental solitude that hand-delivers interesting shower thoughts, or that let’s me sit in a bustling coffee shop contemplating life.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martinrue.com/head-up-head-down/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Advantage of the App Store That’s Gone</title>
      <link>https://inessential.com/2020/06/20/one_advantage_of_the_app_store_thats_gon</link>
      <description>The best part of the App Store, years ago, from this developer’s point of view, was that it was easy to charge money for an app. No need to set up a system — just choose the price, and Apple takes care of everything. So easy!</description>
      <author> (by Brent Simmons)</author>
      <guid>https://inessential.com/2020/06/20/one_advantage_of_the_app_store_thats_gon</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kara Swisher: ‘Is It Finally Hammer Time for Apple and Its App Store?’</title>
      <link>https://daringfireball.net/linked/2020/06/19/swisher-app-store-hey</link>
      <description>Link to: https://www.nytimes.com/2020/06/19/opinion/apple-app-store-hey.html</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://daringfireball.net/linked/2020/06/19/swisher-app-store-hey</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proofs and computation with trees</title>
      <link>https://bor0.wordpress.com/2020/06/20/proofs-and-computation-with-trees/</link>
      <description>In this post, I will make the analogy between trees and proofs and computation. Lately (after a long pause), I started reading Logical Foundations again and started re-doing the exercises for the l…</description>
      <author> (Boro Sitnikovski)</author>
      <guid>https://bor0.wordpress.com/2020/06/20/proofs-and-computation-with-trees/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons Learned: Giving Feedback as an Engineering Manager</title>
      <link>http://alexeymk.com/2020/06/20/lessons-learned-in-giving-feedback-as-an-engineering-manager.html</link>
      <description>“Alexey, do you feel the points you bring up during our post-mortems are productive?” my tech lead asked at our 1:1.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://alexeymk.com/2020/06/20/lessons-learned-in-giving-feedback-as-an-engineering-manager.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 23:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A NVIDIA Engineer In His Spare Time Wrote A Vulkan Driver That Works On Older Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RPi-VK-Driver</link>
      <description>Phoronix is the leading technology website for Linux hardware reviews, open-source news, Linux benchmarks, open-source benchmarks, and computer hardware tests.</description>
      <author> (Written by Michael Larabel in Vulkan on 20 June 2020 at 08:45 AM EDT. 21 Comments)</author>
      <guid>https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=news_item&amp;px=RPi-VK-Driver</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 22:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Dennis Ritchie’s Lost Dissertation - CHM</title>
      <link>https://computerhistory.org/blog/discovering-dennis-ritchies-lost-dissertation/</link>
      <description>Until recently, across a half-century perhaps fewer than a dozen people had ever had the opportunity to read Dennis Ritchie’s dissertation—the intellectual and biographical fork-in-the-road separating an academic career in computer science from the one at Bell Labs leading to C and Unix. Why?</description>
      <author> (David C. Brock)</author>
      <guid>https://computerhistory.org/blog/discovering-dennis-ritchies-lost-dissertation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 20:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 2</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mCrhSBCju4E</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mCrhSBCju4E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 18:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual:  Steve Collins - .NET Core Dependency Injection – The Booster Jab</title>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Milton-Keynes-NET-Meetup-Group/events/271371131/</link>
      <description>Tue, Jul 14, 2020, 7:00 PM: Hello MK.NET folks,We're proud to present another virtual MK .NET meetup for July;As before, we'll be hosting on Zoom.We're excited to be joined by Steve Collins who will b</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.meetup.com/Milton-Keynes-NET-Meetup-Group/events/271371131/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juneteenth Conference - Track 1</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ysmejeF5umg</link>
      <description>https://www.juneteenthconf.com/</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ysmejeF5umg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>