<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - LyalinDotCom/MetadataUpdateHandlersDemo</title>
      <link>https://github.com/LyalinDotCom/MetadataUpdateHandlersDemo</link>
      <description>Contribute to LyalinDotCom/MetadataUpdateHandlersDemo development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (LyalinDotCom)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/LyalinDotCom/MetadataUpdateHandlersDemo</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 21:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Russians want a war?</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/BbR19ZMpSF0</link>
      <description>0:00 - Do Russia needs a war?0:51 - Ukraine versus Russia1:17 - Who controls the Crimea?2:41 - Would you drop a bomb on the US?To show your love:https://www....</description>
      <author> (Langfocus
  
  
  
    Langfocus
  




  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/BbR19ZMpSF0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 20:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RepoDb.PostgreSql.BulkOperations 0.0.9</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/RepoDb.PostgreSql.BulkOperations/</link>
      <description>An extension library that contains the official Bulk Operations of RepoDb for PostgreSQL.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/RepoDb.PostgreSql.BulkOperations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 20:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ziplnk.py</title>
      <link>https://gist.github.com/wybiral/29960f1140bd70c2bffe0c8c4527baf1</link>
      <description>GitHub Gist: instantly share code, notes, and snippets.</description>
      <author> (262588213843476)</author>
      <guid>https://gist.github.com/wybiral/29960f1140bd70c2bffe0c8c4527baf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 20:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://repodb.net/feature/bulkoperations/postgresql</link>
      <description>It is the process of bringing all the data from the application into the database server at once, and at the same time, ignoring some database specific activities behind the scene. Thus gives you maximum performance during the operation.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://repodb.net/feature/bulkoperations/postgresql</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 20:02:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic SBOMs with ko</title>
      <link>https://blog.chainguard.dev/auto-sboms-with-ko/</link>
      <description>For those unfamiliar with ko, it “is a simple, fast container image builder for Go applications;” its objective is to enable developers to stop worrying about containers, and focus on their application. &amp;#160;The philosophy of ko aligns with our mission at Chainguard: to make the software supply chain secure by</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.chainguard.dev/auto-sboms-with-ko/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 19:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Associate, Disputes &amp;amp; Economics (.NET Developer) (Remote)</title>
      <link>https://ankura.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Ankura/job/Senior-Associate--Disputes---Economics--NET-Developer---Remote-_R101851-1</link>
      <description>Ankura is a team of excellence founded on innovation and growth. Ankura is accepting applications for the Senior Associate position to support the Disputes &amp;amp; Economics business group - one of seven practices focused on client delivery services across the Firm. A Senior Associate is responsible for developing and maintaining software written using Microsoft .NET technologies to provide software consulting services to clients. The Senior Associate must be capable of assisting clients with complex information management and analysis challenges by combining software development techniques, sophisticated technology tools, and information management principles. Ankura provides Senior Associates with the opportunity to work collaboratively on diverse teams with other skilled, intelligent, and driven professionals. Ankura is focused on hiring Senior Associates who will serve as the foundation of a growing firm dedicated to its people, culture, and delivering high quality service to clients. ***This opportunity offers a flexible/hybrid work schedule that combines an on-premises (in the office) and remote environment.*** ESSENTIAL DUTIES &amp;amp; RESPONSIBILITIES: Senior Associates are intimately familiar with their clients&amp;#39; big-picture objectives and challenges as well as the smallest details of their organization’s data and IT infrastructure. With this knowledge you are responsible for designing and executing efficient, innovative analytical software solutions to address feature requests and troubleshoot issues. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to: Participating in the entire software development life cycle, designing, developing, configuring, and testing applications. Working with stakeholders to analyze system requirements, prioritize development tasks and plan releases. Performing day-to-day client engagement activities, including interaction with client personnel, internal Ankura team members, and other stakeholders REQUIRED SKILLS &amp;amp; CHARACTERISTICS: Experience with Full Stack Software development using C#, JavaScript, SQL (or another similar stack) Experience with (or desire to learn) Agile development methodologies Familiarity with source code control, code reviews and continuous integration Strong problem-solving and analytical skills Excellent communication (written and verbal), mathematical, and organizational skills Ability to produce high quality work while managing multiple/evolving tasks and/or re-prioritized deadlines Hard-working, self-motivated, thoughtful, collaborative, with a positive outlook and confidence Ankura is proud to be an equal opportunity employer committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive environment where mutual respect and collaboration is paramount. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to age, race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, disability, protected veteran status, national origin, or any other legally protected status.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ankura.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Ankura/job/Senior-Associate--Disputes---Economics--NET-Developer---Remote-_R101851-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 19:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux developers patch security holes faster than anyone else, says Google Project Zero | ZDNet</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/google-project-zero-finds-linux-developers-patch-security-holes-faster-than-anyone-else/</link>
      <description>Linux programmers do a better job of patching security holes than programmers at Apple, Google, and Microsoft.</description>
      <author> (https://twitter.com/sjvn)</author>
      <guid>https://www.zdnet.com/article/google-project-zero-finds-linux-developers-patch-security-holes-faster-than-anyone-else/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 18:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online exif data viewer</title>
      <link>https://www.metadata2go.com/</link>
      <description>This online metadata viewer will show you all hidden metadata info of audio, video, document, ebook &amp;amp; image files.</description>
      <author> (online-metadata.com)</author>
      <guid>https://www.metadata2go.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 15:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nix: An Idea Whose Time Has Come</title>
      <link>https://revelry.co/insights/development/nix-time/</link>
      <description>In which I shill you Nix, a purely functional package manager.</description>
      <author> (Julien Urraca)</author>
      <guid>https://revelry.co/insights/development/nix-time/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 13:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Populate an Array With the Same Value in C#</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-populate-array-same-value/</link>
      <description>In this article, we are going to learn how to populate an array with the same value in C# using different thecnhiques.</description>
      <author> (()x)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-populate-array-same-value/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 09:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fritz.InstantAPIs 0.1.0</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Fritz.InstantAPIs/</link>
      <description>A library that generates Minimal API endpoints for an Entity Framework context.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Fritz.InstantAPIs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 08:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Protection Software | Varonis</title>
      <link>https://www.varonis.com/use-case/ransomware-prevention</link>
      <description>Varonis fights ransomware by limiting access and detecting threats to your on-prem and cloud-hosted data. </description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.varonis.com/use-case/ransomware-prevention</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 07:03:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - gristlabs/grist-core: Grist is the evolution of spreadsheets.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/gristlabs/grist-core</link>
      <description> Grist is the evolution of spreadsheets. . Contribute to gristlabs/grist-core development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (gristlabs)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/gristlabs/grist-core</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 05:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chorded Keyboard</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2583/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2583/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 04:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Shadow Profiles</title>
      <link>https://www.cesifo.org/en/publikationen/2022/working-paper/facebook-shadow-profiles</link>
      <description>Data is often at the core of digital products and services, especially when related to online advertising. This has made data protection and privacy a major policy concern. When surfing the web, consumers leave digital traces that can be used to build user profiles and infer preferences. We quantify the extent to which Facebook can track web behavior outside of their own platform. The network of engagement buttons, placed on third-party websites, lets Facebook follow users as they browse the web. Tracking users outside its core platform enables Facebook to build shadow profiles.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.cesifo.org/en/publikationen/2022/working-paper/facebook-shadow-profiles</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 03:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Hanselman on TikTok</title>
      <link>https://www.tiktok.com/@shanselman/video/7065944760246324527?_r=1</link>
      <description>Reply to @truetalelive too much free time @talaexe ? LOL I also have a 9-5 and make stuff as a hobby. You keep being awesome!</description>
      <author> (shanselmanScott Hanselman &amp;#183; 19h ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiktok.com/@shanselman/video/7065944760246324527?_r=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 03:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Tools for GitHub Notifications</title>
      <link>https://neat.run/blog/best-tools-for-github-notifications</link>
      <description>How to harness GitHub notifications to review, merge, and ship faster. Comparison of the best tools, including Octobox, DevHub, Gitify, and Neat.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://neat.run/blog/best-tools-for-github-notifications</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 03:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Value, not Quantity</title>
      <link>http://agileotter.blogspot.com/2022/02/maximize-value-not-quantity.html</link>
      <description>I was chatting with a manager who was once a PO on a team I coached many years ago. This is only my best memory of the conversation (I didn&amp;#39;...</description>
      <author> (Agileotter)</author>
      <guid>http://agileotter.blogspot.com/2022/02/maximize-value-not-quantity.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build tool requirements</title>
      <link>https://ekhabarov.com/post/build-tool-requirements/</link>
      <description>Some thoughts about the perfect build world.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ekhabarov.com/post/build-tool-requirements/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spam Accounts in 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.joshbeckman.org/what-spam-accounts-look-like-in-2022/</link>
      <description>I fell down this rabbit hole while trying to investigate some spammy account behavior on Narro. I&amp;#39;ve been running Narro as a SAAS application with a free trial for several years now, which means I have dealt with a lot of spam account creation. Every once in a while, when</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.joshbeckman.org/what-spam-accounts-look-like-in-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralization Is a Quality</title>
      <link>https://aditya.rs/2022/02/19/decentralization-is-a-quality/</link>
      <description>Decentralization is a quality. Looking at the constituents of crypto as decentralization + money provides some valuable methods to analyze the prevalence of platforms in the crypto space.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://aditya.rs/2022/02/19/decentralization-is-a-quality/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repos that always pass their tests</title>
      <link>https://tylercipriani.com/blog/2022/02/17/its-still-not-rocket-science/</link>
      <description>Losing faith in your build hobbles a software project. Continual test failures create alarm fatigue—people habituate to ignoring test results.</description>
      <author> (Tyler Cipriani)</author>
      <guid>https://tylercipriani.com/blog/2022/02/17/its-still-not-rocket-science/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New graduate EU offers - is It possible to negotiate?</title>
      <link>https://ludoro.github.io/blog/career/2022/02/14/newgrad.html</link>
      <description>Discussing compensation and negotiation for new graduates in EU.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ludoro.github.io/blog/career/2022/02/14/newgrad.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kash Goudarzi</title>
      <link>https://kg.dev/thoughts/weaponizing-decision-fatigue</link>
      <description>My website.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kg.dev/thoughts/weaponizing-decision-fatigue</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Every Programmer Absolutely, Positively Needs to Know About Encodings and Character Sets to Work With Text</title>
      <link>https://kunststube.net/encoding/</link>
      <description>If you are dealing with text in a computer, you need to know about encodings. Period. Yes, even if you are just sending emails. Even if you are just receiving emails. You don&amp;#39;t need to understand every last detail, but you must at least know what this whole &amp;quot;encoding&amp;quot; thing is about. And the good news first: while the topic can get messy and confusing, the basic idea is really, really simple.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kunststube.net/encoding/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 01:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical bruteforce of military grade AES-1024 Remote Rhein Ruhr Stage</title>
      <link>https://pretalx.c3voc.de/rc3-2021-r3s/talk/QMYGR3/</link>
      <description>The DataVault solution is a stand-alone application used by default as an encryption solution for many Sony, SanDisk, and Lexar products and as well used by some libraries to offer data security. This solution was not analyzed before, and the strong security claims were not assessed to match the reality. This presentation gives background details of the analysis and the context which brought us to perform the analysis. The method for reverse engineering and inspecting the DataVault solution will be presented. It turned out that the key derivation function was PBKDF2 using 1000 iteration of MD5 to derive the encryption key. The salt used to derive the keys is constant and hardcoded in all the solutions and all the vendors. This makes it easier for an attacker to guess the user password of a vault using time/memory tradeoff attack techniques such as rainbow tables and to re-use the tables to retrieve passwords for all users using the software. The implementation itself was incorrect and even with a randomly generated unique salt, it would be effortless to recover the password of a user. Other flaws of the key derivation function will be discussed and compared with nowadays good practices.

The data encryption method was also found to be malleable, allowing malicious modifications of files in a vault without any detection. No data integrity mechanism was set up. The settings of the full version of the software allows choosing between 4 different levels of security, namely AES-128, 256, 512 and 1024 bits. The encryption method has been reversed and is a CTR like construction based on AES-128 using a single key. Multiple iterations of encryptions are chained with the keys obtained by the key derivation function used as IVs. However, it turned out after the analysis that all these modes offer only a security level of 128-bit.

A plugin in John the ripper software to allow everyone to &amp;quot;practically brute force military grade AES-1024&amp;quot; will be released at the time of the presentation.

We have a continuous, welcomed, and constructive collaboration with the ENCSecurity company. During this presentation, we will explain the coordinated disclosure process, which was difficult since it impacted several vendors and some deployed libraries. The solution which was provided for the correction will be presented and compared to the best practice standards along with a discussion of the process of selecting the specific improvements.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pretalx.c3voc.de/rc3-2021-r3s/talk/QMYGR3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 23:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>