<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>PySkyWiFi: completely free, unbelievably stupid wi-fi on long-haul flights | Robert Heaton</title>
      <link>https://robertheaton.com/pyskywifi/</link>
      <description>The plane reached 10,000ft. I took out my laptop, planning to peruse the internet and maybe do a little work if I got really desperate.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robertheaton.com/pyskywifi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating an already-completed asynchonous activity in C++/WinRT, part 1 - The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240709-00/?p=109961</link>
      <description>The simplest version.</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240709-00/?p=109961</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DB Browser for SQLite</title>
      <link>https://sqlitebrowser.org/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sqlitebrowser.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C++ Design Patterns for Low-latency Applications Including High-frequency Trading</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2309.04259</link>
      <description>This work aims to bridge the existing knowledge gap in the optimisation of latency-critical code, specifically focusing on high-frequency trading (HFT) systems. The research culminates in three main contributions: the creation of a Low-Latency Programming Repository, the optimisation of a market-neutral statistical arbitrage pairs trading strategy, and the implementation of the Disruptor pattern in C++. The repository serves as a practical guide and is enriched with rigorous statistical benchmarking, while the trading strategy optimisation led to substantial improvements in speed and profitability. The Disruptor pattern showcased significant performance enhancement over traditional queuing methods. Evaluation metrics include speed, cache utilisation, and statistical significance, among others. Techniques like Cache Warming and Constexpr showed the most significant gains in latency reduction. Future directions involve expanding the repository, testing the optimised trading algorithm in a live trading environment, and integrating the Disruptor pattern with the trading algorithm for comprehensive system benchmarking. The work is oriented towards academics and industry practitioners seeking to improve performance in latency-sensitive applications.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 8 Sep 2023])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2309.04259</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entering text in the terminal is complicated</title>
      <link>https://jvns.ca/blog/2024/07/08/readline/</link>
      <description>Entering text in the terminal is complicated</description>
      <author> (Julia Evans)</author>
      <guid>https://jvns.ca/blog/2024/07/08/readline/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 08:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rye: a Hassle-Free Python Experience</title>
      <link>https://rye.astral.sh/</link>
      <description>An Experimental Package Management Solution for Python</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rye.astral.sh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 08:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Round Trips are Evil</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/07/08/network-round-trips-are-evil/</link>
      <description>As Houston gets drenched by Hurricane Beryl as I write this, I’m reminded of a formative set of continuing education courses I took when I was living in Houston in the late 90’s and plo…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2024/07/08/network-round-trips-are-evil/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use VS Code to develop and build a .NET application</title>
      <link>https://www.roundthecode.com/dotnet-tutorials/how-to-use-vs-code-develop-build-dotnet-application</link>
      <description>How to develop a .NET application with VS Code, including how to install the .NET SDK, adding extensions and how to build and run an app.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.roundthecode.com/dotnet-tutorials/how-to-use-vs-code-develop-build-dotnet-application</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystify history with GitHub Copilot commit explanations - Visual Studio Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/demystify-history-with-github-copilot-commit-explanations/</link>
      <description>GitHub Copilot can analyze your code differences and produce concise summaries that highlight the key points.</description>
      <author> (Jessie Houghton)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/demystify-history-with-github-copilot-commit-explanations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:01:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capture and review .Net Profiler Traces on App Service (Windows)</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/capture-and-review-net-profiler-traces-on-app-service-windows/ba-p/4185377</link>
      <description>This blog emphasizes the process of gathering profiler traces for applications hosted on App Service that are experiencing slowness. It also provides guidance..</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/2559632)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/apps-on-azure-blog/capture-and-review-net-profiler-traces-on-app-service-windows/ba-p/4185377</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify Your .NET Aspire Caching With Metalama</title>
      <link>https://blog.postsharp.net/aspire-caching-metalama</link>
      <description>Learn how to cache method results in a .NET Aspire distributed cloud-native app with minimal boilerplate in this step-by-step guide.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.postsharp.net/aspire-caching-metalama</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:01:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failing to map: a tale of false hopes in mmap land</title>
      <link>https://ayende.com/blog/201345-B/failing-to-map-a-tale-of-false-hopes-in-mmap-land?Key=a76ad01a-ac92-462a-bce1-89907cf6aa1a</link>
      <description>I usually talk about the things that I do that were successful. Today I want to discuss something that I tried but failed at. Documenting failed approaches i...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ayende.com/blog/201345-B/failing-to-map-a-tale-of-false-hopes-in-mmap-land?Key=a76ad01a-ac92-462a-bce1-89907cf6aa1a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS0012: The type &amp;#39;System.Object&amp;#39; is defined in an assembly that is not referenced.</title>
      <link>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/07/cs0012-type-systemobject-is-defined-in.html</link>
      <description>A fter referencing a .NET Standard 2.0 project in a .NET 4.8 ASP.NET MVC project, the project failed ant runtime with the following error me...</description>
      <author> (Share)</author>
      <guid>https://bartwullems.blogspot.com/2024/07/cs0012-type-systemobject-is-defined-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should interfaces be asynchronous?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/07/08/should-interfaces-be-asynchronous/</link>
      <description>Async and await are notorious for being contagious. Must all interfaces be Task-based, just in case?</description>
      <author> (Mark Seemann)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.ploeh.dk/2024/07/08/should-interfaces-be-asynchronous/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Right Kind of Stubborn</title>
      <link>https://paulgraham.com/persistence.html</link>
      <description>Successful people tend to be persistent. New ideas often don&amp;#39;t work
at first, but they&amp;#39;re not deterred. They keep trying and eventually
find something that does.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://paulgraham.com/persistence.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more boot loader: Please use the kernel instead DevConf.CZ</title>
      <link>https://pretalx.com/devconf-cz-2024/talk/W3AVCT/</link>
      <description>We are working on a new scheme to replace the GRUB bootloader with a fast, secure, Linux-based, user-space solution: nmbl (for no more boot loader).
Most people are familiar with GRUB, a powerful, flexible, fully-featured bootloader that is used on multiple architectures (x86_64, aarch64, ppc64le OpenFirmware). Although GRUB is quite versatile and capable, its features create complexity that is difficult to maintain, and that both duplicate and lag behind the Linux kernel while also creating numerous security holes. On the other hand, the Linux kernel, which has a large developer base, benefits from fast feature development, quick responses to vulnerabilities and greater overall scrutiny.
We (Red Hat boot loader engineering) will present our solution to this problem, which is to use the Linux kernel as its own bootloader. Loaded by the EFI stub on UEFI, and packed into a unified kernel image (UKI), the kernel, initramfs, and kernel command line, contain everything they need to reach the final boot target. All necessary drivers, filesystem support, and networking are already built in and code duplication is avoided. 
We will showcase the work done so far, and ask you for your feedback and use cases.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pretalx.com/devconf-cz-2024/talk/W3AVCT/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Mini Monitor for a Pi</title>
      <link>https://noamzeise.com/2024/07/05/mini-monitor.html</link>
      <description>This post outlines how I used a small 2 inch display as a monitor for my pi. Where it can display tty terminals and X desktops and applications as if it was a normal screen connected over hdmi. My overall goal is to have a sort of handheld “console” that I can connect a keyboard to and use as a normal computer. This post implements the display functionality needed to fulfill part of the goal. I lay out the steps needed for interacting with the display over spi and the issues I encountered trying to use it like a monitor. The end result is a system service that runs on startup, consuming 2.5 mb of ram and ~2% of the CPU. It also respects the X display power management system (dpms) to save on battery life by going to sleep and turning the backlight off.</description>
      <author> (05 Jul 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://noamzeise.com/2024/07/05/mini-monitor.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Burnout, Mental Health, And Not Being Okay — Ludicity</title>
      <link>https://ludic.mataroa.blog/blog/on-burnout-mental-health-and-not-being-okay/</link>
      <description>This blog did so many hits last week that the host platform experienced timeouts. I&amp;#39;ve been invited onto podcasts, and offered both small technical projects and journalism work, of all things. It was a crazy time. But the internet moves on, as it always does, and I am left, as we all always are, to figure out what to write about next.</description>
      <author> (Published on July 2, 2024)</author>
      <guid>https://ludic.mataroa.blog/blog/on-burnout-mental-health-and-not-being-okay/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroPython Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://www.tolidano.com/micropython-smartwatch.html</link>
      <description>While browsing Hacker News one day, I came across this post. It shows an intense segment of getting MicroPython running on a $3 smartwatch. I was not interested in so much work. But maybe you are. Either way, it got me thinking about MicroPython and tiny portal computing environments.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.tolidano.com/micropython-smartwatch.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extrinsic Hallucinations in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://lilianweng.github.io/posts/2024-07-07-hallucination/</link>
      <description>Hallucination in large language models usually refers to the model generating unfaithful, fabricated, inconsistent, or nonsensical content. As a term, hallucination has been somewhat generalized to cases when the model makes mistakes. Here, I would like to narrow down the problem of hallucination to be when the model output is fabricated and not grounded by either the provided context or world knowledge.
There are two types of hallucination:
In-context hallucination: The model output should be consistent with the source content in context.</description>
      <author> (Lilian Weng)</author>
      <guid>https://lilianweng.github.io/posts/2024-07-07-hallucination/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Values</title>
      <link>https://benji.org/family-values</link>
      <description>What makes Family, Family.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://benji.org/family-values</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&amp;#39;t use a $5 range outlet for EV charging</title>
      <link>http://nerdralph.blogspot.com/2024/07/dont-use-5-range-outlet-for-ev-charging.html</link>
      <description>Many level 2 home chargers plug into a NEMA 14-50R outlet, which is the same type a kitchen range would plug into.&amp;#160; A 40A EVSE is considered...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://nerdralph.blogspot.com/2024/07/dont-use-5-range-outlet-for-ev-charging.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enchanting the Workplace</title>
      <link>https://irfankurtagic.wordpress.com/2024/07/02/enchanting-the-workplace/</link>
      <description>Transform your workplace with a Hogwarts-inspired system of rewards and punishments! By earning points for achievements and losing them for rule-breaking, employees stay motivated and disciplined. …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://irfankurtagic.wordpress.com/2024/07/02/enchanting-the-workplace/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making My Own Wedding Rings</title>
      <link>https://geoff.greer.fm/2024/07/07/making-my-own-wedding-rings/</link>
      <description>I’m getting married pretty soon, and I figured it’d be fun to make my own rings. I’d seen a Nile Red video where he made purple gold, and the process seemed simple enough: Make a mold, pour some mol…</description>
      <author> (Geoff Greer)</author>
      <guid>https://geoff.greer.fm/2024/07/07/making-my-own-wedding-rings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personality Basins | near.blog</title>
      <link>https://near.blog/personality-basins/</link>
      <description>Personality basins are the mental model that I use to reason about humans within their environment. They are an elucidating way to think about many concepts: from modelling why people are they way they are, how they change over time, how mental illnesses and addiction function along with how we should look for their cures, and how the attention economy optimizes itself to consume all of your free time.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://near.blog/personality-basins/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using an LLM and RAG to Wring Insights From My Posts</title>
      <link>https://www.joshbeckman.org/blog/using-an-llmand-rag-to-wring-insights-from-my-posts</link>
      <description>I’ve been using large language models - LLMs - and retrieval-augmented generation - RAG - at work for over a year now. I use it to write code, to refine my ideas and writing, and we have been building products on top of it.

It’s long overdue fo...</description>
      <author> (https://www.joshbeckman.org/about/)</author>
      <guid>https://www.joshbeckman.org/blog/using-an-llmand-rag-to-wring-insights-from-my-posts</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anna: A Key-Value Store For Any Scale</title>
      <link>http://muratbuffalo.blogspot.com/2022/04/anna-key-value-store-for-any-scale.html</link>
      <description>This paper (ICDE&amp;#39;18) introduces Anna,  a CALM / CRDT  implementation of a distributed key-value system both at the data structure level as w...</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>http://muratbuffalo.blogspot.com/2022/04/anna-key-value-store-for-any-scale.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rails Add ActiveRecord.after_all_transactions_commit Callback</title>
      <link>https://blog.saeloun.com/2024/07/08/rails-active-record-after_all_transactions_commit/</link>
      <description>ActiveRecord.after_all_transactions_commit ensures specified actions execute only after all database transactions commit, ensuring reliable post-transaction operations.</description>
      <author> (Saeloun Blog)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.saeloun.com/2024/07/08/rails-active-record-after_all_transactions_commit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to count rows read in sqlite</title>
      <link>https://newbeelearn.com/blog/counting-row-reads-in-sqlite/</link>
      <description>How to count number of rows read in a query in sqlite</description>
      <author> (pdyc)</author>
      <guid>https://newbeelearn.com/blog/counting-row-reads-in-sqlite/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specific Software</title>
      <link>https://saml.dev/blog/specific-software</link>
      <description>The best kind of software is limited in scope.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://saml.dev/blog/specific-software</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WE HAVE MADE SCIENCE!</title>
      <link>https://sfruf.github.io/2024/05/31/science-parody.html</link>
      <description>We Have Made Science!</description>
      <author> (REDACTED BY AUTHORS)</author>
      <guid>https://sfruf.github.io/2024/05/31/science-parody.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Text Formatting in .NET MAUI with Label FormattedText</title>
      <link>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/07/09/dotnet-maui-developer-tips-text-formatting-in-label/</link>
      <description>This is the fifth article in the recently started series titled&amp;#160;Developer Tips, which offers concise hints to enhance productivity. All the articles in this series can be accessed from&amp;#160;he…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://egvijayanand.in/2024/07/09/dotnet-maui-developer-tips-text-formatting-in-label/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 20:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number Line Branch</title>
      <link>https://xkcd.com/2956/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> (About)</author>
      <guid>https://xkcd.com/2956/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 20:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>