<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>EARN IT is a direct attack on end-to-end encryption</title>
      <link>https://blog.cryptographyengineering.com/2020/03/06/earn-it-is-an-attack-on-encryption/</link>
      <description>Yesterday a bipartisan group of U.S. Senators introduced a new bill called the EARN IT act. On its face, the bill seems like a bit of inside baseball having to do with legal liability for informati…</description>
      <author> (Matthew Green)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.cryptographyengineering.com/2020/03/06/earn-it-is-an-attack-on-encryption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Storage for $2 / TB / Mo</title>
      <link>https://blog.sia.tech/cloud-storage-for-2-tb-mo-8a34043e93bb?gi=8df5c4d18671</link>
      <description>Explore the model that shows why Sia storage will stay below $2/TB/Mo for the long term.</description>
      <author> (https://blog.sia.tech/@davidvorick)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.sia.tech/cloud-storage-for-2-tb-mo-8a34043e93bb?gi=8df5c4d18671</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Media Disclosure Statement | TurgenSec</title>
      <link>https://turgensec.com/virgin-media-disclosure-statement/</link>
      <description>This is our statement in response to the two most common questions sent to us by journalists following our disclosure to Virgin Media of a breach on 28th of February. This included personal information corresponding to approximately nine hundred thousand UK residents.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://turgensec.com/virgin-media-disclosure-statement/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 23:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The beautiful machine</title>
      <link>http://fabiensanglard.net/the_beautiful_machine/index.html</link>
      <description>March 6, 2020</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://fabiensanglard.net/the_beautiful_machine/index.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 23:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zip Files: History, Explanation and Implementation</title>
      <link>https://www.hanshq.net/zip.html</link>
      <description>I have been curious about data compression and the Zip file format in particular for a long time. At some point I decided to address that by learning how it works and writing my own Zip program. The implementation turned into an exciting programming exercise; there is great pleasure to be had from creating a well oiled machine that takes data apart, jumbles its bits into a more efficient representation, and puts it all back together again. Hopefully it is interesting to read about too.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanshq.net/zip.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 22:38:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Media breach 'linked customers to porn'</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-51768577</link>
      <description>Researchers say a breached Virgin Media database contained more details than the company suggested.</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/bbcnews)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-51768577</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 22:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zynga faces class action suit over massive Words With Friends hack</title>
      <link>https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2020/03/05/zynga-faces-class-action-suit-over-massive-words-with-friends-hack/</link>
      <description>It’s charging subpar password security and lousy user notification: Zynga has yet to notify users to warn them of the breach, the suit says.</description>
      <author> (by
			Lisa Vaas)</author>
      <guid>https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2020/03/05/zynga-faces-class-action-suit-over-massive-words-with-friends-hack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 22:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Variables: var and let and const</title>
      <link>https://www.prestonlamb.com/blog/javascript-variables-var-and-let-and-const</link>
      <description>There are three ways to create variables in a JavaScript application: using var, using let, or using const. This will not be a post trying to convince you which one you should use, or arguing about what is best. It’s just good to know about the differences and what it means when you use the different options.</description>
      <author> (Preston Lamb)</author>
      <guid>https://www.prestonlamb.com/blog/javascript-variables-var-and-let-and-const</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 21:31:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caffeine Boosts Problem-Solving Ability  but Not Creativity, Study Indicates</title>
      <link>https://news.uark.edu/articles/52447/caffeine-boosts-problem-solving-ability-but-not-creativity-study-indicates</link>
      <description>While the drug is known to increase focus, alertness and motor skills, its effect on creative thinking had not been studied previously.
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://news.uark.edu/articles/52447/caffeine-boosts-problem-solving-ability-but-not-creativity-study-indicates</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 21:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>renderman (RenderMan) | Keybase</title>
      <link>https://keybase.io/renderman</link>
      <description>renderman (RenderMan) is now on Keybase, an open source app for encryption and cryptography.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://keybase.io/renderman</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 21:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build apps for free with Azure Cosmos DB Free Tier | Azure Cosmos DB Blog</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/build-apps-for-free-with-azure-cosmos-db-free-tier/</link>
      <description>This blog post was co-authored by Nikisha Reyes-Grange, Senior Product Marketing Manager, Azure Marketing.
Introducing Azure Cosmos DB Free Tier
Looking to build a new app, develop and test, or run small production workloads with Azure Cosmos DB? Our new Free Tier makes it easy to get started with no cost and save money as you build and grow new apps.</description>
      <author> (Deborah ChenProgram Manager, Azure Cosmos DBFollow Deborah)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/build-apps-for-free-with-azure-cosmos-db-free-tier/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 20:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home | Jovica Turčinović</title>
      <link>https://www.turcinovic.com/</link>
      <description>Hi, I am Jovica. I have been engaged in software design since 1993. I am an experienced Microsoft .NET Developer in:
- .NET programming language, SQL (SQL Server, MySql, DAL), Knockout JS, Umbraco CMS, EPiServer CMS, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), Software Architecture, Software Design Patterns, Software Testing, Project Organization</description>
      <author> (Jovica Turčinović)</author>
      <guid>https://www.turcinovic.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 19:02:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As we work to protect public health, we also need to protect the income of hourly workers who support our campus - Microsoft on the Issues</title>
      <link>https://blogs.microsoft.com/on-the-issues/2020/03/05/covid-19-microsoft-hourly-workers/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has asked its employees who can work from home to do so due to the impact of COVID-19. Despite this meaning a reduced need for many of the hourly workers vital to our daily operations, we’ve decided that Microsoft will continue to pay their regular pay during this period. We hope other large companies will take a similar approach to counteract the economic effect COVID-19 will have on hourly workers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blogs.microsoft.com/on-the-issues/2020/03/05/covid-19-microsoft-hourly-workers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 18:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is Facebook's mysterious "Lan Tim 2"?</title>
      <link>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2020/03/who-is-facebooks-mysterious-lan-tim-2/</link>
      <description>Facebook has an interesting feature. It will let you see which companies have associated your off-Facebook activity with your Facebook account. If you visit: you’ll see what companies are sni…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2020/03/who-is-facebooks-mysterious-lan-tim-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLIDE : In Defense of Smart Algorithms over Hardware Acceleration for Large-Scale Deep Learning Systems</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/1903.03129</link>
      <description>Deep Learning (DL) algorithms are the central focus of modern machine
learning systems. As data volumes keep growing, it has become customary to
train large neural networks with hundreds of millions of parameters to maintain
enough capacity to memorize these volumes and obtain state-of-the-art accuracy.
To get around the costly computations associated with large models and data,
the community is increasingly investing in specialized hardware for model
training. However, specialized hardware is expensive and hard to generalize to
a multitude of tasks. The progress on the algorithmic front has failed to
demonstrate a direct advantage over powerful hardware such as NVIDIA-V100 GPUs.
This paper provides an exception. We propose SLIDE (Sub-LInear Deep learning
Engine) that uniquely blends smart randomized algorithms, with multi-core
parallelism and workload optimization. Using just a CPU, SLIDE drastically
reduces the computations during both training and inference outperforming an
optimized implementation of Tensorflow (TF) on the best available GPU. Our
evaluations on industry-scale recommendation datasets, with large fully
connected architectures, show that training with SLIDE on a 44 core CPU is more
than 3.5 times (1 hour vs. 3.5 hours) faster than the same network trained
using TF on Tesla V100 at any given accuracy level. On the same CPU hardware,
SLIDE is over 10x faster than TF. We provide codes and scripts for
reproducibility.</description>
      <author> (Authors:Beidi Chen, Tharun Medini, James Farwell, Sameh Gobriel, Charlie Tai, Anshumali Shrivastava)</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/1903.03129</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My New Role as Senior Program Manager for .NET Data</title>
      <link>https://blog.jeremylikness.com/blog/new-role-dotnet-data-pm/</link>
      <description>I recently accepted a new role at Microsoft as Senior Program Manager for .NET Data. This post explains the history behind the decision, what I'll be doing and how you can help.</description>
      <author> (Empowering developers to be their best.📅 Mar 6, 2020
🕘 5 min read
💬 898 words)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jeremylikness.com/blog/new-role-dotnet-data-pm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuckDuckGo is good enough for regular use | www.bitlog.com</title>
      <link>https://www.bitlog.com/2020/03/06/duckduckgo-is-good-enough-for-regular-use/</link>
      <description>I haven't tried a new search engine since I tried Bing in 2009. It was time to find out how good DuckDuckGo is in 2020. What was the biggest difference that I found?</description>
      <author> (by jakevoytko)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bitlog.com/2020/03/06/duckduckgo-is-good-enough-for-regular-use/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>piCorePlayer</title>
      <link>https://www.picoreplayer.org/</link>
      <description>pCP is a high quality audio player via Squeezelite. The use of a DAC will greatly improve sound quality (up to to 384 kHz /24 bit). The player can be controlled via touch screen, phone, tablet, iPad, computer or IR/USB remote control. If you add more players you can enjoy a advanced multi-room audio system that can play in sync or play different streams in separate zones.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.picoreplayer.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:03:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mopidy</title>
      <link>https://mopidy.com/</link>
      <description>The extensible music server</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mopidy.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:03:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Odyssey of Stark and Melody</title>
      <link>https://xoofx.com/blog/2020/03/05/stark-melody-dotnet-sel4/</link>
      <description>What would it take these days to build a prototype of a new language and operating system built on top of it, just for fun? This idea started to emerge during the 2018 winter holidays:...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xoofx.com/blog/2020/03/05/stark-melody-dotnet-sel4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stark - Language And Frontend Compiler - Prototype 2019</title>
      <link>https://xoofx.com/blog/2020/03/06/stark-language-frontend-compiler/</link>
      <description>This is the first part of the blog post series about The Odyssey of Stark and Melody and more specifically, about the development of the syntax of the Stark language and its front-end compiler, based...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://xoofx.com/blog/2020/03/06/stark-language-frontend-compiler/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krisp | Noise Cancelling App</title>
      <link>https://account.krisp.ai/ref/u/uc1d377d47</link>
      <description>Krisp is a superior noise cancelling app that mutes background noise in real time calls. With one click it removes all extraneous noises for incoming and outgoing calls.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://account.krisp.ai/ref/u/uc1d377d47</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 12:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invesco | About | Invesco on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://www.invesco.com/socialmedia/</link>
      <description>» 
		Invesco on Social Media</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.invesco.com/socialmedia/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 10:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update 181</title>
      <link>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-181/</link>
      <description>This is the big one. It's all HIBP and Project Svalbard top to bottom this week and I've chosen to exclude everything else in its favour. This is just such an essential part of not just the HIBP narrative, but indeed the narrative of my career and what gets me</description>
      <author> (Troy Hunt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.troyhunt.com/weekly-update-181/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 08:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Guide to Securing Remote Access</title>
      <link>https://duo.com/resources/ebooks/the-essential-guide-to-securing-remote-access?key=th1</link>
      <description>With the convenience of remote access, users are vulnerable to threats like phishing, brute-force attacks and password-stealing malware. Download our guide to learn how to secure remote access, mitigate these attacks and avoid an expensive data breach.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://duo.com/resources/ebooks/the-essential-guide-to-securing-remote-access?key=th1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 08:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft.NET.Sdk.Functions 3.0.4</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Microsoft.NET.Sdk.Functions/3.0.4</link>
      <description>Build SDK for Azure Functions</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/Microsoft.NET.Sdk.Functions/3.0.4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CQRS: Refactoring Queries without Repositories - CodeOpinion</title>
      <link>https://codeopinion.com/cqrs-refactoring-queries-without-repositories/</link>
      <description>Should you eager or lazy load navigation properties in your Aggregate Root? The answer is neither by using queries without Repositories or Aggregate Roots.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://codeopinion.com/cqrs-refactoring-queries-without-repositories/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 8 nullable reference types - Red Hat Developer</title>
      <link>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2020/03/05/c-8-nullable-reference-types/</link>
      <description>Explore how C# 8 lets us express whether a variable shouldn’t be null, and when it can be null.</description>
      <author> (By Tom Deseyn March 5, 2020March 5, 2020)</author>
      <guid>https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2020/03/05/c-8-nullable-reference-types/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love in a time of Corona Virus - Tips, Tricks and Best Practices for Working Remotely</title>
      <link>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/LoveInATimeOfCoronaVirusTipsTricksAndBestPracticesForWorkingRemotely.aspx</link>
      <description>In this time of the Corona Virus and COVID-19, Microsoft has taken the unprecedented move of shutting down their ...</description>
      <author> (Scott Hanselman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hanselman.com/blog/LoveInATimeOfCoronaVirusTipsTricksAndBestPracticesForWorkingRemotely.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of tiny databases</title>
      <link>https://blog.acolyer.org/2020/03/04/millions-of-tiny-databases/</link>
      <description>Millions of tiny databases, Brooker et al., NSDI’20 This paper is a real joy to read. It takes you through the thinking processes and engineering practices behind the design of a key part of …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.acolyer.org/2020/03/04/millions-of-tiny-databases/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Code for PowerShell 7 | PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/visual-studio-code-for-powershell-7/</link>
      <description>We are excited to announce that we have released a major update to the PowerShell extension for Visual Studio Code. This release contains months of architectural work that first shipped in our PowerShell Preview extension in November of 2019, along with incremental bug fixes in the intervening months.</description>
      <author> (Sydney SmithFollow Sydney)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/visual-studio-code-for-powershell-7/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Lights &amp; Lighting Kits - Free Global Shipping | Light My Bricks</title>
      <link>https://www.lightmybricks.com/</link>
      <description>Light My Bricks offers the best and largest range of LEGO lights, including LED light kits for LEGO sets, and DIY components for your own LEGO Creations. Free global shipping available, including US, UK, Europe &amp; Asia.</description>
      <author> (Light My Bricks)</author>
      <guid>https://www.lightmybricks.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 03:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>