<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>slither.io</title>
      <link>http://slither.io/</link>
      <description>The smash-hit game! Play with millions of players around the world and try to become the longest of the day!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://slither.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 12:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor @egil on GitHub Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://github.com/sponsors/egil?sc=t&amp;sp=chrissainty</link>
      <description>Support egil’s open source work</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/sponsors/egil?sc=t&amp;sp=chrissainty</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 11:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fastest way do debug .net code without sources.</title>
      <link>https://cezarypiatek.github.io/post/debug-without-sources-part-one/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://cezarypiatek.github.io/post/debug-without-sources-part-one/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 11:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Asked To Report Recipt of any Unsolicited Packages of Seeds</title>
      <link>http://www.vdacs.virginia.gov//press-releases-200724-seeds.shtml</link>
      <description>July 24, 2020
                      
Public Asked To Report Receipt of any Unsolicited Packages of Seeds
                        Contact: Michael Wallace, 804.786.1904</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.vdacs.virginia.gov//press-releases-200724-seeds.shtml</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 08:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>adam-mcdaniel/oakc</title>
      <link>https://github.com/adam-mcdaniel/oakc</link>
      <description>A portable programming language with an incredibly compact backend - adam-mcdaniel/oakc</description>
      <author> (adam-mcdaniel)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/adam-mcdaniel/oakc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 08:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>froggey/Mezzano</title>
      <link>https://github.com/froggey/Mezzano</link>
      <description>An operating system written in Common Lisp. Contribute to froggey/Mezzano development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (froggey)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/froggey/Mezzano</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 07:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doing Stupid Stuff with GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://devopsdirective.com/posts/2020/07/stupid-github-actions/</link>
      <description>TL;DR: DevOps doesn’t have to be all work and no play. I built 5 stupid (but fun!) GitHub actions… because why not?
The full code for these actions can all be found in this GitHub repo. I encourage you to fork and/or add issues/PRs with impractical actions of your own!
I also recorded a video about this project on YouTube. ← Check out the video and subscribe if you are into this sort of thing 🙏
</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://devopsdirective.com/posts/2020/07/stupid-github-actions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 07:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LunrCore 2.3.8</title>
      <link>https://www.nuget.org/packages/LunrCore/2.3.8</link>
      <description>A .NET Core port of Oliver Nightingale's lunr.js library, a lightweight full-text indexing library that is "a bit like Solr, but much smaller and not as bright." Icon adapted from https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Internal_Structure_of_the_Moon.JPG by Iqbal Mahmud under Creative Commons Attribution Share Alike 4.0 International</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.nuget.org/packages/LunrCore/2.3.8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 04:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promo Data Breach FAQ</title>
      <link>https://support.promo.com/en/articles/4276475-promo-data-breach-faq</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://support.promo.com/en/articles/4276475-promo-data-breach-faq</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 03:02:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of the Vulkan Graphics API: Why Rendering a Triangle is Complicated</title>
      <link>https://liamhinzman.com/blog/vulkan-fundamentals</link>
      <description>Last week, my dad was asking me why I was proud of this triangle on my laptop.</description>
      <author> (Liam Hinzman)</author>
      <guid>https://liamhinzman.com/blog/vulkan-fundamentals</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 00:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working From Home</title>
      <link>https://mikestone.me/working-from-home</link>
      <description>Back in March, my kids were super excited for a few days off for their Spring Break. I took a week off so I could be home with them and n...</description>
      <author> (Mike Stone)</author>
      <guid>https://mikestone.me/working-from-home</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Four Actions I Took To Attract 72,000 Followers</title>
      <link>https://joshspector.com/how-to-get-more-followers/</link>
      <description>How I used content, community, and focus to grow an audience.</description>
      <author> (https://joshspector.com/author/admin/)</author>
      <guid>https://joshspector.com/how-to-get-more-followers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking the Bureaucracy to Get Stuff Done</title>
      <link>https://www.zainrizvi.io/blog/hacking-the-bureaucracy-to-get-stuff-done/</link>
      <description>The Dangerous Professional finds the seams between the policies, and slips inside them to Get Stuff Done</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.zainrizvi.io/blog/hacking-the-bureaucracy-to-get-stuff-done/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art Of Learning For Software Developers</title>
      <link>https://thevaluable.dev/learning-developer-efficiently-effectively/</link>
      <description>As developers, learning is essential: how to learn effectively, efficiently, and have fun doing so?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thevaluable.dev/learning-developer-efficiently-effectively/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Money With Blogging?</title>
      <link>https://rajasimon.io/how-to-make-money-with-blogging/</link>
      <description>Make money with writing blog post that you enjoy.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rajasimon.io/how-to-make-money-with-blogging/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dance training is superior to repetitive physical exercise in inducing brain plasticity in the elderly</title>
      <link>https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0196636</link>
      <description>Animal research indicates that a combination of physical activity and sensory enrichment has the largest and the only sustaining effect on adult neuroplasticity. Dancing has been suggested as a human homologue to this combined intervention as it poses demands on both physical and cognitive functions. For the present exploratory study, we designed an especially challenging dance program in which our elderly participants constantly had to learn novel and increasingly difficult choreographies. This six-month-long program was compared to conventional fitness training matched for intensity. An extensive pre/post-assessment was performed on the 38 participants (63–80 y), covering general cognition, attention, memory, postural and cardio-respiratory performance, neurotrophic factors and–most crucially–structural MRI using an exploratory analysis. For analysis of MRI data, a new method of voxel-based morphometry (VBM) designed specifically for pairwise longitudinal group comparisons was employed. Both interventions increased physical fitness to the same extent. Pronounced differences were seen in the effects on brain volumes: Dancing compared to conventional fitness activity led to larger volume increases in more brain areas, including the cingulate cortex, insula, corpus callosum and sensorimotor cortex. Only dancing was associated with an increase in plasma BDNF levels. Regarding cognition, both groups improved in attention and spatial memory, but no significant group differences emerged. The latter finding may indicate that cognitive benefits may develop later and after structural brain changes have taken place. The present results recommend our challenging dance program as an effective measure to counteract detrimental effects of aging on the brain.</description>
      <author> (Kathrin Rehfeld   ,)</author>
      <guid>https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0196636</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I would grow Gumroad – Min-Kyu Jung</title>
      <link>https://mkjung.com/blog/gumroad</link>
      <description>Let’s say Sahil is right, and that the market is the biggest determinant of growth. If Gumroad's growth is restricted by the size of the indie creator market, then one way for Gumroad to ensure its future growth is to actively grow the indie creator market itself.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mkjung.com/blog/gumroad</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab a Shitty Rod and Start Fishing — Dickie Bush</title>
      <link>https://www.dickiebush.com/articles/fishing</link>
      <description>Few things flood my brain with dopamine more than planning. My brain basks in this planning process because it feels so productive, but involves minimal mental effort.   The antidote? When I find myself gathering gear, I grab a shitty rod and start fishing.</description>
      <author> (by Richard Bush)</author>
      <guid>https://www.dickiebush.com/articles/fishing</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Brain = Your Dog?</title>
      <link>https://www.jamalx31.com/post/your-brain-your-dog</link>
      <description>You got a new dog, he’s very smart. So you decided to call him Brain. You love Brain, he’s your best friend now, and you always do things together. Everything would be perfect if Brain didn’t have this little problem; He gets distracted very easily, and when you go out for a walk, he pulls you around. No matter how tight you hold the leash, he always wins. It doesn’t stop there, and most often you find yourself following Brain rather than the other way around.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.jamalx31.com/post/your-brain-your-dog</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Bergeron | Java Obfuscation: A Pattern Language</title>
      <link>https://www.joe-bergeron.com/posts/Java%20Obfuscation:%20A%20Pattern%20Language/</link>
      <description>I recently took it upon myself to decompile and attempt to deobfuscate the relatively substantial Java codebase of a much-loved childhood MMO, a game which still manages to
attract a sizeable playerbase, despite its age. (Take a guess at what game I'm talking about!) By no means am I the first to attempt this; many third-party clients exist for
this game, some even open-source. My goal with this project wasn't to do anything new, or even to improve on the deobfuscations and client rewrites that already exist. Mostly,
I just wanted to see how it's done, if I could do it, and how, in theory, one might go about programtically integrating with the game's API. The point of this post is not about
the specifics of this game's implementation. Rather, it's about some tricky (read: evil) obfuscation techniques that I've discovered while working through the decompiled Java bytecode.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.joe-bergeron.com/posts/Java%20Obfuscation:%20A%20Pattern%20Language/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>plant99/felicette</title>
      <link>https://github.com/plant99/felicette</link>
      <description>Satellite imagery for dummies. Contribute to plant99/felicette development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (plant99)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/plant99/felicette</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Finally Started Listening to Podcasts Every Day – The Hulry</title>
      <link>https://hulry.com/building-podcasts-habit/</link>
      <description>Read how I finally got into the habit of listening to podcasts every day with a simple habit-building technique.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hulry.com/building-podcasts-habit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>canhorn/EventHorizon.Blazor.TypeScript.Interop.Generator</title>
      <link>https://github.com/canhorn/EventHorizon.Blazor.TypeScript.Interop.Generator</link>
      <description>This project shows off creating a Blazor Interop C# Generator, has a sample against the BabylonJS library. - canhorn/EventHorizon.Blazor.TypeScript.Interop.Generator</description>
      <author> (canhorn)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/canhorn/EventHorizon.Blazor.TypeScript.Interop.Generator</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 20:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse engineering tools for .NET applications</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@pelock/reverse-engineering-tools-for-net-applications-a28275f185b4</link>
      <description>The set of tools for .NET reverse engineering is very different from classic tools used for the reversing of native x86 / x64 applications…</description>
      <author> (https://medium.com/@pelock)</author>
      <guid>https://medium.com/@pelock/reverse-engineering-tools-for-net-applications-a28275f185b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 20:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Component lifecycles – Blazor University</title>
      <link>https://blazor-university.com/components/component-lifecycles/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blazor-university.com/components/component-lifecycles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 18:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperTails/langcraft</title>
      <link>https://github.com/SuperTails/langcraft</link>
      <description>Compiler from LLVM IR to Minecraft datapacks. Contribute to SuperTails/langcraft development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (SuperTails)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/SuperTails/langcraft</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 15:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gopiandcode &gt; logs &gt; Bloom filters debunked: Dispelling 30 Years of bad math with Coq!</title>
      <link>https://gopiandcode.uk/logs/log-bloomfilters-debunked.html</link>
      <description>There's this rather nifty feature of modern web browsers (such as
Firefox or Chrome) where the browser will automatically warn the
user if they happen to navigate to a "malicious" URL:</description>
      <author> (Kiran Gopinathan)</author>
      <guid>https://gopiandcode.uk/logs/log-bloomfilters-debunked.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 14:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: LSD Chemist William Leonard Pickard to be Released From Prison</title>
      <link>https://www.psymposia.com/magazine/william-leonard-pickard-lsd/</link>
      <description>Julie Holland (@BellevueDoc) is reporting that LSD-chemist and longtime drug war prisoner, William Leonard Pickard is being released from prison. Pickard has been locked down since 2000 and was slated to serve two life sentences without parole. This story is breaking news and will be updated. </description>
      <author> (|By Russell Hausfeld)</author>
      <guid>https://www.psymposia.com/magazine/william-leonard-pickard-lsd/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 14:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>