<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Native Nova SHA256 bench - HackMD</title>
      <link>https://hackmd.io/u3qM9s_YR1emHZSg3jteQA?view=</link>
      <description>Context: See https://hackmd.io/0gVClQ9IQiSXHYAK0Up9hg?view= for previous Nova benchmarks, with more of a focus on recursion.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://hackmd.io/u3qM9s_YR1emHZSg3jteQA?view=</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Will Make Your Repositories Obsolete</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=F7DtfSsDsjk</link>
      <description>Using repositories in a setup with Entity Framework Core is a no-go from my point of view. The main reason I think this is because the DbContext class alread...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=F7DtfSsDsjk</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:03:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real World Coding Issues: Part 3 – Design, Diagnostics, and Other Common Code Issues</title>
      <link>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/08/14/real-world-coding-issues-part-3-design-diagnostics-and-other-common-code-issues/</link>
      <description>The article discusses real-world coding issues encountered in a contract project. Part 3 covers common coding issues related to design, diagnostics, and other areas, such as globalization, code dup…</description>
      <author> (Published by dotNetDave
		

		
			I live in San Diego, Ca USA			
				View all posts by dotNetDave)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnettips.wordpress.com/2023/08/14/real-world-coding-issues-part-3-design-diagnostics-and-other-common-code-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>371: The Problem with Walled Gardens in Apps</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/371</link>
      <description>There have been a lot of changes in the world of X/Twitter, YouTube, Instagram, and even how our favorite apps work or don&amp;#39;t work without logging in. We discuss this new world walled garden and also the fall of LK-99!</description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/371</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing APIs using ASP.NET Core and OAuth 2.0 DPoP</title>
      <link>https://damienbod.com/2023/08/14/securing-apis-using-asp-net-core-and-oauth-2-0-dpop/</link>
      <description>This article shows how an ASP.NET Core application can access an ASP.NET Core API using OAuth Demonstrating Proof-of-Possession (DPoP). This is a really powerful security enhancement which is relat…</description>
      <author> (damienbod)</author>
      <guid>https://damienbod.com/2023/08/14/securing-apis-using-asp-net-core-and-oauth-2-0-dpop/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#39;I&amp;#39;ve Got Nothing to Hide&amp;#39; and Other Misunderstandings of Privacy</title>
      <link>https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=998565</link>
      <description>In this short essay, written for a symposium in the San Diego Law Review, Professor Daniel Solove examines the nothing to hide argument.  When asked about gover</description>
      <author> (See all articles by Daniel J. SoloveDaniel J. SoloveGeorge Washington University Law School)</author>
      <guid>https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=998565</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Determine .NET Version Programatically - Code Maze</title>
      <link>https://code-maze.com/csharp-dotnet-version-programatically/</link>
      <description>Learn how to determine .NET version information using C# code for your projects in this comprehensive guide.</description>
      <author> (Code Maze)</author>
      <guid>https://code-maze.com/csharp-dotnet-version-programatically/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 07:02:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - spandanb/learndb-py: Learn database internals by implementing it from scratch.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/spandanb/learndb-py</link>
      <description>Learn database internals by implementing it from scratch. - GitHub - spandanb/learndb-py: Learn database internals by implementing it from scratch.</description>
      <author> (spandanb)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/spandanb/learndb-py</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Created the Nerdiest Game Ever | Pier-Luc Brault - Personal Website</title>
      <link>https://plbrault.com/blog-posts/i-created-the-nerdierst-game-ever-en/</link>
      <description>Have you ever wondered what it&amp;#39;s like to be an OS?</description>
      <author> (Pier-Luc Brault2023-08-13&amp;#160;5&amp;#160;minutes)</author>
      <guid>https://plbrault.com/blog-posts/i-created-the-nerdierst-game-ever-en/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring DockLayout from .NET MAUI Community Toolkit – AskXammy</title>
      <link>https://askxammy.com/exploring-docklayout-from-net-maui-community-toolkit/</link>
      <description>While .NET MAUI layouts are extremely useful for developing graphical interfaces, it’s always nice to have additional options for arranging elements on the screen. In this article, you will learn about the DockLayout, a layout provided by the .NET MAUI Community Toolkit!</description>
      <author> (About Leomaris Reyes)</author>
      <guid>https://askxammy.com/exploring-docklayout-from-net-maui-community-toolkit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 06:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recoverable Errors with Result - The Rust Programming Language</title>
      <link>https://doc.rust-lang.org/book/ch09-02-recoverable-errors-with-result.html#a-shortcut-for-propagating-errors-the--operator</link>
      <description>Most errors aren’t serious enough to require the program to stop entirely.
Sometimes, when a function fails, it’s for a reason that you can easily
interpret and respond to. For example, if you try to open a file and that
operation fails because the file doesn’t exist, you might want to create the
file instead of terminating the process.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://doc.rust-lang.org/book/ch09-02-recoverable-errors-with-result.html#a-shortcut-for-propagating-errors-the--operator</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 06:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mi kama sona e toki pona or something</title>
      <link>https://cohost.org/mcc/post/59045-mi-kama-sona-e-toki</link>
      <description>So I stumbled a few weeks ago on this video [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E4y7tf3VJAM] about the world&amp;#39;s smallest conlang and I&amp;#39;ve been thinking about it ever since.

[https://staging.cohostcdn.org/attachment/91c54129-9425-4695-bd68-6f65d83ae793/maxresdefault.jpeg] [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E4y7tf3VJAM]

(You will probably have the idea more than fully by the ten minute mark.)

This fascinated me. I think languages are really interesting but I&amp;#39;m also really bad at them. I cannot hack the memorization. I&amp;#39;ve mostly avoided conlangs (that&amp;#39;s Constructed Languages, like Esperanto or Klingon) because like, oh no, now there&amp;#39;s even more languages for me to fail at memorizing. So like, a language so minimal you can almost learn it by accident, suddenly my ears perk up.

Toki pona is really interesting, on a lot of different axes. It&amp;#39;s a thought experiment in Taoist philosophy that turns out to be actually, practically useful. It&amp;#39;s Esperanto But It Might Actually Work This Time&amp;#185;. It has NLP implications— it&amp;#39;s a human language which feels natural to speak yet has such a deeply logical structure it seems nearly custom-designed for simple computer programs to read and write it&amp;#178;. Beyond all this it&amp;#39;s simply beautiful as an intellectual object—&amp;#160;nearly every decision it makes feels deeply right. It solves a seemingly insoluble problem&amp;#179; and does it with a sense of effortlessness and an implied &amp;quot;LOL&amp;quot; [https://staging.cohostcdn.org/attachment/747b4517-a3cf-438b-a6a0-07ad9e6883fd/Toki_pona.svg.png] at every step.

So what toki pona is. Toki pona is a language designed around the idea of being as simple as it is possible for a language to be. It has 120 words in its original form (now, at the twenty year mark, up to 123), but you can form a lot of interesting sentences with only around twenty or thirty (I know this because this is roughly the size of my current tok vocabulary). The whole tok-&amp;gt;en dictionary fits on seventeen printed pages [https://devurandom.xyz/tokipona/dictionary.html]⁴. There are no conjugations or tenses to memorize. There are no parts of speech, generally: almost every single word can be used as almost any part of speech, drop a pronoun or a preposition⁵ in the right place and it becomes a verb, drop a verb in the right place and it becomes an adjective. There are almost no ambiguities in sentence structure; I&amp;#39;ve only found one significant one so far (using &amp;quot;of&amp;quot; [pi] twice in the same clause) and the community deals with this by just agreeing not to do that. There&amp;#39;s in one sense quite a lot of ambiguity in the vocabulary but in another sense there&amp;#39;s none; for example nena is listed in the dictionary as meaning hill, mountain, button, bump, nose, but the official ideology of Toki Pona is that this is not a word with five definitions, it is a word with exactly one definition, that being the concept encompassing all five of hills, mountains, buttons, bumps, and noses. Toki pona words are not ambiguous, they&amp;#39;re just broad. I will now teach you enough toki pona to understand most sentences (assuming you consult the dictionary [https://devurandom.xyz/tokipona/dictionary.html] as you go) in a paragraph shorter than this one:

Every sentence has an &amp;quot;verb&amp;quot; or action clause. Most sentences also have a subject clause, which goes before the verb separated by &amp;quot;li&amp;quot;. Some sentences also have an &amp;quot;object&amp;quot; or target clause, which goes after the verb clause separated by &amp;quot;e&amp;quot;. So &amp;quot;[subject] li [verb] e [object]&amp;quot;. All three clauses are any number of words, the first word is the noun (or verb) and the rest are adjectives (or adverbs). If the first word in a sentence is mi or sina you can omit the li in that case only. There is no &amp;quot;is&amp;quot;, a sentence like &amp;quot;a flower is red&amp;quot; is just &amp;quot;[a plant] li [red]&amp;quot; because there are no parts of speech and adjectives are verbs. Pronounce everything the way you would in English except &amp;quot;j&amp;quot; sounds like &amp;quot;y&amp;quot;. If you see &amp;quot;tawa&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;lon&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;tan&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;kepeken&amp;quot; in adjective/adverb position that&amp;#39;s a preposition, so treat whatever comes after it as a fourth clause. &amp;quot;a&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;n&amp;quot; are interjections and can go anywhere in a sentence. If you see &amp;quot;o&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;pi&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;la&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;taso, &amp;quot;anu&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;en&amp;quot;, then you&amp;#39;ve found one of the few special words (particles) and you should probably either read the book [https://www.amazon.com/dp/B012M1RLXS/] or watch the jan Misali instructional videos [https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLLIjft6ja7DM70MkOMu56c4Grku7LXR61] on YouTube.

That&amp;#39;s like… almost it!⁶ Watch one youtube video, or read a half page of grammar summary and keep the dictionary open on your phone, and you&amp;#39;re basically ready to jump into conversations. (You&amp;#39;ll need those last six particles to make nuanced sentences, but sentences do not have to be nuanced.) In my own case I watched the Langfocus video linked at the top and then lazily over the next week watched the jan Misali overview [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eLn6LC1RpAo] and two of their instructional videos then read a few chapters of the book, and was already able to construct a full paragraph and be understood by another person:

&amp;gt; o! mi sona e toki pona. mi lukin sona e toki mute... taso mi toki ike e toki ale. toki mute li jo e nimi mute. nimi mute li pona ala tawa mi. toki pona li pona e mi tan ni. toki pona li jo nimi lili. nimi lili li pona e me :)

(Translation: Hello! I am learning toki pona. I&amp;#39;ve tried to learn many languages… but I speak all of the[m] badly. Most languages have a lot of words. Lots of words is not good for me. Toki pona is good for me because of this. Toki pona has few words. Few words is good for me :)⁷)

So that&amp;#39;s week one. By the end of week three (that&amp;#39;ll be this past Sunday) I had hit three milestones:

 * I was able to make a joke in toki pona. Not a good one.
 * When the joke misfired, I was able to successfully toss off an entire complex paragraph rapidly without really thinking about it.
 * Probably a sign I Am Getting It more significant than anything else: I realized that talking on the Discord I was dropping toki pona words into my English sentences solely because the toki pona word seemed to me to communicate a concept I wanted to communicate more precisely than any particular English word.

(That last one actually kind of excited me when I realized, after the fact, that it had been happening for several days before I noticed it.)

All of the above happened on the toki pona Discord, which seems to be the largest and healthiest outpost of toki pona community online⁸ and, I assume therefore, the world. Here&amp;#39;s my toki pona joke; you&amp;#39;ll notice that I begin by preemptively apologizing for it, but by the end it becomes clear I was, at that moment anyway, apparently completely on the Discord&amp;#39;s level:⁹

[https://staging.cohostcdn.org/attachment/d5366ff6-ae17-4c70-a900-a02ac307f108/tokipona_conversation.png]

----------------------------------------

Footnotes

&amp;#185; Esperanto was meant to be an auxillary language simple enough the entire world could learn it as a second language. But it does not seem to me to be actually all that simple to learn (the verb tenses may be free of exceptions, but there are still like six of them) and it seems hard to convince myself to study it when I could put that effort toward a more widespread language. Toki Pona on the other hand is a language simple enough the entire world actually could learn it, had it reason to, and the buy-in cost in time is a lot lower. Meanwhile Toki Pona just seems to get certain international-accessibility things right, probably due to the advantage of having over a century of conlang practice largely inspired by Esperanto to draw from. The difference that&amp;#39;s most interesting to me, but which I&amp;#39;m also least qualified to evaluate, is that the Toki Pona author had some basic familiarity with, and gave Toki Pona input from, east Asian languages. Both Toki Pona and Esperanto draw roots from a variety of languages but in Esperanto&amp;#39;s case this winds up being mostly European languages, mostly Italian, whereas Toki Pona has Mandarin and Cantonese in its mix. Both languages were intended to have a minimal, universal phonology but Esperanto&amp;#39;s is not very universal at all and has some consonant sounds that are going to be be totally unfamiliar unless you speak Polish or a language related to Polish. Toki Pona&amp;#39;s phonology is actually minimal-- it has the letters in the sentence &amp;quot;mi jan pi ko suwi lete&amp;quot; and nothing else and the legal syllabary is basically hiragana without the combination syllables. Now, what I don&amp;#39;t know is whether any of this actually helps speakers of Asian languages in practice or if it just makes surface choices that make it seem that way to a westerner like me. In practice if you find a toki pona speaker their native language is almost certainly English, so there doesn&amp;#39;t seem to have been a great deal of testing as to how learnable it is to people from varied regions.

&amp;#178; I kept imagining toki pona as being like LLVM IR for human languages or something.

&amp;#179; Designing an actually learnable, universal(?) international auxillary language.

⁴ By which I mean if you print the unofficial web version it&amp;#39;s 17 pages long. But you can fit it in sixteen if you remove the web-specific introductory paragraph, the &amp;quot;joke word&amp;quot; kijetesantakalu, and the web footer with the &amp;quot;trans rights now!&amp;quot; banner in it.

⁵ There&amp;#39;s an awkward nuance in the specific case of prepositions: if you drop a preposition into verb position it still winds up &amp;quot;behaving like&amp;quot; a preposition, it&amp;#39;s just that the preposition describes an action. It&amp;#39;s probably more accurate to say that the preposition phrase becomes a verb rather than the preposition itself. So for example &amp;quot;mi tawa kalama&amp;quot; means &amp;quot;I went toward the sound&amp;quot; [kamala is a noun and the object of the preposition] not &amp;quot;I went loudly&amp;quot; [as it would be if kamala were an adverb modifying tawa as a verb]. Going into detail on this because I don&amp;#39;t want to mislead anyone but &amp;quot;you can form a sentence using an unmodified preposition as a verb&amp;quot; is such a fun fact I wanted to include it.

⁶ I guess I could say &amp;quot;what I&amp;#39;m calling &amp;#39;clauses&amp;#39; are called &amp;#39;word groups&amp;#39; in official sources; word groups are always separated by a particle or preposition&amp;quot; but I&amp;#39;m not sure that&amp;#39;s interesting unless you&amp;#39;re a linguist.

⁷ There&amp;#39;s a lot of repetition in this paragraph of both kinds that show what&amp;#39;s cool about toki pona and what&amp;#39;s kinda impractical about it. Cool, it has some sentences where a single word shows up twice conveying two different clear things based only on where it is in the sentence, like &amp;quot;mi toki ike e toki ale&amp;quot; where toki is a verb (&amp;quot;I speak&amp;quot;) the first time and a noun (&amp;quot;language&amp;quot;) the second. Less cool, because so much of the meaning of the hyper-versatile toki pona words is based on context, you sometimes wind up having to include multiple sentences saying nearly the same thing just to make sure the reader selects the correct context. I may have overdone it here.

⁸ There&amp;#39;s also a low-traffic Mastodon instance, multiple forums including one run by the Merveilles crowd, and something called &amp;quot;Wikipesija&amp;quot;

⁹ Translation/explanation:

 * ME: jan utala pi toki ni [&amp;quot;We are the knights who say &amp;#39;this&amp;#39;!&amp;quot;]
   (&amp;quot;ni&amp;quot; is &amp;quot;this&amp;quot; in toki pona, which means the Holy Grail scene would seem to be the guy yelling &amp;quot;We are the knights who say &amp;#39;We are the knights who say this!&amp;#39;&amp;quot; after which everyone else jumps around yelling &amp;quot;this!&amp;quot; &amp;quot;this!&amp;quot; as if agreeing)
 * PERSON 1: (Responding to the fact I initially mispelled &amp;quot;toki&amp;quot; as &amp;quot;toka&amp;quot;) What is a toka
 * ME: ... spelling error :( ... deeply weird one
   (Weird because toki is literally in the name &amp;quot;toki pona&amp;quot; so it is by definition the first toki pona word anyone learns)
 * BOT 1: a and i are 8 keys apart :/
 * BOT 2: (Trying to translate my comment) Could be &amp;quot;an arguer in this conversation&amp;quot; perhaps?
 * ME: mi jo e ijo ike sina pi sijelo pi luka luka luka tu tu lon tenpo suno ni. sona lawa mi li pona ala tawa ni [&amp;quot;I have [[literal translation: &amp;quot;new bad thing of the body-19&amp;quot;]] today. I am not thinking well because of this.&amp;quot;]
   If that doesn&amp;#39;t come across that&amp;#39;s the best I can do right now
 * PERSON 2: &amp;quot;toki&amp;quot; [lit. &amp;quot;It communicates!&amp;quot;]
 * BOT 1: two PIs (Complaining you&amp;#39;re not supposed to chain &amp;quot;of&amp;quot; clauses like I did)
 * (Skipped)
 * PERSON 2: tenpo Mopiju li lon [literal translation: &amp;quot;It is the time of Morbin&amp;#39;!&amp;quot;]
   EMOJI REACTIONS: S O N Y a! [apparent intended translation: &amp;quot;Sony is angry now!&amp;quot;]
   </description>
      <author> (https://cohost.org/mcc)</author>
      <guid>https://cohost.org/mcc/post/59045-mi-kama-sona-e-toki</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 03:02:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today I realized I now trust Microsoft more than I trust google. What is happening?</title>
      <link>https://old.reddit.com/r/degoogle/comments/15pd5si/today_i_realized_i_now_trust_microsoft_more_than/</link>
      <description>Google ||Google Pros|MS Pros|Google deficiencies|MS deficiencies| |:-|:-|:-|:-|:-| |Product 1|Chromebook|VS Code|Youtube &amp;quot;free&amp;quot; experience....</description>
      <author> (kajEbrA3)</author>
      <guid>https://old.reddit.com/r/degoogle/comments/15pd5si/today_i_realized_i_now_trust_microsoft_more_than/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 03:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Safe Browsing – Google Transparency Report</title>
      <link>https://transparencyreport.google.com/safe-browsing/search?url=https%3A%2F%2Fold.reddit.com%2Fr%2Fprogramming%2F</link>
      <description>Safe Browsing is a service that Google’s security team built to identify unsafe websites and notify users and website owners of potential harm. This report shares details about the threats detected and the warnings shown to users.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://transparencyreport.google.com/safe-browsing/search?url=https%3A%2F%2Fold.reddit.com%2Fr%2Fprogramming%2F</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 03:02:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I lost my hair, and what I found instead</title>
      <link>https://www.sahilarora.in/personal-life/hair-loss/</link>
      <description>My 10 year journey of losing hair and how it has impacted me.</description>
      <author> (Sahil Arora)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sahilarora.in/personal-life/hair-loss/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why skilled immigration (usually) benefits both countries</title>
      <link>https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/why-skilled-immigration-usually-benefits</link>
      <description>When to worry about brain drain, and when not to worry.</description>
      <author> (Noah Smith)</author>
      <guid>https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/why-skilled-immigration-usually-benefits</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Text-Based Content on the Gemini Protocol</title>
      <link>https://rickcarlino.com/2023/exploring-text-based-content-on-gemini.html</link>
      <description>Exploring Text-Based Content on the Gemini Protocol</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rickcarlino.com/2023/exploring-text-based-content-on-gemini.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data compression</title>
      <link>https://matradomski.com/posts/data_compression/</link>
      <description>There is a very high possibility that your browser downloaded this website as compressed data. I can feel sure saying this because the web standard defines gzip as a standard compressor for web content. So what it achieved by compressing this webpage? As with any data compression algorithm, it reduces the data’s size with no or very little data loss. Data compression is a bigger deal than you might imagine, some works conclude that compression is equal to intelligence.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matradomski.com/posts/data_compression/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning 40; life as a 39-year-old :: Sacha Chua</title>
      <link>https://sachachua.com/blog/2023/08/turning-40-life-as-a-39-year-old/</link>
      <description>Less childcare, because sometimes she&amp;#39;s lost in a book and I can do
something else like sewing, drawing, coding. Less sleep because I&amp;#39;ve
been setting an alarm so that I can water the garden before I wake up
A+. W-&amp;#39;s been doing more of the cooking because we&amp;#39;re often out at
playdates, although sometimes I shift things around so that I cook
lunch. I feel good about how our days generally go, especially when
we&amp;#39;re out for playdates.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://sachachua.com/blog/2023/08/turning-40-life-as-a-39-year-old/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Misconceptions About Communal Living</title>
      <link>https://www.baileymerlin.com/post/5-misconceptions-about-communal-living</link>
      <description>These 5 misconceptions will change your mind about communal living.</description>
      <author> (Bailey Merlin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.baileymerlin.com/post/5-misconceptions-about-communal-living</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Etifoxine: is this drug a Xanax killer?</title>
      <link>https://www.alexkesin.com/2023/08/etifoxine-is-this-drug-xanax-killer.html</link>
      <description>The website all about a clueless guy named Alex Kesin.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.alexkesin.com/2023/08/etifoxine-is-this-drug-xanax-killer.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My favorite macOS command linen #blog</title>
      <link>https://www.linen.dev/s/linen/t/13909921/my-favorite-macos-command</link>
      <description>For macOS developers efficiency is everything Enter `mdfind` a command that marries speed with precision What makes it stand head and shoulders above the rest 1 Diving into Mdfind `mdfind` is like hav</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.linen.dev/s/linen/t/13909921/my-favorite-macos-command</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return to the office mandate? You just may be a bad leader. How to drive results and have your employees do their best work</title>
      <link>https://matthewduff.com/2023/08/13/return-to-office-often-means-you-have-bad-leadership/</link>
      <description>Requiring presence is often bad management</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://matthewduff.com/2023/08/13/return-to-office-often-means-you-have-bad-leadership/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perpetually Declining Population?</title>
      <link>https://www.jefftk.com/p/perpetually-declining-population</link>
      <description>In  With a Whimper: Depopulation and Longtermism, Geruso and Spears give the following argument for why most people who&amp;#39;ll ever live may have already died:    People are generally having children below replacement rate: 1.66 children per woman in the US, and total global annual births peaked in 2014.  If you project this forward 300-600 years, annual births fall below ~10M.  This would leave us wi</description>
      <author> (Jeff Kaufman)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jefftk.com/p/perpetually-declining-population</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concepts for Reliability of LLMs in Production</title>
      <link>https://jytan.net/posts/llm-reliability/</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://jytan.net/posts/llm-reliability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozymandias</title>
      <link>https://blog.vslira.net/2023/08/ozymandias.html</link>
      <description>Look on my works, ye Mighty, and despair! The common interpretation of the poem  is that we&amp;#39;re supposed to appreciate the irony of the self-...</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.vslira.net/2023/08/ozymandias.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factorials &amp;amp; Fun with Vim</title>
      <link>https://grohan.co/2023/08/10/vim/</link>
      <description>Vim trix and more</description>
      <author> (Ronalds Vilcins - https://grohan.co)</author>
      <guid>https://grohan.co/2023/08/10/vim/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowdrifts – brr</title>
      <link>https://brr.fyi/posts/snowdrifts</link>
      <description>4 days of blown snow into a doorway.</description>
      <author> (brr)</author>
      <guid>https://brr.fyi/posts/snowdrifts</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Sql Server as a Message Queue with Wolverine</title>
      <link>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/08/13/using-sql-server-as-a-message-queue-with-wolverine/</link>
      <description>Wolverine 1.4.0 was released last week (and a smaller 1.5.0, with a medium sized 1.6.0 coming Monday). The biggest new feature was a brand new option to use Microsoft Sql Server (or Azure Sql) as a…</description>
      <author> (jeremydmiller)</author>
      <guid>https://jeremydmiller.com/2023/08/13/using-sql-server-as-a-message-queue-with-wolverine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 23:02:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elite&amp;#39;s War on Remote Work Has Nothing to Do with Productivity</title>
      <link>https://www.okdoomer.io/heres-why-they-want-you-back-at-the-office-so-bad/</link>
      <description>The elite are trying to whip everyone back to the office to avoid a commercial real estate crash.</description>
      <author> (Jessica Wildfire)</author>
      <guid>https://www.okdoomer.io/heres-why-they-want-you-back-at-the-office-so-bad/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 23:02:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HalvarFlake (@HalvarFlake@mastodon.social)</title>
      <link>https://mastodon.social/@HalvarFlake/110883667162838296</link>
      <description>Downloading a YouTube video should be just as covered by &amp;quot;fair use&amp;quot; as recording a song from the radio onto cassette was.

Unfortunately, courts tend to continuously weaken society in the grand bargain between society and copyright holders.

https://torrentfreak.com/youtube-dl-site-goes-offline-as-hosting-provider-enforces-court-ordered-ban-230809/</description>
      <author> (By Ernesto Van der Sar)</author>
      <guid>https://mastodon.social/@HalvarFlake/110883667162838296</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 22:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - microsoft/azurechatgpt: &amp;#129302; Azure ChatGPT: Private &amp;amp; secure ChatGPT for internal enterprise use &amp;#128188;</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/azurechatgpt</link>
      <description>&amp;#129302; Azure ChatGPT: Private &amp;amp; secure ChatGPT for internal enterprise use &amp;#128188;  - GitHub - microsoft/azurechatgpt: &amp;#129302; Azure ChatGPT: Private &amp;amp; secure ChatGPT for internal enterprise use &amp;#128188;</description>
      <author> (microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/azurechatgpt</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 22:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Storage Account: Best Practices for Efficient and Secure Storage</title>
      <link>https://luismts.com/azure-storage-account/</link>
      <description>In today&amp;#39;s digital age, data storage is a critical need for organizations of all sizes. Cloud adoption has revolutionized the way we store</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/luismatosluna/)</author>
      <guid>https://luismts.com/azure-storage-account/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 20:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDF Tool - HodlSoftware</title>
      <link>https://www.pdftool.org/</link>
      <description>Simple tool to edit PDFs for free, with privacy integrated.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.pdftool.org/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 20:03:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WinUI 3 mouse cursors with the UIElement.ProtectedCursor | WinAppSDK | XAML | UWP | WPF | .NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ord6ie_nilI</link>
      <description>In this video we&amp;#39;ll see how to change the mouse cursor by setting the UIElement.ProtectedCursor.Chapters:00:00 Intro00:14 UIElement.ProtectedCursor doc00:32 ...</description>
      <author> (LambdaTest
  
  
  
    LambdaTest
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=ord6ie_nilI</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 16:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MassTransit #1 : A Game-Changer for .NET Messaging</title>
      <link>https://goatreview.com/masstransit-game-changer-dotnet-messaging/</link>
      <description>As a discerning software professional, it&amp;#39;s essential to be constantly aware of efficient tools at our disposal. One such tool, unrivalled in its scope and robustness within the .NET ecosystem, is MassTransit.

MassTransit is a free, open-source distributed application framework for .NET. It eases the process of creating applications and</description>
      <author> (Pierre Belin)</author>
      <guid>https://goatreview.com/masstransit-game-changer-dotnet-messaging/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 16:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unit Testing Hosted Services in ASP.NET Web API</title>
      <link>https://ilovedotnet.org/blogs/unit-testing-hosted-services-in-asp-net-webapi/</link>
      <description>In this post I will teach how to unit test hosted services in ASP.NET web api. All with live working demo.</description>
      <author> (Abdul Rahman Shabeek Mohamed)</author>
      <guid>https://ilovedotnet.org/blogs/unit-testing-hosted-services-in-asp-net-webapi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 15:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build your own Mocking library in C#</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=AgjTl2rRPoc</link>
      <description>In this video I show you how you can build your own mocking library so you don&amp;#39;t have to beg maintainers of libraries to behave a certain way.Support my Work...</description>
      <author> (Raw Coding
  
  
  
    Raw Coding
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=AgjTl2rRPoc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 13:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Strongly Typed IDs Popular? #shorts</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_POXOlZmZKY</link>
      <description>&amp;#128204; Check out my Pragmatic Clean Architecture course: https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/pragmatic-clean-architecture&amp;#128640; Join 770+ engineers in my  Patreon commun...</description>
      <author> (Lenny&amp;#39;s Podcast
  
  
  
    Lenny&amp;#39;s Podcast
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_POXOlZmZKY</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 12:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous database deployments to Azure Sql Server with Bitbucket</title>
      <link>https://dotnetthoughts.net/continuous-database-deployments-to-azure-sql-server-with-bitbucket/</link>
      <description>This post is about configuring continuous database deployments to Azure Sql Server with Bitbucket. We are deploying it using EF Core migrations. We can can modify the existing bit bitbucket-pipelines.yml file and add the following code.</description>
      <author> (Anuraj)</author>
      <guid>https://dotnetthoughts.net/continuous-database-deployments-to-azure-sql-server-with-bitbucket/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhobosLab</title>
      <link>https://phoboslab.org/log/2023/08/rewriting-wipeout</link>
      <description>— Thursday, August 10th 2023</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://phoboslab.org/log/2023/08/rewriting-wipeout</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>