<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>The All-Seeing &amp;quot;i&amp;quot;: Apple Just Declared War on Your Privacy</title>
      <link>https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/all-seeing-i</link>
      <description>“Under His Eye,” she says. The right farewell. “Under His Eye,” I reply, and she gives a little nod.</description>
      <author> (Edward Snowden)</author>
      <guid>https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/all-seeing-i</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:06:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiku, Inc. has hired an existing contributor to work on Haiku full-time!</title>
      <link>https://www.haiku-os.org/news/2021-08-25_hiring_waddlesplash/</link>
      <description>Haiku, Inc. is proud to announce that we have hired existing contributor waddlesplash to work on general Haiku improvement full-time. The contract was signed on Monday, August 23, 2021 and waddlesplash plans to start work tomorrow.
In the past Haiku, …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.haiku-os.org/news/2021-08-25_hiring_waddlesplash/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:06:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure SDK: Goodbye QnA Maker, Hello AI &amp;#39;Question Answering&amp;#39; -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/08/25/azure-sdk-aug21.aspx</link>
      <description>The regular monthly update to Microsoft&amp;#39;s Azure SDK improves Cognitive Services text analytics, specifically with a new Question Answering SDK that supplants QnA Maker.</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel08/25/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/08/25/azure-sdk-aug21.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 01:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Login | Microsoft Careers</title>
      <link>https://careers.microsoft.com/i/us/en/job/1120170/Senior-Program-Manager</link>
      <description>This site uses cookies for analytics, personalized content and ads. By continuing to browse this site, you agree to this use.
          Learn more
         .</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://careers.microsoft.com/i/us/en/job/1120170/Senior-Program-Manager</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My experience dealing with Microsoft in the old Windows Phone times</title>
      <link>https://blog.kulman.sk/dealing-with-microsoft-in-wp-times/</link>
      <description>This summer marks exactly a decade since I started doing mobile apps development. My first mobile app was called MyTVShows and was released to the Windows Phone Store in summer of 2011.
The app solved a practical problem for me, keeping track of new episodes. I later rewrote the app as TvTime which was one of my most successful Windows Phone apps.

  
  
  


My times of doing Windows Phone development are long over as the platform has been dead for many years but this reminded me of all the struggles I had to deal with when interacting with the local Microsoft branch.
Disclaimer: Microsoft is a huge company so my experience is hopefully not the general experience of everyone from those times, people on all the local branches are different.
Windows Phone app competitions
In 2012 the Czech Microsoft started a competition giving every developer a Nokia Lumia 800 for publishing 3 apps to the Windows Phone Store.
The problem was the quality of those apps did not matter at all. The goal was to increases the number of the apps as much as possible, probably reaching some arbitrary number set by Redmond.

  
  
  


The Czech Windows Phone Store was flooded by crappy apps created only because of this competition, not having any real value for the user. I remember an app with one input and one button doing some kind of number conversion.
Microsoft just wanted to bump the app numbers count by any means necessary to be able to compare the Windows Phone Store to other mobile app stores.
This also reminded me that Microsoft was really bad at competitions overall, another example was destroying DVLUP after purchasing Nokia.</description>
      <author> (Igor Kulman)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.kulman.sk/dealing-with-microsoft-in-wp-times/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I use attrs instead of pydantic</title>
      <link>https://threeofwands.com/why-i-use-attrs-instead-of-pydantic/</link>
      <description>This post is an account of why I prefer using the attrs library over Pydantic. I&amp;#39;m writing it since I am often asked this question and I want to have something concrete to link to.</description>
      <author> (Tin
                    
                        More posts)</author>
      <guid>https://threeofwands.com/why-i-use-attrs-instead-of-pydantic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptography Engineer</title>
      <link>https://boards.greenhouse.io/o1labs/jobs/4023646004</link>
      <description>Remote</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://boards.greenhouse.io/o1labs/jobs/4023646004</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomadism, Mobility and Risk — Travel Writer Shaun Busuttil</title>
      <link>https://www.shaunbusuttil.com/academic-writing/2021/8/18/digital-nomadism-mobility-and-risk</link>
      <description>This article analyses the global mobility patterns of digital nomads through a Beckian model of risk. It argues that digital nomads use mobility as a hedge against the precarious (and risky) employment relations they often find themselves in. At the same time, however, these same mobility practices </description>
      <author> (Shaun Busuttil)</author>
      <guid>https://www.shaunbusuttil.com/academic-writing/2021/8/18/digital-nomadism-mobility-and-risk</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of the Desk Setup</title>
      <link>https://www.arun.is/blog/desk-setup</link>
      <description>What are the principles underlying the ideal desk setup? How do we balance great design with modern technology? Let’s plunge into my desk setup and my philosophy behind it.</description>
      <author> (Arun Venkatesan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.arun.is/blog/desk-setup</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking a closer look at lodash&amp;#39;s chain</title>
      <link>https://www.maartenhus.nl/blog/lodash-chain-vs-native-methods/</link>
      <description>Comparing lodash&amp;#39;s chain method versus the native methods of Array in JavaScript, and see how chain works under the hood.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.maartenhus.nl/blog/lodash-chain-vs-native-methods/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absurdest Academia (A ‘Darkest Dungeon’ Parody)</title>
      <link>https://bastian.rieck.me/blog/posts/2021/absurdest_academia/</link>
      <description>Staying in academia requires, among other things, a healthy dose of
humour. Its is therefore not surprising that many academical aspects are
likened to more whimsical pursuits. The great Matt Might,
for instance, has a roaringly funny series of posts, describing both the
nine kinds of students you will meet in the
classroom and
the types of reviewers you will face
in terms of characters from the game Team Fortress 2.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://bastian.rieck.me/blog/posts/2021/absurdest_academia/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friendship ended with the garbage collector</title>
      <link>https://yorickpeterse.com/articles/friendship-ended-with-the-garbage-collector/</link>
      <description>Published on:

August 24, 2021</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://yorickpeterse.com/articles/friendship-ended-with-the-garbage-collector/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:06:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why can’t we just give steroids to people with muscular dystrophy? – Trevor Klee</title>
      <link>https://trevorklee.com/why-cant-we-just-give-steroids-to-people-with-muscular-dystrophy/</link>
      <description>I like to start all my scientific inquiries off with really dumb questions. It makes life more fun. Here’s my latest: why can’t we just give steroids to people with muscular dystrophy?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://trevorklee.com/why-cant-we-just-give-steroids-to-people-with-muscular-dystrophy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:06:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning out and quitting</title>
      <link>https://mayakaczorowski.com/blogs/burnout</link>
      <description>I’m burnt out. If you’re reading this, there’s a strong chance you’re burnt out too. We’re about to have, uh, a moment, so brace yourself.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mayakaczorowski.com/blogs/burnout</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:06:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>canistilluse.com</title>
      <link>https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2021/canistilluse.com/</link>
      <description>There’s something beautiful about the website caniuse.com which I never fully appreciated until last week when news spread that alert, prompt, and confirm are in danger of being deprecated from the web platform.</description>
      <author> (p-author)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2021/canistilluse.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:06:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token Authentication for&amp;#160;django-rest-framework — /var/</title>
      <link>https://spapas.github.io/2021/08/25/django-token-rest-auth/</link>
      <description>In a a previous article
I explained how to authenticate for your django-rest-framework API
using the django-rest-auth package.
Since then I have observed that various things have changed and most importantly that
the library I used there (django-rest-auth) is not updated anymore and has been
superseded by another one. Also, some of my information there is contradictory,
especially the parts that deal with the session authentication and csrf&amp;#160;protection.</description>
      <author> (Serafeim Papastefanos)</author>
      <guid>https://spapas.github.io/2021/08/25/django-token-rest-auth/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would the World Be a Better Place If More People Baked Bread?</title>
      <link>https://carolthecook.com/would-the-world-be-a-better-place-if-more-people-baked-bread/</link>
      <description>Nearly ten years ago, researchers from the University of Southern Brittany published a study in the Journal of Social Psychology that found the aroma of fresh baked bread made people nicer to strangers. In the study participants stood outside either a bakery or a clothing store and when passerby approached, they dropped something such as a pack of tissues or keys. Outside of the bakery 77% of the passerby helped pick up the dropped item while only 52% of passerby helped in front of the clothing store.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://carolthecook.com/would-the-world-be-a-better-place-if-more-people-baked-bread/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>59a34eabe31910abfb06f308 - Apple NeuralHash Collision</title>
      <link>https://thishashcollisionisnotporn.com/</link>
      <description>This site is a proof of concept for NeuralHash collision attacks.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://thishashcollisionisnotporn.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 21:08:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Service Bus for .NET deep dive resources</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-service-bus-for-net-deep-dive-resources/</link>
      <description>I’m Daniel Marbach, Platform Architect for Switzerland’s biggest online retailer Digitec Galaxus AG. Architectural decisions related to messaging have followed me throughout my professional career. Our solution heavily relies on the powerful messaging capabilities of Azure Service Bus. With it, we can build complex distributed systems that are reliable and scalable because of less coupling between individual system components.</description>
      <author> (Daniel Marbach)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-service-bus-for-net-deep-dive-resources/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 20:05:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Careers - RelevantDB Next Generation Search</title>
      <link>https://relevantdb.com/careers.html</link>
      <description>Careers at RelevantDB</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://relevantdb.com/careers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 20:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Download Visual Studio/VS Code from Microsoft Store? -- Visual Studio Magazine</title>
      <link>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/08/25/store-ides.aspx</link>
      <description>&amp;#39;Is there any advantage to installing them through the Windows Store rather than normally?&amp;#39;</description>
      <author> (By David Ramel08/25/2021)</author>
      <guid>https://visualstudiomagazine.com/articles/2021/08/25/store-ides.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 19:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OnlyFans Drops Planned Porn Ban, Will Continue to Allow Sexually Explicit Content</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/digital/news/onlyfans-drops-porn-ban-sexually-explicit-policy-1235048705/</link>
      <description>OnlyFans dropped plans to ban pornography from its service, less than a week after the U.K. content-creator subscription site had announced the change citing the need to comply with policies of ban…</description>
      <author> (Todd Spangler)</author>
      <guid>https://variety.com/2021/digital/news/onlyfans-drops-porn-ban-sexually-explicit-policy-1235048705/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 19:05:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - marceloprates/prettymaps: A small set of Python functions to draw pretty maps from OpenStreetMap data. Based on osmnx, matplotlib and shapely libraries.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/marceloprates/prettymaps</link>
      <description>A small set of Python functions to draw pretty maps from OpenStreetMap data. Based on osmnx, matplotlib and shapely libraries. - GitHub - marceloprates/prettymaps: A small set of Python functions t...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/marceloprates/prettymaps</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 17:06:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programmers Don’t Understand Hash Functions</title>
      <link>https://soatok.blog/2021/08/24/programmers-dont-understand-hash-functions/</link>
      <description>Programmers don’t understand hash functions, and I can demonstrate this to most of the people that will read this with a single observation: When you saw the words “hash function”…</description>
      <author> (By Soatok)</author>
      <guid>https://soatok.blog/2021/08/24/programmers-dont-understand-hash-functions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 17:06:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity Framework Community Standup - Dapper</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=txiQar6PqvA</link>
      <description>Dapper maintainers and key contributors Nick and Marc will show people the glorious power of Dapper and everything it can do, so they are fully informed and ...</description>
      <author> (dotNET
  
  
  
    dotNET
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=txiQar6PqvA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 17:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability in Bumble dating app reveals any user&amp;#39;s exact location | Robert Heaton</title>
      <link>https://robertheaton.com/bumble-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>The vulnerability in this post is real. The story and characters are obviously not.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://robertheaton.com/bumble-vulnerability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 17:05:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - roboflow-ai/neuralhash-collisions: A catalog of naturally occurring images whose Apple NeuralHash is identical.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/roboflow-ai/neuralhash-collisions</link>
      <description>A catalog of naturally occurring images whose Apple NeuralHash is identical. - GitHub - roboflow-ai/neuralhash-collisions: A catalog of naturally occurring images whose Apple NeuralHash is identical.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/roboflow-ai/neuralhash-collisions</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 16:09:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Login | Giving Portal</title>
      <link>https://microsoft.benevity.org/user/login</link>
      <description>&amp;#169; 2021 Benevity, Inc. All Rights Reserved.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://microsoft.benevity.org/user/login</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 16:09:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALWAYS Valid Domain Model</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JZetlRXdYeI</link>
      <description>Always having your Domain Model in a valid state means it will be predictable. You&amp;#39;ll write less defensive code or conditional code because your domain objec...</description>
      <author> (CodeOpinion
  
  
  
    CodeOpinion
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JZetlRXdYeI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 15:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Catch Block #71 - Conflict, Lambdas, Updating Tests, and Defaults</title>
      <link>https://exceptionnotfound.net/the-catch-block-71-conflict-lambdas-updating-tests-and-defaults/</link>
      <description>In this edition: keep your tests updated; software as a product; getting prop names from lambda expressions; resolving conflict in remote teams; and default browser problems in Windows 11.</description>
      <author> (Telerik)</author>
      <guid>https://exceptionnotfound.net/the-catch-block-71-conflict-lambdas-updating-tests-and-defaults/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 15:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Search for a FLOSS Mobile OS (Aug 2021) — Emacsen&amp;#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.emacsen.net/blog/2021/08/23/floss-mobile-os-aug-2021/</link>
      <description>For the last few weeks, I&amp;#39;ve been running CalyxOS. It is the latest in Free/Open Source mobile phone operating systems that I&amp;#39;ve used. This post is a summary of my experience using FLOSS mobile OSes and what my experience can tell us not only about phones, but Free/Open Source OSes in general.</description>
      <author> (Serge Wroclawski)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.emacsen.net/blog/2021/08/23/floss-mobile-os-aug-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 15:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A closer look at C# 8 &amp;amp; 9 language features - PHINUG 2021.09</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jaxi21vQhVE</link>
      <description>With every iteration of C#, we get more and more features that are meant to make our lives as developer a lot easier.Let&amp;#39;s look closer at the language featur...</description>
      <author> (.NET Foundation
  
  
  
    .NET Foundation
  






    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jaxi21vQhVE</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 15:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Windows Runtime PassArray is a read-only array, even though it isn&amp;#39;t declared const</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210825-00/?p=105606</link>
      <description>As I noted some time ago, the Windows Runtime PassArray pattern passes a read-only non-owning counted array which is nevertheless not declared as const. Indeed, if you try to force the array type to be const in your IDL declaration: HRESULT SetData([in] UINT32 dataSize,</description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20210825-00/?p=105606</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 14:06:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Varasano&amp;#39;s NY Pizza Recipe</title>
      <link>http://www.varasanos.com/pizzarecipe.htm</link>
      <description>The most accurate and complete PIZZA RECIPE on the net. How to make a true Pizza Napoletana by Jeff Varasano, Voted Atlanta&amp;#39;s Best Pizza, Located at 2171 Peachtree Rd. NE, Atlanta GA 30309</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://www.varasanos.com/pizzarecipe.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 14:06:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. drone pilot leaks footage reveals accidental killing of two children and two adults in Afghanistan - Eminetra.co.uk</title>
      <link>https://eminetra.co.uk/u-s-drone-pilot-leaks-footage-reveals-accidental-killing-of-two-children-and-two-adults-in-afghanistan/663346/</link>
      <description>U.S. drone pilot working at Afghanistan He admitted that he had accidentally killed two Afghan civilians and a child, and questioned the tactics used by his troops to complete the withdrawal. The pilot worked in Helmand in 2019, he told the website Veterinary connection.. He and other drone operators were disappointed in their work with …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://eminetra.co.uk/u-s-drone-pilot-leaks-footage-reveals-accidental-killing-of-two-children-and-two-adults-in-afghanistan/663346/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 14:06:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporting NUKE build failures on Slack</title>
      <link>https://www.erikheemskerk.nl/reporting-nuke-build-failures-slack/</link>
      <description>Let’s make our NUKE builds report failures by themselves, using a little reflection magic.</description>
      <author> (Erik Heemskerk


2021-08-25

• 4 minutes)</author>
      <guid>https://www.erikheemskerk.nl/reporting-nuke-build-failures-slack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 11:06:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API Tokens: A Tedious Survey</title>
      <link>https://fly.io/blog/api-tokens-a-tedious-survey/</link>
      <description>More, I promise, than you ever wanted to know about API tokens.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://fly.io/blog/api-tokens-a-tedious-survey/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 08:06:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 vBulletin Forums Hacked; Millions of Accounts Being Sold on Dark Web</title>
      <link>https://www.hackread.com/vbulletin-forums-hacked-accounts-sold-on-dark-web/</link>
      <description>A Dark Web hacker going by the handle of Cfnt hacked 25 outdated vBulletin web forums and leaked their data on Hansa Dark Web marketplace.</description>
      <author> (Waqas)</author>
      <guid>https://www.hackread.com/vbulletin-forums-hacked-accounts-sold-on-dark-web/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2021-08-25</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/08/app-developer-links-2021-08-25/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2021/08/app-developer-links-2021-08-25/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA shares five innovations via Accessibility Patent Pledge, wants other devs to do the same</title>
      <link>https://www.gamesindustry.biz/articles/2021-08-23-ea-shares-five-innovations-via-accessibility-patent-pledge-wants-other-devs-to-do-the-same</link>
      <description>Chris Bruzzo tells us why the publisher is sharing its patented technology, including Apex Legends&amp;#39; Ping System</description>
      <author> (James BatchelorEditor-in-ChiefTuesday 24th August 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gamesindustry.biz/articles/2021-08-23-ea-shares-five-innovations-via-accessibility-patent-pledge-wants-other-devs-to-do-the-same</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 06:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Delete Behavior and more on EF Core - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/blogs/change-delete-behavior-and-more-on-ef-core/</link>
      <description>Entity Framework had objects called conventions. These objects can be used to make configurations on the entity framework context to change its default</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/dennes.torres)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/blogs/change-delete-behavior-and-more-on-ef-core/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 06:04:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the New TypeScript Homepage</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-the-new-typescript-homepage/</link>
      <description>Hey folks, we’re happy to announce that the next iteration version of the TypeScript Website has been switched on for the TypeScript homepage. Last August we deployed a re-design and re-architecture of the entire TypeScript web presence. The goals were to provide new foundations for documenting TypeScript,</description>
      <author> (Orta Therox)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-the-new-typescript-homepage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 06:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# Language Highlights: Deconstructing Non-tuple Types</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/C-Language-Highlights-Deconstructing-Non-tuple-Types</link>
      <description>In this short video, David and Kendra diving into the deconstruction of non-tuple types.   Useful Links Deconstructing tuples and other typesCreating record typesTuple types.NET Videos  </description>
      <author> (by Cecil Phillip, Ricardo Esway)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/On-NET/C-Language-Highlights-Deconstructing-Non-tuple-Types</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 06:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publish apps and games to the Microsoft Store – Develop for Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://developer.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-store/</link>
      <description>Publish your apps and games to the Microsoft Store for Windows, including traditional desktop apps and PWAs.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developer.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-store/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 05:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t take #advice from people who don’t want you to win</title>
      <link>https://www.tiktok.com/@shanselman/video/7000189495261826310?_d=secCgYIASAHKAESPgo8vlbAmMCPC%2FAQ3b4fLB7LlICZocbRiQ8goIib8dT5EQxlomgqtV4gr%2FWx7UOqrzUKVrYK4ANAnlr6SHgpGgA%3D&amp;checksum=6bd55938e6e179b576aa8c32e5655f371e8363ca11b255658ef0c25a3d5849a4&amp;language=en&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;sec_user_id=MS4wLjABAAAAFt5MIdypn_f0WZh40awWRF89Zw9Amdawzs3Uv8kCYseoyWirUnzj1bZawGbeNpw4&amp;share_app_id=1233&amp;share_item_id=7000189495261826310&amp;share_link_id=85894851-9FA5-407A-99E0-5B12445581E2&amp;timestamp=1629858672&amp;u_code=de1hm7ac6mg7id&amp;user_id=6860974717076014086&amp;_r=1</link>
      <description>Scott Hanselman (@shanselman) has created a short video on TikTok with music original sound. | Don’t take #advice from people who don’t want you to win</description>
      <author> (shanselmanScott Hanselman &amp;#183; 2h ago)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tiktok.com/@shanselman/video/7000189495261826310?_d=secCgYIASAHKAESPgo8vlbAmMCPC%2FAQ3b4fLB7LlICZocbRiQ8goIib8dT5EQxlomgqtV4gr%2FWx7UOqrzUKVrYK4ANAnlr6SHgpGgA%3D&amp;checksum=6bd55938e6e179b576aa8c32e5655f371e8363ca11b255658ef0c25a3d5849a4&amp;language=en&amp;preview_pb=0&amp;sec_user_id=MS4wLjABAAAAFt5MIdypn_f0WZh40awWRF89Zw9Amdawzs3Uv8kCYseoyWirUnzj1bZawGbeNpw4&amp;share_app_id=1233&amp;share_item_id=7000189495261826310&amp;share_link_id=85894851-9FA5-407A-99E0-5B12445581E2&amp;timestamp=1629858672&amp;u_code=de1hm7ac6mg7id&amp;user_id=6860974717076014086&amp;_r=1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 05:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eatigo reports data breach, personal data from customer accounts listed for sale online</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/singapore/eatigo-data-breach-personal-information-millions-account-1307916</link>
      <description>SINGAPORE: Personal data from potentially 2.8 million eatigo accounts were illegally assessed&amp;#160;in a data breach.In an email to customers on Saturday (Oct 31), the restaurant reservation platform said that along with other e-commerce sites, it was the&amp;#160;subject of &amp;quot;a data security incident</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/singapore/eatigo-data-breach-personal-information-millions-account-1307916</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 04:04:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>