<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>N: Game Concepts 2 (Category Compilation) #06～#09</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=f-O_sdH6CUo</link>
      <description>In Category N: Game Concepts, I look back at how I came up with the ideas for each of the games I worked on, in release order. Rather than sharing anecdotes from development, I&amp;#39;ve chosen to focus on the inspirations and thought processes behind their creation.

[Index]
0:00 Opening
0:11 N-06 Kirby Air Ride
6:42 N-07 Meteos
15:13 N-08 Sodatete! Kouchuu Ouja Mushiking
24:29 N-09 Super Smash Bros. Brawl

[Playlist N: Game Concepts]
https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLgKCjZ2WsVLTbEJdN9Rs6FWnOjlIj4Tdt</description>
      <author> (Masahiro Sakurai on Creating Games)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=f-O_sdH6CUo</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 12:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility essentials every front-end developer should know by Martijn Hols</title>
      <link>https://martijnhols.nl/blog/accessibility-essentials-every-front-end-developer-should-know</link>
      <description>Essential accessibility practices for front-end developers, including semantic HTML, alt texts, ARIA, and keyboard navigation tips to build inclusive components.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://martijnhols.nl/blog/accessibility-essentials-every-front-end-developer-should-know</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tracked everything I could in 2024, here&amp;#39;s the data</title>
      <link>https://lorenzomodolo.com/posts/2024-tracking-recap/</link>
      <description>In February 2024, I embarked on a journey that I’d been contemplating for many years. I’ve always been fascinated with collecting data, visualising it, and looking back at patterns in my life. There’s something deeply satisfying about looking at myself through data.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://lorenzomodolo.com/posts/2024-tracking-recap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#39;m in exile</title>
      <link>https://luis.com/p/im-in-exile</link>
      <description>Nations routinely purge their talented and free thinking citizens. I&amp;#39;m one of them.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://luis.com/p/im-in-exile</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Headspace is Perishable</title>
      <link>https://www.coryzue.com/writing/headspace/</link>
      <description>And when you have it, it’s worth acting on.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.coryzue.com/writing/headspace/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Eval is More Important Than the Model</title>
      <link>https://www.dbreunig.com/2025/01/08/evaluating-llms-as-knowledge-banks.html</link>
      <description>A well-built custom eval lets you quickly test the newest models, iterate faster when developing prompts and pipelines, and ensure you’re always moving forward against your product’s specific goal. Let’s build an example eval – made from Jeopardy questions – to illustrate the value of a custom eval.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.dbreunig.com/2025/01/08/evaluating-llms-as-knowledge-banks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Quest For A Minimal Phone (for my kid) | Saurabh &amp;quot;Sam&amp;quot; Khawase</title>
      <link>https://samkhawase.com/blog/dumb-smartphone/</link>
      <description>I design products, fine-tune strategies, build teams, and create rock solid software.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://samkhawase.com/blog/dumb-smartphone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eBPF Research Papers</title>
      <link>https://pchaigno.github.io/bpf/2025/01/07/research-papers-bpf.html</link>
      <description>Interactive list of eBPF research papers from top conferences according to CSRankings. The list can be filtered according to types of publications (ex., improving, using) and areas (ex., networking, verifier, offload, security).</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://pchaigno.github.io/bpf/2025/01/07/research-papers-bpf.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shortcomings of Modern Automation</title>
      <link>https://melvintercan.com/p/shortcomings-of-modern-automation</link>
      <description>Modern automation platforms like SaaS, RPA &amp;amp; Low-Code/No-Code promised transformation but failed to deliver, causing new problems instead.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://melvintercan.com/p/shortcomings-of-modern-automation</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happened to Lightweight Desktop Apps? History of Electron’s Rise</title>
      <link>https://smalldiffs.gmfoster.com/p/what-happened-to-lightweight-desktop</link>
      <description>It had one key killer feature: &amp;quot;embedding Node.js and Chromium to provide a powerful desktop runtime for web technologies.&amp;quot; But is that worth a world of bloated desktop apps?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://smalldiffs.gmfoster.com/p/what-happened-to-lightweight-desktop</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The easiest way to run an LLM locally on your Mac</title>
      <link>https://www.jeremymorgan.com/blog/generative-ai/how-to-llm-local-mac-m1</link>
      <description>Want to run a large language model (LLM) locally on your Mac? Here&amp;#39;s the easiest way to do it. I&amp;#39;ll review the LM studio here, and I run it my M1 Mac Mini. Is it fast enough?</description>
      <author> (https://plus.google.com/+JeremyMorgan)</author>
      <guid>https://www.jeremymorgan.com/blog/generative-ai/how-to-llm-local-mac-m1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Feed as a Life Journal | Digital Notes</title>
      <link>https://digitalnotes.com/blog/social-feed-as-a-life-journal/</link>
      <description>Rethink the way you share moments—post freely for yourself, your family, or your team.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://digitalnotes.com/blog/social-feed-as-a-life-journal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-saving Rails forms with Turbo Streams</title>
      <link>https://nts.strzibny.name/rails-autosave-form-turbo-stream/</link>
      <description>Here’s how to implement autosaving for inline input fields the Hotwire way.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nts.strzibny.name/rails-autosave-form-turbo-stream/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing out on jobs because of LeetCode</title>
      <link>https://skarlso.github.io/2025/01/08/missing-out-on-jobs-because-of-leetcode/</link>
      <description>Missing out of jobs because of LeetCode
At the end of the last year, my previous workplace ( Weaveworks ) went bankrupt. I found myself without a job.
I didn’t have to interview for a long time and I certainly wasn’t planning on it any time soon. I enjoyed my
work.
Thus, I started to learn a bit because I forgot how to interview. I refreshed my knowledge on LeetCode, I
did some exercises, I read some books, post, whatever. I refreshed my algo knowledge because that’s what people
most likely will ask, right?</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://skarlso.github.io/2025/01/08/missing-out-on-jobs-because-of-leetcode/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQL NULLs are Weird!</title>
      <link>https://jirevwe.github.io/sql-nulls-are-weird.html</link>
      <description>Yes, you read that right. SQL does treat all NULL values differently. I learnt this a while back while working on Convoy and again on LiteQueue: a Golang a queueing library.  Basically, any column wit</description>
      <author> (Raymond Tukpe)</author>
      <guid>https://jirevwe.github.io/sql-nulls-are-weird.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Power of AI: Jim Bennett on Pieces for Developers</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_CGh61pdhMs</link>
      <description>RJJ Software&amp;#39;s Software Development Service This episode of The Modern .NET Show is supported, in part, by RJJ Software&amp;#39;s Podcasting Services, whether your company is looking to elevate its UK operations or reshape its US strategy, we can provide tailored solutions that exceed expectations.

 Show Notes &amp;quot;So we&amp;#39;re dealing with code bases that are getting bigger and bigger every day. You know, those million line code bases, two million line code bases is not unusual. We are being pushed to do more. I remember when I was working at Microsoft a couple of years ago, Satya Nadella, CEO, his favourite phrase was, &amp;quot;you have to do more with less.&amp;quot; But yeah, so Satya was big on this idea of do more with less. And this has kind of resonated across the industry as a whole.&amp;quot;— Jim Bennett

 Welcome friends to The Modern .NET Show; the premier .NET podcast, focusing entirely on the knowledge, tools, and frameworks that all .NET developers should have in their toolbox. We are the go-to podcast for .NET developers worldwide, and I am not your host: Jamie. I&amp;#39;m Delilah and I will be recording the intro for this episode because Jamie is suffering with a throat infection.

 In this episode, Jim Bennett returns to the show after a six-year absence. In his previous appearance, Jim introduced us to Xamarin, but in the time since that appearance, Xamarin has been sunsetted. So it felt natural to start our conversation about the wonderful outpouring of support over on X with the hashtag #XamarinGaveMe.

 The main topic of conversation is about Generative AI, Large Language Models, and how the new startup, Pieces, can help developers to keep the context of what they are working on at the front of their mind at all times; both when they are online and off.

 &amp;quot;If I said to you, &amp;quot;which character from the Pixar movie Up are you?&amp;quot; The answer is going to be, &amp;quot;Doug,&amp;quot; we&amp;#39;re all Doug. We&amp;#39;re all like, &amp;quot;squirrel!&amp;quot;

 So if we have to go from our IDE to a browser to ask a question, we&amp;#39;re reading email on the way. We are looking at chat tools on the way. Oh, we&amp;#39;re in a browser. &amp;quot;Oh, I&amp;#39;ve got a notification on Blue Sky. I&amp;#39;m going to have a look at that.&amp;quot; We are context switching. We are distracted. We are drinking coffee. We are losing our productivity&amp;quot;— Jim Bennett

 Anyway, without further ado, let&amp;#39;s sit back, open up a terminal, type in `dotnet new podcast` and we&amp;#39;ll dive into the core of Modern .NET.

 My voice was created using Generative AI.

 Supporting the Show If you find this episode useful in any way, please consider supporting the show by either leaving a review (check our review page for ways to do that), sharing the episode with a friend or colleague, buying the host a coffee, or considering becoming a Patron of the show.

 Full Show Notes The full show notes, including links to some of the things we discussed and a full transcription of this episode, can be found at:  https://dotnetcore.show/season-7/unlocking-the-power-of-ai-jim-bennett-on-pieces-for-developers

 Jim&amp;#39;s Links:  Jim&amp;#39;s linked on Link Tree  Pieces  Pieces Discord #XamarinGaveMe Xamarin in Action (AKA Jim&amp;#39;s book on Xamarin)  Jamie&amp;#39;s Public NuGet Packages:  OwaspHeaders.Core ClackMiddleware OnionArch.Mvc  Useful Links   Generative AI for .NET Developers with Amit Bahree Ollama OpenVino  LLMs Mentioned:  Llama Microsoft Phi Mistral Qwen-2.5 which Jamie mis-names as Quon.  Supporting the show:  Leave a rating or review Buy the show a coffee Become a patron  Getting in Touch:  Via the contact page Joining the Discord  Remember to rate and review the show on  Apple Podcasts, Podchaser, or wherever you find your podcasts, this will help the show&amp;#39;s audience grow. Or you can just share the show with a friend.

 And don&amp;#39;t forget to reach out via our Contact page. We&amp;#39;re very interested in your opinion of the show, so please get in touch.

 You can support the show by making a monthly donation on the show&amp;#39;s Patreon page at: https://www.patreon.com/TheDotNetCorePodcast.</description>
      <author> (Jamie Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_CGh61pdhMs</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy of a Large Language Model output</title>
      <link>https://nikkin.dev/blog/llm-entropy.html</link>
      <description>Large language models like ChatGPT &amp;amp; Claude have become
ubiquitous in today’s world. I visited a friend for the New years eve
and was impressed by how ChatGPT was being extensively used within the
family. The friend’s little kid is going to grow up in a world, where
turning to large language models (LLM) for quick answers is going to be
the norm rather than the exception.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://nikkin.dev/blog/llm-entropy.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Reasons Why You&amp;#39;re Still Unsuccessful</title>
      <link>https://durmonski.com/self-improvement/reasons-you-are-unsuccessful/</link>
      <description>What, are you still unsuccessful? Still getting by despite the avalanche of advice circling in the online realm? Read this...</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/durmonski/)</author>
      <guid>https://durmonski.com/self-improvement/reasons-you-are-unsuccessful/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Rust 1.84.0 | Rust Blog</title>
      <link>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2025/01/09/Rust-1.84.0.html</link>
      <description>Empowering everyone to build reliable and efficient software.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://blog.rust-lang.org/2025/01/09/Rust-1.84.0.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epoch Semantic Versioning</title>
      <link>https://antfu.me/posts/epoch-semver</link>
      <description>Proposal for an extended Semantic Versioning called Epoch SemVer to provide more granular versioning information to users.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://antfu.me/posts/epoch-semver</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trying and failing to interpret sentence embeddings</title>
      <link>https://timbrell.dev/ai/2025/01/09/trying-and-failing-to-interpret-embeddings.html</link>
      <description>I was born with congenital anosmia i.e. I cannot and have never been able to smell. Farts, flowers, cookies, and perfume; I have no personal experience of any of these smells. Yet, I can tell you that farts take over a room and cookies smell like home. This is all picked up through context. It’s picked up from watching my friends retching at the stench of the small animal that died in the vents of my middle school. For me, a smell is defined by its relation to other smells and the emotive descriptions of others. This is not altogether different from a sentence embedding.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://timbrell.dev/ai/2025/01/09/trying-and-failing-to-interpret-embeddings.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I quit search engines for three months.</title>
      <link>https://vkc.sh/quit-search/</link>
      <description>Yup. Here&amp;#39;s what I learned about myself.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://vkc.sh/quit-search/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:00:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Align the Button Text in .NET MAUI</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/vhugogarcia/align-the-button-text-in-net-maui-1900</link>
      <description>Mobile app developers often encounter seemingly simple UI challenges that require platform-specific...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/vhugogarcia/align-the-button-text-in-net-maui-1900</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 21:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Languages &amp;amp; Runtime Community Standup - .NET 9 Performance Improvements Q&amp;amp;A</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=hJIrbWzoeP0</link>
      <description>Let&amp;#39;s chat with Stephen Toub about how .NET got _even faster_ in .NET 9. We&amp;#39;ll condense hundreds of pages of deep dives into an hour, by talking really fast!

Featuring: Bill Wagner(@billwagner), Stephen Toub(@stephentoub), Chet Husk(@chethusk)</description>
      <author> (dotnet)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=hJIrbWzoeP0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 20:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>api problems #dotnet #programming #coding</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2Ocnw6CadUs</link>
      <description>question about problems you face while developing .NET apis</description>
      <author> (Mohamad Lawand)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=2Ocnw6CadUs</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 20:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - piebro/factorio-blueprint-visualizer: A python library to artfully visualize Factorio Blueprints and an interactive web demo for using it.</title>
      <link>https://github.com/piebro/factorio-blueprint-visualizer</link>
      <description>A python library to artfully visualize Factorio Blueprints and an interactive web demo for using it. - piebro/factorio-blueprint-visualizer</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/piebro/factorio-blueprint-visualizer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 19:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>99 Dev Problems with James Quick</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_NEjH2vIOso</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

99 Dev Problems features candid conversations with developers at every level about real-world challenges, career growth, and the evolving tech landscape. From technical deep dives to career advice, each episode brings practical insights from developers actively building in the field. Join us as we explore the human side of coding, share battle stories, and uncover solutions to the problems developers face daily. Whether you&amp;#39;re a seasoned engineer or just starting your journey, tune in for authentic tech talk.</description>
      <author> (James Q Quick)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=_NEjH2vIOso</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run Windows on an Apple Silicon Mac with VMware Fusion Pro free (Full setup guide)</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pkhui1qIozA</link>
      <description>Looking to run Windows on your new Apple Silicon Mac with M1, M2, M3, or M4 chips? I got you covered with my full setup guide and customizations with VMware Fusion Pro, which is free for personal use.

Links:
VMware Fusion: https://www.vmware.com/products/desktop-hypervisor/workstation-and-fusion
VMware Fusion free annoucement: https://blogs.vmware.com/teamfusion/2024/05/fusion-pro-now-available-free-for-personal-use.html

Videos:
Mac Mini M4 Pro Dev Setup: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kPGcIyxYfBE
VS Code for .NET MAUI Setup: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1t2zzoW4D98

Chapters: 
00:00 - Intro
01:33 - Installing VMWare Fusion Pro
03:10 - Enabling Accessibility Permissions
03:30 - Download Windows 11
04:10 - Default Virtual Machine Settings
07:00 - Installing Windows 11
09:00 - Installing VMware Tools
11:00 - Pause, Resume, and Updating VM Settings
13:30 - Expanding VMWare fusion hard drive in Windows 11
18:01 - Wrap-up

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCENTmbKaTphpWV2R2evVz2A/join

&amp;#128085; Buy some swag! - https://jamesmontemagno.myspreadshop.com/
☕️ Buy me a coffee - https://www.buymeacoffee.com/jamesmontemagno

Follow:
&amp;#128104;‍&amp;#128187; GitHub: https://github.com/jamesmontemagno
&amp;#129436; X: https://x.com/jamesmontemagno
&amp;#128196; Website: https://www.montemagno.com
&amp;#128240; Newsletter: https://newsletter.montemagno.com/

Disclaimer: This channel, videos, and streams are created in my spare time and are a product of me... James Montemagno! They are NOT officially affiliated or endorsed by Microsoft (my employer) in any way. Opinions and views are my own.

What is on my hat? It is the CLE clothing logo because I am from Cleveland! Checkout their awesome CLE merch: https://cleclothingco.myshopify.com/

What is that art on my wall? It is an original piece from the French street artist Gregos of La Butte Montmartre: https://www.instagram.com/p/BceZ1oNHiQx/

My Setup:
&amp;#128247; Canon M50 Mark II - https://amzn.to/3P8R7lp
&amp;#128161; Nanoleaf Elements Lights - https://amzn.to/3umwJVW
&amp;#127897; Blue Spark Microphone - https://amzn.to/3qgtYkq
&amp;#127897; Blue Pop Filter - https://amzn.to/3jEWM3r
&amp;#129331; Rode Microphone Arm - https://amzn.to/2Z68AlE
&amp;#127911; Sony MDR7306 Headphones - https://amzn.to/372jxta
&amp;#128242; Stream Deck - https://amzn.to/373Uk1n
&amp;#128433; MX Master 2S Mouse - https://amzn.to/3d7J2gj
⌨️ Tecware Phantom Keyboard - https://amzn.to/3aUP4y9

Using links I provide I may receive a commission if you buy something which helps support the channel.

#dotnet #windows11 #vmware #macmini #macos</description>
      <author> (James Montemagno)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=pkhui1qIozA</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source CMS with C# - integrating plugins</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=vp9te-wL2dA</link>
      <description>Turn your videos into live streams with https://restream.io

Let&amp;#39;s work on SharpSite, an open source CMS that you can contribute to and learn from.  https://github.com/FritzAndFriends/SharpSite</description>
      <author> (Fritz&amp;#39;s Tech Tips and Chatter)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=vp9te-wL2dA</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socket Types: Choosing the Right Tool for the Job - Chris Woody Woodruff</title>
      <link>https://woodruff.dev/socket-types-choosing-the-right-tool-for-the-job/</link>
      <description>Sockets, the unsung architects of digital communication, are each crafted with precision to meet the intricate demands of networking. The right socket choice is not just a technical decision—it’s a transformative step that can elevate your application’s performance from ordinary to extraordinary. With the wrong choice, efficiency crumbles; with the right one, your application thrives, and you, as a professional, are empowered.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://woodruff.dev/socket-types-choosing-the-right-tool-for-the-job/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 15:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Set Up an Awesome PowerShell Environment for Script Development</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/how-i-set-up-an-awesome-powershell-environment-for-script-development-d4p</link>
      <description>Over the past few years, I’ve had the opportunity to help colleagues write and refine PowerShell...</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/how-i-set-up-an-awesome-powershell-environment-for-script-development-d4p</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 15:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TUnit Integration Testing Tutorial for .NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=X91Bxe0llR8</link>
      <description>&amp;#128142; Get the source code for free: https://guiferreira.kit.com/a2541d4a4e</description>
      <author> (Gui Ferreira)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=X91Bxe0llR8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 14:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>