<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Element suspended on Google Play Store: now resolved.</title>
      <link>https://element.io/blog/element-on-google-play-store/</link>
      <description>Hi all, At 2021-01-29 at 21:35 UTC Google suspended Element from the Play Store without warning or notification. &amp;#160;We submitted an appeal asking for clarification at 23:18, and at 05:31 received a generic update from the Google Play Policy team citing that the app has been removed</description>
      <author> (Matthew Hodgson)</author>
      <guid>https://element.io/blog/element-on-google-play-store/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 16:06:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker, Django, Traefik, and IntercoolerJS is My Go-To Stack for Building a SaaS in 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.simplecto.com/docker-django-traefik-intercoolerjs-is-my-stack-for-2021/</link>
      <description>I provide a deeper-dive on the tech stack I like to use in 2021. It is simple, easy to work with, and allows you to grow out of it when the time comes. Updated for 2021!</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.simplecto.com/docker-django-traefik-intercoolerjs-is-my-stack-for-2021/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 15:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical ASP.NET - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/574/practical-asp.net</link>
      <description>My mission is to help ASP.NET web developers be much much more productive, by giving them tools and techniques to focus on their features, and minimise all the other frustrations that come with modern web application development.

I want to put the fun back into developing for the web.

Practic…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/574/practical-asp.net</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 12:07:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebAtoms for Xamarin.Forms - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/576/write-xamarin.forms-apps-with-typescript-and-tsx</link>
      <description>What is “Web Atoms”?
Web Atoms is an advanced MVVM JavaScript framework for Xamarin.Forms and Web.

What it does
It allows you to write Xamarin.Forms app in TypeScript (transpiled to JavaScript)
You can write your Views in TSX and ViewModels in TypeScript
You can use Visual Studio Code on Lin…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/576/write-xamarin.forms-apps-with-typescript-and-tsx</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 08:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 90&amp;#39;s TV!</title>
      <link>https://my90stv.com/</link>
      <description>Go back to the 1990&amp;#39;s via this nostalgic TV simulator and relive the original ads, music videos, movie trailers, shows and more!</description>
      <author> (Joey Cato)</author>
      <guid>https://my90stv.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 07:09:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>microsoft/Extensible-Storage-Engine</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/Extensible-Storage-Engine</link>
      <description>ESE is an embedded / ISAM-based database engine, that provides rudimentary table and indexed access. However the library provides many other strongly layered and and thus reusable sub-facilities as...</description>
      <author> (microsoft)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/microsoft/Extensible-Storage-Engine</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 05:43:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https global tool - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/188/https</link>
      <description>This project was built to help make submitting HTTP requests from a terminal easy for a human to use.

https is a global .net core tool that submits HTTP requests using simple arguments and stdin.
</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/188/https</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 05:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret History of Windows Bluescreens by Davepl</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/KgqJJECQQH0</link>
      <description>Dave tracks down the original developer responsible for the very first Windows Bluescreen, plus how to make your machine Bluescreen in other colors.How to sh...</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage
  
  
    

    
      
    Dave&amp;#39;s Garage
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://youtu.be/KgqJJECQQH0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 05:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lynn Conway&amp;#39;s Story</title>
      <link>https://ai.eecs.umich.edu/people/conway/LynnsStory.html</link>
      <description>Lynn Conway is a 
famed pioneer of 
microelectronics chip design.
Her innovations during the 1970&amp;#39;s at the Xerox Palo Alto Research
Center (PARC) have impacted chip design worldwide. Many high-tech
companies and computing methods have foundations in her work.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ai.eecs.umich.edu/people/conway/LynnsStory.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 04:07:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What went wrong with America’s $44 million vaccine data system?</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/01/30/1017086/cdc-44-million-vaccine-data-vams-problems/</link>
      <description>The CDC ordered software that was meant to manage the vaccine rollout. Instead, it has been plagued by problems and abandoned by most states.</description>
      <author> (by Cat Ferguson archive page)</author>
      <guid>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/01/30/1017086/cdc-44-million-vaccine-data-vams-problems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 04:07:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regular afternoon naps linked to improved cognitive function</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencefocus.com/the-human-body/afternoon-naps-linked-to-improved-cognitive-function/</link>
      <description>Researchers find that afternoon snoozes may help your brain function, but not all naps were created equal.</description>
      <author> (By Frankie Macpherson, PA Science)</author>
      <guid>https://www.sciencefocus.com/the-human-body/afternoon-naps-linked-to-improved-cognitive-function/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 03:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal experiences bridge moral and political divides better than facts</title>
      <link>https://www.pnas.org/content/118/6/e2008389118</link>
      <description>All Americans are affected by rising political polarization, whether because of a gridlocked Congress or antagonistic holiday dinners. People believe that facts are essential for earning the respect of political adversaries, but our research shows that this belief is wrong. We find that sharing personal experiences about a political issue—especially experiences involving harm—help to foster respect via increased perceptions of rationality. This research provides a straightforward pathway for increasing moral understanding and decreasing political intolerance. These findings also raise questions about how science and society should understand the nature of truth in the era of “fake news.” In moral and political disagreements, everyday people treat subjective experiences as truer than objective facts.

Raw data and materials are available at Open Science Framework (&amp;lt;https://osf.io/kbvmn/&amp;gt;).</description>
      <author> (View ORCID ProfileEmily Kubin)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pnas.org/content/118/6/e2008389118</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 02:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About GitHub Security Advisories - GitHub Docs</title>
      <link>https://docs.github.com/en/github/managing-security-vulnerabilities/about-github-security-advisories</link>
      <description>You can use GitHub Security Advisories to privately discuss, fix, and publish information about security vulnerabilities in your repository.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://docs.github.com/en/github/managing-security-vulnerabilities/about-github-security-advisories</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 01:06:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitLocker touch-device lockscreen bypass</title>
      <link>https://secret.club/2021/01/29/touch-lockscreen-bypass.html</link>
      <description>Microsoft has for the past years done a great job at hardening the Windows lockscreen, but after Jonas published CVE-2020-1398, I put effort into weaponizing an old bug I had found in Windows Touch devices.</description>
      <author> (Abdelhamid Naceri)</author>
      <guid>https://secret.club/2021/01/29/touch-lockscreen-bypass.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max Hodak - Do words mean anything?</title>
      <link>https://maxhodak.com/nonfiction/2021/01/30/do-words-mean-anything.html</link>
      <description>The principle of absolute freedom of speech has embedded in it a basic premise that words do not inherently mean anything. This wasn’t obvious to me and felt surprising, in the this-must-be-wrong way, when I noticed it. But if we agree that there exist things so bad that they should be prohibited, like murder, and simultaneously take that there is no sequence of words that are so inherently bad that they should be prohibited, then we must subscribe to a view that words-in-themselves must not, in the general case, map to anything imbued with inherent meaning.</description>
      <author> (January 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://maxhodak.com/nonfiction/2021/01/30/do-words-mean-anything.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advice to My Younger Software Developer Self</title>
      <link>https://joshhornby.com/blog/advice-to-my-younger-software-developer-self</link>
      <description>As I look back over what’s almost a decade in software development, there are some things I wish I’d started doing sooner. This is the advice I’d give my younger self, who has just landed their first professional software development job.</description>
      <author> (Josh Hornby)</author>
      <guid>https://joshhornby.com/blog/advice-to-my-younger-software-developer-self</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARS-CoV-2 variants of concern</title>
      <link>https://www.virology.ws/2021/01/28/sars-cov-2-variants-of-concern/</link>
      <description>In recent months variants of SARS-CoV-2 have been detected that are unusual in that they have many more genome mutations than have been detected previously.</description>
      <author> (28 January 2021)</author>
      <guid>https://www.virology.ws/2021/01/28/sars-cov-2-variants-of-concern/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:04:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Stories Are Wrong, but Some Are Useful</title>
      <link>https://neilkakkar.com/story-of-stories.html</link>
      <description>Stories are powerful, and they rule our world. This post explores how we’re always telling ourselves a story, and how choosing the right story has long term, surprising implications.</description>
      <author> (https://neilkakkar.com/about/)</author>
      <guid>https://neilkakkar.com/story-of-stories.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> How Many Days Has It Been Since a JWT alg=none Vulnerability?</title>
      <link>https://www.howmanydayssinceajwtalgnonevuln.com/</link>
      <description>It has been 102 days since the last alg=none JWT vulnerability.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.howmanydayssinceajwtalgnonevuln.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 23:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniwidth typefaces for interface design</title>
      <link>https://uxdesign.cc/uniwidth-typefaces-for-interface-design-b6e8078dc0f7</link>
      <description>Uniwidth typefaces have great potential for the use in interactive interfaces. This is a short compilation of some available typefaces.</description>
      <author> (https://lisa-staudinger.medium.com)</author>
      <guid>https://uxdesign.cc/uniwidth-typefaces-for-interface-design-b6e8078dc0f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 23:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The student clique system of a desegregated high school</title>
      <link>https://ufdc.ufl.edu/AA00047446/00001</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://ufdc.ufl.edu/AA00047446/00001</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 23:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Patterns at Scale: Findings from a Crawl of 11K Shopping Websites</title>
      <link>https://webtransparency.cs.princeton.edu/dark-patterns/</link>
      <description>Dark patterns are user interface design choices that benefit an online service by coercing, steering, or deceiving users into making unintended and potentially harmful decisions. We conducted a large-scale study, analyzing ~53K product pages from ~11K shopping websites to characterize and quantify the prevalence of dark patterns.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://webtransparency.cs.princeton.edu/dark-patterns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 22:04:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subscribe to read | Financial Times</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/7e00a348-d768-4618-b1c9-eb040b2c54e1</link>
      <description>News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the worldʼs leading global business publication</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.ft.com/content/7e00a348-d768-4618-b1c9-eb040b2c54e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 22:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Algorithms in Low-Frequency Trading</title>
      <link>https://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?id=3448307</link>
      <description></description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?id=3448307</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 22:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Json2Email.com - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/4/json2emailcom</link>
      <description>Json2Email is a simple HTML e-mail generation API for developers. POST a JSON definition with your e-mail to the endpoint and the API returns a fully responsive HTML e-mail, ready to be sent. It&amp;#39;s meant for transactional e-mails and simple mailings primarily. It&amp;#39;s built on asp.net core mvc 2 with a…</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/4/json2emailcom</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 22:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>r/wallstreetbets - Times Square right now</title>
      <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/l8rf4k/times_square_right_now/</link>
      <description>111,382 votes and 3,682 comments so far on Reddit</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/l8rf4k/times_square_right_now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 20:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Website Fingerprinting on Early QUIC Traffic</title>
      <link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2101.11871</link>
      <description>Cryptographic protocols have been widely used to protect the user&amp;#39;s privacy
and avoid exposing private information. QUIC (Quick UDP Internet Connections),
as an alternative to traditional HTTP, demonstrates its unique transmission
characteristics: based on UDP for encrypted resource transmission, accelerating
web page rendering. However, existing encrypted transmission schemes based on
TCP are vulnerable to website fingerprinting (WFP) attacks, allowing
adversaries to infer the users&amp;#39; visited websites by eavesdropping on the
transmission channel. Whether QUIC protocol can effectively resisting to such
attacks is worth investigating. In this work, we demonstrated the extreme
vulnerability of QUIC under WFP attacks by comparing attack results under
well-designed conditions. We also study the transferability of features, which
enable the adversary to use proven effective features on a special protocol
attacking a new protocol. This study shows that QUIC is more vulnerable to WFP
attacks than HTTPS in the early traffic scenario but is similar in the normal
scenario. The maximum attack accuracy on QUIC is 56.8 % and 73 % higher than on
HTTPS utilizing Simple features and Transfer features. The insecurity
characteristic of QUIC explains the dramatic gap. We also find that features
are transferable between protocols, and the feature importance is partially
inherited on normal traffic due to the relatively fixed browser rendering
sequence and the similar request-response model of protocols. However, the
transferability is inefficient when on early traffic, as QUIC and HTTPS show
significantly different vulnerability when considering early traffic. We also
show that attack accuracy on QUIC could reach 95.4 % with only 40 packets and
just using simple features, whereas only 60.7 % when on HTTPS.</description>
      <author> ([Submitted on 28 Jan 2021])</author>
      <guid>https://arxiv.org/abs/2101.11871</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 20:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWC9: Windows Terminal 1.6 Preview, Python in VS Code, Pulumi, and more!</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/This+Week+On+Channel+9/TWC9-Windows-Terminal-16-Preview-Python-in-VS-Code-Pulumi-and-more</link>
      <description>[01:02] - Windows Terminal 1.6 Preview[02:04] - Introduction to Azure Boards[02:36] - Python in VS Code January 2021[03:13] - Introduction to Pulumi[04:18] - Using Tailscale on Windows with WSL2[05:29</description>
      <author> (by Christina Warren)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/This+Week+On+Channel+9/TWC9-Windows-Terminal-16-Preview-Python-in-VS-Code-Pulumi-and-more</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 19:06:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# Nullable reference types – No more null reference exceptions!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NDweaZZZcbc</link>
      <description>Are you tired of null reference exceptions and unexpected crashes due to uninitialized variables? There’s a very handy feature in C# called nullable referenc...</description>
      <author> (Mosern1977)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NDweaZZZcbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 18:06:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret History of Windows Bluescreens by Davepl</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KgqJJECQQH0</link>
      <description>Dave tracks down the original developer responsible for the very first Windows Bluescreen, plus how to make your machine Bluescreen in other colors.Download ...</description>
      <author> (Dave&amp;#39;s Garage
  
  
    

    
      
    Dave&amp;#39;s Garage
  
    





    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KgqJJECQQH0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 18:06:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 9.0: Top Level Programs</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iGrZys6Vo_E</link>
      <description>Curious about C# 9.0? In this video we are exploring the new language feature that allows you to skip all the boilerplate code in Program.cs to test APIs, th...</description>
      <author> (Jojor)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iGrZys6Vo_E</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 18:06:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 9.0: Record types</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oSQDZ7GpKwg</link>
      <description>Curious about C# 9.0? In this video we are exploring the new language feature known as records, or record types. This is a great addition to the C# language ...</description>
      <author> (Alexander Vlassov)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oSQDZ7GpKwg</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 18:06:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 9.0: Pattern Matching</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9lvx6mzCAE4</link>
      <description>Curious about C# 9.0? In this video we are exploring pattern matching in C#. This is a great addition to the C# language and is something I&amp;#39;ve personally bee...</description>
      <author> (PushInMatt)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9lvx6mzCAE4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 18:06:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pidget, a Sentry.io client &amp;amp; library - BuiltWithDot.Net</title>
      <link>https://builtwithdot.net/project/6/pidget-a-sentry.io-client-library</link>
      <description>Pidget is an exception and error-reporting library for Sentry.io. It uses modern technologies and paradigms and ideas. The project revolves around simplicity and extensibility, making the client itself super light-weight.</description>
      <author> (Corstiaan Hesselink)</author>
      <guid>https://builtwithdot.net/project/6/pidget-a-sentry.io-client-library</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 17:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Networks Explained from Scratch using Python</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9RN2Wr8xvro</link>
      <description>When I started learning Neural Networks from scratch a few years ago, I did no think about just looking at some Python code or similar. I found it quite hard...</description>
      <author> (freeCodeCamp.org
  
  
    

    
      
    freeCodeCamp.org
  
    



  
    
    
  



    •)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9RN2Wr8xvro</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 17:08:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>