<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Service principles and app registration</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2s0vS3RyaVw</link>
      <description>In this episode, Christos chats with Matthijs Hoekstra from the Identity team to get a better understanding of how Service principles and app registrations work in Azure AD

[01:50] - What is an Azure AD App?
[03:57] - Creating an Azure AD App
[07:16] - Brief overview of authentication
[10:55] - Authentication for Native APPS
[13:13] - What are Service Principals?
[17:58] - Add applications from the gallery
[20:40] - Secrets and certificates
[21:23] - Configuring security tokens
[25:38] - Query applications In Microsoft Graph


What is application management?
https://docs.microsoft.com/azure/active-directory/manage-apps/what-is-application-management?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli


Add an application to your Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) tenant
https://docs.microsoft.com/azure/active-directory/manage-apps/add-application-portal?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli


Application management best practices
https://docs.microsoft.com/azure/active-directory/manage-apps/application-management-fundamentals?WT.mc_id=ondotnet-c9-cephilli


#azure #security #ActiveDirectory #dotnet</description>
      <author> (dotNET)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2s0vS3RyaVw</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 22:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>muesli/duf</title>
      <link>https://github.com/muesli/duf</link>
      <description>Disk Usage/Free Utility. Contribute to muesli/duf development by creating an account on GitHub.</description>
      <author> (muesli)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/muesli/duf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 22:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Okhakumhe - Intellectual Property Rights in the Technology Sector [w/ASL Interpreting]</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZF_HOeJh2Dw</link>
      <description>The slave who made the whiskey, Jack Daniel, was not given recognition until 2016. This recognition was 150 years late. This is not an isolated incident as there are several instances in the past where inventions and ideas by black people were stolen.

So much has changed all over the world, especially in countries where the rights of black people have always been a subject of constant discourse. A 2016 study found that black Americans “apply for patents at nearly half the rate of whites". This shows that a lot still needs to done to protect the intellectual property rights of black people in tech.

In my session, I will address the subject of what intellectual property rights are, how they can be protected and what the black community can do to help facilitate this protection. I will speak on the jurisdictional nature of intellectual property rights and why it is important for black people in tech to apply for triadic or international patents.
---
Mark is a trained lawyer and mediator actively building a career in tech &amp; innovation, corporate practice, intellectual property, dispute resolution, and impact investment.

He enjoys speaking to people on emerging areas of law, Impact Investment, branding and personal development, startups, and Sustainable Development Goals (SDG), especially SDGs 1, 4, 7, 11 and 16.

As a humanitarian, he volunteered at one of Nigeria's correctional facilities as an ad-hoc lecturer with the National Open Univerisity. He also volunteered with the Legal Aid Council of Nigeria to take on pro bono cases, and DEVATOP to tackle human trafficking.

He was a judge at the regional rounds of the Philip Jessup International Law Moot Competition. More recently, he was part of the #AfricaVsVirus Ideathon and also the COVID-19 Challenge organised by UNICEF.

He has advised various tech startups on matters of compliance and IP protection. He is open to all types of engagements including speaking, volunteer, and full or part-time career opportunities.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZF_HOeJh2Dw</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 22:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Service Fabric managed clusters are now in public preview</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-service-fabric/azure-service-fabric-managed-clusters-are-now-in-public-preview/ba-p/1721572</link>
      <description>Azure Service Fabric is the foundational technology that powers Azure core infrastructure and mission critical services such as Azure SQL Database, Event Hubs, and Microsoft Teams. This technology, exactly as we use it within Microsoft, was made publicly available in 2015. Since then, we have seen i...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/220459)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-service-fabric/azure-service-fabric-managed-clusters-are-now-in-public-preview/ba-p/1721572</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 22:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get promoted</title>
      <link>https://defmacro.substack.com/p/how-to-get-promoted</link>
      <description>Almost everyone who does great work toils in relative obscurity. Performance reviews are social fiction. How do people really advance through the corporate hierarchy?</description>
      <author> (Slava Akhmechet)</author>
      <guid>https://defmacro.substack.com/p/how-to-get-promoted</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 21:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maoni0/mem-doc</title>
      <link>https://github.com/Maoni0/mem-doc/blob/master/presentation/dotnetos2020-Pinning.pptx</link>
      <description>This is a document to help with .NET memory analysis and diagnostics. - Maoni0/mem-doc</description>
      <author> (Maoni0)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/Maoni0/mem-doc/blob/master/presentation/dotnetos2020-Pinning.pptx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 20:04:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I was wrong. CRDTs are the future</title>
      <link>https://josephg.com/blog/crdts-are-the-future/</link>
      <description>I saw Martin Kleppmann’s talk a few weeks ago about CRDTs, and I felt a deep sense of despair. Maybe all the work I’ve been doing for the past decade won’t be part of the future after all, because Martin’s work on CRDTs will supersede it.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://josephg.com/blog/crdts-are-the-future/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 19:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to bring SQL to the IoT edge using SQL Edge on Azure IoT Edge with Vasiya Krishnan and @obloch on the #IoTShow</title>
      <link>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Internet-of-Things-Show/Intelligent-Manufacturing-with-IoT-Edge-and-SQL-Edge</link>
      <description>Delve into the capabilities enabled by SQL Edge and Azure IoT Edge in an intelligent manufacturing scenario. Focus into the value-add or benefits of being able to deploy AI and analytics workloads to </description>
      <author> (by Olivier Bloch, jorgievision)</author>
      <guid>https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Internet-of-Things-Show/Intelligent-Manufacturing-with-IoT-Edge-and-SQL-Edge</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 19:04:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a Director of Program Management with .NET’s Scott Hunter</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JbweO2GYkFw</link>
      <description>Today’s episode features Scott Hunter who is the PM director for the .NET team.
We chat about the challenges that come with growing your scope, applying the lessons learned in startups and consulting to large corporations, and his early days working on BBS (bulletin board systems) for fun lead to meeting the people he’d need to know to grow his career.

00:39 - Meet Scott Hunter, Director of Program Management for .NET
01:46 – What does a director of program management do day to day? 
05:26 – How did Scott managed his transition to director of all of .NET from his previous role?
08:41 – How did Scott get the role?   Taking initiative to find the right place.
12:31 – Growing scope and managing perceived identities, from ASP.NET to just .NET
17:31 – Why team cultures differ and don’t align even when they ship in the same product
19:14 – How did Scott learn and build the skills to make these transitions?  Practicing integration in early startup days, consulting.
22:47 – Most important lesson from previous managers: Don’t surround yourself with people like yourself and building a team with diverse opinions
25:13 – Deciding between going with a new project or continuing along on a journey not complete.   
28:00 – Accidentally attending Microsoft’s conference and joining Microsoft
31:55 – Moving from dev to PM and learning communication skills
33:45 – Becoming a manager and intentionally stopping himself from coding
37:20 – How did Scott into computers?  Typing programs into the Commodore PET he stole from his dad.
38:35 – Scott’s history of working on Wildcat BBS to avoid forklift driving   
41:52 – Turbo Pascal and hanging at Anders Hejlsberg’s house and serendipity
43:58 – Failing his first Microsoft interview, knowing what you want.
45:36 – Trust your internal sense of when to act fast

#MicrosoftCareers #CareersBehindTheCode #Director #ProgramMangement</description>
      <author> (Microsoft Developer)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JbweO2GYkFw</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 18:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maoni Stephens - Dotnetos Week</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=troNdmHEu2g</link>
      <description>What's so hard about pinning?
Everyone knows what pinning means - the GC cannot move the object. Sounds simple enough but is it actually? In this talk Maoni will explain challenges of handling pinning in the runtime and how it evolved over the years.

Maoni Stephens is the architect and main developer for the .NET GC in Microsoft. Her blog is at https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/author/maoni/. Cats and anime lover.</description>
      <author> (Dotnetos)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=troNdmHEu2g</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 18:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# in Simple Terms - Primitive Types, Literals, and Nullables</title>
      <link>https://exceptionnotfound.net/csharp-in-simple-terms-2-primitive-types-literals-and-nullables/</link>
      <description>int, string, char, double, decimal, float, long, short, byte, and more!</description>
      <author> (https://www.facebook.com/exceptionnotfnd/)</author>
      <guid>https://exceptionnotfound.net/csharp-in-simple-terms-2-primitive-types-literals-and-nullables/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 17:04:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Adapt Your .NET App for SameSite</title>
      <link>https://developer.okta.com/blog/2020/09/28/adapt-dotnet-app-for-samesite-fix</link>
      <description>Have you heard about the SameSite changes you need to make to your .NET apps?.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://developer.okta.com/blog/2020/09/28/adapt-dotnet-app-for-samesite-fix</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 17:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dew Drop – September 28, 2020 (#3284)</title>
      <link>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/2020/09/28/dew-drop-september-28-2020-3284/</link>
      <description>About Me</description>
      <author> (Alvin A.)</author>
      <guid>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/2020/09/28/dew-drop-september-28-2020-3284/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 17:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic factory with Microsoft.Extensions.DependencyInjection and Castle DynamicProxy</title>
      <link>https://thomaslevesque.com/2020/09/27/automatic-factory-with-microsoft-extensions-dependencyinjection-and-castle-dynamicproxy/</link>
      <description>Dependency injection: the good and the bad Dependency injection (DI) is a great pattern, which can really help make your code cleaner, more decoupled and more testable. There are many DI libraries, like Autofac, Lamar (StructureMap’s successor), Castle Windsor, etc., but lately I’ve mostly been using the one provided by Microsoft in .NET Core : Microsoft.Extensions.DependencyInjection. It’s not the most full-featured (in fact, it’s pretty bare-bones), but I find it sufficient in most cases.</description>
      <author> (About Thomas Levesque
	
	
		Thomas Levesque is a French software developer from Paris.)</author>
      <guid>https://thomaslevesque.com/2020/09/27/automatic-factory-with-microsoft-extensions-dependencyinjection-and-castle-dynamicproxy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 17:04:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Launch a Browser Running ASP.NET Core Back-end Created from Web Template Studio</title>
      <link>https://elanderson.net/2020/09/dont-launch-a-browser-running-asp-net-core-back-end-created-from-web-template-studio/</link>
      <description>In last week’s post, I mentioned off-hand that we could stop VSCode from launching a web browser when starting a debug session on the back-end of our application. This is going to be a quick …</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://elanderson.net/2020/09/dont-launch-a-browser-running-asp-net-core-back-end-created-from-web-template-studio/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:51 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DevOps Handbook – The Value of A/B Testing</title>
      <link>https://www.codingblocks.net/podcast/the-devops-handbook-the-value-of-a-b-testing/</link>
      <description>We wrap up the second way from The DevOps Handbook, while Joe has a mystery episode, Michael doesn't like ketchup, and Allen has a Costco problem.</description>
      <author> (About Michael Outlaw)</author>
      <guid>https://www.codingblocks.net/podcast/the-devops-handbook-the-value-of-a-b-testing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://conference.nber.org/conf_papers/f143926.pdf</link>
      <description />
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://conference.nber.org/conf_papers/f143926.pdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advisory: security issues in AWS KMS and AWS Encryption SDKs</title>
      <link>https://vnhacker.blogspot.com/2020/09/advisory-security-issues-in-aws-kms-and.html</link>
      <description>I discovered and reported to Amazon the following security vulnerabilities affecting AWS KMS and all versions of AWS Encryption SDKs  prior ...</description>
      <author> (Get link







Facebook







Twitter







Pinterest







Email







Other Apps)</author>
      <guid>https://vnhacker.blogspot.com/2020/09/advisory-security-issues-in-aws-kms-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:25 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You Don't Understand Quantum Physics, Try This!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Usu9xZfabPM</link>
      <description>A simple and clear explanation of all the important features of quantum physics that you need to know. Check out this video's sponsor https://brilliant.org/dos 
I have spent a lot of time thinking about how best to explain quantum physics and this is the result of all my hours of pondering, and I’m really happy with how it turned out. I decided to just explain it as it actually is, rather than rely on analogies. The video explains the quantum wavefunction, particle-wave duality, the measurement problem, the double-slit experiment, superposition, entanglement, quantum tunnelling, the Heisenberg uncertainty principle, and energy quantisation. Let me know if it was helpful! Cheers Dx

You can get the posters and other merch here:
https://store.dftba.com/collections/domain-of-science 

Or posters for outside the US here:
https://www.redbubble.com/people/dominicwalliman
I have also made versions available for educational use which you can find here: https://www.flickr.com/photos/95869671@N08/

If you want to check out my Professor Astro Cat books go here:
http://profastrocat.com 

Thanks so much to my supporters on Patreon. If you enjoy my videos and would like to help me make more this is the best way and I appreciate it very much. https://www.patreon.com/domainofscience

Further reading
For a more detailed introduction to quantum physics: 'The Quantum Universe' by Brian Cox and Jeff Forshaw is good.
And a slightly more advanced but fantastic description of what we do and don't know about quantum physics is the excellent book 'Beyond Weird' by Philip Ball.

Music by
Dominic ‘Wibblyfingers’ Walliman

Find me on twitter, instagram, and my website:
http://dominicwalliman.com
https://twitter.com/DominicWalliman
https://www.instagram.com/dominicwalliman
https://www.facebook.com/domainofscience
https://www.patreon.com/domainofscience</description>
      <author> (Domain of Science)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Usu9xZfabPM</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eat The World Vs. Eaten by The World — Juan David Campolargo</title>
      <link>https://www.juandavidcampolargo.com/blog/ambition</link>
      <description>When we are kids, we have many aspirational dreams and ambitious goals.  You want to eat the world.  Then, when you’re an adult,  the world eats you.&amp;nbsp;   We grow up, and the same dreams become impossible or we stop pursuing them. But why? Was it because our dreams were straight-up stupid? Or</description>
      <author> (Sep 27
            
            Written By Juan David Campolargo)</author>
      <guid>https://www.juandavidcampolargo.com/blog/ambition</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:21 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Structured Editing: Breaking Away from Syntax</title>
      <link>https://mbuffett.com/posts/structured-editing-syntax/</link>
      <description>I was aimlessly browsing Github and came across sapling, a very early-stage structured editor. It was inspired by this blog post, which talks about structured editing.
Structured editing has had my interest for a while. I’ve put a lot of time and effort into getting really good at text editing, but I’m holding out hope that in 10 years plaintext editing will be outdated. The idea behind structured editing is to edit code instead of text, so instead of “move cursor to next parentheses, delete in parentheses”, you’d have operations like “change function argument”.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://mbuffett.com/posts/structured-editing-syntax/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I keep ads away from me</title>
      <link>https://akhil.me/2020/How-I-keep-ads-away-from-me/</link>
      <description>We live in a world where we are being looked at all the time. I say “looked at” because that kind of sounds less harsh compared to “tracked and surveilled”. The phones and smart devices that we ourselves make sure are with us all the time are always listening to us - even when we are no talking to them. Google and Apple, even Instagram and Tiktok, know where you are all the time even when you are not even using their apps. Google has access to all your emails and can shut you out of your life just because. You cannot escape the Facebook mafia. If you stop using Facebook, they catch you with Instagram. If you don’t use Instagram they will catch you with Whatsapp. If you somehow even escape that. Facebook now owns “Giphy”  the gif search engine that is built in your phone keyboard. Hell, let’s say you don’t even use that they can track you with their integrations in every single website and app that you are using. They have a profile of you even if you never made it and it is more detailed than it would have been if you have provided that data yourself.</description>
      <author> (Akhil Gupta)</author>
      <guid>https://akhil.me/2020/How-I-keep-ads-away-from-me/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bipolar: feelings vs. reality - BrettTerpstra.com</title>
      <link>https://brettterpstra.com/2020/09/21/bipolar-from-the-other-side/</link>
      <description>I wrote a couple of weeks ago about being bipolar. I wrote that piece while I was in a manic phase, and I told myself I'd write another one while I was in a depression, just to contrast. If I'm going</description>
      <author> (503440548)</author>
      <guid>https://brettterpstra.com/2020/09/21/bipolar-from-the-other-side/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sidecar Pattern in Action</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-architecture-blog/sidecar-pattern-in-action/ba-p/1714983</link>
      <description>     The Sidecar pattern enables the extension and enhancement  - of an existing process or an application container  -without affecting/modifying the original process or container - thus ensuring the single-responsibility of the existing process / container. The problem context, solution, considera...</description>
      <author> (https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/user/viewprofilepage/user-id/487038)</author>
      <guid>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-architecture-blog/sidecar-pattern-in-action/ba-p/1714983</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle of the $350 laptops: Acer Swift 1 vs. Gateway Ryzen 3 3200U</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2020/09/battle-of-the-350-laptops-acer-swift-1-vs-gateway-ryzen-3-3200u/</link>
      <description>Gateway's GWTN141-2 is the best under-$400 laptop we've seen so far.</description>
      <author> (Jim Salter
    -  9/27/2020, 5:30 AM)</author>
      <guid>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2020/09/battle-of-the-350-laptops-acer-swift-1-vs-gateway-ryzen-3-3200u/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:25:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edgescan Questions &amp; Answers with Troy Hunt Part 2 - Cyber Security, Security Scan, Full Stack Vulnerability Management</title>
      <link>https://www.edgescan.com/edgescan-questions-answers-with-troy-hunt-part-2/?hss_channel=tw-2925438791</link>
      <description>The Edgescan Team Sent Questions to Troy Hunt (Part 2 of 3)   ﻿ Troy answers the following questions in this video   Does being a public figure within the cybersecurity world leave you more exposed as a target to malicious attacks. If so, how do you manage and deal with these? What developments do […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.edgescan.com/edgescan-questions-answers-with-troy-hunt-part-2/?hss_channel=tw-2925438791</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC Micro Elite source code</title>
      <link>https://www.bbcelite.com/</link>
      <description>Fully documented source code for Elite on the BBC Micro</description>
      <author> (Mark Moxon)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bbcelite.com/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>221: Swift on Windows, Clean Code, and iOS 14</title>
      <link>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/221</link>
      <description>Now back to our normally scheduled lightning topics with awesome listener suggestions including Swift on Windows, .NET Maui, Database selection, clean code, iOS 14, and more.</description>
      <author> (soundbite.fm)</author>
      <guid>https://www.mergeconflict.fm/221</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:45 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I remove the first 300 million lines from a 700 GB txt file on a system with 1 TB max disk space?</title>
      <link>https://unix.stackexchange.com/questions/610494/how-do-i-remove-the-first-300-million-lines-from-a-700-gb-txt-file-on-a-system-w</link>
      <description>The answers I found use sed, tail, head:

How do I delete the first n lines of an ascii file using shell commands?
https://askubuntu.com/questions/410196/remove-first-n-lines-of-a-large-text-file

...</description>
      <author> (KrisKris
        
            1,10322 gold badges77 silver badges66 bronze badges)</author>
      <guid>https://unix.stackexchange.com/questions/610494/how-do-i-remove-the-first-300-million-lines-from-a-700-gb-txt-file-on-a-system-w</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Documentation Upfront</title>
      <link>https://davidgomes.com/reading-documentation-upfront/</link>
      <description>Before I was actually getting paid to write code, I got extremely accustomed to picking up new frameworks and libraries very quickly. I'd bootstrap a new web application in Rails in one week, but then the next week I'd be using Python and Flask for a different project. I also</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://davidgomes.com/reading-documentation-upfront/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Subtle Gotcha with Azure Deployment Slots and ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://haacked.com/archive/2020/09/28/azure-swap-with-warmup-aspnetcore/</link>
      <description>Setting up a proper continuous deployment with Azure Deployment Slots and ASP.NET Core is trickier than I anticipated. Here’s a particular issue I ran into and my solution.</description>
      <author> (Phil Haack)</author>
      <guid>https://haacked.com/archive/2020/09/28/azure-swap-with-warmup-aspnetcore/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Xamarin.Forms Moon Phase App – .NET Tools Blog | JetBrains</title>
      <link>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/09/25/build-a-xamarin-forms-moon-phase-app/</link>
      <description>One of the wonderful things about .NET is the vast array of platforms .NET developers can target. My personal experience has been developing ASP.NET applications and HTTP APIs, but recently I've been</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.jetbrains.com/dotnet/2020/09/25/build-a-xamarin-forms-moon-phase-app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My summer 2020 road trip along the Italian Riviera</title>
      <link>https://st.im/summer-2020-road-trip-along-the-italian-riviera/</link>
      <description>Travelling in the midst of a global pandemic isn't necessarily the smartest of ideas. But we'd had enough of being cooped up, living within one square mile. This is the story of our two week Italian road trip. I hope you enjoy.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://st.im/summer-2020-road-trip-along-the-italian-riviera/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:28 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Hotel Guest In Thailand Arrested &amp; Jailed For Defamation After Posting Bad Online Reviews</title>
      <link>https://loyaltylobby.com/2020/09/27/american-hotel-guest-in-thailand-arrested-jailed-for-defamation-after-posting-bad-online-reviews/?omhide=true</link>
      <description>A disgruntled American hotel guest who posted several bad TripAdvisor and other online reviews about a resort in Koh Chang, Thailand has been arrested by the police and spent several days in jail after the hotel filed a police complaint for defamation. In what turned into a case of media mudslinging over the last few days, the resort which initially got a lot of flak defended itself saying that the defamation complaint was the last resort after American posted repeated 'untrue' reviews. According to media reports the whole drama initially started as the guest brought outside alcohol into the hotels</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://loyaltylobby.com/2020/09/27/american-hotel-guest-in-thailand-arrested-jailed-for-defamation-after-posting-bad-online-reviews/?omhide=true</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Hacked Coffee Maker Demands Ransom and Demonstrates a Terrifying Implication About the IoT</title>
      <link>https://www.gizmodo.com.au/2020/09/this-hacked-coffee-maker-demands-ransom-and-demonstrates-a-terrifying-implication-about-the-iot/</link>
      <description>It’s no secret that the Internet of Things is full of insecure gadgets. All you need is one high profile incident to be flooded with terrifying headlines about how everything from robotic vacuum cleaners to smart sex toys can be hacked to spy on you. However, apparently some devices like...</description>
      <author> (Share this Story




 



 



 



 





Get our Newsletter

 Subscribe)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gizmodo.com.au/2020/09/this-hacked-coffee-maker-demands-ransom-and-demonstrates-a-terrifying-implication-about-the-iot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Contributions</title>
      <link>https://tweetlog.azureedge.net/</link>
      <description>Web site created using create-react-app</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://tweetlog.azureedge.net/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to Machine Learning Basics - Decision Tree &amp; Random Forest</title>
      <link>https://rubikscode.net/2020/09/28/back-to-machine-learning-basics-decision-tree-random-forest/</link>
      <description>In this article, we explore Decision Tree and Random Forest algorithms, implement them from scratch with Python and learn how to use from Sci-Kit Learn.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://rubikscode.net/2020/09/28/back-to-machine-learning-basics-decision-tree-random-forest/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming an HTTP response in Blazor WebAssembly - Gérald Barré</title>
      <link>https://www.meziantou.net/streaming-an-http-response-in-blazor-webassembly.htm</link>
      <description>In this post, I describe how to stream an HTTP response in ASP.NET Core Blazor WebAssembly.</description>
      <author> (Gérald Barré)</author>
      <guid>https://www.meziantou.net/streaming-an-http-response-in-blazor-webassembly.htm</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Split Screen</title>
      <link>https://universalsplitscreen.github.io/</link>
      <description>Split screen multiplayer for any game with multiple keyboards, mice and controllers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://universalsplitscreen.github.io/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:24:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s not free software if you can’t easily fork it (and how to fix it)</title>
      <link>https://d33tah.wordpress.com/2020/09/27/its-not-free-software-if-you-cant-easily-fork-it/</link>
      <description>Yesterday I had spent a few hours trying to fix a broken update of Discourse on a VM controlled by our Hackerspace. What was meant to be a five-minutes update turned out involve rolling back, resto…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://d33tah.wordpress.com/2020/09/27/its-not-free-software-if-you-cant-easily-fork-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft.PowerShell.ConsoleGuiTools 0.5.0</title>
      <link>https://www.powershellgallery.com/packages/Microsoft.PowerShell.ConsoleGuiTools/0.5.0</link>
      <description>Cross-platform Console Gui Tools for PowerShell</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.powershellgallery.com/packages/Microsoft.PowerShell.ConsoleGuiTools/0.5.0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Azure Deprecation Notices</title>
      <link>https://blog.tomkerkhove.be/2020/09/25/announcing-azure-deprecation-notices/</link>
      <description>Trying to keep up with the deprecation of Azure services &amp; features? Don't worry, we've got this!</description>
      <author> (Tom Kerkhove)</author>
      <guid>https://blog.tomkerkhove.be/2020/09/25/announcing-azure-deprecation-notices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Static hosting with Azure Blob Storage and Azure CDN - Simple Talk</title>
      <link>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/cloud/cloud-development/static-hosting-with-azure-blob-storage-and-azure-cdn/</link>
      <description>No matter what you need, Azure probably has a solution. In this article Diogo Souza demonstrates how to host a static web page in Azure in just a few steps with Azure Blob Storage and Azure CDN.</description>
      <author> (Diogo Souza)</author>
      <guid>https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/cloud/cloud-development/static-hosting-with-azure-blob-storage-and-azure-cdn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Fathers Will Now Get Double the Paternity Leave</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.com/article/french-fathers-paternity-leave-doubled</link>
      <description>“There is no reason it should be just the mother” who takes care of a new baby, said President Macron.</description>
      <author> (Michelle Ruiz)</author>
      <guid>https://www.vogue.com/article/french-fathers-paternity-leave-doubled</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zig's New Relationship with LLVM</title>
      <link>https://kristoff.it/blog/zig-new-relationship-llvm/</link>
      <description>While not yet at version 1.0, Zig is about to reach a new level of maturity and stability.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kristoff.it/blog/zig-new-relationship-llvm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Serverless Hype Explained!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tgFiOzVEL0Q</link>
      <description>Why are "serverless" cloud products so popular right now? What makes them different from using traditional server infrastructure? In this video, I'll go over all the pros and cons of going for a serverless architecture. On it, you can run your website or any web application.

🌍 Social
Twitter: https://twitter.com/Savjee
Facebook: https://facebook.com/Savjee
Blog: https://savjee.be

❤️  Become a Simply Explained member: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCnxrdFPXJMeHru_b4Q_vTPQ/join

📚 Sources used to make this video:
https://savjee.be/videos/simply-explained/serverless-hype-explained/</description>
      <author> (Simply Explained)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tgFiOzVEL0Q</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Us, Without Us: Addressing Tech's Shortcomings in Creating Equity for Black People [w/ASL]</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2uoaVYkHA-M</link>
      <description>Many consider technology to be the “great equalizer”, but it’s evident that Black people are not benefiting at the same rates as others. This session will discuss how the forces that limit Black people’s ability to navigate the physical also prevent us from exerting agency via the digital. Together, we’ll discuss the ways that anti-Blackness is replicated in technology, the discrepancies faced by Black communities due to the digital divide, and the changes required for us to have a more equitable future. Because we can never fully benefit if technology continues to be made for us, without us.
---
Jacqueline Gibson
Software Engineer focusing on accessibility at Microsoft

Jacqueline is a Digital Equity Advocate &amp; Software Engineer building change from the code up. She's interested in leveraging technology for social good, particularly identifying ways in which current technology maintains social inequities and working to eliminate these biases. She strives to understand what is necessary to create systems that everyone, regardless of ability, can use with ease.

She graduated with dual degrees in Computer Science and African &amp; African Diaspora Studies from the University of Texas at Austin. She's currently developing tools to create accessible applications for Android, Windows, and web as part of Microsoft's Accessibility Insights team.</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2uoaVYkHA-M</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>git commit-tree parlor tricks, Part 9: How can I bulk-revert an entire repo to an earlier commit? | The Old New Thing</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20200928-00/?p=104302</link>
      <description>Suppose you’ve made a bunch of commits to a branch, and then you decide that you want to roll back the entire repo to an earlier commit. Just pretend the last dozen commits never happened. The branch policy prevents force-pushes, so you will have to make a new commit that effectively reverts a large number of commits.    </description>
      <author> (Raymond Chen  Follow)</author>
      <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20200928-00/?p=104302</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Man in the Public Gallery: Assange Hearing Day 18 - Craig Murray</title>
      <link>https://www.craigmurray.org.uk/archives/2020/09/your-man-in-the-public-gallery-assange-hearing-day-18/</link>
      <description>It is hard to believe, but Judge Baraitser on Friday ruled that there will be no closing speeches in the Assange extradition hearing. She accepted the proposal initially put forward by counsel for the US government, that closing arguments should simply be submitted in writing and without an oral hearing. This was accepted by the […]</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://www.craigmurray.org.uk/archives/2020/09/your-man-in-the-public-gallery-assange-hearing-day-18/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town Hall [w/ASL Interpreting]</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZdSCr_vDoS4</link>
      <description>#BlackLivesMatter: What Next

Lance Goudy
Goudy Management Group, CEO

Kimeka Campbell
Young Professionals of Color--Greater Harrisburg

Michael Brown 

Senior Software Engineer at Microsoft
Twitter: https://twitter.com/browniepoints


Nicole Tinson

Franklin Rosado</description>
      <author> (JuneteenthConf)</author>
      <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZdSCr_vDoS4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET App Developer Links - 2020-09-28</title>
      <link>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/09/app-developer-links-2020-09-28/</link>
      <description>The latest news and resources for .NET app developers.</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://links.danrigby.com/2020/09/app-developer-links-2020-09-28/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happiness is Bad - Naughty Computer</title>
      <link>http://www.naughtycomputer.uk/happiness_is_bad.html</link>
      <description>While the header-image of this blog invites you to contemplate
        the concept "technology is bad"; this article invites you to
        contemplate the concept of "happiness is bad".</description>
      <author> (27th September 2020)</author>
      <guid>http://www.naughtycomputer.uk/happiness_is_bad.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnthonyGiretti/commonfeatures-webapi-aspnetcore</title>
      <link>https://github.com/AnthonyGiretti/commonfeatures-webapi-aspnetcore/tree/migration-to-aspnetcore5</link>
      <description>Authenticating, validating, caching, error handling, logging, documenting, testing and profiling are common features in web API, here are code samples to show how to implement them. I also added CR...</description>
      <author> (AnthonyGiretti)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/AnthonyGiretti/commonfeatures-webapi-aspnetcore/tree/migration-to-aspnetcore5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing DotNet.SystemCollections.Analyzers</title>
      <link>https://kevinavignon.com/2020/09/22/introducing-dotnet-systemcollections-analyzers/</link>
      <description>I have been a developer for the past 7 years. I’ve gone through a lot of code reviews during that time. I have devoted my time to learn good software engineering practices through C#. Last ye…</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>https://kevinavignon.com/2020/09/22/introducing-dotnet-systemcollections-analyzers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Debugging: Watching Element Changes</title>
      <link>https://textslashplain.com/2020/09/25/web-debugging-watching-element-changes/</link>
      <description>Recently, I was debugging a regression where I wanted to watch change’s in an element’s property at runtime. Specifically, I wanted to watch the URL change when I select different color…</description>
      <author> (Published by ericlaw)</author>
      <guid>https://textslashplain.com/2020/09/25/web-debugging-watching-element-changes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shawn Wildermuth's Blog</title>
      <link>http://wildermuth.com/2020/09/27/Playing-with-Vuelidate-Alpha-with-Vue-3</link>
      <description>Playing with Vuelidate Alpha with Vue 3 - Shawn Wildermuth</description>
      <author> ()</author>
      <guid>http://wildermuth.com/2020/09/27/Playing-with-Vuelidate-Alpha-with-Vue-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:23:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASP.NET Core 3.1 Migration by NickCraver · Pull Request #355 · opserver/Opserver</title>
      <link>https://github.com/opserver/Opserver/pull/355</link>
      <description>This is the overall migration from full framework to ASP.NET Core 3.1. All components are up and running and after docs are in place, it&amp;#39;ll be ready for a master merge.
There is some more Linux...</description>
      <author> (opserver)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/opserver/Opserver/pull/355</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:22:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember ASP.NET Request Culture Using Middleware</title>
      <link>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/remember-asdotnet-request-culture-using-middleware</link>
      <description>In the last post, we explored a jumpstart guide to working with a user’s request culture. While localization works out of the box, there seems to be a caveat when it comes to remembering the culture a user prefers.</description>
      <author> (Khalid Abuhakmeh)</author>
      <guid>https://khalidabuhakmeh.com/remember-asdotnet-request-culture-using-middleware</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:22:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ongoing by Tim Bray · Won’t Subscribe</title>
      <link>https://www.tbray.org/ongoing/When/202x/2020/09/25/Subscription-Overload</link>
      <description>Since I’m lightly employed these days, I enjoy keeping up with the news. In recent weeks, I’ve been blocked by the paywalls
    of the Wall Street Journal, Globe &amp; Mail (closest thing Canada has to a national newspaper), the
    Times/Sunday Times (of London), the Telegraph (also UK), Business Insider, and
    Bloomberg.
    Recently I got a bit of inside info on how these publications think about the economics, and I’m here to explain why they’re
    wrong.</description>
      <author> (Tim Bray)</author>
      <guid>https://www.tbray.org/ongoing/When/202x/2020/09/25/Subscription-Overload</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:22:46 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>codemix/ts-sql</title>
      <link>https://github.com/codemix/ts-sql</link>
      <description>A SQL database implemented purely in TypeScript type annotations. - codemix/ts-sql</description>
      <author> (codemix)</author>
      <guid>https://github.com/codemix/ts-sql</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 16:14:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>