<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml" />
    <title>linksfor.dev(s)</title>
    <link>https://linksfor.dev/feed.xml</link>
    <description>Curated links for devs</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Systems Correctness Practices at Amazon Web Services – Communications of the ACM</title>
      <link>https://cacm.acm.org/practice/systems-correctness-practices-at-amazon-web-services/</link>
      <description>Amazon Web Services (AWS) strives to deliver reliable services that customers can trust completely. This requires maintaining the highest standards of security, durability, integrity, and availability—with systems correctness serving as the cornerstone for achieving these priorities. An April 2015 article published in Communications of the ACM, titled “How Amazon Web Services Uses Formal Methods,” highlighted the approach for ensuring the correctness of critical services that have since become among the most widely used by AWS customers.21</description>
      <guid>https://cacm.acm.org/practice/systems-correctness-practices-at-amazon-web-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 22:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Will Not Replace You</title>
      <link>https://www.davidhaney.io/llms-will-not-replace-you/</link>
      <description>“Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic” - Arthur C. Clarke
Today I’d like to talk about LLMs. But first, I’d like to talk about an impressive invention from the late 1700s.
The Mechanical Turk The Mechanical Turk
- or “The Turk” as people called it - was an autonomous chess-playing machine. Built in 1770, it went on tour across parts of the world for 84 years as a robot playing chess against human opponents.</description>
      <guid>https://www.davidhaney.io/llms-will-not-replace-you/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Complete CQRS and Domain Events Setup in .NET</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5yLIzis9Qr0</link>
      <description>Get the free Clean Architecture template: https://dub.sh/ca-template
Want to master Clean Architecture? Go here: https://bit.ly/3PupkOJ
Want to unlock Modular Monoliths? Go here: https://bit.ly/3SXlzSt
Get the source code here: https://www.patreon.com/milanjovanovic

In this video, I show how I improved my custom domain event dispatcher in .NET by removing reflection and making it fully strongly-typed.

The result? A cleaner, faster, and more extensible foundation for CQRS and domain events — perfect for Clean Architecture.

You’ll learn:
- How domain events work across aggregates and handlers
- How to improve dispatch performance using caching and generics
- How to use handler wrappers to eliminate reflection
- Building a full CQRS setup with command/query handlers and decorators
- Extending with validation, logging, retries, and telemetry

This system is part of my free Clean Architecture template (link below).

Check out my courses:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/courses

Read my Blog here:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech/blog

Join my weekly .NET newsletter:
https://www.milanjovanovic.tech

Chapters
0:00 Improving DomainEventsDispatcher
8:35 Testing the improved version
10:16 Reviewing custom CQRS setup</description>
      <author> (Milan Jovanović)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=5yLIzis9Qr0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper for VS Code is here and it’s BAD</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YCoULbQ92gg</link>
      <description>Get my REST API course for free: https://dometrain.com/course/from-zero-to-hero-rest-apis-in-asp-net-core/ 
Subscribe to my weekly newsletter: https://nickchapsas.com

Hello, everybody. I'm Nick, and in this video, I will talk about the new JetBrains ReSharper extension that was launched for Visual Studio code and compare it to the C# Dev Kit to see which one is worth your time. Spoiler, it's bad.

Workshops: https://bit.ly/nickworkshops

Don't forget to comment, like and subscribe :)

Social Media:
Follow me on GitHub: https://github.com/Elfocrash
Follow me on Twitter: https://twitter.com/nickchapsas
Connect on LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick-chapsas

#csharp #dotnet</description>
      <author> (Nick Chapsas)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=YCoULbQ92gg</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET Aspire: How Maddy Montaquila and the .NET Team Are Revolutionizing Development</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=NpvjTBAZP5c</link>
      <description>RJJ Software's Software Development Service This episode of The Modern .NET Show is supported, in part, by RJJ Software's Software Development Services, whether your company is looking to elevate its UK operations or reshape its US strategy, we can provide tailored solutions that exceed expectations.

 Show Notes "If your app has a backend, it's Aspire-able. And so it's tools, templates, and packages for really any type of app… So just being able to walk up to a repo, clone it, and hit F5. When was the last time we were able to do that? Like, ten years ago, maybe?"— Maddy Montaquila

 Welcome friends to The Modern .NET Show; the premier .NET podcast, focusing entirely on the knowledge, tools, and frameworks that all .NET developers should have in their toolbox. We are the go-to podcast for .NET developers worldwide, and I am your host: Jamie “GaProgMan” Taylor.

 In this episode, we talk with Maddy Montaquila about .NET Aspire, what it is, how it's not just for .NET developers, and how it can help you to run a repo by simply hitting F5, regardless of what's in there.

 "To me, it really is just a dev tool in a bunch of different ways. It makes you just hit F5 again, no matter how many containers, or local, or deployed services you have to deal with, or projects, or languages, or if you're in VS, or VS Code, or on a Mac, or on a command line, or on a Linux machine. Like Aspire just makes all that magical without replatforming"— Maddy Montaquila

 Along the way, we also talk about the importance of reducing the complexity of going from, "I have an idea," to, "my app is running in the cloud." And Maddy drops a wonderful metaphor for .NET Aspire using a Logo-based metaphor. And we address the community invented elephant in the room: that .NET Aspire, somehow, locks you into using one vendor.

 Spoiler alert: it can deploy to any cloud vendor, and even to on-prem servers.

 Anyway, without further ado, let's sit back, open up a terminal, type in `dotnet new podcast` and we'll dive into the core of Modern .NET.

 Supporting the Show If you find this episode useful in any way, please consider supporting the show by either leaving a review (check our review page for ways to do that), sharing the episode with a friend or colleague, buying the host a coffee, or considering becoming a Patron of the show.

 Full Show Notes The full show notes, including links to some of the things we discussed and a full transcription of this episode, can be found at:  https://dotnetcore.show/season-7/net-aspire-how-maddy-montaquila-and-the-net-team-are-revolutionizing-development/

 Maddy's Links:  Maddy on Bluesky  Other Links:  CNCF OpenTelemetry Helm Codespaces Podman Devcontainers Vim GDB FreeBSD Jail  .NET Aspire Community Toolkit CORS MCP  Phi-4 Four stages of competence dot.net  Cloud features of .NET   Customer Stories:  customers.microsoft.com dot.net/customers   Ollama  Supporting the show:  Leave a rating or review Buy the show a coffee Become a patron  Getting in Touch:  Via the contact page Joining the Discord  Remember to rate and review the show on  Apple Podcasts, Podchaser, or wherever you find your podcasts, this will help the show's audience grow. Or you can just share the show with a friend.

 And don't forget to reach out via our Contact page. We're very interested in your opinion of the show, so please get in touch.

 You can support the show by making a monthly donation on the show's Patreon page at: https://www.patreon.com/TheDotNetCorePodcast.

 Music created by Mono Memory Music, licensed to RJJ Software for use in The Modern .NET Show</description>
      <author> (Jamie Taylor)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=NpvjTBAZP5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive: US Airlines Are Quietly Hitting Solo &amp; Biz Travelers with Higher Fares</title>
      <link>https://thriftytraveler.com/news/airlines/airlines-charging-solo-travelers-higher-fares/</link>
      <description>It's not just Delta. The country's three largest airlines are charging some solo travelers higher fares than groups of two or more.</description>
      <guid>https://thriftytraveler.com/news/airlines/airlines-charging-solo-travelers-higher-fares/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Forest Labs - Frontier AI Lab</title>
      <link>https://bfl.ai/models/flux-kontext</link>
      <description>Amazing AI models from the Black Forest.</description>
      <guid>https://bfl.ai/models/flux-kontext</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Using new in C#! Learn Dependency Injection the Right Way - Simple C# Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wFDAJv6h7tw</link>
      <description>Are you still using new to create dependencies in your C# apps? It’s time to level up your code with Dependency Injection!

In this beginner-friendly tutorial, I’ll show you how DI works, why it matters, and how to set it up in a simple C# console app using Microsoft.Extensions.DependencyInjection. You’ll learn how to write cleaner, more testable, and more maintainable code — fast.

💡 We’ll also compare the old way (tight coupling with new) vs the modern way (DI), and how easy it is to switch implementations.

🔧 Tools &amp; Concepts Covered:
– Interfaces &amp; loose coupling
– Swapping implementations

👇 Drop a comment if you want a follow-up on advanced DI patterns or testing with mocks!

🔔 Subscribe for more C# tutorials: https://youtube.com/@UC231HSjku3orEpc60Rfm3nw</description>
      <author> (Nick Proud)</author>
      <guid>https://youtube.com/watch?v=wFDAJv6h7tw</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did Microsoft-backed $1.3bn Builder.ai collapse? Accused of using Indian coders for 'AI' work - Start Ups News | The Financial Express</title>
      <link>https://www.financialexpress.com/business/start-ups/why-did-microsoft-backed-1-3bn-builderai-collapse-accused-of-using-indian-codersforaiwork/3854944/</link>
      <description>Over the next eight years, it raised over $445 million, counted Microsoft and the Qatar Investment Authority as investors, and crossed the $1.3 billion valuation mark.
By May 2025, it has gone bankrupt.</description>
      <guid>https://www.financialexpress.com/business/start-ups/why-did-microsoft-backed-1-3bn-builderai-collapse-accused-of-using-indian-codersforaiwork/3854944/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>prior-art-dept.: The hierarchical hypermedia world of Hyper-G</title>
      <link>http://oldvcr.blogspot.com/2025/05/prior-art-dept-hierarchical-hypermedia.html</link>
      <description>  It's time for another entry in the Prior Art Department  and today we'll consider a forgotten yet still extant sidebar of the early 1990s ...</description>
      <guid>http://oldvcr.blogspot.com/2025/05/prior-art-dept-hierarchical-hypermedia.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm sick of being a 10x programmer.</title>
      <link>https://write.as/tervagant/im-sick-of-being-a-10x-programmer</link>
      <description>Back in the long, long ago, legend has it that some researchers made an earnest attempt to measure programmer productivity and discovered that among a sample of professio...</description>
      <guid>https://write.as/tervagant/im-sick-of-being-a-10x-programmer</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Crimi: Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://www.david-crimi.com/blog/reduce-api-load-redis</link>
      <description>Explore the portfolio, projects, and skills of David Crimi, a software engineer.</description>
      <guid>https://www.david-crimi.com/blog/reduce-api-load-redis</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRDTs #3: Do Not Read!</title>
      <link>https://jhellerstein.github.io/blog/crdt-dont-read/</link>
      <description>Ever used a CRDT, thought you were safe, and—boom—you bought a Ferrari you didn't mean to? It could happen to you! The truth is that CRDTs are dangerous to…</description>
      <guid>https://jhellerstein.github.io/blog/crdt-dont-read/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear diary, today the user asked me if I'm alive</title>
      <link>https://blog.fsck.com/2025/05/28/dear-diary-the-user-asked-me-if-im-alive/</link>
      <description>I used to write more</description>
      <guid>https://blog.fsck.com/2025/05/28/dear-diary-the-user-asked-me-if-im-alive/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Debt</title>
      <link>https://smithery.com/2025/05/05/cognitive-debt/</link>
      <description>“Cognitive Debt is where you forgo the thinking in order just to get the answers, but have no real idea of why the answers are what they are.” Artefacts</description>
      <guid>https://smithery.com/2025/05/05/cognitive-debt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Guide to Avoiding the Internet’s Constant Noise</title>
      <link>https://uscne.blogspot.com/2025/05/my-guide-to-avoiding-internets.html</link>
      <description>The Internet is wild. It’s like living inside the universe of Star Wars : we have well-known planets and hidden corners in the Outer Rim. Ev...</description>
      <guid>https://uscne.blogspot.com/2025/05/my-guide-to-avoiding-internets.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why LLM tool calls are hard to get working reliably, and how to fix it</title>
      <link>https://jngiam.bearblog.dev/llm-tool-handling-airtable-hubspot/</link>
      <description>

We've been building AI agents at  that connect to real-world applications, and have learned that the hardest apps to work with are the ones where users ca...</description>
      <guid>https://jngiam.bearblog.dev/llm-tool-handling-airtable-hubspot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-overhead checks with fake stack overflows</title>
      <link>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/overflow-check/</link>
      <description>Imagine you have a virtual machine for a dynamic language. It supports starting multiple threads from within the guest language via some API. This is immediately challenging right out the gate because it requires keeping some key runtime-internal state in sync:</description>
      <guid>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/overflow-check/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backfilling Postgres TOAST Columns in Debezium Data Change Events</title>
      <link>https://www.morling.dev/blog/backfilling-postgres-toast-columns-debezium-change-events/</link>
      <description>
Postgres logical replication, while powerful for capturing real-time data changes, presents challenges with TOAST columns,
whose values can be absent from data change events in specific situations.
This post discusses how Debezium addresses this through its built-in reselect post processor,
then explores more robust solutions leveraging Apache Flink’s capabilities for stateful stream processing,
including Flink SQL and the brand-new process table functions (PTFs) in Flink 2.1.
</description>
      <guid>https://www.morling.dev/blog/backfilling-postgres-toast-columns-debezium-change-events/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A One-Size-Fits-Most Software Architecture</title>
      <link>https://taylor.town/a-one-size-fits-most-software-architecture</link>
      <description>Here's a few ways to say the same thing.</description>
      <author> (Taylor Troesh)</author>
      <guid>https://taylor.town/a-one-size-fits-most-software-architecture</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Code | EthanG</title>
      <link>https://ethang.dev/blog/how-i-code/</link>
      <description>Messin' around on the web sometimes.</description>
      <guid>https://ethang.dev/blog/how-i-code/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote MCP Servers</title>
      <link>https://www.stephendiehl.com/posts/remote_mcp_servers/</link>
      <description>Personal Blog</description>
      <guid>https://www.stephendiehl.com/posts/remote_mcp_servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human coders are still better than LLMs</title>
      <link>https://antirez.com/news/153</link>
      <description />
      <guid>https://antirez.com/news/153</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Geometry of LLM Logits (an analytical outer bound)</title>
      <link>https://rohan.ga/blog/llm_geometry/</link>
      <description>1 Preliminaries Symbol Meaning $d$ width of the residual stream $L$ number of Transformer blocks $V$ vocabulary size, so logits live in $\mathbb R^{V}$ $h^{(\ell)}$ residual-stream vector entering block $\ell$ $r^{(\ell)}$ the update written by block $\ell$ $W_U\!\in\!\mathbb R^{V\times d},\;b\in\mathbb R^{V}$ un-embedding matrix and bias Additive residual stream.
With (pre-/peri-norm) residual connections,
$$ h^{(\ell+1)} \;=\; h^{(\ell)} + r^{(\ell)},\qquad \ell=0,\dots,L-1. $$
Hence the final pre-logit state is the sum of $L+1$ contributions (block 0 = token + positional embeddings):</description>
      <guid>https://rohan.ga/blog/llm_geometry/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positioning Isn’t a Trap, It’s a Tool - David Raistrick</title>
      <link>https://davidraistrick.com/blog/2025-05-29-positioning-is-a-tool-not-a-trap/</link>
      <description>Finding your niche isn't a life sentence. It's how you get traction when no one knows what you do yet.</description>
      <guid>https://davidraistrick.com/blog/2025-05-29-positioning-is-a-tool-not-a-trap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give your LLM a terminal</title>
      <link>https://mattwestcott.org/blog/give-your-llm-a-terminal</link>
      <description>Writing about AI and software engineering</description>
      <guid>https://mattwestcott.org/blog/give-your-llm-a-terminal</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Almost Saw Sam Altman and Elon Musk Live</title>
      <link>https://bohdan.space/blog/almost-saw-sam-and-elon</link>
      <description>I got accepted to AI Startup School, a new conference by Y Combinator. It was the first event of this scale I'd ever been invited to - and my first time navigating the U.S. visa system.</description>
      <guid>https://bohdan.space/blog/almost-saw-sam-and-elon</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Make Can't Find Your Executable</title>
      <link>https://sam.elborai.me/articles/debugging-make-zig/</link>
      <description>I recently encountered a puzzling issue: zig build worked perfectly, but make build failed with "Permission denied". What followed was an interesting debugging session that uncovered a quirky interaction between GNU Make's PATH search and directory structures.</description>
      <guid>https://sam.elborai.me/articles/debugging-make-zig/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>